PV01_701_A	1	1	Yukikaze: 「Aah! W-Wait―― Hyan! Ah! Haannn!!」	s17a	0388
PV01_701_A	1	2	Sweet moans come out of Yukikaze's mouth.	s17a	0389
PV01_701_A	1	3	Her body, glittering with the aphrodisiac oil, is touched and felt by countless men.	s17a	0390
PV01_701_A	1	4	Yukikaze: 「Fan! Ah!……Aah! So-So many at once…… Ah! Nu, ah! Aah!!」	s17a	0391
PV01_701_A	1	5	Man: 「Yukikaze-chan, here is 3000 yen! Give me a lot of service!!」	s17a	0392
PV01_701_A	1	6	The men are grasping 3000 yen in one hand, and scrambling to touch Yukikaze's body with their other hand.	s17a	0393
PV01_701_A	1	7	Her oily skin is rubbed vigorously by the hands of the men.	s17a	0394
PV01_701_A	1	8	Yukikaze: 「W-Wait!……I can't attend to so many people at once…… Hya! Ah! Haan!!」	s17a	0395
PV01_701_A	1	9	Man: 「Your mouth is being neglected, Yukikaze-chan.」	s17a	0396
PV01_701_A	1	10	Before Yukikaze can reply, a dirty finger is shoved into her mouth.	s17a	0397
PV01_701_A	1	11	Yukikaze: 「Naaan!? Han, Don't stuff things in my mouth……Churu!」	s17a	0398
PV01_701_A	1	12	Though Yukikaze protests against it, her sex slave tongue moves without thinking and starts licking the finger.	s17a	0399
PV01_701_A	1	13	Yukikaze: 「Chu……Nh! Npu!……Rero, chupachupa…… Nh! Rero, rerorero~~」	s17a	0400
PV01_701_A	1	14	Sucking it as if it was a dick, suction noises resonates.	s17a	0401
PV01_701_A	1	15	Man: 「I'll take those tits!」 「Hold on, those tits are mine!」	s17a	0402
PV01_701_A	1	16	Yukikaze: 「Hyaannn!!」	s17a	0403
PV01_701_A	1	17	This time, two, three, four hands are fighting over her breasts and start squeezing them.	s17a	0404
PV01_701_A	1	18	Yukikaze: 「Ah, Ahn……Nu! I-I told you not too…… Hyan! Haan! Uun!!」	s17a	0405
PV01_701_A	1	19	Compared to the last time she came to this street, her breasts didn't really get bigger, but they did become several times more sensitive.	s17a	0406
PV01_701_A	1	20	Yukikaze: 「Ah, aah! My cheest! Hiaa, Ah! Nuu, yaan, too rough……Ah! Aah!」	s17a	0407
PV01_701_A	1	21	Even before the men massaged her breasts, her nipples have been painfully erect ever since her sleazy introduction.	s17a	0408
PV01_701_A	1	22	Now that they are being furiously squeezed, Yukikaze's voice becomes sweetly hoarse.	s17a	0409
PV01_701_A	1	23	Man: 「Whoa, even though she's flat-chested her nipples are so hard!」 「Her areola is also pretty big. What a perverted flat chest.」	s17a	0410
PV01_701_A	1	24	Yukikaze: 「Sh-Shud up!……S-Sho what if my chest is……Small…… It's not my fault!!」	s17a	0411
PV01_701_A	1	25	Yukikaze: 「Yaan! Don't rub my nipples that much…… Ah! Aahn! Don't twist them! Doon't!」	s17a	0412
PV01_701_A	1	26	Jostled by the men, Yukikaze's body pulses and twists in pleasure.	s17a	0413
PV01_701_A	1	27	Man: 「Yukikaze-chan's body is becoming quite erotic♪」 「You really have talent as a sex slave～」	s17a	0414
PV01_701_A	1	28	Yukikaze is unable to stand straight anymore because of the pleasure. Her thighs, butt and crotch are swarmed by hands.	s17a	0415
PV01_701_A	1	29	Yukikaze: 「Hahiin! Ya, yaan! So many hands! Ah! So many hands on my pussy!!」	s17a	0416
PV01_701_A	1	30	Rather than being groped by men, she feels like she's being groped by tentacles. Her love juices are spilling without end.	s17a	0417
PV01_701_A	1	31	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Nuu……Ah! Ah!……That's…… S-Stoop!……All your hands feel……Too good!…… Aah good, this is goood!!」	s17a	0418
PV01_701_A	1	32	The smell of the horny slut juices and the smell of the aphrodisiac oil spread all over her body blend together and make the men even more aroused.	s17a	0419
PV01_701_A	1	33	Man: 「To think you were a Taimanin even though you have so much talent as a filthy sow, what a waste it was～!」	s17a	0420
PV01_701_A	1	34	Yukikaze: 「Ahi! Nhi! D-Don't say it was a waste!! Y-You're wrong! I'm feeling it, but! Ah! Ah! That's not iiit!!」	s17a	0421
PV01_701_A	1	35	Yukikaze shakes her head in denial while saying that, but the men just grin and laugh.	s17a	0422
PV01_701_A	1	36	Man: 「You're getting so excited by us touching you, where are we wrong?! You whore!」	s17a	0423
PV01_701_A	1	37	Yukikaze: 「I said you're wrong! I was remodeled…… And I became really dirty!…… I-I am――」	s17a	0424
PV01_701_A	1	38	Before she can finish her sentence, someone suddenly pushes on her swollen clitoris through her bikini.	s17a	0425
PV01_701_A	1	39	Yukikaze: 「Nhiiiii! Hi! Ahhiiiiiiiiiiii!!」	s17a	0426
PV01_701_A	1	40	Yukikaze screams from her first orgasm of the day.	s17a	0427
PV01_701_A	2	1	Her ass is thrusted forward as her entire body bends like a bow and trembles.	s17a	0428
PV01_701_A	2	2	Man: 「She already came!! Haha, this dirty pig!」	s17a	0429
PV01_701_A	2	3	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Ah! Aaaaaaaaaaaah!!」	s17a	0430
PV01_701_A	2	4	Yukikaze: （I can't help it, alright?!! I can't hold back from cumming anymore!! My brain has been damaged before!!）	s17a	0431
PV01_701_A	2	5	Even if a part of her brain has been damaged, the only thing coming out of Yukikaze's mouth is the voice of a satisfied sex slave.	s17a	0432
PV01_701_A	2	6	Yukikaze: 「Aah! I came! I caaame!! My clit feels good! Ah! Ah! It feels gooooood!!」	s17a	0433
PV01_701_A	2	7	Her orgasm scream marks the beginning of Yukikaze's mad feast.	s17a	0434
PV01_701_A	2	8	Man: 「Now, I wonder how her cunt tastes now that it just came?」	s17a	0435
PV01_701_A	2	9	One man puts his finger on her panties.	s17a	0436
PV01_701_A	2	10	Yukikaze: 「Wait! I just came!!」	s17a	0437
PV01_701_A	2	11	Man: 「I know. Now show us!!」	s17a	0438
PV01_701_A	2	12	Yukikaze: 「Hiyaaaaan!!」	s17a	0439
PV01_701_A	2	13	Yukikaze sweetly moans again.	s17a	0440
PV01_701_A	2	14	The man not only reveals Yukikaze's secret place, but spreads out her slit with his fingers.	s17a	0441
PV01_701_A	2	15	Yukikaze: 「Nfaa! Ah! Aah!……Do-Doon't…… R-Right now……My p-pussy is……really sensitive……」	s17a	0442
PV01_701_A	2	16	Despite saying so with her mouth, Yukikaze's crotch is shaking hungrily.	s17a	0443
PV01_701_A	2	17	Since she came from her clitoris, her miserable cunt is tightening and shivering.	s17a	0444
PV01_701_A	2	18	Man: 「Yukikaze-chan, your pussy juices are making a mess. Slurp♪」	s17a	0445
PV01_701_A	2	19	Yukikaze: 「Hahiinnn!!」	s17a	0446
PV01_701_A	2	20	The man extends his warm tongue to lick Yukikaze's selfish genitals.	s17a	0447
PV01_701_A	2	21	Man: 「Oh! What an amazing reaction. Bero! Berobero, jyurubero, bero.」	s17a	0448
PV01_701_A	2	22	The man gets carried away and presses his face against her pussy, moving his tongue again and again.	s17a	0449
PV01_701_A	2	23	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Ha! Hahi! Hi! Aah! Aaah! Nu, aahn!!」	s17a	0450
PV01_701_A	2	24	His tongue slips inside her vagina, licking and rubbing her folds.	s17a	0451
PV01_701_A	2	25	Yukikaze can't help moaning from such a direct attack.	s17a	0452
PV01_701_A	2	26	Yukikaze: （It feels……Good, my pussy…… Being licked feels……So goood!）	s17a	0453
PV01_701_A	2	27	Man: 「Let me enjoy myself with this hole then.」	s17a	0454
PV01_701_A	2	28	The voice of another man close to her ass is heard.	s17a	0455
PV01_701_A	2	29	Yukikaze: 「Eh!? W-Wait! M-My ass is――」	s17a	0456
PV01_701_A	2	30	Understanding what the man intends to do, her asshole tightens in expectation of the immoral pleasure.	s17a	0457
PV01_701_A	2	31	The man slips his finger inside her tightened asshole.	s17a	0458
PV01_701_A	2	32	Yukikaze: 「Nhooo!」	s17a	0459
PV01_701_A	2	33	A deep, shameful voice escapes her O-shaped lips.	s17a	0460
PV01_701_A	2	34	Yukikaze: 「Hofuu! Oh! Oooh! My ass! Ooh! In my ass! Ah! Ehaa! It-It's going inside!!」	s17a	0461
PV01_701_A	2	35	Every time his fat, burly finger enters inside her bowels, Yukikaze's voice stiffens.	s17a	0462
PV01_701_A	2	36	Yukikaze: 「Nfuuuu! Kuu! Hifuuuuu!」	s17a	0463
PV01_701_A	2	37	From the pleasure of having her asshole touched, Yukikaze sweetly moans and her whole body stiffens as well.	s17a	0464
PV01_701_A	2	38	Yukikaze: （N-No good……My ass is way more sensitive than usual…… Ever since I saw……Rinko-senpai doing that…… My ass has beeen really sensitive……）	s17a	0465
PV01_701_A	2	39	Man: 「Watching your pal give birth made you horny right? Your asshole is all soft like a cunt. What's up with that?」	s17a	0466
PV01_701_A	2	40	Yukikaze: 「Nuuu, Do-Don't say that……Hiiin! T-Today is…… Aahn! Nuu……Different than usual…… My ass! Oh, ooh! It's really sensitiive!!」	s17a	0467
PV01_701_A	3	1	It's obvious even to men she never met.	s17a	0468
PV01_701_A	3	2	Yukikaze's asshole is wet and sticky with bowel juices. A viscous and obscene sound resonates.	s17a	0469
PV01_701_A	3	3	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Aah! Noo! Don't make those dirty sounds with my ass…… I-It's embarrassiing……Oooh!!」	s17a	0470
PV01_701_A	3	4	Man: 「You're just a sex slave sow who gets horny no matter who your partner is, why are you acting all reserved?! Aren't you happy that we're groping your cunt and ass?!」	s17a	0471
PV01_701_A	3	5	Yukikaze: 「I-I'm not happyyy! I'm not! Ah! Aah! I'm not happy at all! You're wrong!!」	s17a	0472
PV01_701_A	3	6	Man: 「You're saying that while exposing your ahegao!」 「Your pussy feels good, right? Slurp!」 「You also like having your asshole toyed with, right? You slut!」	s17a	0473
PV01_701_A	3	7	What are the men saying? Yukikaze can't tell anymore.	s17a	0474
PV01_701_A	3	8	While holding a finger in her mouth, her cunt is being licked and her asshole kneaded. Not to mention chest and thighs, her entire body is groped.	s17a	0475
PV01_701_A	3	9	Yukikaze: 「I-I han't help it ahlright?! If-If shou lick my pushy that much, I'm going to feel it!」	s17a	0476
PV01_701_A	3	10	Yukikaze: 「And my tits became so hard after you rubbed them so much! If you mess with my butthole too, obviously I'm gonna feel it!!」	s17a	0477
PV01_701_A	3	11	Yukikaze: 「I-I'm not lewd! It's only because it feels too good!! Stupid, stupid, stupiiiid!!」	s17a	0478
PV01_701_A	3	12	Man: 「Gyahahaha! It's only because it feels too good? You're a funny one!!」	s17a	0479
PV01_701_A	3	13	Yukikaze: 「Uu! Shud up, shud up! Shud uuuup!!」	s17a	0480
PV01_701_A	3	14	Yukikaze continues frantically denying it.	s17a	0481
PV01_701_A	3	15	However, her expression has loosened due to bliss. There doesn't seem to be any reason left in her.	s17a	0482
PV01_701_A	3	16	Yukikaze: （This is all because of the oil! It's because of the oil that my head goes blank……！）	s17a	0483
PV01_701_A	3	17	Yukikaze: （That's why Yukikaze will pretend to be a lewd pig!!）	s17a	0484
PV01_701_A	3	18	There is no trace left of the Yukikaze from a month ago, who damaged her brain to resist the pleasure for Tatsurou's sake.	s17a	0485
PV01_701_A	3	19	Her pride as a Taimanin and her dignity as a woman are also gone. She lets herself at the mercy of vulgar men she has never met, welcoming the orgasms they provide her with.	s17a	0486
PV01_701_A	3	20	Yukikaze: 「Ahe! Hahe! Ah! Aheahihe! Hahee! Aah! I-I'm cumming! I'm cumming so hard!!」	s17a	0487
PV01_701_A	3	21	Man: 「Do you want to cum? Do you want to expose your pathetic ahegao?」	s17a	0488
PV01_701_A	3	22	Yukikaze: 「I-I want to cum! Let me cum!! E-Everyone, look at my ahegao! A big one is coming, so watch me! Aah! Aah!!」	s17a	0489
PV01_701_A	3	23	Yukikaze: 「Aah, I'll cum! I-I can't hold back anymore! Ah! I'll cum, I'll cuum! Aahn! Everyone! I'm cumming, I'm cummiiiiing!!」	s17a	0490
PV01_701_A	3	24	Man: 「Look! Yukikaze the filthy sow is cumming!」	s17a	0491
PV01_701_A	3	25	Immediately after someone said that――	s17a	0492
PV01_701_A	3	26	Yukikaze: 「Aaaaaannnnnnnn!!」	s17a	0493
PV01_701_A	3	27	Yukikaze screams from her orgasm.	s17a	0494
PV01_701_A	3	28	Man: 「Yukikaze-chan came!」	s17a	0495
PV01_701_A	3	29	The man who was tasting her pussy moves his mouth away.	s17a	0496
PV01_701_A	3	30	Yukikaze: 「Aah!! Aaahn!! Hyaaan! Hahi! Nhiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii!!!」	s17a	0497
PV01_701_A	3	31	This man spreads out her entrance with his fingers. From down there, Yukikaze squirts like a water gun.	s17a	0498
PV01_701_A	3	32	Man: 「Whoah! Amazing!!」 「Yukikaze-chan, you squirted a lot!!」	s17a	0499
PV01_701_A	3	33	Yukikaze: 「Hi! I squirted! Nhii! It came ouut!  A lot of my dirty juices came ouuut!」	s17a	0500
PV01_701_A	3	34	Yukikaze: （It's embarrassing……But, It feels good!…… Cumming and squirting in front of everyone…… It's the best!!）	s17a	0501
PV01_701_A	3	35	Showing her vulgar self in front of so many men makes her feel even more pleasure.	s17a	0502
PV01_701_A	3	36	Yukikaze: 「Aah! Cumming, cumming! I'm cumming again even though I just came! Look, everyone! I'm going to cum, so watch me!!」	s17a	0503
PV01_701_A	3	37	Man: 「Of course we're looking at you!」 「Show off your ahegao, you sow!」	s17a	0504
PV01_701_A	3	38	Yukikaze: 「Yes, yes! Cumming! Cumming! I'm cumming while showing my ahegao! I'm cumming like a sow! Ah! Cumming! Cumming like a sow! Cumming like a sow――」	s17a	0505
PV01_701_A	3	39	Yukikaze: 「I'm cumming like a soooooooooooooow!!!」	s17a	0506
PV01_701_A	3	40	Yukikaze finally calls herself a sow.	s17a	0507
PV01_701_A	4	1	While squirting as usual from her cunt, bowel juices also come gushing from her asshole.	s17a	0508
PV01_701_A	4	2	However, no matter how intense it is, climaxing without a male's cock is painful for Yukikaze.	s17a	0509
PV01_701_A	4	3	Yukikaze: 「Haaa! Haa! Haa! Coock…… I want cock!……Everyone's cock…… Please, fuck me with your wonderful cocks……」	s17a	0510
PV01_701_A	4	4	Dicks are the only thing in Yukikaze's glittering eyes.	s17a	0511
PV01_701_A	4	5	Man: 「Do you really want our cocks that much? You whore.」	s17a	0512
PV01_701_A	4	6	Yukikaze: 「I-I want them!……I want cock! I'm fine with being a whore. I'm fine with being a perverted sex slave……」	s17a	0513
PV01_701_A	4	7	While she's jostled by the men, Yukikaze supplicates them and drools .	s17a	0514
PV01_701_A	4	8	Man: 「So that's the infamous Taimanin.」 「She really degraded into a sow! This is awesome!」	s17a	0515
PV01_701_A	4	9	Caught up in the obscenity of a real sex slave, the men swallow deeply and their dicks get even more swollen.	s17a	0516
PV01_701_A	4	10	Who will violate Yukikaze first? They start playing "Rock, paper, scissors" to decide.	s17a	0517
PV01_701_A	4	11	Yukikaze: 「Haa! Haa! Haa! Aaaaaah!!」	s17a	0518
PV01_701_A	4	12	Yukikaze: （I-It's like the other day, the day when my head broke. Everyone wants to violate me so much!!）	s17a	0519
PV01_701_A	4	13	Even though she understands that feeling this way isn't normal, Yukikaze's womb shivers with such anticipation that it's painful.	s17a	0520
PV01_701_A	4	14	Her vagina, having just came from a tongue, is twitching. Her greedy love juices are dripping just like drool.	s17a	0521
PV01_701_A	4	15	Man: 「Come on! Don't just sit there waiting!」 「Your little hands aren't doing anything, Yukikaze-chan!」	s17a	0522
PV01_701_A	4	16	The men who lost at "Rock, paper, scissors" push their cocks at Yukikaze for some handjobs.	s17a	0523
PV01_701_A	4	17	Yukikaze: （Aah! This smell! The pungent smell of this stinking cock!…… I know it isn't good, but I've really been wanting this!!）	s17a	0524
PV01_701_A	4	18	Yukikaze: 「Haa, ahaa, Amazing……Cocks……So many…… Your twitching, erect cocks, so many……so many……」	s17a	0525
PV01_701_A	4	19	Yukikaze, lightheaded from lust, eyes up two cocks amongst those lined up before her and grabs them.	s17a	0526
PV01_701_A	4	20	The two lucky men start groaning.	s17a	0527
PV01_701_A	4	21	Without realizing it, Yukikaze uses the technique she trained in as a sex slave to skillfully stimulate the meat rods.	s17a	0528
PV01_701_A	4	22	Yukikaze: 「Ah!……Aah! Hard! Your stiff cocks are……Hard…… Your erect cocks……are soo hard……Haan!」	s17a	0529
PV01_701_A	4	23	Like a junkie suffering from cock addiction, Yukikaze starts stroking their dicks with a look of bliss on her face.	s17a	0530
PV01_701_A	4	24	Yukikaze: 「Nh! Fu! Ahn! Does it feel good? It feels good right? Your cocks are twitching…… Aha! I love energetic cocks……Nh! Nh!」	s17a	0531
PV01_701_A	4	25	Yukikaze's handjob is perfect, her movement not too weak nor too strong.	s17a	0532
PV01_701_A	4	26	Then, Yukikaze starts playing using her finger with the precum on her hands.	s17a	0533
PV01_701_A	4	27	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Aah!! The early cock juice came out!…… Ahn! Chupu! Rero! Delicious! It tastes like thin semen……Rerorero!」	s17a	0534
PV01_701_A	4	28	Without hesitation, Yukikaze tastes the precum on her hands.	s17a	0535
PV01_701_A	4	29	Yukikaze: 「Chupa……Nnpa……Haan! I really…… Shouldn't do that……Nuu, I can't stoop…… Cocks are delicious, so delicious……」	s17a	0536
PV01_701_A	4	30	Man: 「Incredible. So that's an authentic sex slave?」 「Real's brothel is too expensive for us so we can't go. It was worth it to come watch the show!」	s17a	0537
PV01_701_A	4	31	The men surrounding Yukikaze are talking in agreement.	s17a	0538
PV01_701_A	4	32	While one person gropes Yukikaze's breast and thighs, another one strokes his own cock and rubs the tip against her skin.	s17a	0539
PV01_701_A	4	33	Yukikaze: 「Th-That's right……O-Only 3,000 yen…… Nuu! You wouldn't usually be able to purchase me!!」	s17a	0540
PV01_701_A	4	34	Yukikaze: （Wh-What am I saying?! It's not like I'm proud that I became a sex slave!）	s17a	0541
PV01_701_A	4	35	Realizing the words that just came out of her mouth, Yukikaze is terrified at how crazy she has become.	s17a	0542
PV01_701_A	4	36	Man: 「Today is just 3,000 for one go, that's a pretty cheap cunt. I'll really enjoy myself here.」	s17a	0543
PV01_701_A	4	37	The large man tucks 3,000 yen between her bikini string and pulls aside the cloth covering her crotch.	s17a	0544
PV01_701_A	4	38	Yukikaze: 「Hyaann! Ah! Aaah!!」	s17a	0545
PV01_701_A	4	39	Her impatient pussy painfully tightens at the sensation of open air.	s17a	0546
PV01_701_A	4	40	Yukikaze glances back at the man who won at "Rock, paper scissors".	s17a	0547
PV01_701_A	5	1	Yukikaze: 「Aaaaaaaaaah!」	s17a	0548
PV01_701_A	5	2	A shriek of joy comes out Yukikaze's mouth.	s17a	0549
PV01_701_A	5	3	As expected from his build, his huge cock is about as big as her arm. It stands tall with its head swollen, ready to pierce the heavens.	s17a	0550
PV01_701_A	5	4	Yukikaze: （I-Incredible……What an incredible cock!…… If he puts puts this inside me, I will definitely go crazy!…… I will be cumming like a retard……）	s17a	0551
PV01_701_A	5	5	Man: 「Your cheap cunt is opening and closing, inviting me in. What a filthy sow you are.」	s17a	0552
PV01_701_A	5	6	Lust glitters in the eyes of the large man. He shoves his large cock inside in one go.	s17a	0553
PV01_701_A	5	7	Yukikaze: 「Ahii! Hii! Hahiiiiiiiiii!」	s17a	0554
PV01_701_A	5	8	Yukikaze's body twitches at the fierce penetration.	s17a	0555
PV01_701_A	5	9	The big man's cock forces open her entrance, spreading out her walls as he plunges in deeper and deeper.	s17a	0556
PV01_701_A	5	10	Yukikaze: 「It's entering! Your amazing cock! Your amazing cock is entering me! Aah! My pussy is getting stretched out!!」	s17a	0557
PV01_701_A	5	11	Man: 「Ku! In spite of being a sex slave your loli cunt is really tight! It's eating my dick.」	s17a	0558
PV01_701_A	5	12	While Yukikaze is moaning from pleasure, the man penetrating her has a pained expression.	s17a	0559
PV01_701_A	5	13	Yukikaze: 「Hya! Ah! Nu, nuuu, ahn!……Hanhan! Inside me!……Uuu! Your cock is twitching!!」	s17a	0560
PV01_701_A	5	14	Yukikaze distinctly feels that the man's cock  is aroused by her tight, dripping wet pussy.	s17a	0561
PV01_701_A	5	15	Feeling like the center of her body is on fire, Yukikaze's brain breaks from the sensation of being impaled by a lance of meat.	s17a	0562
PV01_701_A	5	16	Yukikaze: 「A-After all……Cocks feel goood…… Why does it feels so good…… My pussy is so delighted……Ah! Aaah!」	s17a	0563
PV01_701_A	5	17	Man: 「I'll make it feel even better!」	s17a	0564
PV01_701_A	5	18	Yukikaze: 「Hiuunn!」	s17a	0565
PV01_701_A	5	19	The man grabs Yukikaze's waist with his massive hands.	s17a	0566
PV01_701_A	5	20	His cock pushes deeper inside her vagina.	s17a	0567
PV01_701_A	5	21	At the sweet expectation of the piston action that's about to begin, her pussy tightly coils around his dick.	s17a	0568
PV01_701_A	5	22	Man: 「Rejoice yourself with my cock! You loli cunt slut!!」	s17a	0569
PV01_701_A	5	23	Yukikaze: 「Nhoooooo! Oh! Ohooooooo!!」	s17a	0570
PV01_701_A	5	24	The yell of a bitch in heat comes out of her mouth.	s17a	0571
PV01_701_A	5	25	Without holding back, the large man's cock starts punishing her naughty snatch.	s17a	0572
PV01_701_A	5	26	Yukikaze: 「Ihii! Hahi! Nhii! Dooon't! You just inserted it……!!! You're too rooouuugh!!!」	s17a	0573
PV01_701_A	5	27	With his aroused cock growing even bigger, her pussy is hollowed out evenly, from the entrance to its depths.	s17a	0574
PV01_701_A	5	28	The love juices that were accumulating in her vagina are raked out by his head and gush outside with a wet sound.	s17a	0575
PV01_701_A	5	29	Yukikaze: 「Hahii! Nhiiin! Amashing! An amashing sound is coming out!!」	s17a	0576
PV01_701_A	5	30	Yukikaze: 「My pussy! My pussy is! Aahn! Your fat cock is grinding mee! Nhii! I'm squealing like a retard!!」	s17a	0577
PV01_701_A	5	31	Yukikaze's frail body looks like it's about to collapse each time the huge piece of meat stabs the depths of her vagina.	s17a	0578
PV01_701_A	5	32	Man: 「Her legs are shaking like a newborn fawn!」 「Stand straight, you pig whore!!」 「If even a great Taimanin acts like that, she must be done for!」	s17a	0579
PV01_701_A	5	33	The vulgar men laugh at Yukikaze, who is unable to stand anymore because of the pleasure.	s17a	0580
PV01_701_A	5	34	Yukikaze: 「I-It can't be helped, alright?! I'm being watched by such a huge crowd! I'm being fucked so haaard!!」	s17a	0581
PV01_701_A	5	35	Yukikaze: 「In the public square, I-I……I'm having sex in front of everyone……! I'm whoring myself in front of everyone……!!!!」	s17a	0582
PV01_701_A	5	36	Man: 「Ku! I'll fuck you even harder in front of everyone!」	s17a	0583
PV01_701_A	5	37	The man's hips start moving faster.	s17a	0584
PV01_701_A	5	38	Yukikaze: 「Nhooo! Oh! Oooooooooh!!」	s17a	0585
PV01_701_A	5	39	Yukikaze: 「M-My pussy! My pussy will break! But it feels good! Even though my pussy will break it feels so good I'll go crazy!!」	s17a	0586
PV01_701_A	5	40	Yukikaze's slender body bends backwards like a bow.	s17a	0587
PV01_701_A	6	1	Feeling that the man is about to come, Yukikaze's pussy starts furiously twitching and tightening.	s17a	0588
PV01_701_A	6	2	Yukikaze: 「Hyahi! S-Semen is coming!! It's coming! Your semen will be coming inside my pussy!!」	s17a	0589
PV01_701_A	6	3	Man: 「As expected from a sex slave sow, I'm about to cum!! I'll cum inside you a lot! I'll impregnate you with my first shot!!」	s17a	0590
PV01_701_A	6	4	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Ah! Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!!」	s17a	0591
PV01_701_A	6	5	Yukikaze: （I will get creampied again!!! I will definitely cum!…… I can't hold back from cumming anymore……I want to cum…… I want to cum like a retard!!）	s17a	0592
PV01_701_A	6	6	Yukikaze: （B-But!……Getting pregnant……Getting pregnant is no good…… It's no good, but! My dirty sow cunt! It really hungers for semen!）	s17a	0593
PV01_701_A	6	7	――Byuru, Byuru, Byurubyuru!!	s17a	0594
PV01_701_A	6	8	Yukikaze: 「Hahii! S-Semeeeen!!」	s17a	0595
PV01_701_A	6	9	Pulsing inside her pussy, the man's penis starts vomiting semen.	s17a	0596
PV01_701_A	6	10	Yukikaze instantly reaches the apex of pleasure.	s17a	0597
PV01_701_A	6	11	Yukikaze: 「Nhooooo! Ooh! I'm cumming! I'm cumming from being creampied! Cumming! Cummiiiiing――」	s17a	0598
PV01_701_A	6	12	Her tiny body suddenly stiffens.	s17a	0599
PV01_701_A	6	13	Yukikaze: 「Cummiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiing!!」	s17a	0600
PV01_701_A	6	14	She climaxes once more.	s17a	0601
PV01_701_A	6	15	The orgasm from being creampied is incomparable to her previous one.	s17a	0602
PV01_701_A	6	16	Yukikaze: （It feels good! It feels good! It feels so gooooooooodd!!!）	s17a	0603
PV01_701_A	6	17	Yukikaze: 「Hahii! Hahiii! Hyahahiiiiiiiiii!!」	s17a	0604
PV01_701_A	6	18	She screams with her eyes rolled back in her head.	s17a	0605
PV01_701_A	6	19	Her pussy is squeezing cock juice out of his miserable dick.	s17a	0606
PV01_701_A	6	20	Yukikaze: 「Aah! I caaame! It feeels goood! The semen inside me……It's so hot, thick and sirupy…… Ooh! Cumming! Cummiiiiiiiiing!!」	s17a	0607
PV01_701_A	6	21	Whenever hot semen is vomited inside her, Yukikaze screams from her orgasm, her body twitching.	s17a	0608
PV01_701_A	6	22	Man: 「We are also cumming!!」 「Yukikaze-chan, we will shower your face!!」	s17a	0609
PV01_701_A	6	23	Yukikaze: （Nowaynowaynowaaaaaaay!!）	s17a	0610
PV01_701_A	6	24	The other dicks surrounding her also splash jizz, aiming straight at her.	s17a	0611
PV01_701_A	6	25	Yukikaze: 「Nhiiiiiiiiiiiiiii!!」	s17a	0612
PV01_701_A	6	26	Waves of a muddy white stream appear before Yukikaze's eyes.	s17a	0613
PV01_701_A	6	27	Yukikaze: 「Aaah! So much semen! With so much semen! I'll be drowned in it! Ah! Ah! Aaaaaah!!」	s17a	0614
PV01_701_A	6	28	Her body is stained on both the inside and the outside by the men's filthy juices.	s17a	0615
PV01_701_A	6	29	Yukikaze: 「N-No more……I will really become stupid…… Semen feels too good…… I can't take anymore……」	s17a	0616
PV01_701_A	6	30	Yukikaze: 「That's why, pleashe……Don't get pregnant……Eh…… Please, my body……Just don't……get pregnant……」	s17a	0617
PV01_701_A	6	31	While her entire body is shaking from an unstopable orgasm, Yukikaze keeps praying with what little reason is left in her.	s17a	0618
PV01_701_A	6	32	Yukikaze: 「Ahehaa……Hehaa……So much…… You've released so much……」	s17a	0619
PV01_701_A	6	33	The ejaculation of the first man finally ends. He pulls out his penis with a "schlorp".	s17a	0620
PV01_701_A	6	34	Yukikaze doesn't even try to conceal her expression, melted by several consecutive orgasms, from the men.	s17a	0621
PV01_701_A	6	35	Yukikaze: 「Hyaan……Ah! Ahn! From my pussy…… Syrupy semen is dripping…… Ahe! Hahe!……」	s17a	0622
PV01_701_A	6	36	Her pussy opens and closes, matching her hiccups.	s17a	0623
PV01_701_A	6	37	The recently released semen is regurgitated by her pussy with an obscene noise. This sight becomes a show for everyone.	s17a	0624
PV01_701_A	6	38	Yukikaze: 「Haa……Haa……Hihaa, haa……Haan!……」	s17a	0625
PV01_701_A	6	39	Man: 「Hoho! I really released a lot, Yukikaze-chan♪」	s17a	0626
PV01_701_A	6	40	Man: 「Even the great Taimanin-sama gets subjugated by my wicked sperm!」	s17a	0627
PV01_701_A	7	1	Yukikaze: 「Haa, haa……Haa, haa, haa……」	s17a	0628
PV01_701_A	7	2	Man: 「Your erotic expression is the best, Yukikaze-chan!」	s17a	0629
PV01_701_A	7	3	Man: 「With this, Yukikaze-chan has become a true Yomihara citizen! Please do your best as a sex slave by cumming everyday♪」	s17a	0630
PV01_701_A	7	4	Yukikaze: （Those guys……are too noisy. If you have time to run your mouth just hurry up and fuck me……You guys are just pigs good only for their dicks anyway……）	s17a	0631
PV01_701_A	7	5	Ignoring the men's jokes, Yukikaze basks in the reverberations of her orgasms.	s17a	0632
PV01_701_A	7	6	Man: 「Let me take a picture to commemorate the ally of justice, government dog Yukikaze-chan orgasming and joining the inhabitants of darkness!」	s17a	0633
PV01_701_A	7	7	Man: 「Good idea! Let me take a picture with my cellphone too!」	s17a	0634
PV01_701_A	7	8	Man: 「Me too!!!」	s17a	0635
PV01_701_A	7	9	Yukikaze: 「Hya, a pishture? Wh-What are you saying……」	s17a	0636
PV01_701_A	7	10	Yukikaze glances at the men.	s17a	0637
PV01_701_A	7	11	Man: 「Idiot! You are supposed to smile on a commemorative picture! Wake up, you cunt!」	s17a	0638
PV01_701_A	7	12	Did he fail to ejaculate earlier? The man rudely speaks with his dick still erect.	s17a	0639
PV01_701_A	7	13	Yukikaze: 「D-Dahm yo――」	s17a	0640
PV01_701_A	7	14	The man goes behind Yukikaze and suddenly shoves the second dick inside her.	s17a	0641
PV01_701_A	7	15	Yukikaze: 「Hoheeeeeeeeeeeee!!」	s17a	0642
PV01_701_A	7	16	Yukikaze's body twiches and bends back again.	s17a	0643
PV01_701_A	7	17	Yukikaze: 「Nho! Oh! Oh! Oooooooooooooh!!」	s17a	0644
PV01_701_A	7	18	The orgasm waves, which had been diminishing, spring up again.	s17a	0645
PV01_701_A	7	19	Man: 「We're taking a picture there. Hurry up and show off your ahegao already!!」	s17a	0646
PV01_701_A	7	20	Yukikaze: 「E-Even if you tell me that! Nhyafu! Ehaa! Aaaah!!」	s17a	0647
PV01_701_A	7	21	His cock pumps into her pussy, still sensitive no matter how many times she comes.	s17a	0648
PV01_701_A	7	22	Yukikaze: 「S-Stop! Let my pussy rest a little, Don't thrust it in like thaaat!! This isn't gooood!!」	s17a	0649
PV01_701_A	7	23	Man: 「Do you think a cunt like you can have the leisure to rest?!! Oraoraora!!」	s17a	0650
PV01_701_A	7	24	The man earnestly and violently punishes Yukikaze.	s17a	0651
PV01_701_A	7	25	Though she's asking for the man to stop, Yukikaze also understands it's useless for her to try to resist the pleasure.	s17a	0652
PV01_701_A	7	26	Yukikaze: （I-I can't anymore! I can't hold back my pussy anymore!! I'm starting to climax again!!）	s17a	0653
PV01_701_A	7	27	Yukikaze: 「Nhohiiii! Hieaa! Ah! Aah! Your cock! Your cock is amashiiiiing!!」	s17a	0654
PV01_701_A	7	28	Man: 「Whoa, what a great ahegao! Yukikaze-chan, peace! Do the peace sign in front of everyone♪」	s17a	0655
PV01_701_A	7	29	Yukikaze: 「P-Peaace!」	s17a	0656
PV01_701_A	7	30	Doing as she's told, Yukikaze makes a peace sign with her two hands still sticky from the ejaculation a little while ago.	s17a	0657
PV01_701_A	7	31	Thanks to her intense sex slave training, the smile of a sow trying to please a man appears on her face through reflex.	s17a	0658
PV01_701_A	7	32	Man: 「Gyahaha! You're the most erotic, Yukikaze-chan!」	s17a	0659
PV01_701_A	7	33	The men take pictures of Yukikaze's face while sneering at her.	s17a	0660
PV01_701_A	7	34	Yukikaze: （Aah, I'm being photographied……The men are recording my face as a filthy sow……）	s17a	0661
PV01_701_A	7	35	Yukikaze's body starts shivering from the pleasure of being abused.	s17a	0662
PV01_701_A	7	36	From being violated, from being scorned, her sex slave body becomes excited.	s17a	0663
PV01_701_A	7	37	Yukikaze: （This feeling……No good, I hate it but, it feels good…… It's so embarrassing I feel like dying…… But it feels so good I feel like dying.）	s17a	0664
PV01_701_A	7	38	Yukikaze: 「Ahe! Ahaa! Look, peeaace! Peace, Peaaafee……」	s17a	0665
PV01_701_A	7	39	Yukikaze: 「Everyone, take moooore pictures! It's fine to set my ahegao as your wallpaper……」	s17a	0666
PV01_701_A	7	40	Yukikaze: 「No, if you don't, I hon't forgif you! Come on, you love my pusshy right? Peaace! It's the peace ahegao of a sow……Ahaaa.」	s17a	0667
PV01_701_A	8	1	In front of Yukikaze's hazy double peace ahegao obscenity, the men actually forget to take a picture.	s17a	0668
PV01_701_A	8	2	Man: 「Is she really a former Taimanin? She's too erotic.」	s17a	0669
PV01_701_A	8	3	Man: 「I-I can't take it anymore! I'll use Yukikaze-chan's asshole!」	s17a	0670
PV01_701_A	8	4	Man: 「Then, let's change the position!」	s17a	0671
PV01_701_A	8	5	Yukikaze: 「Eh!?」	s17a	0672
PV01_701_A	8	6	The peace ahegao photoshoot abruptly ends.	s17a	0673
PV01_701_A	8	7	Yukikaze's body is lifted by the men and her position changes.	s17a	0674
PV01_701_A	8	8	Yukikaze: 「Hyaan! W-Wait!」	s17a	0675
PV01_701_A	8	9	Of course, there is still a penis inside her vagina.	s17a	0676
PV01_701_A	8	10	The bumps on the dick inside her rub against her vaginal walls.	s17a	0677
PV01_701_A	8	11	Yukikaze: 「Hyan! Ah! Ahi! Inside my pussy! The bumps on the cock……Aahn! It's rubbing so much!」	s17a	0678
PV01_701_A	8	12	While Yukikaze is moaning, the man who was penetrating her from behind lies on the ground.	s17a	0679
PV01_701_A	8	13	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Aaah! Aaaahnnn!!」	s17a	0680
PV01_701_A	8	14	Yukikaze is straddling over the man, assuming a cowgirl position.	s17a	0681
PV01_701_A	8	15	Yukikaze: 「Haa, haa, haa……Haan! Haa, hiaan!」	s17a	0682
PV01_701_A	8	16	The stimulation of the dick caused by the position switch makes Yukikaze come again, albeit lightly.	s17a	0683
PV01_701_A	8	17	The man is now skewering her from below, causing Yukikaze to gasp for air again and again.	s17a	0684
PV01_701_A	8	18	Man: 「Your body is so light but your amazing cunt is clamping down!」	s17a	0685
PV01_701_A	8	19	Yukikaze: 「Nhiiiiiinn!!」	s17a	0686
PV01_701_A	8	20	The man's dick pushes Yukikaze up.	s17a	0687
PV01_701_A	8	21	As her delicate body twitches and shivers, Yukikaze lets out a shrill moan.	s17a	0688
PV01_701_A	8	22	Yukikaze: 「Haahaa, haa……P-Please……Let me rest a little…… I've been cumming again and again……Haa, haan, I can't breathe……」	s17a	0689
PV01_701_A	8	23	Man: 「You're really sensitive, Yukikaze-chan. I'm sure I'll be able to enjoy your ass like that.」	s17a	0690
PV01_701_A	8	24	A fat man turns towards Yukikaze's back, rubbing her asshole with his finger.	s17a	0691
PV01_701_A	8	25	Yukikaze: 「Hyannn!!」	s17a	0692
PV01_701_A	8	26	The pleasure from her ass runs through her spine, causing her entire body to stiffen.	s17a	0693
PV01_701_A	8	27	Her coveting asshole twitches and tightens powerfully.	s17a	0694
PV01_701_A	8	28	Yukikaze: 「Haa, haa……Y-You're going to put it in my ass? R-Right……Now? It'll be inside me?」	s17a	0695
PV01_701_A	8	29	Yukikaze asks while panting like an animal.	s17a	0696
PV01_701_A	8	30	Man: 「Of course, your asshole looks yummy! Thanks for your ass pussy, Yukikaze-chan!」	s17a	0698
PV01_701_A	8	31	The fatty who speaks like a child presses his large cock against Yukikaze's anus.	s17a	0699
PV01_701_A	8	32	Yukikaze: 「W-Wait……Please, just wait a moment…… Even a little while is fine…… D-Don't put it inside my ass yet――」	s17a	0700
PV01_701_A	8	33	Yukikaze turns back, begging the man to stop.	s17a	0701
PV01_701_A	8	34	Man: 「No can dooooo!」	s17a	0702
PV01_701_A	8	35	The fatty suddenly falls down on Yukikaze, shoving his cock inside her ass with all his weight.	s17a	0703
PV01_701_A	8	36	Yukikaze: 「Nhiho! Uuuuuuu!!」	s17a	0704
PV01_701_A	8	37	Yukikaze moans at the top of her lungs.	s17a	0705
PV01_701_A	8	38	Yukikaze: （Something amazing came in my ass!!）	s17a	0706
PV01_701_A	8	39	The pleasure is completely different compared to her pussy being violated; the feeling of immorality makes her body twitch.	s17a	0707
PV01_701_A	8	40	The fatty's huge cock rapidly spreads out her asshole, crushing her intestines as it enters.	s17a	0708
PV01_701_A	9	1	Yukikaze: 「Ohhofu! My asshole! It's spreading out! Hiha! Ha! It's going in deeper and deepeeer!!」	s17a	0709
PV01_701_A	9	2	Man: 「Fuhihihi! Yukikaze-chan, your ass pussy is clamping on me!」	s17a	0710
PV01_701_A	9	3	Yukikaze: 「Nuu! Hafuiuu! Nua! Ah! Hahi! Fuhiiii!!」	s17a	0711
PV01_701_A	9	4	Yukikaze: （Th-That disgusting fatty……Is violating my ass…… N-No good……I'm feeling iiit!）	s17a	0712
PV01_701_A	9	5	Yukikaze is filled with the pleasure of being violated by a man who physically repulses her inside her asshole.	s17a	0713
PV01_701_A	9	6	Man: 「Deyufufu, Yukikaze-chan's ass pussy feels gooood～♪」	s17a	0714
PV01_701_A	9	7	That man buries his cock up to the base inside her intestines, and starts crashing into her oily body in a piston motion.	s17a	0715
PV01_701_A	9	8	Yukikaze: 「Nehaa! Hahi! Ohi! Hehyaa! Ehii!!」	s17a	0716
PV01_701_A	9	9	Yukikaze's frail body is shaking, hit from front and the rear.	s17a	0717
PV01_701_A	9	10	Without worrying about her reputation or appearance, Yukikaze moans again and again, unable to properly articulate anymore.	s17a	0718
PV01_701_A	9	11	Yukikaze: 「Nhii! My-My asshole! My asshoole! It's getting turned inside ouuut!!」	s17a	0719
PV01_701_A	9	12	The man's dick is drawing out her spread asshole, moving her juices from the inside to the outside.	s17a	0720
PV01_701_A	9	13	The sticky sounds of his thick cock rubbing inside her ass resonate as her bowel juices overflow like a fountain.	s17a	0721
PV01_701_A	9	14	Yukikaze: 「Ohee! Haheee! Hiheha! Nhiiiiiiiiiii!!」	s17a	0722
PV01_701_A	9	15	Man: 「Your ass pussy feels good? It must feel good, right? Come on, answer me, Yukikaze-chan. Say that your ass pussy feels good!」	s17a	0723
PV01_701_A	9	16	Speaking with a syrupy voice, the man keeps pounding his cock inside Yukikaze's asshole.	s17a	0724
PV01_701_A	9	17	Man: 「It's not just her ass pussy. This cunt here also can't get enough of my dick! That fucking sow!!」	s17a	0725
PV01_701_A	9	18	Yukikaze: 「Ehyaaaaaaaaa!!」	s17a	0726
PV01_701_A	9	19	The man below Yukikaze starts pushing his penis even higher.	s17a	0727
PV01_701_A	9	20	Her cervix is completely crushed.	s17a	0728
PV01_701_A	9	21	At the same time, the two cocks furiously grind against  the thin membrane between her ass and her vagina.	s17a	0729
PV01_701_A	9	22	Yukikaze: （Aah, no more! I can't hold anymore!! There's no way I could hold back any longer!!）	s17a	0730
PV01_701_A	9	23	Yukikaze: （It's fine, right? Rinko-senpai also was so miserably lewd…… So just a little…… Going crazy on those dicks just a little should be fine!）	s17a	0731
PV01_701_A	9	24	Yukikaze: （I mean, my pussy and asshole, they feel, so, so gooooood, I have to!!）	s17a	0732
PV01_701_A	9	25	Before she notices, using Rinko as an excuse, Yukikaze starts proactively indulging on the pleasure of the dicks.	s17a	0733
PV01_701_A	9	26	Yukikaze: 「Oh! Ooooh! It feeels gooood!! My pussy and ass pussy, they both feel too goood!!」	s17a	0734
PV01_701_A	9	27	Yukikaze: 「Y-Your cocks are! Your two cocks are thrusting, messing up my insides! I'm about to lose my mind!!」	s17a	0735
PV01_701_A	9	28	Yukikaze: （I……!! I'm just a sex slave right now……!!! So having sex right now is fine……!!!）	s17a	0736
PV01_701_A	9	29	Unlike before, Yukikaze subdues her reason and starts indulging in the pleasure.	s17a	0737
PV01_701_A	9	30	Yukikaze: 「Nfah! Ah! Hieaah! Dicksh heel goood!!! My asshole alsho feelsh good!!!」	s17a	0738
PV01_701_A	9	31	Using the sex technique she was taught in sex slave training, Yukikaze furiously shakes her hips trapped between the two men.	s17a	0739
PV01_701_A	9	32	Their two cocks repeatedly enter her holes, meeting inside of her as her crotch shakes in all directions.	s17a	0740
PV01_701_A	9	33	Yukikaze: 「Moore! Fuck me more! Fuck me until my pussy and my asshole become one!!」	s17a	0741
PV01_701_A	9	34	Man: 「Ku! It feels like my dick is going to be ripped off!!」 「Oink! Yukikaze-chan, this is bad!!」	s17a	0742
PV01_701_A	9	35	Yukikaze: 「Noooo!! Don't stop moving your cocks! Don't cum either! More, fuck me more!! Come on! Come on! Come oooon!!」	s17a	0743
PV01_701_A	9	36	Her two holes have completely constricted their cocks. They are not allowed to ejaculate, and her hips move furiously.	s17a	0744
PV01_701_A	9	37	Man: 「Ooh! Uoooooo!!」 「Yu-Yu-Yukikaze-chan!! Uhiii!!」	s17a	0745
PV01_701_A	9	38	The situation is completely reversed.	s17a	0746
PV01_701_A	9	39	The men who were tormenting Yukikaze a little while ago now have a stiff expression as pleasure is forced on them.	s17a	0747
PV01_701_A	9	40	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Aaah! Thish feels gooood!! Amazing!! Sex slave sex feels goooood!!!」	s17a	0748
PV01_701_A	10	1	Using the men as live dildos, Yukikaze approaches her biggest orgasm.	s17a	0749
PV01_701_A	10	2	At that moment, Tatsurou's face appears in Yukikaze's mind.	s17a	0750
PV01_701_A	10	3	Yukikaze: 「Nooooooooooooo!!」	s17a	0751
PV01_701_A	10	4	Yukikaze screams.	s17a	0752
PV01_701_A	10	5	Yukikaze: 「D-Don't appear at a time like this!!」	s17a	0753
PV01_701_A	10	6	For her brain on the verge of climaxing, it isn't her beloved Tatsurou that appears before her, but a hindrance to her pleasure.	s17a	0754
PV01_701_A	10	7	Yukikaze: （Go away, Tatsurou!!!）	s17a	0755
PV01_701_A	10	8	Yukikaze: （J-Just for now!!! Just for now, go away!!!!）	s17a	0756
PV01_701_A	10	9	Yukikaze: 「You're a pain! Hurry up and go awaaaaaay!!!」	s17a	0757
PV01_701_A	10	10	Yukikaze: 「Aaaaah! Cocks! cocks! cooooooocks! Right now I just want cocks!!!」	s17a	0758
PV01_701_A	10	11	Yukikaze frantically shouts.	s17a	0759
PV01_701_A	10	12	After chasing Tatsurou from her mind with no hesitation, an orgasm comes to replace him.	s17a	0760
PV01_701_A	10	13	Yukikaze: 「Oho! Hoooo! A big one is coming! I'm coming from my cunt! I'm coming from my ass! It's comiiiiing!!」	s17a	0761
PV01_701_A	10	14	Yukikaze: 「Nhoooooooooo!! I'm cumming! My pussy is cumming! My ass is cumming! Cumming! Cumming! Cumming――」	s17a	0762
PV01_701_A	10	15	Yukikaze: 「I'm cummiiiiiiiiiiiiing!!!」	s17a	0763
PV01_701_A	10	16	Yukikaze screams as if she were howling at the moon.	s17a	0764
PV01_701_A	10	17	Although it was just for a moment, Yukikaze threw away her lover to be wrapped in an intense orgasm.	s17a	0765
PV01_701_A	10	18	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Aaah! It feels good! It feels gooood! My pussy and my asspussy feel goooooood!!」	s17a	0766
PV01_701_A	10	19	Cloudy semen is vomited inside her shivering pussy and asshole.	s17a	0767
PV01_701_A	10	20	The moment Yukikaze came, the men were allowed to ejaculate.	s17a	0768
PV01_701_A	10	21	Yukikaze: 「Nhoon! Ooon! Your sticky semen is coming inside my pussy and my asshole!! Cocks feel good! Cocks feel goood!!」	s17a	0769
PV01_701_A	10	22	Like hot magma, the man juice fills her womb and her bowels.	s17a	0770
PV01_701_A	10	23	However, for the finally unrestrained Yukikaze, the feeling only arouses her more, and her orgasm looks to be unending.	s17a	0771
PV01_701_A	10	24	Yukikaze: 「Aaahn! More! Cum more please!! Everyone's special juice, please shove it inside my fuckhoooles!!」	s17a	0772
PV01_701_A	10	25	Man: 「Oh! Oooooooooh!!」 「Oink, Oink! Oiiiiiink!!」	s17a	0773
PV01_701_A	10	26	The men have already become simple semen dispensers, forced to ejaculate as much as Yukikaze desires.	s17a	0774
PV01_701_A	10	27	However, their expression is filled with joy. Their brain is breaking from the pleasure given by the sex slave Yukikaze.	s17a	0775
PV01_701_A	10	28	Yukikaze: 「Turn me into a sex slave who can do nothing but think about cocks!! Make me into a meat toilet pig good only for her holes!!」	s17a	0776
PV01_701_A	10	29	Yukikaze: 「Oooooh! I'm cumming! Cumming, cumming! I'm going to cum like this! I don't want to think about anything! Aaaaaaaaah!!!」	s17a	0777
PV01_701_A	10	30	Throwing away what dignity she had left, Yukikaze earnestly wallows in the delight of her sow orgasm.	s17a	0778
PV01_701_A	10	31	Yukikaze: 「……a……a…………a…………」	s17a	0779
PV01_701_A	10	32	When her consecutive orgasms end, Yukikaze faints.	s17a	0780
PV01_701_A	10	33	Behind her slightly open eyelids, her eyes are completely white.	s17a	0781
PV01_701_A	10	34	Her expression is completely loose from her orgasm while her body keeps twitching.	s17a	0782
PV01_701_A	10	35	Yukikaze: 「Hea……a…………a……i」	s17a	0783
PV01_701_A	10	36	The sighs that sometimes escape from her drooling lips are extremly lewd.	s17a	0784
PV01_701_A	10	37	That Yukikaze, who forced two men to ejaculate, has completely passed out	s17a	0785
PV01_701_A	10	38	As the men pull out their limp dicks from her holes, semen is regurgitated from her gaping asshole and pussy.	s17a	0786
PV01_701_A	10	39	Yukikaze: 「……Au……Hiu……Hahi……i……」	s17a	0787
PV01_701_A	10	40	Although unconscious, it becomes clear Yukikaze is still feeling it.	s17a	0788
PV01_701_A	11	1	Man: 「Come on! How long is this semen tank going to sleep?!」	s17a	0789
PV01_701_A	11	2	――Pachin!	s17a	0790
PV01_701_A	11	3	Yukikaze: 「…………Uu.」	s17a	0791
PV01_701_A	11	4	The men start spanking Yukikaze to wake her up.	s17a	0792
PV01_701_A	11	5	Man: 「It's still too early for bedtime. You still have to attend to all of us, sex slave!」	s17a	0793
PV01_701_A	11	6	――Pachin Pachin!!!!	s17a	0794
PV01_701_A	11	7	Yukikaze: 「Nuu! Fu! Kuun!」	s17a	0795
PV01_701_A	11	8	The miserable sound of her ass getting slapped echoes in the plaza.	s17a	0796
PV01_701_A	11	9	The men and the spectators sneer at Yukikaze.	s17a	0797
PV01_701_A	11	10	Yukikaze: 「Ku! Nh! Nnh, Nnnh!!」	s17a	0798
PV01_701_A	11	11	Whenever her ass is spanked, her body painfully springs up.	s17a	0799
PV01_701_A	11	12	Although she's still unconscious, pleasure already appears on her face.	s17a	0800
PV01_701_A	11	13	Man: 「Whoa! She's feeling it even while sleeping!!」 「You're right! There must be nothing but dicks in her head!!」	s17a	0801
PV01_701_A	11	14	The more the men laugh at Yukikaze, the hornier they become.	s17a	0802
PV01_701_A	11	15	Man: 「Wake up already, cock woman!!」	s17a	0803
PV01_701_A	11	16	――Bachin!!	s17a	0804
PV01_701_A	11	17	Yukikaze: 「Hia!? Wh-What……What ish it?」	s17a	0805
PV01_701_A	11	18	Yukikaze's eyes suddenly fling open.	s17a	0806
PV01_701_A	11	19	Without understanding what's going on, Yukikaze looks around her.	s17a	0807
PV01_701_A	11	20	Man: 「You passed out while moaning so we're waking you up.」 「It won't end after just one or two dicks!!」	s17a	0808
PV01_701_A	11	21	Bachin! Bachin! Bachin!!	s17a	0809
PV01_701_A	11	22	The men get carried away and keep beating the ass of the now-awake Yukikaze.	s17a	0810
PV01_701_A	11	23	Yukikaze: 「Hyahi! I-I'm awake now……Hyaun!! Stop spanking me…… Ahn! I get it already!!」	s17a	0811
PV01_701_A	11	24	Whenever it is struck, the sound of her firm ass echoes.	s17a	0812
PV01_701_A	11	25	Her sphincter tightens, and the semen that was ejaculated inside her overflows with strength.	s17a	0813
PV01_701_A	11	26	Man: 「Gyahaha! Is this a semen squirt gun?!!」 「Are you taking everything out before the next cock hammers you?!」	s17a	0814
PV01_701_A	11	27	Bachin! Bachin Bachin!! Bachin Bachin Bachin!!	s17a	0815
PV01_701_A	11	28	Yukikaze: 「Nhi! Ahi! S-Stop! Oh! Ohii!! Don't say that!! Just fuck me already!!」	s17a	0816
PV01_701_A	11	29	Yukikaze: 「Today, my pussy and my ass pussy! Aun, Hifuun! They are for everyone to use freely!!」	s17a	0817
PV01_701_A	11	30	That night, in Yomihara, Yukikaze's sweet moans merged with the voices of the men mocking her.	s17a	0818
PV01_701_A	11	31	Thereafter, each time Yukikaze passed out after being fucked and climaxing, she was fucked again.	s17a	0819
PV01_701_A	11	32	Until the desire of the all the men who gather there was satisfied, every one of her holes was used repeatedly.	s17a	0820
