PV01_1001_A	1	1	Yukikaze: 「Those people are really……!!」	s23a	0128
PV01_1001_A	1	2	Yazaki: 「Now then, we should get started too.」	s23a	0129
PV01_1001_A	1	3	Yukikaze: 「Eh!? Wai-Hold on!」	s23a	0130
PV01_1001_A	1	4	Yukikaze reflexively resists Yazaki.	s23a	0131
PV01_1001_A	1	5	She dreads the shame that she would feel if she had an orgasm in this sort of situation.	s23a	0132
PV01_1001_A	1	6	Yukikaze: （If I'm violated in front of so many people, I'll cum like an idiot again!!）	s23a	0133
PV01_1001_A	1	7	Yazaki: 「Everyone is watching you.」	s23a	0134
PV01_1001_A	1	8	Yazaki winks at her.	s23a	0135
PV01_1001_A	1	9	Yukikaze: 「N-No way!」	s23a	0136
PV01_1001_A	1	10	Looking at her surroundings, Yukikaze notices the men nearby  are indeed staring at her ardently.	s23a	0137
PV01_1001_A	1	11	Yukikaze: （Noo! I'm being stared at!）	s23a	0138
PV01_1001_A	1	12	They are waiting for Yukikaze, the  former Taimanin turned sex slave, to display her unsightly ahegao.	s23a	0139
PV01_1001_A	1	13	Yazaki: 「Let's show them the proof that you became my little piggy.」	s23a	0140
PV01_1001_A	1	14	With his strong arms, Yazaki embraces Yukikaze.	s23a	0141
PV01_1001_A	1	15	Yukikaze: 「Hyau!!」	s23a	0142
PV01_1001_A	1	16	Yukikaze lets out a yell.	s23a	0143
PV01_1001_A	1	17	Yazaki forcefully seizes her lips.	s23a	0144
PV01_1001_A	1	18	Yukikaze: 「Nnuu……Nu……N-Noo…… Ngu, nnh.」	s23a	0145
PV01_1001_A	1	19	His wet tongue enters her mouth like a snake.	s23a	0146
PV01_1001_A	1	20	Yukikaze: 「Kuuu……Nh! Kafu……Uu, do……doon't…… Nnnh, i-if you kiss me……like that……Nnnnh.」	s23a	0147
PV01_1001_A	1	21	Yukikaze: （Kissing is bad……Even with someone like Yazaki……If I'm kissed…… My body becomes completely limp……Nooo……）	s23a	0148
PV01_1001_A	1	22	Helpless inside Yazaki's arms, Yukikaze's delicate body starts to shiver.	s23a	0149
PV01_1001_A	1	23	Yukikaze: 「Nuu……Kuu, ah……Uu……Kafuu…… Nnh, nu, ah……Aah……Yaa, yaaann!」	s23a	0150
PV01_1001_A	1	24	Her partner is Yazaki whom she hates to death.	s23a	0151
PV01_1001_A	1	25	However, for an entire month, he violated her again and again, and now her body remembers him.	s23a	0152
PV01_1001_A	1	26	Even if her mind is against it, her body wants to be abused by this odious man.	s23a	0153
PV01_1001_A	1	27	Yukikaze: （M-My pussy is getting wet…… My lewd juices are flooding…… Ah, Wai-What are you doing?!）	s23a	0154
PV01_1001_A	1	28	While pressing against her lips, Yazaki takes out his dick and makes Yukikaze grab it.	s23a	0155
PV01_1001_A	1	29	Yukikaze: 「Haaaann!」	s23a	0156
PV01_1001_A	1	30	Yukikaze lets out a conditionated sweet yell.	s23a	0157
PV01_1001_A	1	31	Yukikaze: （His cock, his amazing cock! Aah, it's erect, it already got so hard…… It's hot, so hoot! Ah! Aaah!!）	s23a	0158
PV01_1001_A	1	32	Many times, she was made to swallow it,  and it would later go on to violate her other holes.  The memories of her many orgasms come back to her.	s23a	0159
PV01_1001_A	1	33	Yazaki: 「Stroke it.」	s23a	0160
PV01_1001_A	1	34	Yazaki didn't even need to give the order.	s23a	0161
PV01_1001_A	1	35	Before she realized it, Yukikaze's hand was tightly grasping his large dick, shaking up and down.	s23a	0162
PV01_1001_A	1	36	Yukikaze: （Wh-What am I doing……This! Aah…… No good, his cock is so hard, so hot! I can't stop moving my hands!）	s23a	0163
PV01_1001_A	1	37	Yukikaze: 「Haa! Haaa,Haaaa…… Aah, dicks, dick are amazing……Aah, they are too goood!」	s23a	0164
PV01_1001_A	1	38	Her heart pounds like an alarm bell, and her breath becomes rough.	s23a	0165
PV01_1001_A	1	39	Her legs can't stop shaking. Her cunt, below her clothing, is damp and wet.	s23a	0166
PV01_1001_A	1	40	Yazaki: 「Yukikaze, that hand there is free.」	s23a	0167
PV01_1001_A	2	1	While abusing her lips, Yazaki grabs Yukikaze's hand that's not grasping a cock.	s23a	0168
PV01_1001_A	2	2	Yukikaze: 「I-I can stroke it with both hands? You want me to stroke it with both hands?!」	s23a	0169
PV01_1001_A	2	3	With her eyes starting to water from the pleasure, Yukikaze sounds like she herself wants to do it.	s23a	0170
PV01_1001_A	2	4	Yazaki: 「That would also be nice, but I want you to masturbate before those guys staring at you.」	s23a	0171
PV01_1001_A	2	5	Yukikaze: 「Hyan!」	s23a	0172
PV01_1001_A	2	6	Yukikaze lets out a sweet voice when her own hands are pressed against her crotch.	s23a	0173
PV01_1001_A	2	7	Yazaki: 「Masturbate, Yukikaze.」	s23a	0174
PV01_1001_A	2	8	Yukikaze: 「N-No way……Doing such an embarrassing thing……」	s23a	0175
PV01_1001_A	2	9	Yukikaze: （I don't want to……I really don't want to masturbate in front of everyone, but……）	s23a	0176
PV01_1001_A	2	10	Her hand doesn't leave her crotch.	s23a	0177
PV01_1001_A	2	11	Yukikaze: （I want to……I want to fondle my pussy…… Aaah, I can't anymore……My finger is moving……）	s23a	0178
PV01_1001_A	2	12	Just like her hand started stroking his cock by itself, her finger starts caressing her own cunt through her clothes.	s23a	0179
PV01_1001_A	2	13	Yukikaze: 「Hiu……Nh! Kuu……Haa, ah……Aah…… Nutsu, kuu!……」	s23a	0180
PV01_1001_A	2	14	Guest: 「Oh dear, she started masturbating while giving him a handjob.」	s23a	0181
PV01_1001_A	2	15	Guest: 「If she wasn't dressed like that, no one would believe she's a former Taimanin.」	s23a	0182
PV01_1001_A	2	16	Sneer arises from the men around Yukikaze.	s23a	0183
PV01_1001_A	2	17	Yukikaze: 「Uu!……Kuu, uu……Th-They are watching me…… Stroking his cock, fondling my pussy…… Those guys are……」	s23a	0184
PV01_1001_A	2	18	Yazaki: 「You're becoming aroused from being watched, Yukikaze.」	s23a	0185
PV01_1001_A	2	19	Yukikaze: 「W-Wrong, I……Nnh! I'm not……I'm not becoming aroused!……」	s23a	0186
PV01_1001_A	2	20	Yazaki: 「You're lying.」	s23a	0187
PV01_1001_A	2	21	Yukikaze: 「Hiaannn!!」	s23a	0188
PV01_1001_A	2	22	Yazaki brushes across her pussy with his hand.	s23a	0189
PV01_1001_A	2	23	From just that, Yukikaze's body bends backward and she lets out a high-pitched, coquettish squeal.	s23a	0190
PV01_1001_A	2	24	Yukikaze: 「Haa, haa! nu……I-I……I…… S-Some……Aah! Something like that……Aah!」	s23a	0191
PV01_1001_A	2	25	While her reason is still screaming with everyone ridiculing her, as she's being humiliated, she feels more and more excited.	s23a	0192
PV01_1001_A	2	26	Yukikaze: （Getting excited from that……is bad, but…… Even though I know it's bad……Noo! My pussy is getting so wet!……）	s23a	0193
PV01_1001_A	2	27	Yukikaze: 「Haan! Nh, nu, ahaa, nh! Ah, ah, nuun, nnu!」	s23a	0194
PV01_1001_A	2	28	Her moans, which she was attempting to conceal, gradually become louder.	s23a	0195
PV01_1001_A	2	29	Yukikaze: （Noo……It feels good……Being watched……Being humiliated…… I'm really feeling it……I'm a pervert……A huge pervert.）	s23a	0196
PV01_1001_A	2	30	Because of the masochistic pleasure she feels, her masturbation starts becoming more passionate.	s23a	0197
PV01_1001_A	2	31	Her finger, initially moving steadily and quietly, changed in the blink of an eye into a fierce, obscene movement.	s23a	0198
PV01_1001_A	2	32	Yukikaze: 「Nu……Kuu, u……Faan, u…… Uu, ah, ah……Aahn!」	s23a	0199
PV01_1001_A	2	33	Love juices overflow from her vagina and soak her Taimanin clothes, darkening the crotch area.	s23a	0200
PV01_1001_A	2	34	Moving her fingers through her clothes as if she wanted to push them inside, Yukikaze is stimulating herself without holding back.	s23a	0201
PV01_1001_A	2	35	Yukikaze: 「Nkuun, nnn, nnnーーーーー!!」	s23a	0202
PV01_1001_A	2	36	Her love juices are now seeping from her clothes, soaking her fingers.	s23a	0203
PV01_1001_A	2	37	Yazaki: 「Yukikaze, you really got into it.」	s23a	0204
PV01_1001_A	2	38	Yazaki remarks while pressing against her gooey lips.	s23a	0205
PV01_1001_A	2	39	Yukikaze: 「No……No way! I……Nu! I'm not getting……into iih……」	s23a	0206
PV01_1001_A	2	40	Whether she like it or not, Yazaki's lukewarm tongue makes Yukikaze's senses melt.	s23a	0207
PV01_1001_A	3	1	Yukikaze: （Th-This kiss……Feeling so good……is bad, but……）	s23a	0208
PV01_1001_A	3	2	Yukikaze: 「I-I……Jyuru, npu…… I hate thish sho……Jyupujyupu……Jyurero.」	s23a	0209
PV01_1001_A	3	3	Though she thinks that, Yukikaze's tongue coils around Yazaki's.	s23a	0210
PV01_1001_A	3	4	Yukikaze: 「Jyuru, npa……Kishing you in front of eferyone…… Shtrocking your dick…… Rubbing my pusshy……」	s23a	0211
PV01_1001_A	3	5	Yukikaze: 「The trufh ish……Jupajajupa, I hate all of dish! Jupajupajupa.」	s23a	0212
PV01_1001_A	3	6	Yukikaze and Yazaki's tongue play together an extremely lewd and sticky tune.	s23a	0213
PV01_1001_A	3	7	Their mixed saliva loosely hangs and falls from her lips.	s23a	0214
PV01_1001_A	3	8	Yazaki: 「You say one thing but do the opposite.」	s23a	0215
PV01_1001_A	3	9	Yukikaze: 「I don't haf a choice……Njyupa, I, I'm a sex shlave so……Jupajupa! I haf to……do it.」	s23a	0216
PV01_1001_A	3	10	Deceiving herself into believing that she's doing all this for her mission, Yukikaze loosens her reason, and gives herself completely to the pleasure.	s23a	0217
PV01_1001_A	3	11	Yukikaze: 「You too……Njyupa, your dick alheady got this wet…… Aah, your precum juishe is drippiing!」	s23a	0218
PV01_1001_A	3	12	Yazaki: 「Hu!……Ku!」	s23a	0219
PV01_1001_A	3	13	Yazaki groans, his dick pulsing inside of Yukikaze's hand.	s23a	0220
PV01_1001_A	3	14	From his swollen glans, his translucent precum is overflowing.	s23a	0221
PV01_1001_A	3	15	Yukikaze: 「Haan, haan! Nuu, faa, ah, aaahn!」	s23a	0222
PV01_1001_A	3	16	Pressing her thumb against the glans, Yukikaze smears his precum.	s23a	0223
PV01_1001_A	3	17	Yukikaze: 「Hyan, amashing!……It looks like you're cumming…… your precum juice keeps coming out! It keeps coming out!」	s23a	0224
PV01_1001_A	3	18	Watching her extremely lewd finger movements, the other guests start jeering at Yukikaze.	s23a	0225
PV01_1001_A	3	19	Guest: 「That sex slave gives a really skillful handjob.」	s23a	0226
PV01_1001_A	3	20	Guest: 「It makes sense. If Mister Real trained her, he probably made her fondle cocks without letting her sleep.」	s23a	0227
PV01_1001_A	3	21	Guest: 「No, looking at her freak expression, I'm sure she was a cock-crazy slut from the beginning.」	s23a	0228
PV01_1001_A	3	22	Yukikaze: （Wh-What……Are you saying…… Don't say just whatever you want……）	s23a	0229
PV01_1001_A	3	23	The voices of the guests despising her make her heart tingle.	s23a	0230
PV01_1001_A	3	24	Yukikaze: （If you say those horrible things like that, I will feel it even more! Stop it!!）	s23a	0231
PV01_1001_A	3	25	The abuse from being called a freak or a sow- she can't help but feel masochistic pleasure from it.	s23a	0232
PV01_1001_A	3	26	Yukikaze: 「Hiuaa! Ah! Nh! I-It just han't be helped!」	s23a	0233
PV01_1001_A	3	27	Yazaki: 「Kuku! What can't?」	s23a	0234
PV01_1001_A	3	28	While Yukikaze's hand rubs his dick, Yazaki tries to confirm her feelings.	s23a	0235
PV01_1001_A	3	29	Yukikaze: 「I can't help feeling that good! I can't help it that being despised and abused makes my pussy dripping wet!!」	s23a	0236
PV01_1001_A	3	30	Yazaki: 「It's because you're a sex slave.」	s23a	0237
PV01_1001_A	3	31	Yukikaze: 「That's right! I'm a sex slave! When I see a man's dick I immediately want it! A perverted sex slave sow is exactly what I have become!」	s23a	0238
PV01_1001_A	3	32	Guest: 「Oh dear, she started screaming.」	s23a	0239
PV01_1001_A	3	33	Guest: 「Is she admitting defeat as a former Taimanin turned sex slave?」	s23a	0240
PV01_1001_A	3	34	Yukikaze: 「Shut up! Shud up, be quieet! It's because I'm a sex slave! It's because my body was changed to be a pervert who loves sex!」	s23a	0241
PV01_1001_A	3	35	Yukikaze: 「E-Everyone can watch! You're free to watch Yukikaze the sow if you want, you pigs!!」	s23a	0242
PV01_1001_A	3	36	While ranting and raving with a miserable moaning voice, Yukikaze also thinks of Tatsurou.	s23a	0243
PV01_1001_A	3	37	Yukikaze: （Tatsurou, watch me! I'm doing something that lewd with Yazaki!）	s23a	0244
PV01_1001_A	3	38	Yukikaze: （I'm a pervert who's masturbating in front of everyone, while kissing him and stroking his cock! And it feels really gooood!!）	s23a	0245
PV01_1001_A	3	39	Yukikaze: 「I'm a pervert! I've become a helpless perverted bitch pussy sex slave!!」	s23a	0246
PV01_1001_A	3	40	The masochistic pleasure bursts open inside Yukikaze.	s23a	0247
PV01_1001_A	4	1	With so many people looking, she reaches her limit faster than usual.	s23a	0248
PV01_1001_A	4	2	Yazaki: 「You've become really eager to put on a show for those guys.」	s23a	0249
PV01_1001_A	4	3	Yukikaze: 「Yeah! I am, I really am! I'll show them all my dirty self!」	s23a	0250
PV01_1001_A	4	4	Yukikaze greedily nibbles on Yazaki's tongue.	s23a	0251
PV01_1001_A	4	5	Just like that, she narrows her mouth like she was giving him a blowjob and starts sucking on his tongue.	s23a	0252
PV01_1001_A	4	6	Yukikaze: 「Zujyuruu, bujyuruu, jyurujyurujyuruuuuu!!」	s23a	0253
PV01_1001_A	4	7	Yazaki: 「Hu!……Ku……」	s23a	0254
PV01_1001_A	4	8	Yazaki's countenance changes at the sudden vacuum kiss.	s23a	0255
PV01_1001_A	4	9	Yukikaze: 「Jyuru! Nnnh, let out, your tongue! I'll suck it, just like a cock…… Tongue cock blowjob, feels goood!」	s23a	0256
PV01_1001_A	4	10	However, during the last month, Yazaki also got used to her body.	s23a	0257
PV01_1001_A	4	11	He entrusts his tongue to Yukikaze to suck on.	s23a	0258
PV01_1001_A	4	12	Yazaki: 「Your mouth is just like your cunt.」	s23a	0259
PV01_1001_A	4	13	Yukikaze: 「That'sh riiight, my moufh and my pusshy are the same! My mouth pusshy would rather eat three cocks than one meal!」	s23a	0260
PV01_1001_A	4	14	Yukikaze: 「Zujyuruuuu, zuryuzuryuuu, bujyurujyurujyubuuuu!!」	s23a	0261
PV01_1001_A	4	15	Guest: 「Ooh, that's incredible!」	s23a	0262
PV01_1001_A	4	16	Guest: 「The thought of her mouth eating cocks sends shivers down my spine!」	s23a	0263
PV01_1001_A	4	17	The spectators are captivated by Yukikaze's transformation.	s23a	0264
PV01_1001_A	4	18	Yukikaze: （Ahaa, everyone is watching! With their dicks erect, they're all watching me!!）	s23a	0265
PV01_1001_A	4	19	While vacuum-kissing Yazaki, a bewitching smile appears on Yukikaze's face when she notices the swollen crotches of the spectators.	s23a	0266
PV01_1001_A	4	20	Yukikaze: 「Jyuru! Npu! They are watching! Their eyes are saying  they want to put their cocks in my mouth!」	s23a	0267
PV01_1001_A	4	21	Yazaki: 「Any man would think that.」	s23a	0268
PV01_1001_A	4	22	Yukikaze: 「Then, want to put your cock in? I'll suck everything anyway, so wouldn't you rather it be your cock than your tongue? Jyuru, chupubujyu, how about iih?」	s23a	0269
PV01_1001_A	4	23	Yukikaze asks while sucking on his tongue.	s23a	0270
PV01_1001_A	4	24	Yazaki: 「Right now, I'm fine with a handjob. This is acceptable on its own.」	s23a	0271
PV01_1001_A	4	25	Yukikaze: 「Jyujyu! You're still composed? I guess that's normal, since we've done it so many times. Hauun! I hate thiis! Jyujyuu～～～～～!」	s23a	0272
PV01_1001_A	4	26	Yazaki is still composed even against Yukikaze's sex slave tongue technique.	s23a	0273
PV01_1001_A	4	27	Acting like his sulking girlfriend, Yukikaze keeps sucking on Yazaki's tongue,	s23a	0274
PV01_1001_A	4	28	Yukikaze: 「Then, I'll make you cum just like this! Npujuru, let out all of your thick cock juice inside my hands!!」	s23a	0275
PV01_1001_A	4	29	Frustrated that she can't hold his cock in her mouth, Yukikaze's handjob becomes fiercer.	s23a	0276
PV01_1001_A	4	30	Yukikaze: 「Jyruun! Naah! Aah…… Hahi! Nuu, nuu, my pusshy too, nh! My pussy is wishing for your cock! Aauaah!!」	s23a	0277
PV01_1001_A	4	31	Pulling away the cloth covering her crotch, Yukikaze plunges her finger in her twitching greedy pussy.	s23a	0278
PV01_1001_A	4	32	Yukikaze: 「Nhii! Look! Look! The pussy of the debauched sex slave Yukikaze has become so wet! Look, everyone!!」	s23a	0279
PV01_1001_A	4	33	While appealing to the audience, her finger is inserted up to the base and twists again and again.	s23a	0280
PV01_1001_A	4	34	Her aroused sticky walls are scraped out, causing her love juices to drip to the outside.	s23a	0281
PV01_1001_A	4	35	Yukikaze: 「Hiuun! Ah! Aah! My pussy is making such a wet sound! It wants cocks! It wants cock so much, my naughty cunt juices are dripping!!」	s23a	0282
PV01_1001_A	4	36	Yazaki: 「Do you want my cock, you dirty pig?!」	s23a	0283
PV01_1001_A	4	37	Yazaki presses his cock, wet with precum, against Yukikaze's hand-pussy.	s23a	0284
PV01_1001_A	4	38	Yukikaze: 「Yeah! I want it! I want it! My bitch cunt! It wants this cock! Put it deep inside me! Thrust it! I want you to make a mess out of my cunt!!」	s23a	0285
PV01_1001_A	4	39	While begging for dick with no shame or honor, Yukikaze continues her handjob with his precum as lubricant.	s23a	0286
PV01_1001_A	4	40	Her hand movement matches the movement of her finger buried deep inside her pussy.	s23a	0287
PV01_1001_A	5	1	While doing that, rather than giving a handjob while masturbating, she deludes herself thinking his dick is inside her pussy.	s23a	0288
PV01_1001_A	5	2	Yukikaze: 「Haan! Haan! I want it! I want a real cock! I want a cock to enter my pussy! Aah, cocks, cocks, cooocks!!」	s23a	0289
PV01_1001_A	5	3	Yazaki: 「No good, I'll cum just like this. You can cum while being frustrated with just a handjob and fingering yourself!」	s23a	0290
PV01_1001_A	5	4	Yukikaze: 「M-Mean! So meaaan!! I want your cock! I want it to hammer in my pussy!!」	s23a	0291
PV01_1001_A	5	5	However, Yazaki's ban on penetration might have the opposite effect of bringing Yukikaze closer to orgasm, as both hands suddenly move faster.	s23a	0292
PV01_1001_A	5	6	Yukikaze: 「Aah! But! I'll cum! It's just a handjob while I'm fingering myself but I'm cumming! Ah! Cumming! It's unsatisfying, but I'll cum! Auaah!」	s23a	0293
PV01_1001_A	5	7	While clinging on Yazaki, one hand strokes his dick, and the other hand stirs her pussy.	s23a	0294
PV01_1001_A	5	8	Yukikaze: 「H-Hey, Let's cum together! Cum together with me! Let out your cock juice! I'm also about to cum! Please, please! Juuuuuu!!」	s23a	0295
PV01_1001_A	5	9	Although she can control her urge to orgasm, there's not a shred of reason left.	s23a	0296
PV01_1001_A	5	10	Acting as if Yazaki is her lover, Yukikaze supplicates and deeply kisses him.	s23a	0297
PV01_1001_A	5	11	Yukikaze: 「Come! Come! Spread semen with your cock! Let's cum together! My lewd cunt will cum too! Aah, I'm cumming! Cumming, cumming! I can't hold back anymore!」	s23a	0298
PV01_1001_A	5	12	Yazaki: 「Uh!……Sh-Shit……!!」	s23a	0299
PV01_1001_A	5	13	Yazaki probably wanted to tease Yukikaze even further.	s23a	0300
PV01_1001_A	5	14	However, the fierce handjob and deep kiss of the sex slave makes his lust suddenly reach its limit.	s23a	0301
PV01_1001_A	5	15	Byuku! Byuku! Byukubyuku!	s23a	0302
PV01_1001_A	5	16	Yukikaze: 「Ahiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii!!」	s23a	0303
PV01_1001_A	5	17	The second she feels hot semen in her hand, Yukikaze reaches the climax she wished for.	s23a	0304
PV01_1001_A	5	18	Her body, held by Yazaki, becomes stiff and goes into convulsions.	s23a	0305
PV01_1001_A	5	19	Yukikaze: 「Aahn! It's coming out! Your dick juice is coming out! Aah, amazing amazing amaziiiiing!!」	s23a	0306
PV01_1001_A	5	20	While screaming hysterically, Yukikaze keeps stroking his cock as it ejaculates inside her hand.	s23a	0307
PV01_1001_A	5	21	From the gap between her pussy and her finger deep inside her, squirts come out like urine.	s23a	0308
PV01_1001_A	5	22	Yukikaze: 「More! Let out more! Your smelly, syrupy, thick dick juice, cum more of it! Dirty me with it! Pleaaase, jyu, jyuryuuuuu!」	s23a	0309
PV01_1001_A	5	23	While shaking from her orgasm, throwing her tongue at Yazaki, she supplicates him to ejaculate and disgrace her more.	s23a	0310
PV01_1001_A	5	24	A month after becoming a sex slave, her sloppy cumming expression is the proof of her continuous violation.	s23a	0311
PV01_1001_A	5	25	Yukikaze: 「Hyaaan! Aah! Cock! So good! Cock semen! Why does it feel so good?! Haaan!」	s23a	0312
PV01_1001_A	5	26	Yazaki: 「You look happy to receive my semen.」	s23a	0313
PV01_1001_A	5	27	Yazaki says with a satisfied expression, as he pulls out his cock from Yukikaze's hand pussy.	s23a	0314
PV01_1001_A	5	28	Yukikaze: 「I hate it but it's so good! Your hot semen makes me useless! Because I'm a sex slave, it makes me useless!」	s23a	0315
PV01_1001_A	5	29	Without her noticing, Yukikaze smears the semen on her hand against her cunt.	s23a	0316
PV01_1001_A	5	30	The cloudy juice clinging to the palm of her hand is rubbed again and again on her shivering, climaxing snatch.	s23a	0317
PV01_1001_A	5	31	Yukikaze: 「Aahn! Aahn! My pussy is so painful! I want it deeper! I want you to put out semen deep inside my pussy!」	s23a	0318
PV01_1001_A	5	32	Yazaki: 「Yukikaze, do creampies really feel that good?」	s23a	0319
PV01_1001_A	5	33	Yukikaze shakes her head up and down to answer, with no hesitation, to Yazaki's malicious question.	s23a	0320
PV01_1001_A	5	34	Yukikaze: 「Yeah, yeah! Creampies are good, I don't want anything else more than a creampie! Please, creampie me! Release your semen inside my pussy!!」	s23a	0321
PV01_1001_A	5	35	Yukikaze: 「I beg you, if I don't climax from a creampie, my pussy is so miserable it hurts! My head feels like it'll go crazy! Let me cum! Let me cum from a creampie!!」	s23a	0322
PV01_1001_A	5	36	Guest: 「Oh dear, she started asking for a creampie like a bitch in heat.」	s23a	0323
PV01_1001_A	5	37	Guest: 「That's because she's a real sex slave. As expected from Real-dono, he did a wonderful job breaking her.」	s23a	0324
PV01_1001_A	5	38	Yukikaze: 「That's riight! This is a sex slaave! I became one! Someone who loves creampies inside her filthy cunt, a real sex slave!!」	s23a	0325
PV01_1001_A	5	39	In the middle of the hall, Yukikaze announces her status as a sex slave.	s23a	0326
PV01_1001_A	5	40	She does it all for the sake of her own pleasure.	s23a	0327
PV01_1001_A	6	1	Yazaki: 「Very well then. Let's show them your creampie climax. You debauched sow.」	s23a	0328
PV01_1001_A	6	2	While saying that, he holds Yukikaze's still-shivering body from behind.	s23a	0329
PV01_1001_A	6	3	Yukikaze: 「Hyaan♪」	s23a	0330
PV01_1001_A	6	4	Delighted from finally being allowed to have a dick inside her pussy, Yukikaze lets out a coquettish yell.	s23a	0331
PV01_1001_A	6	5	Then, straddling on Yazaki as he sits down on the floor, she spreads open her legs towards the audience.	s23a	0332
PV01_1001_A	6	6	Yazaki: 「Pull away the cloth covering your crotch. Show them your pussy.」	s23a	0333
PV01_1001_A	6	7	Yukikaze: 「N-No way……!」	s23a	0334
PV01_1001_A	6	8	Yukikaze acts like she doesn't want to.	s23a	0335
PV01_1001_A	6	9	However, her mind is focused on her pussy that just came, shivering from the joy of being shown to so many people.	s23a	0336
PV01_1001_A	6	10	Yazaki: 「Show them. Show them your cunt, as a full-fledged sex slave. Fufu, Or would you rather have me do it?」	s23a	0337
PV01_1001_A	6	11	Rather than letting someone else do it, she should do it herself. His words completely pierce through her defenses.	s23a	0338
PV01_1001_A	6	12	Yukikaze: 「Haahaa, I'll do it, I'll do it myself, I'll show them my pussy!」	s23a	0339
PV01_1001_A	6	13	Gulping down the saliva accumulating in her mouth, Yukikaze pulls away her clothes in front of the attentive guests.	s23a	0340
PV01_1001_A	6	14	Yukikaze: 「Aaaahnnnnn!!」	s23a	0341
PV01_1001_A	6	15	Yukikaze exposes her pussy that just came from her own fingering.	s23a	0342
PV01_1001_A	6	16	Her bright red, aroused labia is squirming. Love juices endlessly stream from her meat hole.	s23a	0343
PV01_1001_A	6	17	Guest: 「Oh, is that the pussy of a former-Taimanin-turned-sex-slave?」	s23a	0344
PV01_1001_A	6	18	Guest: 「You wouldn't think she's a sex slave who's continuously violated by men. It has a pretty pink color, like a virgin. Nonetheless, it's overflowing with indecent love juices. She's of really high quality.」	s23a	0345
PV01_1001_A	6	19	Yukikaze: （Th-They are watching……My dirty pussy, everyone is watching it!……It's so embarrassing…… But, I'm really feeling it……My head feels like it'll go crazy.）	s23a	0346
PV01_1001_A	6	20	A crowd of men are watching her most private place, commenting on its shape and color.	s23a	0347
PV01_1001_A	6	21	But even though it's so embarrassing she feels she'll go mad, Yukikaze becomes more and more aroused.	s23a	0348
PV01_1001_A	6	22	Yukikaze: 「Haa, haa, haa, haaa, haaa!」	s23a	0349
PV01_1001_A	6	23	Yukikaze: （I-I really became a weirdo. I want to show to everyone the pussy they called 'pretty' swallowing a cock whole!)	s23a	0350
PV01_1001_A	6	24	Yukikaze: （Satisfying cocks until I go crazy, my shameful creampie climax, I want to show them all of it!!）	s23a	0351
PV01_1001_A	6	25	Yazaki whispers a command in her ear.	s23a	0352
PV01_1001_A	6	26	Yazaki: 「Yukikaze, greet them like a sex slave would. Ask them to watch you cum from my thick cock. Say it.」	s23a	0353
PV01_1001_A	6	27	Driven by her urge to shamefuly expose herself, there was no way Yukikaze could oppose that order.	s23a	0354
PV01_1001_A	6	28	Yukikaze: 「E-Everyone! Right now, the slutty sex slave Yukikaze will cum from Yazaki-sama's thick cock! I'll climax from his creampie, so please watch my ahegao!!」	s23a	0355
PV01_1001_A	6	29	Because of how aroused she is, Yukikaze's voice cracks. Sneers and cheers erupt from the guests.	s23a	0356
PV01_1001_A	6	30	Yukikaze: （Aaaah! This feels gooooooood!!）	s23a	0357
PV01_1001_A	6	31	Yukikaze lightly cums just from saying that.	s23a	0358
PV01_1001_A	6	32	Yazaki shoves his large cock inside her cunt, gushing with love juices.	s23a	0359
PV01_1001_A	6	33	Yukikaze: 「Ahii! Hahi! Nhiiiiiiiiiiiinnn!!」	s23a	0360
PV01_1001_A	6	34	As if she wanted all of the audience to hear it, Yukikaze screams without reservation.	s23a	0361
PV01_1001_A	6	35	Her cunt is squirming, swallowing his dick deeper and deeper.	s23a	0362
PV01_1001_A	6	36	Yukikaze: 「Hyaa! Ah! Hahi! Your dick! Ooh! Inside my pussy! It's coming in! It's coming in!!」	s23a	0363
PV01_1001_A	6	37	Yazaki: 「Is this what you wanted?」	s23a	0364
PV01_1001_A	6	38	Yukikaze: 「Yeah, that's right! I wanted this! This cock! My cunt wanted this cock!!」	s23a	0365
PV01_1001_A	6	39	Yukikaze: 「Aahn! Anan♪ It feels good! Your cock feels goood! So goood! Ahiiinn!!」	s23a	0366
PV01_1001_A	6	40	Yukikaze's reason is completely blown away at the insertion of the long-awaited dick.	s23a	0367
PV01_1001_A	7	1	Yukikaze: 「Haan! Ah! Ah! Nuuuu, nan! Ahnan!」	s23a	0368
PV01_1001_A	7	2	Her expression melts completely. With lust glittering in her eyes, she wriggles left and right, her body held by Yazaki.	s23a	0369
PV01_1001_A	7	3	In this obscene dance, she moves her hips herself, putting strength in her pussy meat to constrict his dick.	s23a	0370
PV01_1001_A	7	4	Yukikaze: 「Ahn! Aah! Cock! This hot and hard amazing coock! Aaah! It's inside my pussy! It's there!」	s23a	0371
PV01_1001_A	7	5	Yazaki: 「After a month, it seems you have become completely accustomed to the taste of my dick.」	s23a	0372
PV01_1001_A	7	6	While playing with Yukikaze's breasts with his two hands, Yazaki speaks loudly enough for everyone to hear.	s23a	0373
PV01_1001_A	7	7	Yukikaze's shame completely burns away.	s23a	0374
PV01_1001_A	7	8	Yukikaze: 「Th-That's……Hyaan!!」	s23a	0375
PV01_1001_A	7	9	His crooked dick rubs against her clitoris, gouging out the top of her walls.	s23a	0376
PV01_1001_A	7	10	Yazaki: 「I have also become accustomed to the taste of your cunt. This is the place where you are the most sensitive.」	s23a	0377
PV01_1001_A	7	11	Yukikaze: 「Ohiiin! Hi! Hahii! Uu! Ah! Ya! Dooon't! Not there! Aaahn! Don't hit me theeere!!」	s23a	0378
PV01_1001_A	7	12	His large dick relentlessly stimulates her weakest spot.	s23a	0379
PV01_1001_A	7	13	It's just as he said.	s23a	0380
PV01_1001_A	7	14	Yukikaze's cunt remembers Yazaki's cock, and Yazaki's cock remembers Yukikaze's cunt.	s23a	0381
PV01_1001_A	7	15	Yukikaze: 「Hian! If-If you keep hitting me there! I-I'll lose it! I'll really lose it!!」	s23a	0382
PV01_1001_A	7	16	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Hahi! Nhii! Aahnananan! Incredible! My pussy feels so good it feels like it's melting!!」	s23a	0383
PV01_1001_A	7	17	The climax comes to her all at once in a single, massive burst.	s23a	0384
PV01_1001_A	7	18	Scattering drool and spraying love juices; a slave to Yazaki's cock, Yukikaze is overwhelmed by pleasure.	s23a	0385
PV01_1001_A	7	19	Yukikaze: 「Hia! Ah! Hahi! Hi! Ah! Ah! Aaahnnnn!!」	s23a	0386
PV01_1001_A	7	20	Yazaki: 「Doesn't my cock feel better everytime we fuck? Your reactions are proof of that!!」	s23a	0387
PV01_1001_A	7	21	Yukikaze: 「Th-That's true! I-It's embarrassing but, Your cock! Feels better and better! I'm feeling it way more than yesterday!!」	s23a	0388
PV01_1001_A	7	22	Yukikaze: 「I-I hate it but, my pussy has grown used to this cock! I feel it way more than with any other man! I've become used to the feeling of your cock inside my pussy!!」	s23a	0389
PV01_1001_A	7	23	Guest: 「Yazaki-san is impressive. For a sex slave of Yomihara to speak of him like that, that man got more than he deserved.」	s23a	0390
PV01_1001_A	7	24	Guest: 「Indeed, it looks like that sow cannot live without Yazaki's dick anymore.」	s23a	0391
PV01_1001_A	7	25	With glasses of wine in their hands, the guests chat about Yukikaze's foolishness.	s23a	0392
PV01_1001_A	7	26	Yukikaze: （Th-There's no way that would be true! If this man was gone, if his cock was gone, I-I would be perfectly fine!）	s23a	0393
PV01_1001_A	7	27	Yukikaze: （Aah! But, but! His cock still feel really good! My pussy is really delighted! Ah, I can't anymore!!）	s23a	0394
PV01_1001_A	7	28	Whenever her reason comes back, she easily yields to the pleasure from the cock that had disgraced her for a month.	s23a	0395
PV01_1001_A	7	29	Yukikaze: 「Hiaa! Ah! Aah! Nu! I-I'll cum! My pussy will cum again!!」	s23a	0396
PV01_1001_A	7	30	Yazaki: 「Uh……Ku, let's go, Yukikaze.」	s23a	0397
PV01_1001_A	7	31	Feeling his second ejaculation drawing near, Yazaki roughly gropes Yukikaze's breasts while moving his hips even more violently.	s23a	0398
PV01_1001_A	7	32	Yukikaze: 「Ehyaaaaaaaaaa!!」	s23a	0399
PV01_1001_A	7	33	Yazaki: 「Cum from my creampie, alright?!」	s23a	0400
PV01_1001_A	7	34	Yukikaze replies to Yazaki's words, just moments before he cums.	s23a	0401
PV01_1001_A	7	35	Yukikaze: 「Yes, yes! I'll do it! I'll cum from your creampie!! Aah! I'll cum, an amazing orgasm is coming! Ah! Aaaaaah!!」	s23a	0402
PV01_1001_A	7	36	Completely accustomed to his dick, Yukikaze's womb descends.	s23a	0403
PV01_1001_A	7	37	Yukikaze: 「Ahiaah! M-My womb came down! Hyaa! Your cock! Ah! Your cock is is hitting my womb! Aahn! Amazing, amazing!!」	s23a	0404
PV01_1001_A	7	38	Ready to catch every drop of his creampie, her cervix swallows and tightens against his glans.	s23a	0405
PV01_1001_A	7	39	Yukikaze: 「Hi! Hya! Cum! Cum with your cock! I'll catch all of your semen! I'll climax from your creampie!」	s23a	0406
PV01_1001_A	7	40	Yukikaze: 「Ha! Ha! I can't anymore! No more! Cumming! I'm cumming! My cunt is cumming, my cunt is cummiiing!!」	s23a	0407
PV01_1001_A	8	1	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Cumming! Cummingcummingcumming! Cummiiiiiing～～～～～～～～～～!」	s23a	0408
PV01_1001_A	8	2	Yazaki: 「Ku!!」	s23a	0409
PV01_1001_A	8	3	Yukikaze: 「Cummiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiing!!!」	s23a	0410
PV01_1001_A	8	4	――Byuru! Byurubyuru! Dobyurubyuru!!	s23a	0411
PV01_1001_A	8	5	Yukikaze: 「Aaaaaahn! Anan! Hiaaaaaaannnnn!!」	s23a	0412
PV01_1001_A	8	6	Yukikaze's climaxing scream surges.	s23a	0413
PV01_1001_A	8	7	The semen she longed for violently strikes against her womb.	s23a	0414
PV01_1001_A	8	8	Yukikaze: 「Hiaaan! Semen feels good! It really feels good! It's hot and striking against my womb! It's good! It feels good!!」	s23a	0415
PV01_1001_A	8	9	Reaching climax from the creampie, her face writhes and twists while she moans.	s23a	0416
PV01_1001_A	8	10	Yazaki: 「That's exactly right, you filthy sow!!」	s23a	0417
PV01_1001_A	8	11	Yazaki roars, stretching Yukikaze's nipples to the limit.	s23a	0418
PV01_1001_A	8	12	Yukikaze: 「Nhiiiii! Hii! Hiiiiiiiii!!」	s23a	0419
PV01_1001_A	8	13	The pain from feeling her nipples almost torn off quickly shifts into pleasure, and her climaxing voice springs up again.	s23a	0420
PV01_1001_A	8	14	Yazaki: 「Does a creampie really feel that good? How is it? Tell me while you cum, dirty sow!!」	s23a	0421
PV01_1001_A	8	15	Yukikaze's body is still shaking up and down, his still-ejaculating dick rubbing her cervix.	s23a	0422
PV01_1001_A	8	16	Yukikaze: 「Hahi! Good! It heally feels good! My sow cunt reaally feelsh gooood!!」	s23a	0423
PV01_1001_A	8	17	Yukikaze: 「Because! While your cock is still vomiting semen, it's rubbing against my sow cunt!!」	s23a	0424
PV01_1001_A	8	18	Scorning herself with a designation like 'sow cunt', Yukikaze screams from her orgasm again and again.	s23a	0425
PV01_1001_A	8	19	Yukikaze: 「Hyaa! Aah! It's good! With your hot and syrupy semen, my slimy sow cunt ish melhing……」	s23a	0426
PV01_1001_A	8	20	Yazaki: 「It's still too early! I'll creampie you five times today!!」	s23a	0427
PV01_1001_A	8	21	Once his first creampie ends, Yazaki's still erect and raging meat pole stabs again at Yukikaze's vagina.	s23a	0428
PV01_1001_A	8	22	Yukikaze: 「Yes, do it……Cum inside me a lot…… Until my womb is bursting with your semen…… Cum inside……me……」	s23a	0429
PV01_1001_A	8	23	Yukikaze: 「I……I'll cum! If you cum inside me…… I'll definitely climax……I want it!  Your cock, semen, I want more……」	s23a	0430
PV01_1001_A	8	24	As for Yukikaze, she can't tell how many times she came from the first creampie.	s23a	0431
PV01_1001_A	8	25	Like that, with her expression melted from the orgasm, she asks for even more creampies.	s23a	0432
PV01_1001_A	8	26	Yukikaze: （I'm done for……Cumming a lot is all I can think about now……）	s23a	0433
PV01_1001_A	8	27	Yazaki: 「Yuikaze, if you want me to cum more inside you, tighten properly around my dick!」	s23a	0434
PV01_1001_A	8	28	Yazaki forces his dick deeper inside her vagina.	s23a	0435
PV01_1001_A	8	29	Yukikaze: 「Hahiiiiinn!」	s23a	0436
PV01_1001_A	8	30	She still hasn't recovered from the previous orgasm before the pleasure causes her entire body to tense up.	s23a	0437
PV01_1001_A	8	31	Yukikaze: （Aah! His cock is there again! His wonderful, erect cock, it's piercing me deep inside my pussy!!）	s23a	0438
PV01_1001_A	8	32	Yukikaze's body bends backwards, and her vaginal walls tighten again.	s23a	0439
PV01_1001_A	8	33	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Haaa! Hahi! Hi! Kahiii!」	s23a	0440
PV01_1001_A	8	34	Her breath roughs up from the feeling of his dick; her mouth opens and closes repeatedly, like a fish.	s23a	0441
PV01_1001_A	8	35	Yazaki: 「Come on! This isn't the time to rest!!」	s23a	0442
PV01_1001_A	8	36	While carrying her with his two hands, He shakes her up and down while thrusting his cock.	s23a	0443
PV01_1001_A	8	37	Yukikaze: 「Hyaan! An! Ah! An! Nuuu, hiin! Ahiin!!」	s23a	0444
PV01_1001_A	8	38	Her hole swallowing Yazaki's fat dick causes an unbearable noise to resound.	s23a	0445
PV01_1001_A	8	39	Because of his piston motion, the semen he had just released is scraped out.	s23a	0446
PV01_1001_A	8	40	Yukikaze: 「Nhi! It's making such a dirty sound! My pussy and your cock are all like "guchuguchu"!!」	s23a	0447
PV01_1001_A	9	1	Yazaki: 「Yukikaze, you're getting better and better.」	s23a	0448
PV01_1001_A	9	2	After cumming once from her handjob and another time inside of her, he was able to regain his composure.	s23a	0449
PV01_1001_A	9	3	Yukikaze: 「R-Really?……Nuu, nnh, My pussy- Is my pussy feeling better than before? Does your cock feel good?」	s23a	0450
PV01_1001_A	9	4	Yazaki: 「The more I fuck you, the more my cock grows used to your cunt.」	s23a	0451
PV01_1001_A	9	5	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Aaahnnnn!!」	s23a	0452
PV01_1001_A	9	6	The instant Yukikaze hears that, her heart and womb tighten from delight.	s23a	0453
PV01_1001_A	9	7	Yukikaze is the first to be surprised at her own reaction.	s23a	0454
PV01_1001_A	9	8	Yukikaze: （Aah! Nooo! This guy, even though I hate him- I've come to love his cock! I'm feeling his cock, it really feels better and better!）	s23a	0455
PV01_1001_A	9	9	And then, as if to make fun of her dread at what she had become, Yazaki strikes her mental precious spot.	s23a	0456
PV01_1001_A	9	10	Yazaki: 「Yukikaze, don't you think what you're doing is horrible for your lover, that Tatsurou guy?」	s23a	0457
PV01_1001_A	9	11	Yukikaze: 「N-Noooooo! Don't say it! Don't talk about Tatsurou!!」	s23a	0458
PV01_1001_A	9	12	Yazaki: 「If he were to learn that his sweetheart's cunt was getting used to the cock of another man, I wonder what his face would look like?」	s23a	0459
PV01_1001_A	9	13	Yukikaze: 「Nonononooo! Didn't I tell you to not talk about him?! When we're fucking, don't remind me of Tatsurou!!」	s23a	0460
PV01_1001_A	9	14	Yukikaze screams.	s23a	0461
PV01_1001_A	9	15	However, at the mention of Tatsurou's name, the immoral feelings of lust grow bigger in her.	s23a	0462
PV01_1001_A	9	16	Yazaki: 「Why? Because you're betraying your lover? That's not it. Aren't you feeling it more because you're betraying your sweetheart? You debauched sow!」	s23a	0463
PV01_1001_A	9	17	Yukikaze: 「Wrong, wrong, wrooong!! I'm not that kind of woman! I might be a sex slave, but I don't feel good about betraying Tatsurou!!」	s23a	0464
PV01_1001_A	9	18	Yukikaze hysterically denies Yazaki's words.	s23a	0465
PV01_1001_A	9	19	However, her meat sleeve swallowing a dick that's not Tatsurou's starts obscenely wriggling even more intensely.	s23a	0466
PV01_1001_A	9	20	Yazaki: 「Kuhahaha! Your lower mouth is much more honest! It's clamping around my dick even more fiercely!!」	s23a	0467
PV01_1001_A	9	21	Yukikaze: 「N-Noooo! Stoop! I-If you stab that my pussy that much! If it feels so good, I-I will!!」	s23a	0468
PV01_1001_A	9	22	Yukikaze: （I will forget about Tatsurou! Because this cock that isn't Tatsurou's feels so good! Tatsurou will completely disappear from my mind!!）	s23a	0469
PV01_1001_A	9	23	Yukikaze desperately clings to the memories of Tatsurou in her head.	s23a	0470
PV01_1001_A	9	24	However, the pleasure of Yazaki's cock pressing repeatedly against her womb destroys everything.	s23a	0471
PV01_1001_A	9	25	Yukikaze: （T-Tatsurou……Sorry, cocks feel too good…… When my pussy is bullied, I don't care about anything else.）	s23a	0472
PV01_1001_A	9	26	Yukikaze: （But I can't help it, Tatsurou never entered my pussy…… Even if I want to remember, I never experienced Tatsurou's cock…… That's why! That's whyy!!）	s23a	0473
PV01_1001_A	9	27	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Aah! No good! No good! Aah! No! No! Noooooooooo!!」	s23a	0474
PV01_1001_A	9	28	The second her heart yields――	s23a	0475
PV01_1001_A	9	29	Yazaki throws out his semen inside her for the second time.	s23a	0476
PV01_1001_A	9	30	Yukikaze: 「Nhooooooooooooooooooo!!」	s23a	0477
PV01_1001_A	9	31	Yukikaze: （Semen feels good! It feels gooooood!!）	s23a	0478
PV01_1001_A	9	32	The moment her womb feels the cloudy male juice, Tatsurou completely vanishes from Yukikaze's mind.	s23a	0479
PV01_1001_A	9	33	Prisoner of her own lust, she tightens her cunt meat to wriggle in all of Yazaki's semen.	s23a	0480
PV01_1001_A	9	34	Yukikaze: 「Ahi! Hahi! It's coming out! Semen is coming out agaiin!!」	s23a	0481
PV01_1001_A	9	35	Yazaki: 「How quickly you've fallen. Come on, I'll give you plenty of my semen!!」	s23a	0482
PV01_1001_A	9	36	Speaking with a satisfied tone, Yazaki throws his male juice at Yukikaze to his heart's content.	s23a	0483
PV01_1001_A	9	37	Yukikaze: 「Ah! Ah! Aahn! Please do! Please give me your semen! My womb! My womb is delighted from bathing in your semen!」	s23a	0484
PV01_1001_A	9	38	Catching all the semen thrown at her, Yukikaze's womb is burning hot.	s23a	0485
PV01_1001_A	9	39	Yukikaze: 「Aah! Cumming! I came! I'm cumming from being creampied again! Cumming! Climaxing from a creampie! Ah! Aaaaaah!!」	s23a	0486
PV01_1001_A	9	40	Yukikaze's body arches back like a bow, her flesh still squeezing out his cock.	s23a	0487
PV01_1001_A	10	1	Yazaki: 「Gu!!」	s23a	0488
PV01_1001_A	10	2	――Bobyubyubyu!!	s23a	0489
PV01_1001_A	10	3	Yukikaze: 「Nhooooooooooooooo!!」	s23a	0490
PV01_1001_A	10	4	Another torrent of jizz strikes Yukikaze.	s23a	0491
PV01_1001_A	10	5	Yukikaze: 「Hooo! Hooo! Ohoooo! My cunt is gumming! My cunt ish cumming!! Cummingcummingcumiiiiiiiiiiing!!」	s23a	0492
PV01_1001_A	10	6	Her droopy eyes are completely rolled back.	s23a	0493
PV01_1001_A	10	7	Yukikaze: 「Ahaaaaah! Ahnhaahaaaaaaaaaa!!」	s23a	0494
PV01_1001_A	10	8	Her stretched-out tongue twitches as it emerges from her screaming mouth.	s23a	0495
PV01_1001_A	10	9	From the hole that's sucking up Yazaki's sperm, a tide of squirt and love juices gushes in counter-current.	s23a	0496
PV01_1001_A	10	10	Yukikaze: 「Aheeeeee! Hahieeee! Nheeeeeeeeee!!」	s23a	0497
PV01_1001_A	10	11	Yukikaze basks in the pleasure of her second creampie.	s23a	0498
PV01_1001_A	10	12	Of course, there isn't a single thought left for Tatsurou.	s23a	0499
PV01_1001_A	10	13	In front of other men, Yukikaze keeps showing off the moaning face of a dirty sow.	s23a	0500
PV01_1001_A	10	14	Yazaki: 「Well now, let's see how much you've collected.」	s23a	0501
PV01_1001_A	10	15	While grinning, Yazaki pulls out his dick from her wet slit.	s23a	0502
PV01_1001_A	10	16	Yukikaze: 「Kuhi! Hi! Hahiiii!」	s23a	0503
PV01_1001_A	10	17	From that simple stimulation, Yukikaze reaches a light orgasm, as her body wriggles.	s23a	0504
PV01_1001_A	10	18	In that obscene movement, her cunt opens her mouth and regurgitates two creampies' worth of semen.	s23a	0505
PV01_1001_A	10	19	Yukikaze: 「Heyaah! I caaame……My sow cunt that has heen filled with shemen……has been cumming for a while……」	s23a	0506
PV01_1001_A	10	20	As she scatters man-juice, an absentminded smile of joy appears on her face.	s23a	0507
PV01_1001_A	10	21	Yukikaze: 「Ahyaa, yaa……Aaah, it feels good…… My pussy, kuhi……Feels amazing～～っ♪」	s23a	0508
PV01_1001_A	10	22	After cumming from two creampies her sphincter loosens, and urine starts dripping.	s23a	0509
PV01_1001_A	10	23	Yazaki: 「Fun, you even started pissing yourself, you debauched sow!」	s23a	0510
PV01_1001_A	10	24	Yazaki plucks on Yukikaze's nipples, who's dizzy after cumming several times in a row.	s23a	0511
PV01_1001_A	10	25	Yukikaze: 「Hyahi! Hi! Hin! Nya-What?! Nhiin! M-My nipples! Don't pinch fem!!」	s23a	0512
PV01_1001_A	10	26	Yazaki: 「Did you finally wake up? I still have to cum inside you three more times, so it's too early to rest!」	s23a	0513
PV01_1001_A	10	27	Yukikaze: 「Y-Yeah! Be it three or four more times! Ah! Ahn! Cum inside me! I'll cum! I- no matter how many times you creampie me, I'll climax!!」	s23a	0514
PV01_1001_A	10	28	Guest: 「She has been wonderfully trained, Yazaki-san.」	s23a	0515
PV01_1001_A	10	29	Guest: 「Indeed. That "Lightning Strike" Taimanin has been completely broken, to cum from being inseminated.」	s23a	0516
PV01_1001_A	10	30	The guests unanimously praise Yukikaze's coquetry.	s23a	0517
PV01_1001_A	10	31	Yazaki: 「It's because I've been spending money on her every day. Even though she has a lover, nowaways, whenever her womb gets filled, she forgets about everything else. Isn't that right?!」	s23a	0518
PV01_1001_A	10	32	Yukikaze: 「Fuhiiiiiiinn!!」	s23a	0519
PV01_1001_A	10	33	Yazaki flicks her nipples with his finger, and Yukikaze screams again, climaxing.	s23a	0520
PV01_1001_A	10	34	Yukikaze: 「Ahyaah! I-I came again……Hihya… It feels goood……It feels sho goood……Ahe, hyahe……Ahaha!」	s23a	0521
PV01_1001_A	10	35	Yukikaze grumbles, unaware of Yazaki and the guests scorning her.	s23a	0522
PV01_1001_A	10	36	Guest: 「To think that this annoying Taimanin is now the shadow of her former self makes me even more aroused.」	s23a	0523
PV01_1001_A	10	37	Guest: 「Indeed. It was worth coming here today just for this.」	s23a	0524
PV01_1001_A	10	38	The men's jeers wrap Yukikaze.	s23a	0525
PV01_1001_A	10	39	However, the only thing on her mind is the cock that made her cum.	s23a	0526
PV01_1001_A	10	40	Yukikaze: 「Ahaa, haan, coock, hurry with your cock, give it to my pussy……」	s23a	0527
PV01_1001_A	11	1	……………………	s23a	0528
PV01_1001_A	11	2	…………	s23a	0529
