S010C	1	1	Shifting Yogiri to an underhand grip, I lower my body and dash toward Sakura-sensei.	s10a	0104
S010C	1	2	Sakura: 「Oh, a swordfight first-thing?」	s10a	0105
S010C	1	3	Her eyes are sparkling.	s10a	0106
S010C	1	4	It's good that she thinks so.	s10a	0107
S010C	1	5	Neither my swordplay nor my Ninpou would give me a chance in a straight fight.	s10a	0108
S010C	1	6	But if I can create the smallest of openings――	s10a	0109
S010C	1	7	Tatsurou: 「Yaaaaaaaaaa!」	s10a	0110
S010C	1	8	Sakura-sensei indolently draws her twin kodachi and falls into her stance just as I unleash my Ittou-ryuu at her.	s10a	0111
S010C	1	9	Sakura: 「Eeh, that's pretty sharp swordsmanship.」	s10a	0112
S010C	1	10	Sakura-sensei might be praising me, but she's nimbly evading my consecutive slashes.	s10a	0113
S010C	1	11	Ugh, she's fast!	s10a	0114
S010C	1	12	This isn't the kind of speed Rinko-ane possesses, that comes from years of practice in a sword style; this is raw talent.	s10a	0115
S010C	1	13	She moves just like the wind.	s10a	0116
S010C	1	14	Sakura: 「I see. You're Rinko-chan's little brother? Then, can you dodge this?」	s10a	0117
S010C	1	15	Tatsurou: 「…………!」	s10a	0118
S010C	1	16	Incoming!!	s10a	0119
S010C	1	17	Sakura: 「Haaa!!」	s10a	0120
S010C	1	18	Sakura-sensei's kodachi are darting at me from two angles.	s10a	0121
S010C	1	19	Tatsurou: 「Ugh!!」	s10a	0122
S010C	1	20	What an attack.	s10a	0123
S010C	1	21	Her blades move even faster than Rinko-ane's sword.	s10a	0124
S010C	1	22	Moreover, each of her weapons moves like it has a will of its own.	s10a	0125
S010C	1	23	Only the Ittou-ryu ingrained in my body and tempered during my week of training allows me to barely deflect the blows.	s10a	0126
S010C	1	24	Tatsurou: 「Haaa!!」	s10a	0127
S010C	1	25	Just as her kodachi are about to meet, I leap over.	s10a	0128
S010C	1	26	Sakura: 「Well dodged. But just jumping like that isn't going to work!」	s10a	0129
S010C	1	27	Sakura-sensei takes to the sky as well, giving pursuit.	s10a	0130
S010C	1	28	Now!!	s10a	0131
S010C	1	29	As I'm about to start falling, she readies a strike timed for when I'll be the most vulnerable.	s10a	0132
S010C	1	30	Tatsurou: 「Ninpou, Paper Garments Arts.」	s10a	0133
S010C	1	31	I finally use my trump card.	s10a	0134
S010C	1	32	That technique reduces my body weight to nothing.	s10a	0135
S010C	1	33	Soaring like a leaf on the wind, I smoothly avoid her attack.	s10a	0136
S010C	1	34	Sakura: 「Good!」	s10a	0137
S010C	1	35	Although I spoiled her finishing blow, Sakura-sensei praises me.	s10a	0138
S010C	1	36	Surely she didn't expect that? Doubts assail me.	s10a	0139
S010C	1	37	Thankfully, even she can't escape gravity and she soon starts her descent toward the ground.	s10a	0140
S010C	1	38	Now's my only chance!	s10a	0141
S010C	1	39	Tatsurou: 「Yaaaaaaa!!」	s10a	0142
S010C	1	40	Repeatedly adjusting my weight in irregular patterns, I let loose a flurry of slashes at my opponent.	s10a	0143
S010C	2	1	Sakura: 「Nice! That's the spirit!」	s10a	0144
S010C	2	2	Sakura-sensei keeps parrying my assaults with her own blades.	s10a	0145
S010C	2	3	That level of agility surely is among the best the Taimanin have to offer.	s10a	0146
S010C	2	4	I managed to lure my foe midair, but I fail to end it there.	s10a	0147
S010C	2	5	Tatsurou: 「Shit!!」	s10a	0148
S010C	2	6	Sakura: 「Come on, your sword is losing it!」	s10a	0149
S010C	2	7	Just as I hear that――	s10a	0150
S010C	2	8	Sakura-sensei, who had been defending thus far, simply vanishes.	s10a	0151
S010C	2	9	Sakura: 「Look, you're out of it again.」	s10a	0152
S010C	2	10	A voice coming from my back.	s10a	0153
S010C	2	11	Tatsurou: 「Wha-!?」	s10a	0154
S010C	2	12	Sakura: 「Hey, caught you.」	s10a	0155
S010C	2	13	Sakura binds my arms behind my back.	s10a	0156
S010C	2	14	Sakura: 「Heave-ho!」	s10a	0157
S010C	2	15	And quickly flips my head toward the ground.	s10a	0158
S010C	2	16	Tatsurou: 「Uwa!」	s10a	0159
S010C	2	17	I frantically nullify my weight, but her grapple makes it pointless.	s10a	0160
S010C	2	18	I simply fall along with Sakura-sensei.	s10a	0161
S010C	2	19	Until my skull is rammed in the dirt.	s10a	0162
S010C	2	20	Tatsurou: 「I-I yield!」	s10a	0163
S010C	2	21	Sakura: 「Yep, checkmate.」	s10a	0164
S010C	2	22	Just before the moment of impact, Sakura-sensei reverses my position back to normal.	s10a	0165
S010C	2	23	Tatsurou: 「Wh-When did you get behind me?」	s10a	0166
S010C	2	24	With a sigh of relief for the feeling of solid ground under my feet, I ask the teacher.	s10a	0167
S010C	2	25	Sakura: 「Umbral Arts. You're not the only one with tricky moves.」	s10a	0168
S010C	2	26	The instructor says so while chuckling.	s10a	0169
S010C	2	27	Umbral Arts――Melding into shadows, moving from one to another, that's Sakura-sensei's secret technique.	s10a	0170
S010C	2	28	Tatsurou: 「But, how did you do it in midair??」	s10a	0171
S010C	2	29	Sakura: 「During your unsteady trip back to the ground, it was easy enough to cast a shadow on your body.」	s10a	0172
S010C	2	30	She smiles cheerfully while sheathing her kodachi.	s10a	0173
S010C	2	31	Could it be that she managed to put a shadow on my back with one of her weapons in the middle of my attacks?	s10a	0174
S010C	2	32	Sakura: 「You've trained your Ninpou well, but the way you use it in combat is sort of naive.」	s10a	0175
S010C	2	33	Tatsurou: 「Yes……I'm sorry……」	s10a	0176
S010C	2	34	Sakura: 「Luring me to the air was a good plan, the problem was that you were unable to exploit the situation. It seems you are unable to blend your Ninpou with your swordmanship.」	s10a	0177
S010C	2	35	Tatsurou: 「Yes……」	s10a	0178
S010C	2	36	She exposed me thoroughly. I can do nothing but nod feebly.	s10a	0179
S010C	2	37	It seems that getting selected for the special camp was a pipe dream after all.	s10a	0180
S010C	2	38	Tatsurou: 「Thank……you.」	s10a	0181
S010C	2	39	As I bow, I begin to leave the training area.	s10a	0182
S010C	2	40	Sakura: 「Where are you going? You passed!」	s10a	0183
S010C	3	1	Tatsurou: 「Eh?」	s10a	0184
S010C	3	2	Sakura: 「You pass. From now on you'll train on how to properly use your Ninpou in real battle. It's Mu-chan――I mean, it's Murasaki-sensei specialty.」	s10a	0185
S010C	3	3	Tatsurou: 「Th-Thank you!」	s10a	0186
S010C	3	4	I bow again, full of zeal this time.	s10a	0187
S010C	3	5	Sakura: 「Yes, that's better. After all it wouldn't do for the Ittou-ryuu heir to give up so easily.」	s10a	0188
S010C	3	6	Tatsurou: 「Yes!!」	s10a	0189
S010C	3	7	Sakura: 「Good, good. Then, who's the next participant?!」	s10a	0190
S010C	3	8	Sakura-sensei asks the crowd.	s10a	0191
S010C	3	9	But she suddenly looks surprised.	s10a	0192
S010C	3	10	Sakura: 「Eh? Onee-chan?」	s10a	0193
S010C	3	11	Asagi-sensei had arrived.	s10a	0194
S010C	3	12	Asagi: 「Sakura, a word with you.」	s10a	0195
S010C	3	13	Her face is deadly serious.	s10a	0196
S010C	3	14	Sakura: 「What? I'm doing my job just fine, you know. Onee-chan, you really have to stop grading my teaching style.」	s10a	0197
S010C	3	15	Asagi: 「That's not it. Just come.」	s10a	0198
S010C	3	16	Sakura: 「Ugh, what is it?」	s10a	0199
S010C	3	17	After they step away from us, Asagi starts speaking to her.	s10a	0200
S010C	3	18	Sakura-sensei's expression immediately turns serious.	s10a	0201
S010C	3	19	I'm not sure what they're talking about, but it's definitely no light matter.	s10a	0202
S010C	3	20	Something related to the exam?	s10a	0203
S010C	3	21	Or some other mission?	s10a	0204
S010C	3	22	Thinking of it, I wonder how Yukikaze and Rinko-ane's sheathed mission is going.	s10a	0205
S010C	3	23	Of course I'm not privy to any new information, but I'm still worried.	s10a	0206
S010C	3	24	Now that's on my mind, I can't help but have a bad feeling about it.	s10a	0207
S010C	3	25	Please let them be safe.	s10a	0208
S010C	3	26	SALTAR: S011A
