S011A	1	1	…………	s11a	0000
S011A	1	2	It's been two weeks since Rinko and Yukikaze's remodeling started.	s11a	0001
S011A	1	3	The nefarious process that will turn them into sex slaves isn't over yet.	s11a	0002
S011A	1	4	The first step focused on their flesh: continuous application of the demonic drug has put them in a perpetual state of lust. Then came the second one.	s11a	0003
S011A	1	5	While a modified body is certainly an important part of becoming a sex slave, it is not enough; the mind must be reformed as well.	s11a	0004
