S012AB	1	1	…………	s12a	0039
S012AB	1	2	The parade of shame is over.	s12a	0040
S012AB	1	3	Led by their owner, they have entered one of the corridor's many rooms.	s12a	0041
S012AB	1	4	Real: 「You certainly grew more docile.」	s12a	0042
S012AB	1	5	Real is as haughty as ever.	s12a	0043
S012AB	1	6	He makes it sounds as if no harm ever came to them.	s12a	0044
S012AB	1	7	And neither Yukikaze nor Rinko can muster the will to protest.	s12a	0045
S012AB	1	8	Yukikaze: 「Haa, haa……Haa……」	s12a	0046
S012AB	1	9	Rinko: 「Hu……Ku, haa……Haa……」	s12a	0047
S012AB	1	10	Showing mortified eyes and wiping some of the spit off their lips is all they are able to do.	s12a	0048
S012AB	1	11	Yukikaze: 「What are you planning……to do here?」	s12a	0049
S012AB	1	12	At the cost of a tremendous effort, Yukikaze finally manages to produce a frail voice.	s12a	0050
S012AB	1	13	Real: 「Yukikaze, this will be your room..」	s12a	0051
S012AB	1	14	Yukikaze: 「My……room?」	s12a	0052
S012AB	1	15	Yukikaze surveys the 20 square meter studio apartment.	s12a	0053
S012AB	1	16	The first thing she notices is the king-sized bed that occupies most of the space.	s12a	0054
S012AB	1	17	She can also make out a closet, a dresser and a small refrigerator.	s12a	0055
S012AB	1	18	Another door near the entrance most likely leads to the bathroom.	s12a	0056
S012AB	1	19	Finally, a kitchenette to take care of all cooking needs.	s12a	0057
S012AB	1	20	The lack of windows, mixed with the dim lightning and the obscene decorations, contribute to give the room a barren feeling.	s12a	0058
S012AB	1	21	In other words, a hotel room, and the kind you'd expect in a tasteless love hotel.	s12a	0059
S012AB	1	22	A maiden seeking romantic love would doubtlessly feel disgusted at its sight. This place was built solely for sex.	s12a	0060
S012AB	1	23	Yukikaze certainly frowned, but not for the same reason.	s12a	0061
S012AB	1	24	Yukikaze: 「Why is there such a beautiful room in this shady brothel?」	s12a	0062
S012AB	1	25	Rinko: 「This is definitely out of place.」	s12a	0063
S012AB	1	26	Rinko agrees as well.	s12a	0064
S012AB	1	27	They didn't have a chance to notice, but the cerebral remodeling also modified their perception of beauty.	s12a	0065
S012AB	1	28	Real: 「Yukikaze, you will live here from now on. An identical one also has been prepared for Rinko.」	s12a	0066
S012AB	1	29	Rinko: 「Like the sex slaves we saw earlier?……」	s12a	0067
S012AB	1	30	Rinko mumbles.	s12a	0068
S012AB	1	31	Real answers with a chuckle.	s12a	0069
S012AB	1	32	Real: 「Correct. Until you become authentic sex slaves you will stay here, and this is also where you will entertain your customers.」	s12a	0070
S012AB	1	33	Yukikaze: 「Customers……Here?」	s12a	0071
S012AB	1	34	Yukikaze observes the brothel room again.	s12a	0072
S012AB	1	35	Real: 「Yes. Right here.」	s12a	0073
S012AB	1	36	Yukikaze: 「It can't be, starting today?」	s12a	0074
S012AB	1	37	Real: 「Once again you overestimate yourself. Through cutting edge technology, I already gave you a sex slave's body and mind, but to satisfy your guests you still require the adequate skills.」	s12a	0075
S012AB	1	38	Yukikaze: 「Wh-What do you intend to do?」	s12a	0076
S012AB	1	39	Real: 「Shouldn't it be obvious? I will train you.」	s12a	0077
S012AB	1	40	Translating words into action, Real casually undresses.	s12a	0078
S012AB	2	1	Yukikaze&Rinko: 「「Wha……!!!?」」	s12a	0079
S012AB	2	2	The sudden turn of events causes the girls to gasp.	s12a	0080
S012AB	2	3	Between the legs of the now naked Real stand a large, thriving dick.	s12a	0081
S012AB	2	4	Yukikaze: 「Ah, ah, aah……」	s12a	0082
S012AB	2	5	Rinko: 「Ku……It's erect……」	s12a	0083
S012AB	2	6	The two freeze at the sight.	s12a	0084
S012AB	2	7	Although they're still befuddled, it seems that they've figured out what's the training session is going to be about.	s12a	0085
S012AB	2	8	Yukikaze: 「D-Don't joke with us!」	s12a	0086
S012AB	2	9	Rinko: 「How dare you……so shameless……」	s12a	0087
S012AB	2	10	Real: 「Joke? I'm entirely serious. Shame? Don't be ridiculous. You two are my property.」	s12a	0088
S012AB	2	11	Yukikaze: 「Sh-Shut up!」	s12a	0089
S012AB	2	12	Rinko: 「Uu……You beast……」	s12a	0090
S012AB	2	13	Imperceptibly, Yukikaze and Rinko have started to shiver.	s12a	0091
S012AB	2	14	Their eyes are glued to the unsightly meat stick.	s12a	0092
S012AB	2	15	Part of their mind screams that they should feel nothing but disgust, to no avail.	s12a	0093
S012AB	2	16	Yukikaze: 「Aah……Amazing cock……Amazing……」	s12a	0094
S012AB	2	17	Rinko: 「I want it……Cock……I want it.」	s12a	0095
S012AB	2	18	Instinctive words, muttered only to themselves. They gulp down a sudden influx of saliva……	s12a	0096
S012AB	2	19	……and abruptly come back to their senses.	s12a	0097
S012AB	2	20	Yukikaze: 「Ha!? What was I……No!」	s12a	0098
S012AB	2	21	Rinko: 「Ku! Wh-Why……Uu, my body feels so hot…… Damn, why am I……Like this……!」	s12a	0099
S012AB	2	22	Yukikaze: 「S-Senpai……This isn't good……I don't want to…… I really don't want to, yet……My heart is beating so fast…… I don't want this! What's going to happen to me, Senpai?!」	s12a	0100
S012AB	2	23	Rinko: 「Y-Yukikaze!!」	s12a	0101
S012AB	2	24	This, of course, is the result of the remodeling.	s12a	0102
S012AB	2	25	Like stumbling on an oasis after wandering in the desert for days.	s12a	0103
S012AB	2	26	This is how their modified brains make them feel at the sight of a man's cock.	s12a	0104
S012AB	2	27	The only thing that can alleviate their insatiable hunger.	s12a	0105
S012AB	2	28	The only thing they can't help but covet with all their being.	s12a	0106
S012AB	2	29	Real: 「Do you want it that much?」	s12a	0107
S012AB	2	30	Yukikaze: 「Yes! I do!!……Ah! N-No! That's not it. That thing……Uuh! I-I don't……want it!!」	s12a	0108
S012AB	2	31	Rinko: 「Me too……That……Ku, that disgusting dick of yours……Ah! Aaah, I want it―― Not! Who would ever want that?!!」	s12a	0109
S012AB	2	32	Real: 「Impressive display of willpower, but ultimately pointless. Your very core has already been conditioned to become a sex slave.」	s12a	0110
S012AB	2	33	Real: 「You are no longer who you were before coming here; what you are attempting would be similar to a normal person trying to resist the urge of breathing.」	s12a	0111
S012AB	2	34	Real: 「And in both cases, trying too hard will most likely lead to irreversible brain damage.」	s12a	0112
S012AB	2	35	Yukikaze: 「Ku!! How dare you!!!」	s12a	0113
S012AB	2	36	Rinko: 「D-Damn you……!?」	s12a	0114
S012AB	2	37	The girls scowl at Real with eyes full of anger.	s12a	0115
S012AB	2	38	Channeling this rage is their last defense against the overpowering attraction exerted by the dick.	s12a	0116
S012AB	2	39	Real: 「Need I remind you that according to our pact, any harmful action on your part will automatically lead to your dismemberment? It would certainly be distressing for me to lose two expensive sows before they're even tried out.」	s12a	0117
S012AB	2	40	Yukikaze: 「Uh……Uuuh……」	s12a	0118
S012AB	3	1	Rinko: 「You brute……Ga……Shit……」	s12a	0119
S012AB	3	2	They groan and bit their lip.	s12a	0120
S012AB	3	3	Even though they managed to rekindle their anger when confronted with the reality of the remodeling, for now all they can do is submit.	s12a	0121
S012AB	3	4	This is the path they chose, for the greater goal of rescuing Yukikaze's mother and succeeding in their duty.	s12a	0122
S012AB	3	5	Or is it just a pretext?	s12a	0123
S012AB	3	6	They cannot stop staring at Real's towering manhood.	s12a	0124
S012AB	3	7	Yukikaze: 「Haa, haa……Haa……Haa……」	s12a	0125
S012AB	3	8	Rinko: 「Ha……Haa……Uh……Ku……Aah……」	s12a	0126
S012AB	3	9	Cheeks flushed, breath rough, and beads of sweat multiplying on their skin.	s12a	0127
S012AB	3	10	The cloying smell of the devilish lotion they were imbued with grows stronger.	s12a	0128
S012AB	3	11	But even so, it fails to cover the stench of females in heat that overflows from their quivering pussies.	s12a	0129
S012AB	3	12	Yukikaze: 「Rinko-senpai……」	s12a	0130
S012AB	3	13	Rinko: 「I-I know……」	s12a	0131
S012AB	3	14	Finally aware of how much their bodies have changed, Yukikaze and Rinko's eyes turn languorous.	s12a	0132
S012AB	3	15	Real: 「That's better. After all, this is what you chose for yourself, and the seals on your tongues will always label you as filthy sows. Never forget that.」	s12a	0133
S012AB	3	16	Real: 「Work hard, turn into accomplished sex slaves, buy back your freedom. Wouldn't it make for a sweet ending?」	s12a	0134
S012AB	3	17	Yukikaze: 「Kuu……Then begin that training already! Uuu……Becoming a sex slave is nothing!」	s12a	0135
S012AB	3	18	Real: 「It appears that the first thing I will need to teach you is proper behavior.」	s12a	0136
S012AB	3	19	Yukikaze: 「Be-Behavior!?」	s12a	0137
S012AB	3	20	Real: 「Rinko, come over here.」	s12a	0138
S012AB	3	21	Real, clearly planning something, starts whispering into Rinko's ear.	s12a	0139
S012AB	3	22	Rinko: 「……Wha-!? Ku……!?」	s12a	0140
S012AB	3	23	Real: 「The senior should go first.」	s12a	0141
S012AB	3	24	Declaring so, Real leaves Rinko's side.	s12a	0142
S012AB	3	25	Rinko: 「Hu, Huuuu……」	s12a	0143
S012AB	3	26	Yukikaze: 「Senpai!?」	s12a	0144
S012AB	3	27	Yukikaze send a questioning glance to her partner.	s12a	0145
S012AB	3	28	Rinko: 「Yukikaze……」	s12a	0146
S012AB	3	29	Her gaze goes from Yukikaze to Real before shamefully settling on the ground. After a moment, she takes a deep breath and raises her face.	s12a	0147
S012AB	3	30	Rinko kneels before Real.	s12a	0148
S012AB	3	31	Behind the towering cock, she looks her owner in the eye.	s12a	0149
S012AB	3	32	For the first time in her life, Rinko tries to make a seductive expression.	s12a	0150
S012AB	3	33	Rinko: 「M-Master.」	s12a	0151
S012AB	3	34	Yukikaze: 「Wha-!?」	s12a	0152
S012AB	3	35	Avoiding Yukikaze's astonished eyes, Rinko continues.	s12a	0153
S012AB	3	36	Rinko: 「I am an apprentice sex slave called Rinko…… I will do my best to become a great so-……sow…… P-Please take care of me……」	s12a	0154
S012AB	3	37	Yukikaze: 「R-Rinko-senpai……!?」	s12a	0155
S012AB	3	38	Rinko: 「………………」	s12a	0156
S012AB	3	39	Rinko turns her face away from Yukikaze.	s12a	0157
S012AB	3	40	Even though they went through the same remodeling, she didn't want her junior to witness such a pathetic display.	s12a	0158
S012AB	4	1	Even from the side, the shame she feels is obvious.	s12a	0159
S012AB	4	2	Real: 「Mh. Stiff and awkward, but it will have to do for now. Make sure to always smile when you flirt with a man.」	s12a	0160
S012AB	4	3	Rinko: 「………………」	s12a	0161
S012AB	4	4	Real: 「What kind of answer is that!!」	s12a	0162
S012AB	4	5	Rinko: 「Yes. I won't forget to smile when flirting with a man.」	s12a	0163
S012AB	4	6	Real: 「That's better.」	s12a	0164
S012AB	4	7	Yukikaze: 「……Senpai.」	s12a	0165
S012AB	4	8	Real: 「Yukikaze, you're up next.」	s12a	0166
S012AB	4	9	Yukikaze: 「I-I won't!」	s12a	0167
S012AB	4	10	Real: 「Surely you remember the words? Kneel in front of your master's cock and greet him as an apprentice sex slave.」	s12a	0168
S012AB	4	11	Yukikaze: 「…………」	s12a	0169
S012AB	4	12	Yukikaze bites her lip and clenches her fists.	s12a	0170
S012AB	4	13	Real: 「What is it? Do you wish to stop? Fine, but that would constitute a breach of contract. Of course I'll have to dispose of what's left of you, and make Rinko work twice as hard to pick up your slack.」	s12a	0171
S012AB	4	14	Yukikaze: 「I-I just need to do that, right? I'll do it!」	s12a	0172
S012AB	4	15	Shaking with anger, Yukikaze kneels next to Rinko and look up at Real's dick.	s12a	0173
S012AB	4	16	Yukikaze: 「Uu……M-Master……」	s12a	0174
S012AB	4	17	Real: 「Hold on.」	s12a	0175
S012AB	4	18	Yukikaze: 「Eh?」	s12a	0176
S012AB	4	19	Yukikaze's attempt at a sex slave greeting is interrupted by Real.	s12a	0177
S012AB	4	20	He had noticed that Rinko was averting her eyes.	s12a	0178
S012AB	4	21	Real: 「Rinko, I want you to look closely. Engrave in your mind what your precious Yukikaze has become.」	s12a	0179
S012AB	4	22	Rinko: 「……Yes.」	s12a	0180
S012AB	4	23	Real gives no quarter. Rinko can do nothing but witness her junior's introduction.	s12a	0181
S012AB	4	24	Real: 「Then, Yukikaze. Begin.」	s12a	0182
S012AB	4	25	Yukikaze raises her head, but shame fixes her eyes on the floor.	s12a	0183
S012AB	4	26	Her face is full of sorrow.	s12a	0184
S012AB	4	27	Yukikaze: 「I am an apprentice sex slave called Yukikaze…… I will do my best to……B-Become a great filthy sow…… Please take care of me……」	s12a	0185
S012AB	4	28	Yukikaze forces the words out the best she can.	s12a	0186
S012AB	4	29	But Real shakes his head.	s12a	0187
S012AB	4	30	Real: 「Not good enough.」	s12a	0188
S012AB	4	31	Yukikaze: 「What? B-But, I said it like I was told to!」	s12a	0189
S012AB	4	32	Real: 「Didn't you listen what I said? Smile! I want to see that smile plastered on your face at all time when you're working up a customer! Now, do it again. As many time as it takes for you to get it right.」	s12a	0190
S012AB	4	33	Yukikaze: 「Uuu……Ku, aah, aha……Like this?」	s12a	0191
S012AB	4	34	Just like Rinko, Yukikaze never consciously tried to seduce a man.	s12a	0192
S012AB	4	35	As can testify the awkward smile she struggles to put out.	s12a	0193
S012AB	4	36	Real: 「Again, too tense. You still didn't forsake your old self. Tell me, what are you going to become?」	s12a	0194
S012AB	4	37	Yukikaze: 「A-A sex slave……」	s12a	0195
S012AB	4	38	Real: 「Correct. A tool which sole purpose is to slake a man's lust. Do I make myself clear? You are not a human being. Just a professional dirty sow. Say it.」	s12a	0196
S012AB	4	39	Yukikaze: 「I-I am a sex slave……My sole purpose is to slake a man's lust. I am not human. I am a professional dirty sow.」	s12a	0197
S012AB	4	40	Real: 「Fawn over your customer. All men are beings far above you. You're less than an insect. Now smile for me, sow. Smile!」	s12a	0198
S012AB	5	1	Yukikaze: 「I am worth less than an insect. I'm a dirty sow. A sex slave. Nothing more than a helpless subhuman, Master!!」	s12a	0199
S012AB	5	2	Another effect of the cerebral remodeling.	s12a	0200
S012AB	5	3	To follow Real's order, Yukikaze keeps on belittling herself, but as she does so an awkward yet earnest enamored expression forms on her face.	s12a	0201
S012AB	5	4	Real: 「Very well, this will do. Introduce yourself once more. Speak!」	s12a	0202
S012AB	5	5	Yukikaze: 「Master, I am an apprentice sex slave called Yukikaze…… I'll do my best to become a great filthy sow. Please take care of me!」	s12a	0203
S012AB	5	6	Real: 「Kukuku. Good. Let's drop this topic for today. There will be plenty of occasions to inculcate you with the mannerisms of a sex slave.」	s12a	0204
S012AB	5	7	Real: 「I expect you to do your utmost to turn into legitimate sex slave. Anything less will lead to an early death.」	s12a	0205
S012AB	5	8	Real: 「This is why, starting right now, the time you spend alone in your room will be dedicated to perfecting your sexual techniques.」	s12a	0206
S012AB	5	9	Yukikaze: 「Yes. Thank you very much.」	s12a	0207
S012AB	5	10	The words that just flew out of her mouth cause Yukikaze to frown.	s12a	0208
S012AB	5	11	Yukikaze: 「Ah……Uh, I-……This……」	s12a	0209
S012AB	5	12	Real: 「Rinko?」	s12a	0210
S012AB	5	13	Rinko: 「Yes. Understood……Master……」	s12a	0211
S012AB	5	14	Rinko's acknowledgement is filled with dismay.	s12a	0212
S012AB	5	15	Even if it's against their better judgement, they feel unable to disagree.	s12a	0213
S012AB	5	16	Now that it has come to this, they are forced to admit that the situation is far removed from their naive expectations.	s12a	0214
S012AB	5	17	Forget "merely pretending", if they were to lose focus for an instant they would turn into sex slaves, both body and soul.	s12a	0215
S012AB	5	18	Not to mention, their precious first times are about to be taken away by Real.	s12a	0216
S012AB	5	19	And while their minds scream at the mere thought of it, their tragically modified flesh shivers in obscene anticipation.	s12a	0217
S012AB	5	20	Desire and despair are fighting a raging battle inside their hearts.	s12a	0218
S012AB	5	21	Real: 「Now then, who should go first?」	s12a	0219
S012AB	5	22	Real asks.	s12a	0220
S012AB	5	23	Hearing that, Yukikaze raises her face.	s12a	0221
S012AB	5	24	SELECCIONAR 1: S012AC
S012AB	5	25	SELECCIONAR 2: S012AD
