S017A	1	1	Another month goes by.	s17a	0000
S017A	1	2	On the 154th day of Yukikaze and Rinko's sheathed mission.	s17a	0001
S017A	1	3	Real: 「Congratulations. I approve of you as sex slaves.」	s17a	0002
S017A	1	4	Yukikaze: 「………………」	s17a	0003
S017A	1	5	Rinko: 「……………………」	s17a	0004
S017A	1	6	Yukikaze and Rinko have mixed feelings towards Real's words.	s17a	0005
S017A	1	7	They finally got approved as sex slaves.	s17a	0006
S017A	1	8	More than 5 months after their mission started.	s17a	0007
S017A	1	9	They went through unimaginably obscene training. Even with their miserable bodies remodeled,  they overcame their despair, and finally became sex slaves.	s17a	0008
S017A	1	10	For the sake of finding Taimanin Shiranui, and rescuing her.	s17a	0009
S017A	1	11	They became sex slaves able to freely roam the dark underground city.	s17a	0010
S017A	1	12	They put up with the shame of becoming sex outlets for the inhabitants of the dark.	s17a	0011
S017A	1	13	Real: 「What's wrong? Aren't you happy?」	s17a	0012
S017A	1	14	Real speaks with an ill-mannered tone.	s17a	0013
S017A	1	15	Yukikaze: 「We're happy.」	s17a	0014
S017A	1	16	Rinko: 「Indeed, we are.」	s17a	0015
S017A	1	17	They don't sound happy at all.	s17a	0016
S017A	1	18	Even if they say that, they are wearing the sex slave uniforms. Their bodies, plastered with the aphrodisiac oil, lewdly glitter.	s17a	0017
S017A	1	19	Their entire bodies exude the indecent smell of a bitch in heat and their aroused wombs are continuously aching for a male. This is now their daily life.	s17a	0018
S017A	1	20	Besides their purpose as Taimanin, the two unmistakably became sex slaves.	s17a	0019
S017A	1	21	Real: 「For you to earn money as soon as possible, we will need some advertising.」	s17a	0020
S017A	1	22	Yukikaze: 「Advertising?」	s17a	0021
S017A	1	23	Rinko: 「You mean our debut?」	s17a	0022
S017A	1	24	Yukikaze: 「…………Uu.」	s17a	0023
S017A	1	25	Remembering the training that made her unable to endure orgasms, Yukikaze starts shivering.	s17a	0024
S017A	1	26	She will be violated again until her mind breaks.	s17a	0025
S017A	1	27	She feels fear, and expectation.	s17a	0026
S017A	1	28	Real: 「A sex slave needs to be popular. If you're not, you will have to serve your clients in the city, like a prostitute from a rundown district. You don't want that happen, do you?」	s17a	0027
S017A	1	29	Rinko: 「We took your training so that this doesn't happen. We will satisfy as many men as necessary.」	s17a	0028
S017A	1	30	Real grins at Rinko's words.	s17a	0029
S017A	1	31	Real: 「We will have an event. It's somewhat of a custom for a sex slave debut. Follow me, then. To catch a glimpse of you, a large crowd has gathered in front of the establishment.」	s17a	0030
S017A	1	32	Yukikaze: 「A-Are we going outside……!?」	s17a	0031
S017A	1	33	Rinko: 「We're going outside dressed like this!?」	s17a	0032
S017A	1	34	Thinking that their debut would be inside the shop, the two raise their voice in surprise.	s17a	0033
S017A	1	35	Real: 「Obviously. I told you it's your uniform. It's finally suiting you well, don't you want to show it off?」	s17a	0034
S017A	1	36	Real: 「You girls are sex slaves now. Professional sows who have mastered the art of pleasing men.」	s17a	0035
S017A	1	37	Real: 「If you embarrass me I will fire you immediately. Well, you could say your limbs will be fired……Kukuku.」	s17a	0036
S017A	1	38	Rinko: 「Ku……Alright.」	s17a	0037
S017A	1	39	Yukikaze: 「We just have to show ourselves, right? Wearing this outfit?」	s17a	0038
S017A	1	40	…………	s17a	0039
S017A	2	1	A large crowd of people had gathered in front of Under Eden.	s17a	0040
S017A	2	2	The second Real appears outside, Yukikaze and Rinko are surrounded by cheers from the residents of darkness.	s17a	0041
S017A	2	3	Yukikaze: 「Aah!」	s17a	0042
S017A	2	4	Yukikaze is petrified.	s17a	0043
S017A	2	5	She had never exposed herself to so many people at once.	s17a	0044
S017A	2	6	Moreover, her appearance is more shameful than if she were naked.	s17a	0045
S017A	2	7	Yukikaze: 「Uu……Kuu……」	s17a	0046
S017A	2	8	She feels pierced by the dirty glances of people peering at her oily body.	s17a	0047
S017A	2	9	There aren't only men glaring at them with lust in their eyes.	s17a	0048
S017A	2	10	There are also women scoffing at their unsightly appearance.	s17a	0049
S017A	2	11	The shame that was beginning to dissipate after half a year of training starts to resurface.	s17a	0050
S017A	2	12	Yukikaze: （E-Everyone……is watching. They are looking at me like a sex slave……Uu.）	s17a	0051
S017A	2	13	Spectator: 「You have fallen quite low! Did you want men that much, you damned Taimanin?!」	s17a	0052
S017A	2	14	Spectator: 「Those clothes are quite fitting on you, slutty Taimanin skanks!!」	s17a	0053
S017A	2	15	Dirty jeers come from people who know that Yukikaze and Rinko are former Taimanin.	s17a	0054
S017A	2	16	Yukikaze: 「Ku!……」	s17a	0055
S017A	2	17	Yukikaze: （This is embarrassing……Being watched, dressed like this……）	s17a	0056
S017A	2	18	Rinko: 「Yukikaze, are you alright?」	s17a	0057
S017A	2	19	Yukikaze: 「I-I'm alright……Senpai.」	s17a	0058
S017A	2	20	Yukikaze groans.	s17a	0059
S017A	2	21	Real: 「If you're alright then raise your head. You want them to remember this face.」	s17a	0060
S017A	2	22	Yukikaze: 「Au!」	s17a	0061
S017A	2	23	Real grabs Yukikaze's chin and suddenly lifts it up.	s17a	0062
S017A	2	24	Real: 「Well then, let's move, you whores.」	s17a	0063
S017A	2	25	Yukikaze and Rinko's walk of shame begins.	s17a	0064
S017A	2	26	Yukikaze: 「Here is……」	s17a	0065
S017A	2	27	The two are brought to a place they know.	s17a	0066
S017A	2	28	Yomihara's central square.	s17a	0067
S017A	2	29	It is their second time coming here.	s17a	0068
S017A	2	30	The first time was when they were infiltrating Yomihara, led by Zokuto.	s17a	0069
S017A	2	31	However, their situation has changed since then.	s17a	0070
S017A	2	32	Yukikaze: （Me and Senpai were naive. To think we could just pretend to be prostitutes. We didn't understand anything.）	s17a	0071
S017A	2	33	Yukikaze: 「………………」	s17a	0072
S017A	2	34	Reflecting on their own foolishness, Yukikaze bites her lip.	s17a	0073
S017A	2	35	This is the result of not taking their mission seriously.	s17a	0074
S017A	2	36	Forced into this disgraceful appearance, they have become the target of ridicule from inhabitants of darkness.	s17a	0075
S017A	2	37	Sex slaves from Yomihara, that's all those two are now.	s17a	0076
S017A	2	38	By the time they got there, Yukikaze had shaken off the shame.	s17a	0077
S017A	2	39	Inside her permanently aroused body, a furious anger is rising.	s17a	0078
S017A	2	40	Yukikaze: （I won't lose! If I get embarrassed, those guys will be pleased!）	s17a	0079
S017A	3	1	Countless residents who heard the rumor gathered in the public square.	s17a	0080
S017A	3	2	Yukikaze: （Watch if you want to, you beasts!!）	s17a	0081
S017A	3	3	Yukikaze puffs out her chest proudly.	s17a	0082
S017A	3	4	Yukikaze: 「Uu……Ku……Uu……」	s17a	0083
S017A	3	5	Yukikaze intended to show her pride as a Taimanin.	s17a	0084
S017A	3	6	However, amongst the scorn and sneer, the lusty gazes on her body feel almost painful.	s17a	0085
S017A	3	7	In fact, as an approved sex slave, Yukikaze can't help but shiver.	s17a	0086
S017A	3	8	Yukikaze: （No good……I can't get lost in those weird feelings……）	s17a	0087
S017A	3	9	However, the depths of her womb are already melting.	s17a	0088
S017A	3	10	The body of an unsightly female covets a male.	s17a	0089
S017A	3	11	The dick of a male. Its semen.	s17a	0090
S017A	3	12	Yukikaze: 「I-I am……Ku……Uu」	s17a	0091
S017A	3	13	Real: 「That's a nice smile. Seduce them properly.」	s17a	0092
S017A	3	14	Real whispers in Yukikaze and Rinko's ears.	s17a	0093
S017A	3	15	Yukikaze: （A s-seductive smile……）	s17a	0094
S017A	3	16	Of course, she doesn't want to die.	s17a	0095
S017A	3	17	However, she remembers her first training as a sex slave, the smile to seduce a man.	s17a	0096
S017A	3	18	Right now, she probably has that smile on her face.	s17a	0097
S017A	3	19	Without her realizing it, she naturally came to smile like that.	s17a	0098
S017A	3	20	Yukikaze: 「Aha, ahaha……」	s17a	0099
S017A	3	21	Suddenly, she remembers a prostitute she saw when she came here for the first time.	s17a	0100
S017A	3	22	That prostitute was picking up clients with her legs spread in this plaza under everyone's eyes.	s17a	0101
S017A	3	23	She felt contempt, but also pity for the shameless woman.	s17a	0102
S017A	3	24	However, Yukikaze is now even more shameless than that prostitute on the streets.	s17a	0103
S017A	3	25	Dedicating entirely herself to satisfy a male's lust, a perverted whore that is delighted to service. A sex slave.	s17a	0104
S017A	3	26	Whether or not Yukikaze agrees with it, the crowd gathered there thinks so.	s17a	0105
S017A	3	27	Yukikaze: （No. I'm also accepting it. My body is accepting it, and maybe also my heart……）	s17a	0106
S017A	3	28	From being stared at as a sex slave, she feels unbearable frustration and sadness, but there is also without doubt pleasure from being abused.	s17a	0107
S017A	3	29	Yukikaze: （I really became a sex slave……）	s17a	0108
S017A	3	30	Yukikaze vividly comes to this realization.	s17a	0109
S017A	3	31	Yukikaze: （Rinko-senpai……）	s17a	0110
S017A	3	32	Yukikaze looks at Rinko.	s17a	0111
S017A	3	33	Rinko walks in front of her. Until they came here, she couldn't see what kind of face she was making.	s17a	0112
S017A	3	34	Even before that, since they took their training separately, Yukikaze didn't know what Rinko's situation was like.	s17a	0113
S017A	3	35	Her always beautiful, gentle, reliable senpai whom she admired.	s17a	0114
S017A	3	36	Like a sister to Yukikaze.	s17a	0115
S017A	3	37	The idea that Rinko could be a sex slave is unthinkable.	s17a	0116
S017A	3	38	She doesn't want to believe that, just like her, she became depraved and drowned in pleasure.	s17a	0117
S017A	3	39	Yukikaze: （However, Rinko-senpai also got approved as a sex slave. A sex slave just like me……）	s17a	0118
S017A	3	40	Did Rinko cry just like she did during the pleasure training?	s17a	0119
S017A	4	1	Was she also reduced to a woman who, forgetting about Tatsurou, lusted so much for and was delighted with sex?	s17a	0120
S017A	4	2	Yukikaze: （No, I can't believe this. I don't want to believe it.）	s17a	0121
S017A	4	3	Yukikaze looks away from Rinko	s17a	0122
S017A	4	4	The idea that Rinko had become like a bitch in heat frightened her.	s17a	0123
S017A	4	5	At that moment, Real speaks to them.	s17a	0124
S017A	4	6	Real: 「Alright. Give a nice greeting to the audience.」	s17a	0124
S017A	4	7	SELECCIONAR 1: S017B
S017A	4	8	SELECCIONAR 2: S017C
