S022A	1	1	After seeing Tatsurou off, Yukikaze and Rinko are――	s22a	0000
S022A	1	2	Yukikaze: 「Tatsurou really went back.」	s22a	0001
S022A	1	3	Rinko: 「Yes……」	s22a	0002
S022A	1	4	Yukikaze: 「We deceived Tatsurou, right?」	s22a	0003
S022A	1	5	Rinko: 「……Yukikaze.」	s22a	0004
S022A	1	6	Yukikaze: 「I know we had no other choice. But, I……」	s22a	0005
S022A	1	7	Rinko: 「Pull yourself together, Yukikaze. This is all to find Shiranui-dono.」	s22a	0006
S022A	1	8	Yukikaze: 「……Yes.」	s22a	0007
S022A	1	9	The two persuade themselves that this is for the sake of the mission.	s22a	0008
S022A	1	10	However, their expressions are bleak.	s22a	0009
S022A	1	11	Yukikaze: （I've reached the point now where I can lie to Tatsurou with a straight face……）	s22a	0010
S022A	1	12	Yukikaze: （Tatsurou also didn't notice in the slightest……）	s22a	0011
S022A	1	13	Although the one deceived was Tatsurou, the one who's the most in shock is Yukikaze.	s22a	0012
S022A	1	14	Thus, they walk back to Under Eden.	s22a	0013
S022A	1	15	After confirming her surroundings and making sure no one could hear their conversation, Yukikaze opens her mouth.	s22a	0014
S022A	1	16	Yukikaze: 「Senpai, is now a good time?」	s22a	0015
S022A	1	17	Rinko: 「What?」	s22a	0016
S022A	1	18	Rinko quickly pricks up her ears. Yukikaze hesitantly starts talking.	s22a	0017
S022A	1	19	Yukikaze: 「Yesterday, while I was keeping Zokuto company, I heard a story about that sex slave.」	s22a	0018
S022A	1	20	Rinko: 「The former Taimanin?」	s22a	0019
S022A	1	21	Yukikaze gives a small nod.	s22a	0020
S022A	1	22	Yukikaze: 「It seems that her patron came to Yomihara and he brought her along. A lot of other patrons are there too.」	s22a	0021
S022A	1	23	Rinko: 「I see. When I was in the "workplace", I also heard something from Real. There was a party yesterday where VIPs gather.」	s22a	0022
S022A	1	24	Yukikaze: 「A party?」	s22a	0023
S022A	1	25	Rinko: 「It seems to be held every month. Though the event is mainly for the VIPs themselves, it seems that sex slaves can use that opportunity to appeal themselves to the VIPs.」	s22a	0024
S022A	1	26	Rinko: 「Superior sex slaves, in other words, sex slaves with high sales participate to find a patron for themselves.」	s22a	0025
S022A	1	27	Rinko's words have a touch of cynicism in them. A sharp light appears in Yukikaze's eyes.	s22a	0026
S022A	1	28	Yukikaze: 「He must have told you on purpose. He probably wants us to participate ASAP and to find good patrons.」	s22a	0027
S022A	1	29	Rinko: 「It seems so. He invested quite a lot of money on us, so he probably won't get his money back if we're just plain sex slaves.」	s22a	0028
S022A	1	30	Yukikaze: 「But, Senpai. This could be our chance!」	s22a	0029
S022A	1	31	Rinko: 「Yes. If we participate in that party, we could confirm the identity of that former Taimanin sex slave with our own eyes.」	s22a	0030
S022A	1	32	Yukikaze: 「I have a feeling that person has to be mom, senpai. I mean, a former Taimanin sex slave wouldn't  just appear like that. Right?」	s22a	0031
S022A	1	33	Yukikaze's face brightens, as though nothing Rinko says now can faze her.	s22a	0032
S022A	1	34	Rinko: 「I also think the chances are quite high. But, Yukikaze, participating in that party means that――」	s22a	0033
S022A	1	35	Rinko tries to choose her words carefully, but Yukikaze interrupts her worries.	s22a	0034
S022A	1	36	Yukikaze: 「I know. We have to become excellent sex slaves. I'm prepared for that. I deceived Tatsurou for the sake of the mission after all.」	s22a	0035
S022A	1	37	Rinko: 「……Yukikaze.」	s22a	0036
S022A	1	38	Rinko had the expression of a big sister worried about her little sister, but she quickly returns to her stern Taimanin self.	s22a	0037
S022A	1	39	Rinko: 「You're right. We cannot go back. Not anymore.」	s22a	0038
S022A	1	40	Yukikaze: 「Yes.」	s22a	0039
S022A	2	1	The two nod at each other.	s22a	0040
S022A	2	2	Yukikaze: 「Senpai, when the party comes, what should we do about our weapons?」	s22a	0041
S022A	2	3	Rinko: 「About that, I asked Tatsurou to conceal them in this town. I should be able to bring them anytime using my technique.」	s22a	0042
S022A	2	4	Yukikaze: 「As expected from you, Senpai!」	s22a	0043
S022A	2	5	Rinko: 「However, as long as we have the sex slave mark, we will be unable to take drastic measures.」	s22a	0044
S022A	2	6	Yukikaze: 「I guess so……」	s22a	0045
S022A	2	7	Rinko: 「Right now, the only thing we can do is to please as many customers as we can, and to become the top sex slaves of this brothel.」	s22a	0046
S022A	2	8	Yukikaze: 「Then we can participate in that party.」	s22a	0047
S022A	2	9	Rinko: 「The next party is in a month. We will have to bear with the humiliation in the meantime.」	s22a	0048
S022A	2	10	Yukikaze: 「……Yes.」	s22a	0049
S022A	2	11	Yukikaze meant to reply with determination, but at the thought of her days filled with disgrace and pleasure, her body shivers.	s22a	0050
S022A	2	12	A shiver of excitement, a shiver of fear.	s22a	0051
S022A	2	13	As her sex slave body already starts lusting, her heart is in pain when she thinks of Tatsurou.	s22a	0052
S022A	2	14	Yukikaze: （Tatsurou, I'm sorry for lying to you.）	s22a	0053
S022A	2	15	Yukikaze: （Someday, I'll tell you everything about my body and the mission.）	s22a	0054
S022A	2	16	Yukikaze: （Tatsurou, would you forgive me?  I wonder if you will despise me? I am such a filthy woman, after all.）	s22a	0055
S022A	2	17	Yukikaze: （My body has become this dirty, someone other than Tatsurou took my virginity, and people like Zokuto made me cum countless times. I don't like it, but I'm washed away by the pleasure; that is who I am now.）	s22a	0056
S022A	2	18	Yukikaze: （Could Tatsurou love someone like me? Hey, Tatsurou, I want to see you.）	s22a	0057
S022A	2	19	Yukikaze: （I want you to squeeze me, to kiss me, to make love to me. I want you to fuck me so that I forget about all the men before you. I want you Tatsurou, I want your cock.）	s22a	0058
S022A	2	20	Yukikaze's innocent thoughts towards Tatsurou gradually get tainted by her lust as a sow.	s22a	0059
S022A	2	21	However, Yukikaze doesn't even notice it.	s22a	0060
