SA007A	1	1	Sakura: 「Hey, Murasaki, are we gonna drink juice?」	sa07a	0000
SA007A	1	2	Murasaki: 「Shut up, don't follow me.」	sa07a	0001
SA007A	1	3	Sakura: 「Ehh～? I said I was worried about Onee-chan too!」	sa07a	0002
SA007A	1	4	Murasaki: 「Then search for her seriously!」	sa07a	0003
SA007A	1	5	Murasaki: 「Kuu... If I'm lucky, I'll become close with Asagi-sama quickly... If that happened, I would die and go to heaven, but...... Why am I working together with a stupid monkey like this......?」	sa07a	0004
SA007A	1	6	Sakura: 「Mm? What's wrong, Mucchan?」	sa07a	0005
SA007A	1	7	Murasaki: 「Don't call me Mucchan!」	sa07a	0006
SA007A	1	8	Murasaki, who went on ahead, got annoyed by her pace being disturbed when Sakura started talking to her.	sa07a	0007
SA007A	1	9	A few hours since Asagi had disappeared.	sa07a	0008
SA007A	1	10	Sakura and Murasaki were searching everywhere for Asagi, who hadn't come back.	sa07a	0009
SA007A	1	11	She wasn't in the boarding house, and they obviously didn't find her on the beach, so the pair were walking around at random.	sa07a	0010
SA007A	1	12	Then, they discovered a cave near the beach.	sa07a	0011
SA007A	1	13	Sakura: 「Onee-chan, are you here～?」	sa07a	0012
SA007A	1	14	Hearing what sounded like a faint voice from the entrance, Sakura and Murasaki slowly progressed into the darkness.	sa07a	0013
SA007A	1	15	Deeper, relying on the light that shone from the entrance, avoiding the icicle-like stalactites that protruded from the ceiling...	sa07a	0014
SA007A	1	16	Murasaki: 「What's this smell......?」	sa07a	0015
SA007A	1	17	A bad smell gradually became stronger as the entrance got further away.	sa07a	0016
SA007A	1	18	In addition, the thing that sounded like a voice had reached the point where they could tell that it clearly was one.	sa07a	0017
SA007A	1	19	Murasaki: 「This voice is, Asagi-sama's......?」	sa07a	0018
SA007A	1	20	Sakura: 「It's Onee-chan's voice!」	sa07a	0019
SA007A	1	21	At the moment they recognized Asagi's voice, a disgust- ing wall was blocking the way in front of the pair.	sa07a	0020
SA007A	1	22	It was a wriggling──	sa07a	0021
SA007A	1	23	Cage of flesh.	sa07a	0022
SA007A	1	24	Murasaki: 「Wh, what is this?!」	sa07a	0023
SA007A	1	25	Sakura: 「Onee-chan, are you inside this?!」	sa07a	0024
SA007A	1	26	Obstructed by the tentacles, the pair couldn't see the situation on the other side, and they called out, relying on Asagi's voice.	sa07a	0025
SA007A	1	27	Asagi: 「Haguuh! Uuh, ga! Sakura...... Murasaki...... Goahh, run away......」	sa07a	0026
SA007A	1	28	Being called out to, Asagi just barely managed to revive her consciousness.	sa07a	0027
SA007A	1	29	She frantically called out, trying to keep the pair away, but her hoarse voice didn't reach them.	sa07a	0028
SA007A	1	30	Sakura and Murasaki assessed that Asagi was inside the flesh cage, and immediately tried to pull apart the tentacle wall, but it wouldn't budge for the weak humans, who couldn't use their powers.	sa07a	0029
SA007A	1	31	At that time, a harsh, hoarse voice became audible from the other side of the wall.	sa07a	0030
SA007A	1	32	Booker: 「Fuhoo?! H-Hey there, hey there! It's Asagi's sister Sakura, and their friend Murasaki, isn't it?」	sa07a	0031
SA007A	1	33	Sakura: 「The information dealer's voice?!」	sa07a	0032
SA007A	1	34	Murasaki: 「What?!」	sa07a	0033
SA007A	1	35	Booker: 「Even if you are her younger sister and her close friend, I won't p-permit you to hinder our vows of love...... As your big brother, I need to punish you......!」	sa07a	0034
SA007A	1	36	Murasaki: 「Guh?! Kuh...... Shit!」	sa07a	0035
SA007A	1	37	Tentacles stretched out from the wall of squirming flesh, and wrapped around Murasaki's body.	sa07a	0036
SA007A	1	38	Sakura: 「Murasaki?! Uwaaaaaaah?!」	sa07a	0037
SA007A	1	39	Like Murasaki, tentacles also wrapped around Sakura's body, and she was pulled down on the spot.	sa07a	0038
SA007A	1	40	Sakura: 「Ow......! What are you doing?!」	sa07a	0039
SA007A	2	1	Sakura, who had been hauled down to the ground, had both legs forcibly spread, and was put in a piledriver-like position.	sa07a	0040
SA007A	2	2	Furthermore, she had been restrained with her hands behind her back, and even the brassiere of her swimsuit had been pulled down.	sa07a	0041
SA007A	2	3	In contrast to her darkly tanned skin, white swimsuit marks, which were her original colour, were exposed just around the peaks of her breasts, and enticed his carnal feelings.	sa07a	0042
SA007A	2	4	Booker: 「The s-s-sister also has quite obscene tits! The fact that the untanned swimsuit marks are small, and just around the nipples, is nice and erotic......!!」	sa07a	0043
SA007A	2	5	Sakura: 「Let go...... Uuuh, don't rub my boobs with your tentacles......!」	sa07a	0044
SA007A	2	6	The slimy tentacles crept along Sakura's body and twisted around her fleshy breasts, which were voluptuous, like her sister's.	sa07a	0045
SA007A	2	7	Firmly wrapping around them, then loosening their grip, they were massaging Sakura's breasts as if they were hands.	sa07a	0046
SA007A	2	8	Sakura: 「St, stop......! If you don't let me go now...... you'll suffer for it later!」	sa07a	0047
SA007A	2	9	Booker: 「Right now, you're the same as a normal human, and yet, like Nee-san, you're not honest, are you? Even though I'm your big brother...」	sa07a	0048
SA007A	2	10	Booker: 「B-But, here are some boobs that feel about as good, ohooh!」	sa07a	0049
SA007A	2	11	Taking the opportunity of her having lost her strength, Booker also wiggled his demonic limbs to violate Sakura.	sa07a	0050
