S004_02	1	1	And now.	s04a	0060
S004_02	1	2	At last, the time had come to carry it out.	s04a	0061
S004_02	1	3	The goal of the raid was to get Lieri and Naomi.	s04a	0062
S004_02	1	4	If just that was a success, afterwords, I could give them memory implants using the brainwashing devices and "cook" the two to my heart's content.	s04a	0063
S004_02	1	5	Bohgan: 「……………………」	s04a	0064
S004_02	1	6	The five of us, including me, held guns, as we headed towards the section where Lieri's VIP room was located.	s04a	0065
S004_02	1	7	In order to avoid the safeguards Naomi had installed, we had taken a detour to an established location there.	s04a	0066
S004_02	1	8	The near-impossible detoured location involved going through vents and the like, but we had made progress silently.	s04a	0067
S004_02	1	9	Bohgan: 「...what's their status?」	s04a	0068
S004_02	1	10	Subordinate: 『Nothing strange』	s04a	0069
S004_02	1	11	At any time I called for it, I asked for a detailed confirmation of the status of Lieri and Naomi via the hidden camera. Of course, it was all highly encrypted.	s04a	0070
S004_02	1	12	Eventually, having arrived as far as the front door of their room, the two had been asleep the whole time.	s04a	0071
S004_02	1	13	Bohgan: 「……………………」	s04a	0072
S004_02	1	14	In a changing era, however much weapons had evolved, the tactics in using them had not changed.	s04a	0073
S004_02	1	15	Releasing the lock on the door without a sound, we suddenly broke into the room in one swift surge.	s04a	0074
S004_02	1	16	I was the last to go in.	s04a	0075
S004_02	1	17	Lieri and Naomi were---	s04a	0076
S004_02	1	18	My team had split into two groups and had surrounded each of their beds, and as they tore away their blankets at the same time-----!!	s04a	0077
S004_02	1	19	Bohgan: 「-----eh!!?」	s04a	0078
S004_02	1	20	I suddenly became speechless.	s04a	0079
S004_02	1	21	The two women were nowhere to be seen.	s04a	0080
S004_02	1	22	In Lieri and Naomi's places were round, metallic balls.	s04a	0081
S004_02	1	23	Soldier 1: 「Captain!?」	s04a	0082
S004_02	1	24	Soldier 2: 「Hii! That means!?」	s04a	0083
S004_02	1	25	The soldier's eyes became fraught with terror at seeing those balls.	s04a	0084
S004_02	1	26	Soldier 3: 「Gun turtles!?」	s04a	0085
S004_02	1	27	Soldier 1: 「Fuck! It's a trap!!」	s04a	0086
S004_02	1	28	Bohgan: 「Wait! Don't shoot!!」	s04a	0087
S004_02	1	29	My soldiers were falling into a panic.	s04a	0088
S004_02	1	30	I raised my voice in hot haste.	s04a	0089
S004_02	1	31	My angry voice was erased by the bellow of my subordinates' gunshots.	s04a	0090
S004_02	1	32	5.56 millimeters were no match for an armored gun turtle.	s04a	0091
S004_02	1	33	Metallic noises were heard as the gun turtles morphed and pointed the nozzles of the phasor machine guns at my subordinates.	s04a	0092
S004_02	1	34	Flashes flying about. My subordinates' screams. It felt entirely like deja vu.	s04a	0093
S004_02	1	35	I quickly threw myself behind a piece of furniture.	s04a	0094
S004_02	1	36	As soon as the flashes that had killed my subordinates had stopped, an armed Naomi had suddenly appeared before my eyes.	s04a	0095
S004_02	1	37	Bohgan: 「Kuu!?」	s04a	0096
S004_02	1	38	And coming up from behind Naomi-----was Lieri.	s04a	0097
S004_02	1	39	It seems that the two had been hiding in the restroom from the get-go.	s04a	0098
S004_02	1	40	The situation was completely different from what I had validated from the hidden camera.	s04a	0099
S004_02	2	1	Becoming aware they were being observed by a camera, I guess they had shown us a different image, replacing it somehow.	s04a	0100
S004_02	2	2	In any case, I had been completely deceived by the two.	s04a	0101
S004_02	2	3	I stood up in front of Lieri and Naomi with a gun turtle at my back, raising both of my hands into the air.	s04a	0102
S004_02	2	4	Naomi: 「...hmph! The captain himself came, it's an honor」	s04a	0103
S004_02	2	5	Bohgan: 「………………」	s04a	0104
S004_02	2	6	Naomi: 「Go ahead. That way I can shoot you dead without thinking twice」	s04a	0105
S004_02	2	7	Naomi provoked me while still using her hands to manipulate the gun turtle.	s04a	0106
S004_02	2	8	I remained expressionless as I continued raising my hands that held a gun into the air.	s04a	0107
S004_02	2	9	Lieri: 「...I didn't expect you to be such a stupid man. I had thought you were a bit more clever than this」	s04a	0108
S004_02	2	10	Lieri spoke in a cool voice.	s04a	0109
S004_02	2	11	Bohgan: 「Pardon me...if I didn't live up to your expectations」	s04a	0110
S004_02	2	12	Lieri curved her mouth suddenly at my response.	s04a	0111
S004_02	2	13	Lieri: 「I am taking over by a Universal Federation charter, this warship is now under my command!!」	s04a	0112
S004_02	2	14	Lieri announced in a loud voice like that, smiling at me like she had lost her mind.	s04a	0113
S004_02	2	15	Lieri: 「Fufuu. I don't want to look at your useless form any more than this if possible, are you going to cooperate with me now?」	s04a	0114
S004_02	2	16	Bohgan: 「Kuuu...........!?」	s04a	0115
S004_02	2	17	I surveyed my surroundings with my hands still in the air.	s04a	0116
S004_02	2	18	A cord from the hidden camera was connected to a computer.	s04a	0117
S004_02	2	19	Bohgan: （It's as I thought...these conniving bitches）	s04a	0118
S004_02	2	20	One of the two was apparently experienced at hacking.....	s04a	0119
S004_02	2	21	No, perhaps both of them were..... I smiled bitterly all of a sudden.	s04a	0120
S004_02	2	22	Bohgan: 「...so that's why」	s04a	0121
S004_02	2	23	Bohgan: 「You said you're prosecuting the Neo Terrors' key figures. As might be expected, you've come prepared」	s04a	0122
S004_02	2	24	Naomi: 「Hey! Are you not going to cooperate!?」	s04a	0123
S004_02	2	25	Naomi, who was getting impatient, raised her voice.	s04a	0124
S004_02	2	26	Naomi: 「Let me point out that I can operate as many as four gun turtles at once」	s04a	0125
S004_02	2	27	Naomi: 「There is no possible chance of winning if any of you try to contend with me!」	s04a	0126
S004_02	2	28	Bohgan: 「Four at the same time...kukukuu, what a deadly prodigy you are...I give in. It is my loss」	s04a	0127
S004_02	2	29	Naomi: 「Now, throw away your gun nice and slowly!」	s04a	0128
S004_02	2	30	Naomi dipped her chin, seeming to give me an order.	s04a	0129
S004_02	2	31	Bohgan: 「Throw away...my gun?」	s04a	0130
S004_02	2	32	Naomi: 「I'm not going to ask you again」	s04a	0131
S004_02	2	33	Scowling at me, Naomi took a nefarious sounding tone with me.	s04a	0132
S004_02	2	34	Bohgan: 「Understood...」	s04a	0133
S004_02	2	35	Curling my lips wickedly, I tossed the gun I was holding to the floor.	s04a	0134
S004_02	2	36	Lieri: 「Wait!!?」	s04a	0135
S004_02	2	37	Naomi: 「-----ehh!?」	s04a	0136
S004_02	2	38	At that moment, Lieri raised her voice like she had noticed something. However, it was too late.	s04a	0137
S004_02	2	39	Coincidentally as my gun fell upon the floor, the door of the room shut and locked.	s04a	0138
S004_02	2	40	At the same time as that happened, a gas began spewing forcefully out of my uniform.	s04a	0139
S004_02	3	1	Lieri and Naomi covered their mouths and noses with their hands in a panic.	s04a	0140
S004_02	3	2	Lieri: 「This is!?」	s04a	0141
S004_02	3	3	Naomi: 「Kuu!? Youuuuuu! What the hell are you thinking!!」	s04a	0142
S004_02	3	4	Naomi's kick knocked into the right side of my face, blowing off my gaudiness.	s04a	0143
S004_02	3	5	Bohgan: 「.....fufufuu」	s04a	0144
S004_02	3	6	Fresh blood trickled down from the edge of my mouth as I got up laughing at the ordeal.	s04a	0145
S004_02	3	7	Bohgan: 「...you didn't take into count the hidden camera」	s04a	0146
S004_02	3	8	Lieri: 「Bo, Bohgan.....!?」	s04a	0147
S004_02	3	9	Naomi: 「...kuuu!?」	s04a	0148
S004_02	3	10	Bohgan: 「Tossing away my gun onto the floor was a signal」	s04a	0149
S004_02	3	11	While wiping the blood away with my arm, I gave a derisive smile.	s04a	0150
S004_02	3	12	Lieri: 「Ukuuuu...!? N, never... you sacrificed yourself...!?」	s04a	0151
S004_02	3	13	Lieri warped her face, looking to be in pain, worried about the gas she was breathing in.	s04a	0152
S004_02	3	14	Bohgan: 「Kukukuu, don't worry. It's only hypnotic gas」	s04a	0153
S004_02	3	15	The world swayed before me.	s04a	0154
S004_02	3	16	Having inhaled quite a lot of the gas, my consciousness grew hazy and I felt my field of vision begin to blur greatly.	s04a	0155
S004_02	3	17	Naomi: 「...uu, uuu...!?」	s04a	0156
S004_02	3	18	At last, Naomi was fainting.	s04a	0157
S004_02	3	19	The console in her hands tumbled to the floor and made a loud noise.	s04a	0158
S004_02	3	20	Lieri: 「N, Naomi...!? Kuu---!!」	s04a	0159
S004_02	3	21	Lieri, now reeling on her feet because of the gas, also seemed to be on the verge of collapsing, which went against the fearless expression she had on her face.	s04a	0160
S004_02	3	22	Lieri: 「.....hmph」	s04a	0161
S004_02	3	23	Bohgan: 「Smiling.....!?」	s04a	0162
S004_02	3	24	Gradually.	s04a	0163
S004_02	3	25	Gradually my consciousness faded.	s04a	0164
S004_02	3	26	The shape of Lieri bending her knees and slumping onto the floor faintly reflected in my now hazy field of vision.	s04a	0165
S004_02	3	27	I heard a sound far off in the distance.	s04a	0166
S004_02	3	28	My field of vision steadily grew darker.	s04a	0167
S004_02	3	29	Bohgan: 「...why did she smile............」	s04a	0168
S004_02	3	30	Feeling a little distraught, I fell upside down into a bottomless pit of black.	s04a	0169
S004_02	3	31	SALTAR: S005A
