S006_MP3_END	1	1	The 2nd morning of the voyage.	s06a	0001
S006_MP3_END	1	2	I was in good humor.	s06a	0002
S006_MP3_END	1	3	An unbelievable excitement ran throughout my body every time I thought about yesterday.	s06a	0003
S006_MP3_END	1	4	Thinking about how Lieri and Naomi were having another personality crafted for them in secret somewhere uplifted my feelings no matter how much patience I had.	s06a	0004
S006_MP3_END	1	5	Breakfast came around before long.	s06a	0005
S006_MP3_END	1	6	As I waited with my senior officers in the dining hall, the two subjects came into view, walking in a composed manner.	s06a	0006
S006_MP3_END	1	7	Bohgan: 「A very good morning to you. Commander Bishop. Major Naomi」	s06a	0007
S006_MP3_END	1	8	Lieri: 「Good morning, Major Bohgan」	s06a	0008
S006_MP3_END	1	9	Naomi: 「……………………」	s06a	0009
S006_MP3_END	1	10	Lieri returned an elegant, graceful smile.	s06a	0010
S006_MP3_END	1	11	Naomi, on the other hand, kept silent, only nodding, looking to be sullen and in a bad mood.	s06a	0011
S006_MP3_END	1	12	Naturally, the two had no recollection of being assaulted by us, thanks to the manipulations of their memories of last night.	s06a	0012
S006_MP3_END	1	13	Bohgan: 「Did you have a good night's sleep, I wonder?」	s06a	0013
S006_MP3_END	1	14	Lieri: 「Yes...you could say that, but I feel a little heavy-headed, you know」	s06a	0014
S006_MP3_END	1	15	While also still smiling elegantly, Lieri frowned a little as she said that.	s06a	0015
S006_MP3_END	1	16	Bohgan: 「We can't have that, now can we. Can you tell me what's wrong?」	s06a	0016
S006_MP3_END	1	17	Lieri: 「I'm fine. It's nothing serious」	s06a	0017
S006_MP3_END	1	18	Lieri interrupted my words on account of needlessly worrying too much about it.	s06a	0018
S006_MP3_END	1	19	Naomi: 「……………………」	s06a	0019
S006_MP3_END	1	20	You too look like you have a heavy head, Naomi.....	s06a	0020
S006_MP3_END	1	21	Oh well, it's no wonder.	s06a	0021
S006_MP3_END	1	22	In any case, it's so that we can tamper with your minds without you realizing it...fufufu.	s06a	0022
S006_MP3_END	1	23	I ate breakfast while chattering nonstop to the two who looked languid in some way.	s06a	0023
S006_MP3_END	1	24	It was a usual custom for the captain to share breakfast together with VIP's on a warship.	s06a	0024
S006_MP3_END	1	25	They looked so ill that perhaps they would throw up what they were eating.	s06a	0025
S006_MP3_END	1	26	Whether or not they felt that it was wrong not to honor old traditions, they did not refuse to eat together with me.	s06a	0026
S006_MP3_END	1	27	However, I was expecting a cold refusal from today on in wanting to have dinner in their own room, but.....	s06a	0027
S006_MP3_END	1	28	At any rate---I stole a secret glance at their state.	s06a	0028
S006_MP3_END	1	29	Their attitudes had really not changed from yesterday.	s06a	0029
S006_MP3_END	1	30	Lieri was speaking to me in a mature manner and overflowing with composure, and Naomi was being much too authoritative and arrogant to me.	s06a	0030
S006_MP3_END	1	31	Of course, this did not mean that the brainwashing had failed.	s06a	0031
S006_MP3_END	1	32	The brainwashing would take effect in time.	s06a	0032
S006_MP3_END	1	33	And during that time as well, the girls would be subconsciously creating new personalities.	s06a	0033
S006_MP3_END	1	34	"Nano machines" had been embedded in the two last night, and were expected to be working to destroy their personality at even this very moment.	s06a	0034
S006_MP3_END	1	35	Lieri: 「...Major? Could I ask you something?」	s06a	0035
S006_MP3_END	1	36	Bohgan: 「...ehh?」	s06a	0036
S006_MP3_END	1	37	With me watching her, Lieri turned to me, looking doubtful about something.	s06a	0037
S006_MP3_END	1	38	Bohgan: 「Ahh...no, by all means」	s06a	0038
S006_MP3_END	1	39	Lieri: 「Because of the scuffle yesterday, we still didn't get to inspect your warship and I wanted the captain to guide us. I too will be joining you today」	s06a	0039
S006_MP3_END	1	40	Hmm...they're not still trying to lay spying devices, are they?	s06a	0040
S006_MP3_END	2	1	Bohgan: 「But of course. I'll be sure to guide you around personally」	s06a	0041
S006_MP3_END	2	2	I acknowledged Lieri's request while pretending to be calm about it.	s06a	0042
S006_MP3_END	2	3	Lieri: 「And that Major...the talk we had」	s06a	0043
S006_MP3_END	2	4	Bohgan: 「Yes...?」	s06a	0044
S006_MP3_END	2	5	Lieri: 「Have you thought about my proposal, I wonder」	s06a	0045
S006_MP3_END	2	6	Lieri broached the threat she made yesterday while revealing a tantalizingly sexy smile.	s06a	0046
S006_MP3_END	2	7	Bohgan: 「Yes」	s06a	0047
S006_MP3_END	2	8	Lieri: 「I see. And...your response?」	s06a	0048
S006_MP3_END	2	9	Bohgan: 「Yes. I give you my word that the two of you will reach Earth without any problems from me」	s06a	0049
S006_MP3_END	2	10	I spoke while intently watching the two with a firm facial expression.	s06a	0050
S006_MP3_END	2	11	Lieri: 「……………………」	s06a	0051
S006_MP3_END	2	12	Lieri stared directly into my eyes like she was trying to see through that facial expression.	s06a	0052
S006_MP3_END	2	13	I returned a smile to her, while being extra cautious not to let her discern anything.	s06a	0053
S006_MP3_END	2	14	My goal was not to hinder their trip to Earth.	s06a	0054
S006_MP3_END	2	15	Merely to---give them a fresh start on life once they got off on Earth.	s06a	0055
S006_MP3_END	2	16	So, with that in mind, I wasn't necessarily lying to them at all.	s06a	0056
S006_MP3_END	2	17	Bohgan: 「I have to tell you once more my uneasiness」	s06a	0057
S006_MP3_END	2	18	I seemed to break the ice timidly.	s06a	0058
S006_MP3_END	2	19	Bohgan: 「I am not at all a spy working for the Neo Terrors. I just wanted to emphasize that point again」	s06a	0059
S006_MP3_END	2	20	Lieri: 「……………………」	s06a	0060
S006_MP3_END	2	21	Lieri narrowed her lovely eyes as I said that, but in the next moment a smile formed on her lips.	s06a	0061
S006_MP3_END	2	22	Lieri: 「You have wise judgment, don't you, Major」	s06a	0062
S006_MP3_END	2	23	Bohgan: 「Yes Ma'am!」	s06a	0063
S006_MP3_END	2	24	Bohgan: 「If I escort you two to Earth safely, you'll erase all doubts you had about me」	s06a	0064
S006_MP3_END	2	25	Lieri: 「Fufuu...we'll see, won't we. But, are you able to live up to that promise even now」	s06a	0065
S006_MP3_END	2	26	Bohgan: 「...huh?」	s06a	0066
S006_MP3_END	2	27	Lieri: 「Will you give me access to the warship's computers? Naturally I have the same authority as the Major does」	s06a	0067
S006_MP3_END	2	28	Bohgan: 「Wh, what...!?」	s06a	0068
S006_MP3_END	2	29	Giving her access to the warship's computers was the equivalent to transferring full authority to her. In other words, she would have control over all systems.	s06a	0069
S006_MP3_END	2	30	Lieri: 「It's no problem if you aren't my enemy, right?」	s06a	0070
S006_MP3_END	2	31	Kuu...is that your aim. Be that as it may I could simply turn down her request, but she was a completely pretentious woman.	s06a	0071
S006_MP3_END	2	32	However, because the brainwashing systems were not connected to the main warship systems, there really wasn't anything that was harmful, but with her.....	s06a	0072
S006_MP3_END	2	33	SELECCIONAR 1: S006C
S006_MP3_END	2	34	SELECCIONAR 2: S006B
S006_MP3_END	2	35	No, that doesn't necessarily mean there won't be any problems.	s06a	0073
S006_MP3_END	2	36	Of course there was a possibility that various problems would arise in a situation where she was constantly prying into the warship's systems.	s06a	0074
S006_MP3_END	2	37	As for my decision, I have to try to refuse Lieri's request gently.	s06a	0075
S006_MP3_END	2	38	Bohgan: 「I'm very sorry, but Commander...」	s06a	0076
S006_MP3_END	2	39	Bohgan: 「Of course, according to military law, allowing a commander access to the warship's systems on a wish alone would be illegal and so...」	s06a	0077
S006_MP3_END	2	40	Lieri's eyes shined brightly momentarily at my words.	s06a	0078
S006_MP3_END	3	1	Lieri: 「I see...so, as I thought, you are coming to not trust me, I wonder」	s06a	0079
S006_MP3_END	3	2	Bohgan: 「No...but...」	s06a	0080
S006_MP3_END	3	3	Just then, Naomi thrust her way into the conversation in a bossy tone.	s06a	0081
S006_MP3_END	3	4	Naomi: 「Hey, is there something wrong?」	s06a	0082
S006_MP3_END	3	5	Bohgan: 「No, according to regulations.....」	s06a	0083
S006_MP3_END	3	6	Naomi: 「By some chance, are you devising some plot without us knowing, you Neo Terror dog!!」	s06a	0084
S006_MP3_END	3	7	Naomi made a gesture of taking out her gun as she shouted that out.	s06a	0085
S006_MP3_END	3	8	Tension ran through my officers gazing at a distance.	s06a	0086
S006_MP3_END	3	9	I raised a hand to my subordinates to control them.	s06a	0087
S006_MP3_END	3	10	Bohgan: 「……………………」	s06a	0088
S006_MP3_END	3	11	Naomi watched my face like that.	s06a	0089
S006_MP3_END	3	12	Naomi: 「I will ask you one more time, Major Bohgan」	s06a	0090
S006_MP3_END	3	13	Naomi: 「Are you going to cooperate with Mrs. Lieri, or not? Which is it!」	s06a	0091
S006_MP3_END	3	14	It was quite like she was threatening a highly ill reputed Neo Terror intelligence bureau. Should I give into such a brazen threat now?	s06a	0092
S006_MP3_END	3	15	SELECCIONAR 1: S006C
S006_MP3_END	3	16	Bohgan: 「Understood. Well then, I'll give the two of you access to the warship's systems」	s06a	0093
S006_MP3_END	3	17	Lieri and Naomi looked pleased as I said that.	s06a	0094
S006_MP3_END	3	18	Lieri: 「I think you have diligent judgment, Major Bohgan」	s06a	0095
S006_MP3_END	3	19	Lieri said calmly as she floated an elegant smile.	s06a	0096
S006_MP3_END	3	20	Bohgan: 「I am grateful」	s06a	0097
S006_MP3_END	3	21	Lieri: 「Okay, well, could I implore you to guide us around the warship, I wonder」	s06a	0098
S006_MP3_END	3	22	As Lieri departed all of a sudden saying that, Naomi too silently followed behind her.	s06a	0099
S006_MP3_END	3	23	Bohgan: 「Yes. Well then, let's go」	s06a	0100
S006_MP3_END	3	24	I breathed a sigh of relief while a smile too filled my face as I began guiding the two around the warship.	s06a	0101
S006_MP3_END	3	25	And gradually, I led them around all of the facilities with the exception of the captain's room.	s06a	0105
S006_MP3_END	3	26	Whether or not the two felt that it was unnatural to want to see the captain's room, they did not press me that far.	s06a	0106
S006_MP3_END	3	27	Bohgan: 「And the last is...here, the main bridge of the Jasant」	s06a	0107
S006_MP3_END	3	28	Spreading my hands as I said that, I showed them into the main bridge with a face full of self-confidence.	s06a	0108
S006_MP3_END	3	29	Lieri: 「As one would expect of a newly produced warship, isn't it. It's spacious considering it's Aredale class」	s06a	0109
S006_MP3_END	3	30	Naomi: 「...as far as level 5 phasor guns and ultra-long distance sensors. On top of the main armor, why arm a normal class cruiser so heavily?」	s06a	0110
S006_MP3_END	3	31	Bohgan: 「I only just upgraded the equipment last year. I heard they have begun development of a new type of hybrid "cruiser warship" to the model of this warship.」	s06a	0110
S006_MP3_END	3	32	Naomi: 「The firepower and armor of a battleship that travels so far, the speed of a normal cruiser... this warship is wasted by you」	s06a	0111
S006_MP3_END	3	33	I kept a friendly smile on my face, ignoring Naomi's insult.	s06a	0112
S006_MP3_END	3	34	At first, I had estimated about an hour to guide them around, but the two were enthusiastic about seeing the inside of the Jasant.	s06a	0113
S006_MP3_END	3	35	Naomi was using a handheld computer to carefully record everything. Especially our weapons and equipment.	s06a	0114
S006_MP3_END	3	36	I observed them closely to make sure they weren't setting spying devices, but I hadn't yet picked up anything suspicious.	s06a	0115
S006_MP3_END	3	37	However, it could be possible that they were somehow tricking my eyes into believing that.	s06a	0116
S006_MP3_END	3	38	Perhaps...they were thinking about setting the military operations room with something.......	s06a	0117
S006_MP3_END	3	39	While lightly bragging about the equipment on the warship to the two women officers, I pondered about what they could be up to in my mind.	s06a	0118
S006_MP3_END	3	40	And so, it, after all, took all day to show them around the warship with the onset of evening hours.	s06a	0119
S006_MP3_END	4	1	That night.	s06a	0120
S006_MP3_END	4	2	While growing more and more anxious of the events that were going to occur this evening, I kept on top of the mission at hand in the captain's room.	s06a	0121
S006_MP3_END	4	3	Subordinate: 「Captain」	s06a	0122
S006_MP3_END	4	4	And it was there my subordinates were turning up to report their surveillance of Lieri and Naomi.	s06a	0123
S006_MP3_END	4	5	Bohgan: 「...how was it?」	s06a	0124
S006_MP3_END	4	6	Subordinate: 「Yes. It's as suspected, it looks like they're repeatedly accessing it」	s06a	0125
S006_MP3_END	4	7	Bohgan: 「...I wonder」	s06a	0126
S006_MP3_END	4	8	According to what my subordinate said, they are investigating the warship by accessing the main computer of the Jasant from a client machine in their room.	s06a	0127
S006_MP3_END	4	9	I guess they were exercising their right of access without delay.....	s06a	0128
S006_MP3_END	4	10	Why the warship? What were they investigating? By no means are they...investigating the existence of a brainwashing lab!?	s06a	0129
S006_MP3_END	4	11	No, that would be impossible. There is no way anything could have leaked out about the existence of this brainwashing technology.	s06a	0130
S006_MP3_END	4	12	I began feeling gloomy, sensing I was trapped by their actions.	s06a	0131
S006_MP3_END	4	13	But, it wasn't like I was going to figure out what their purpose was no matter how much I thought about it.	s06a	0132
S006_MP3_END	4	14	Bohgan: 「...I must continue doing nothing else but keeping a close eye on them」	s06a	0133
S006_MP3_END	4	15	Making sure to warn myself of that, I looked at the clock unexpectedly while breathing a sigh.	s06a	0134
S006_MP3_END	4	16	10 minutes until 10 PM.	s06a	0135
S006_MP3_END	4	17	Bohgan: 「Well........it's precious brainwashing time」	s06a	0136
S006_MP3_END	4	18	I felt a wicked momentary glare lodge in my eyes.	s06a	0137
S006_MP3_END	4	19	Once again today, it wasn't necessary to fight like yesterday.	s06a	0138
S006_MP3_END	4	20	There would be an indication to Lieri and Naomi.....	s06a	0139
S006_MP3_END	4	21	When a certain signal was cast, their personality would switch into the more "convenient personality" that we had now created for them.	s06a	0140
S006_MP3_END	4	22	And that signal---	s06a	0141
S006_MP3_END	4	23	Looks good.	s06a	0142
S006_MP3_END	4	24	They'll be changing completely in 10 minutes, as the lights inside the warship changed color.	s06a	0143
S006_MP3_END	4	25	That was the switch that changed their personality.	s06a	0144
S006_MP3_END	4	26	However, it didn't meant that the nano machines embedded inside them could do everything.	s06a	0145
S006_MP3_END	4	27	The nano machines were just laying the foundation of the more "convenient personality".	s06a	0146
S006_MP3_END	4	28	Only "experience" could make that personality grow.	s06a	0147
S006_MP3_END	4	29	After being treated from an illness, rehabilitation was often needed to completely recover, rehabilitation was also needed after creating a new personality.	s06a	0148
S006_MP3_END	4	30	Extraordinarily lewd and cruel rehabilitation.	s06a	0149
S006_MP3_END	4	31	The lights inside the warship changed all at once.	s06a	0150
S006_MP3_END	4	32	The blue, blinking lights were on.	s06a	0151
S006_MP3_END	4	33	I waited patiently, reclining back calmly in a chair in the captain's room.	s06a	0152
S006_MP3_END	4	34	Before long, I knew that several clock-like footsteps would be heading this way.	s06a	0153
S006_MP3_END	4	35	My heartbeat sped up as I watched the entrance to the captain's room. I was excited just by imagining it.	s06a	0154
S006_MP3_END	4	36	And then, the door slid to the side, making a sound customary of Universal warships.	s06a	0155
S006_MP3_END	4	37	Lieri: 「Is there something I can do for you, I wonder? Major」	s06a	0156
S006_MP3_END	4	38	Naomi: 「……………………」	s06a	0157
S006_MP3_END	4	39	Lieri asked me in a clear voice.	s06a	0158
S006_MP3_END	4	40	Naomi scowled at me fixedly with a bad-tempered face.	s06a	0159
S006_MP3_END	5	1	Behind the two, a subordinate stood, having brought them this far.	s06a	0160
S006_MP3_END	5	2	Bohgan: 「I'm sorry to bother you like this」	s06a	0161
S006_MP3_END	5	3	Standing from my chair, I bowed to both of them.	s06a	0162
S006_MP3_END	5	4	Bohgan: 「But, I wanted to confirm something for just a minute, Commander... no......Lieri」	s06a	0163
S006_MP3_END	5	5	Lieri: 「……………………？」	s06a	0164
S006_MP3_END	5	6	Lieri: 「Confirm something...is there something wrong?」	s06a	0165
S006_MP3_END	5	7	Bohgan: 「Yes」	s06a	0166
S006_MP3_END	5	8	I continued speaking while watching Lieri and Naomi together.	s06a	0167
S006_MP3_END	5	9	Bohgan: 「I hate to be rude, but...」	s06a	0168
S006_MP3_END	5	10	My heart began beating faster.	s06a	0169
S006_MP3_END	5	11	Bohgan: 「Are you acquainted with "comforting duties", I wonder?」	s06a	0170
S006_MP3_END	5	12	Lieri: 「...ehh?」	s06a	0171
S006_MP3_END	5	13	Naomi: 「……………………」	s06a	0172
S006_MP3_END	5	14	Lieri: 「Of course. Beginning with the captain, I am to treat the sexual urges of the male crew; which is an essential duty as a woman officer, I think」	s06a	0173
S006_MP3_END	5	15	I turned to face Naomi this time.	s06a	0174
S006_MP3_END	5	16	Bohgan: 「Major......what about Naomi, I wonder?」	s06a	0175
S006_MP3_END	5	17	Naomi: 「...I, I know...why do you ask?」	s06a	0176
S006_MP3_END	5	18	Bohgan: 「All right」	s06a	0177
S006_MP3_END	5	19	I stared at the two.	s06a	0178
S006_MP3_END	5	20	Bohgan: 「Well then, I'm giving a comforting duty as captain... to you」	s06a	0179
S006_MP3_END	5	21	Lieri: 「……………………eh！？」	s06a	0180
S006_MP3_END	5	22	Naomi: 「……………………uu!」	s06a	0181
S006_MP3_END	5	23	Bohgan: 「Unfortunately...you are the only two women on this warship, aren't you」	s06a	0182
S006_MP3_END	5	24	Naomi: 「uuu.....u.....uuu.....」	s06a	0183
S006_MP3_END	5	25	Naomi blushed her cheeks as she watched me.	s06a	0184
S006_MP3_END	5	26	I melted in self-satisfaction at seeing these two cheeky woman soldiers' naive expressions for the first time.	s06a	0185
S006_MP3_END	5	27	Lieri: 「I see...well then, that can't be helped, can it」	s06a	0186
S006_MP3_END	5	28	In turn, Lieri answered me while giving her usual smile.	s06a	0187
S006_MP3_END	5	29	I withheld the desperate urge to want to burst into laughter. Naturally, "comforting duties" wasn't allowed in the Universal Federation.	s06a	0188
S006_MP3_END	5	30	Their brains had been altered to accept any kind of input so that, to them, it was obvious and reasonable.	s06a	0189
S006_MP3_END	5	31	Thus, coming from their experiences and memories, they wouldn't be suspicious of any wild ideas.	s06a	0190
S006_MP3_END	5	32	It was a lot like forcibly seducing the two by implanting them with perverted stories.	s06a	0191
S006_MP3_END	5	33	And the director was Donny Bohgan. It was so ridiculous that it made even me laugh.	s06a	0192
S006_MP3_END	5	34	Bohgan: 「I've been under so much stress lately」	s06a	0193
S006_MP3_END	5	35	Bohgan: 「The two of you are my guests on this warship, and I want your full cooperation to make sure everything goes smoothly」	s06a	0194
S006_MP3_END	5	36	Lieri: 「It's our duty as women officers of the Universal Federation. It would be my pleasure」	s06a	0195
S006_MP3_END	5	37	Bohgan: 「My thanks...and what about you Naomi?」	s06a	0196
S006_MP3_END	5	38	Naomi: 「Uu...u...of, of course... I would undertake a comforting duty... but...」	s06a	0197
S006_MP3_END	5	39	Naomi hesitated, dying her face more and more red.	s06a	0198
S006_MP3_END	5	40	Bohgan: 「...yes? But...what, Naomi?」	s06a	0199
S006_MP3_END	6	1	Naomi: 「N, no...uuu...!?」	s06a	0200
S006_MP3_END	6	2	Bohgan: 「……………………」	s06a	0201
S006_MP3_END	6	3	Lieri: 「...Naomi??」	s06a	0202
S006_MP3_END	6	4	Naomi: 「Uuu...!? Th, that duty..... Why is it...that I find it so detestable...u...」	s06a	0203
S006_MP3_END	6	5	I admired her secretly.	s06a	0204
S006_MP3_END	6	6	Lieri wasn't showing any suspicions and had completely accepted the abnormal situation as natural.	s06a	0205
S006_MP3_END	6	7	But Naomi, whether or not she was resisting her sense of reason somewhere deep inside; actually saying words of refusal was highly improbable if not impossible.	s06a	0206
S006_MP3_END	6	8	The brainwashing had been effective for sure. Even so, it was pointless to resist.	s06a	0207
S006_MP3_END	6	9	You...no, both of your brains are being altered, and no one is going to save you until the brainwashing has been completed.	s06a	0208
S006_MP3_END	6	10	Because this battleship---has become your floating prison in space.	s06a	0209
S006_MP3_END	6	11	Bohgan: 「.....Naomi, are you going to deny a noble comforting duty?」	s06a	0210
S006_MP3_END	6	12	I pressed a question upon Naomi in a strong tone, searching for a yes/no answer.	s06a	0211
S006_MP3_END	6	13	Naomi: 「Uu, uuu...!?」	s06a	0212
S006_MP3_END	6	14	Lieri: 「Naomi, what's wrong? Things like not obeying a captain's order, do you want a court-martial?」	s06a	0213
S006_MP3_END	6	15	Lieri, becoming my ally, admonished Naomi, feeling grateful of the unreasonably obscene duty.	s06a	0214
S006_MP3_END	6	16	Again, I held back the urge to burst into laughter at the sight of Lieri reprimanding an unhappy looking Naomi.	s06a	0215
S006_MP3_END	6	17	Naomi: 「...I, I'm sorry. I.....!?」	s06a	0216
S006_MP3_END	6	18	Bohgan: 「It's fine. Naomi」	s06a	0217
S006_MP3_END	6	19	I interrupted Naomi's words.	s06a	0218
S006_MP3_END	6	20	Bohgan: 「Today...just concentrate on comforting me」	s06a	0219
S006_MP3_END	6	21	Naomi: 「.....ehh!」	s06a	0220
S006_MP3_END	6	22	Bohgan: 「For the time being, you would like to watch to get familiar with the duty, right?」	s06a	0221
S006_MP3_END	6	23	Naomi: 「Th, that's...not it...!? Me, with you...!?」	s06a	0222
S006_MP3_END	6	24	Bohgan: 「A comforting duty, are you refusing to perform a noble duty of the Universal Federation?」	s06a	0223
S006_MP3_END	6	25	Naomi: 「N, no...!? Noo, kuu.......!?」	s06a	0224
S006_MP3_END	6	26	Lieri: 「Naomi!」	s06a	0225
S006_MP3_END	6	27	Naomi: 「Uuu.....!?」	s06a	0226
S006_MP3_END	6	28	Naomi: 「It's just that...I really hate... no...having...to do that......」	s06a	0227
S006_MP3_END	6	29	Lieri: 「Na, Naomi!?」	s06a	0228
S006_MP3_END	6	30	Lieri glared at Naomi with intense eyes.	s06a	0229
S006_MP3_END	6	31	Bohgan: 「Hahahaa! It doesn't matter, Lieri」	s06a	0230
S006_MP3_END	6	32	Bohgan: 「It's just that Naomi isn't accustomed to Universal warship duties. I guess I'll have to make sure to train her fully」	s06a	0231
S006_MP3_END	6	33	Naomi: 「...th, thank you for your help」	s06a	0232
S006_MP3_END	6	34	Naomi offered her gratitude to me with a bewildered look.	s06a	0233
S006_MP3_END	6	35	Lieri: 「I will try to help too, Major. Is that ok?」	s06a	0234
S006_MP3_END	6	36	Bohgan: 「Ahh, of course」	s06a	0235
S006_MP3_END	6	37	Of course, it's my plan enjoy myself with you too Lieri. In plenty, with that matured body of yours.	s06a	0236
S006_MP3_END	6	38	Bohgan: 「Well then, to start with...you use your mouth as a starting point」	s06a	0237
S006_MP3_END	6	39	Naomi: 「M, mouth...!?」	s06a	0238
S006_MP3_END	6	40	Bohgan: 「Lieri, could you give her an example, I wonder」	s06a	0239
S006_MP3_END	7	1	Lieri: 「Yes, no problem. Naomi, may I」	s06a	0240
S006_MP3_END	7	2	Naomi: 「Y, yes.....」	s06a	0241
S006_MP3_END	7	3	Sitting in my chair, the two came over and knelt down slowly in front of me.	s06a	0242
S006_MP3_END	7	4	Although they had yet to do anything to me, the excitement I felt was like I was already on the verge of climaxing.	s06a	0243
S006_MP3_END	7	5	So, in any case, the two of you are going to give me fellatio after this.....!	s06a	0244
S006_MP3_END	7	6	Moreover, they did not suspect a thing. My rock hard erection popped out as I pulled down my uniform trousers.	s06a	0245
S006_MP3_END	7	7	Lieri: 「.....wow」	s06a	0246
S006_MP3_END	7	8	Naomi: 「...uu, uuu...!?」	s06a	0247
S006_MP3_END	7	9	The two women officers spontaneously opened their eyes wide at exposing my penis before them.	s06a	0248
S006_MP3_END	7	10	Not to boast, but I was quite proud of my larger-than-normal size.	s06a	0249
S006_MP3_END	7	11	As a result of phimosis, my foreskin was too baggy and hid the lower part of my glans, and rugged veins popped out along the shaft, making it appear somewhat "majestic".	s06a	0250
S006_MP3_END	7	12	Bohgan: 「Well, Lieri. I beg of you」	s06a	0251
S006_MP3_END	7	13	Lieri: 「Yes, Major...」	s06a	0252
S006_MP3_END	7	14	As I said that, Lieri leaned increasingly forward between my legs.	s06a	0253
S006_MP3_END	7	15	Lieri: 「Naomi...please watch carefully」	s06a	0254
S006_MP3_END	7	16	Naomi: 「Y, yes...Ms. Lieri...」	s06a	0255
S006_MP3_END	7	17	That said, Lieri gently gripped my cock with her slender fingers.....	s06a	0256
S006_MP3_END	7	18	Ever so slowly, she brought her face closer and closer to my glans.......!!	s06a	0257
