PV01_301_A	1	1	Asagi: 「Eh, wa, waitt......nuuuuuh！！」	s09a	0303
PV01_301_A	1	2	Pig: 「Loook, I'm going in, I'm going in. Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhah, I've entered!」	s09a	0304
PV01_301_A	1	3	Without foreplay, Pig pushed in at once inside me.	s09a	0305
PV01_301_A	1	4	Asagi: 「Guuuuh! S, so suddenly.......u!」	s09a	0306
PV01_301_A	1	5	Pig: 「Oohhhh.....! It's tight, it's tight!」	s09a	0307
PV01_301_A	1	6	The tip of the penis slipped in without restraint.	s09a	0308
PV01_301_A	1	7	Asagi: 「Uahhhhh.....! Ahguuuuu........!!」	s09a	0309
PV01_301_A	1	8	Pig: 「Ooh, this is the best pussy I've ever had. Hahahaha, I can guarantee you that I'll be able to relish in the flavor of this ADN」	s09a	0310
PV01_301_A	1	9	My pubes collided with Pig, joining together profoundly, as my breathing was blocked at the sudden impact.	s09a	0311
PV01_301_A	1	10	Asagi: 「Hii, giii.......n! Ah, oooh........!」	s09a	0312
PV01_301_A	1	11	Not giving a damn about me, I raised a shriek, as Pig put it in a thrust all the way until the base, and commenced thrusting deeply.	s09a	0313
PV01_301_A	1	12	Pig: 「What, you'll immediately grow accustom. Since we are reproduction monkeys! Huh, elder sister of the ADN?」	s09a	0314
PV01_301_A	1	13	With burying the pointed tip of the glans, while being attracted to the idea of entering my womb, Pig enjoyed my body while saying self-torturing sarcasm.	s09a	0315
PV01_301_A	1	14	Asagi: 「Hii! Ahhhoohh!」	s09a	0317
PV01_301_A	1	15	Pig: 「Hey, in spite of no foreplay, it'll feel good, because we orcs secrete an aphrodisiac from the tip of our penises!!」	s09a	0318
PV01_301_A	1	16	Moaning pleasantly, as Pig said, from the tip of his cock, something hot was absorbed into the insides of my vagina, making my body becoming hot.	s09a	0319
PV01_301_A	1	17	This is the reproduction monkey's...... No, or else it's because of the restructuring by Oboro?	s09a	0320
PV01_301_A	1	18	Not knowing the cause, I raised my voice in reaction to the pleasant feelings each time he joined with me.	s09a	0321
PV01_301_A	1	19	Spreading my pussy, I felt overwhelmed by the vehement foreign sensations with the pleasant feelings of being rubbed with the cock.	s09a	0322
PV01_301_A	1	20	Asagi: 「Uuu! Th, the warts, the warts areaahh.......!」	s09a	0323
PV01_301_A	1	21	Pig: 「Nn, do you realize? The warts are rubbing the flesh of your pussy.....is it good?」	s09a	0324
PV01_301_A	1	22	Asagi: 「Kuuhii……！ Ho, ohhahhhhh........u!」	s09a	0325
PV01_301_A	1	23	As Pig stated, the rugged warts on his penis rubbed intensely against the flesh of my vagina that coiled around it.	s09a	0326
PV01_301_A	1	24	Asagi: 「Kufuu…！ Ooh, ohuuuuuuuohuu……！」	s09a	0327
PV01_301_A	1	25	The vibration that was transmitted as far as my depths together with the taking in and out of his penis, were like electric shocks that shook the flesh of my vagina.	s09a	0328
PV01_301_A	1	26	Asagi: 「Nnn.....u, Ihiii」	s09a	0329
PV01_301_A	1	27	My womb, by itself, was contracting, as I unintentionally let leak a wet moaning.	s09a	0330
PV01_301_A	1	28	Pig: 「Your sensitivity is good. Maa, it's naturally because you're eating my penis」	s09a	0331
PV01_301_A	1	29	While breathing words full of self-confidence, Pig relished in the sensation and texture of the flesh of my pussy many times over.	s09a	0332
PV01_301_A	1	30	Asagi: 「Fumuuuu, ahhh........u！！」	s09a	0333
PV01_301_A	1	31	I came to my senses for a moment with Pig's ugly, slackened face.	s09a	0334
PV01_301_A	1	32	Asagi: （Me.....now, the sensations........!）	s09a	0335
PV01_301_A	1	33	Oboro: 「Fufuu……♪」	s09a	0336
PV01_301_A	1	34	Oboro's scorn was heard. I guess, perhaps for a moment, the hypnotism was untied.	s09a	0337
PV01_301_A	1	35	Oboro watched me while floating a smile, from beginning to end, at being raped by Pig.	s09a	0338
PV01_301_A	1	36	Pig: 「Ooh, ooh, ooh.....! It's really packing in tightly, you're truly a good woman, Asagii, the best!!」	s09a	0339
PV01_301_A	1	37	Addressing me like a close friend, he indulged in only the pleasure of me.	s09a	0340
PV01_301_A	1	38	Pig continued to nail me with enthuisasm, increasing with my insides his wart-covered penis.	s09a	0341
PV01_301_A	1	39	Asagi: 「Hm, hmmph! I'm glad you're speaking so well of me....... Muohhhh!?」	s09a	0342
PV01_301_A	1	40	Suddenly, my spirit seemed to go mad, as pleasure assaulted me.	s09a	0343
PV01_301_A	2	1	Asagi: 「O, Oboroo!! Hypnotizing m, me........」	s09a	0344
PV01_301_A	2	2	Again, Oboro was putting hypnotism on me. working my spirit, in order to make it irresistable to be a prisoner of Pig's cock.	s09a	0345
PV01_301_A	2	3	Oboro: 「What? Aren't you just being a dirty little bitch?」	s09a	0346
PV01_301_A	2	4	Oboro stubbornly played innocent.	s09a	0347
PV01_301_A	2	5	Asagi: 「Kuuu, Oboro.....k, kill you!!」	s09a	0348
PV01_301_A	2	6	Anger with pleasant feelings, both sides perpetrated and played with my body.	s09a	0349
PV01_301_A	2	7	Asagi: 「V, violently like that! Kuuu! Softer, do it softer, nnnnn!!!!!」	s09a	0350
PV01_301_A	2	8	Pig: 「Haa, is this the same Asagi who picked on us up until now? You're going to take it hard because you're only a bitch, isn't that right」	s09a	0351
PV01_301_A	2	9	Pig's wart-covered penis repeatedly expanded and swelled, entwining with the flesh of my vagina and the cum that was overflowing inside.	s09a	0352
PV01_301_A	2	10	Pig: 「The finest pussy from this bitch ADN Asagi. I'm not rubbing my warts firmly enough, ohraa!」	s09a	0353
PV01_301_A	2	11	Asagi: 「Fuhiiiiiiiiii！！！」	s09a	0354
PV01_301_A	2	12	With the vivid rubbing sensations, stretching the flesh of my vagina at once, a flash of lightning ran through my mind momentarily.	s09a	0357
PV01_301_A	2	13	Pig: 「Hehehehe, is it good? Enjoy yourself and forget about how disgusting we are, even if you are a proud ADN, because after all, you're just a dirty bitch」	s09a	0358
PV01_301_A	2	14	Asagi: 「Y, you're annoying! Your social standing is that of a squalid shit reproduction monkey..........aahohh!」	s09a	0359
PV01_301_A	2	15	Pig: 「It's useless to pretend to be tough」	s09a	0360
PV01_301_A	2	16	Pig: 「Asagi from earlier, got soaking wet from thinking about relishing in my splendid cock, my wart covered cock!!」	s09a	0361
PV01_301_A	2	17	Asagi: 「L, liee, nnn……！！」	s09a	0362
PV01_301_A	2	18	Pig's frivolous talk was without rashness.	s09a	0363
PV01_301_A	2	19	Asagi: （Th, the sensations, me.....it's a lie..... It's not right or wrong, it's because of the restructuring by Oboro; it's cause of the orc's aphrodisiacs!）	s09a	0364
PV01_301_A	2	20	In spite of being exposed by acts of rape, for some reason, my genitals were showing furious and intense reactions.	s09a	0365
PV01_301_A	2	21	Asagi: 「Nnuuu! Nuuu.......!」	s09a	0366
PV01_301_A	2	22	Pig: 「Ooh, you're tightening up!! You want it so much? I'll give you my rich semen!! Kekekeeke」	s09a	0367
PV01_301_A	2	23	Although unpleasant feelings and fear was being felt, moreover, in spite of that, my body was going into ecstasy, relishing the sensation of Pig's grotesque genitals.	s09a	0368
PV01_301_A	2	24	Asagi: 「N, no, whyy.......n why, your semenn！！」	s09a	0369
PV01_301_A	2	25	The fact my body had been restructured into debauchery by Oboro and the hypnotism making my sexual desires clump up in my body...	s09a	0370
PV01_301_A	2	26	Pig: 「Kukukuu.....What, don't hate me so much, we're treating Asagi so cruelly because our cocks are so hard like this」	s09a	0371
PV01_301_A	2	27	Orc: 「Holy shit, I'm just itching to rape youu！！」	s09a	0372
PV01_301_A	2	28	The other orcs crowded around and accosted me.	s09a	0373
PV01_301_A	2	29	Asagi: 「S, shut up……！ Reproduction monkeys！！ You're trash, you're shit！！ Ahhhhhooohh！！！」	s09a	0374
PV01_301_A	2	30	Pig: 「So your mouth seems to say, but your mouth down here isn't saying that, it's drooling endlessly, and pressing hard on mee!!」	s09a	0375
PV01_301_A	2	31	Asagi: 「Kuuu....w, whatt! Ah, ahhhh！！」	s09a	0376
PV01_301_A	2	32	I resisted with desperation, pushing aside the pleasant feelings.	s09a	0377
PV01_301_A	2	33	Oboro: 「I'm losing patience, be honest with yourself. This is more than you deserve」	s09a	0378
PV01_301_A	2	34	Asagi: 「Hii……！？」	s09a	0379
PV01_301_A	2	35	Oboro: 「It's okay to be honest. Tell me that cock is making you feel good. As an ADN too, tell me you feel good like the whore that you are, fufufuu」	s09a	0380
PV01_301_A	2	36	Pig: 「Ooh, does it feel good like this, my pet. I'm going to treat Asagi fully to my juice」	s09a	0381
PV01_301_A	2	37	Asagi: 「Kuu.......! What are you saying? What are you, an idiot? I don't want to feel anything......! Take it out, the dirty semen of a reproduction monkey.......! 」	s09a	0382
PV01_301_A	2	38	Pig: 「Heh, does it feel good? I'll put it out with seriousness.....hehehee」	s09a	0383
PV01_301_A	2	39	Asagi: 「S, stop it, that sort of.....!」	s09a	0389
PV01_301_A	2	40	Pig: 「Now, I wonder if raping you in seriousness will make you pregnant」	s09a	0390
PV01_301_A	3	1	Asagi: 「Pregnant!? S, stop it, stop........」	s09a	0391
PV01_301_A	3	2	Pig: 「Ohh! I'm cumming!! Asagi is also feeling it growing in seriousness」	s09a	0392
PV01_301_A	3	3	Asagi: 「Ahhhhh, ahguuu!」	s09a	0393
PV01_301_A	3	4	Spitting out a curse, Pig's waist ran into and pierced my abdomen	s09a	0394
PV01_301_A	3	5	Asagi: 「ihiiiiii！？」	s09a	0397
PV01_301_A	3	6	Caught in the flesh of my vagina were the swelling warts, I let leak a lovely voice unintentionally.	s09a	0398
PV01_301_A	3	7	Asagi: 「It's, it's no goodd……！！」	s09a	0399
PV01_301_A	3	8	The flesh of my pussy trembled with pleasant feelings, my womb was squirming inside, feeling intensely fearful.	s09a	0400
PV01_301_A	3	9	Pig: 「How is it, the feelings like this, ohhhhhh!」	s09a	0401
PV01_301_A	3	10	Asagi: 「Guuuuuu! Like this, like this........!」	s09a	0402
PV01_301_A	3	11	Violating me audaciously with his cock, his semen was going to secrete at an involuntary target, as fluids scattered into the place we were connected, frothing over.	s09a	0404
PV01_301_A	3	12	Pig: 「Is it good, this must be goodahhh!?」	s09a	0405
PV01_301_A	3	13	Asagi: 「Uuuu! Not at alll, reproduction monkey, reproductionuuuuu!」	s09a	0406
PV01_301_A	3	14	Pig: 「I'm going to discharge the persuavie power of my drooling liquid!! My cock is your favorite habit!」	s09a	0407
PV01_301_A	3	15	Asagi: 「Kuhiiiii! No, you're wrong, you're absolutely wrong!」	s09a	0408
PV01_301_A	3	16	With the words that were contrary, I stirred up moral courage in anger, but churning inside my pussy, I felt furiously pleasant feelings.	s09a	0409
PV01_301_A	3	17	Asagi: （It's, it's mortifying......! It's not even like these guys are human......!）	s09a	0410
PV01_301_A	3	18	Pig: 「Very soon, very soon, the aphrodisacs are going to settle in that are packed into spots in my semen.......!」	s09a	0411
PV01_301_A	3	19	Pig's cock made love to me repeatedly. Although unwilling, these pleasant feelings he's giving me are genuine.	s09a	0412
PV01_301_A	3	20	Asagi: 「It's, useless……！」	s09a	0413
PV01_301_A	3	21	Pig: 「What do you mean it's useless!? I'm raping you, I order you to be proud, this bitch!!」	s09a	0414
PV01_301_A	3	22	Asagi: 「Uuu, kuhiuu.....! Already......it's, hehhhh!!」	s09a	0415
PV01_301_A	3	23	;※だへぇええ！！＝駄目ぇ！！	s09a	0416
PV01_301_A	3	24	And then I was finally engulfed in a wave of pleasure.	s09a	0417
PV01_301_A	3	25	Pig: 「Uooohhhhhhh! Cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming inside you!! Look, I'm pregnating you!!!」	s09a	0418
PV01_301_A	3	26	Asagi: 「Stop itt!! Iggu!! Pleaseee!! It's horrible! Pregancy, nooahhhhhhhhhhhh!!!」	s09a	0419
PV01_301_A	3	27	Not lending an ear to my words, Pig pushed against the opening of my womb with skill, as the tip of the glans swelled in growth.	s09a	0420
PV01_301_A	3	28	Pig: 「It's coming, it's coming, it's cominggooooh!! Pressing down! I've decided to give it to you hard in your pussy!! I'm making you pregnant ohhhh!!」	s09a	0421
PV01_301_A	3	29	Asagi: 「Ehgooh! Cumming, cumming!! S, stop it, hehhhhhhhhhh!!」	s09a	0422
PV01_301_A	3	30	Pig: 「Coming, coming, coming, coming...........fugahhh!!」	s09a	0423
PV01_301_A	3	31	All of a sudden it was at an end, the glans convulsed and pushed inside, and in the next moment, seething semen spurted out savagely into my womb.	s09a	0424
PV01_301_A	3	32	Asagi: 「Hebuu…………！？」	s09a	0425
PV01_301_A	3	33	Buboo! Goboboboo! Bobyurororoo!!	s09a	0426
PV01_301_A	3	34	Asagi: 「Ohaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhh!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!」	s09a	0427
PV01_301_A	3	35	The dense, dirty fluid was entirely like a solid state and was pumped into my womb directly, as sparks scattered, blue and while in my mind.	s09a	0428
PV01_301_A	3	36	Pig: 「Gugou! Gou......! Gogaahhhhhhh!! Ooh! Uoohhhh! Ohhohhohhhhh!!」	s09a	0429
PV01_301_A	3	37	The brute raised a war cry as Pig's penis was deeply embedded in me, repeatedly ejaculating explosively and pushing up many times at my uterus.	s09a	0430
PV01_301_A	3	38	Asagi: 「Uhi!? Hiahh! Aaahhh......!! Take it, outtttttttt!」	s09a	0431
PV01_301_A	3	39	The sticky, glutinous sperm rushed up into my womb, accelerating inside, as my body raised up in a shriek.	s09a	0432
PV01_301_A	3	40	Asagi: 「It's hott......u! Oohoohoohh, it's hottttttttt........u!」	s09a	0433
PV01_301_A	4	1	Ejaculating in my body made me convulse, my reasons and intentions utterly gone. The force of the pleasant feelings attacked and beat me, making me breathless.	s09a	0434
PV01_301_A	4	2	Asagi: 「Hyaa.......! Ahhe.......!! Ohahh...........!!」	s09a	0435
PV01_301_A	4	3	Pig: 「Uohhhu, I came, I came........! Holy shit I put out a lot, look at that!」	s09a	0458
PV01_301_A	4	4	At last releasing with force, it lightly churned inside my pussy as his cock weakened.	s09a	0459
PV01_301_A	4	5	Asagi: （Th, this guy, is truly trying to get me pregnant......）	s09a	0460
PV01_301_A	4	6	Pig: 「That's right, since I really filed you up like this, I want some words of gratitude, since I'll be your future husband」	s09a	0461
PV01_301_A	4	7	Asagi: 「Wha, what are you saying, that tone.......nnuuuu!」	s09a	0462
PV01_301_A	4	8	Pig: 「Hey, every drop of our semen is valuable, it has the best aphrodisacs, maa, if you use us like a brat, since it's our sole purpose to train.」	s09a	0463
PV01_301_A	4	9	Asagi: 「Y, you're annoying.......! Shut up, this brute of a reproduction monkeyy！！」	s09a	0464
PV01_301_A	4	10	Pig: 「What a cruel manner of speaking, huh Madam. Saying those sorts of things」	s09a	0465
PV01_301_A	4	11	Pig spoke casually to Oboro, watching with detachment.	s09a	0466
PV01_301_A	4	12	Oboro: 「Oh, bad girl. with all the trouble he went through to fill you with his valuable sperm, not one word of thanks...」	s09a	0467
PV01_301_A	4	13	Asagi: 「What, that sort of thing!! Request........ ah........ it's」	s09a	0468
PV01_301_A	4	14	Again, my senses became hazy.	s09a	0469
PV01_301_A	4	15	It was Oboro's hypnotism.	s09a	0470
PV01_301_A	4	16	Asagi: 「O, Obo...ro.........how far, c, cowardice.....??」	s09a	0471
PV01_301_A	4	17	Oboro: 「Cowardice!? I just don't want a bitch that doesn't have any manners, fufufufufu」	s09a	0472
PV01_301_A	4	18	Oboro floated a scornful laugh.	s09a	0473
PV01_301_A	4	19	Oboro: 「Okay, say it. Maybe he'll become a future papa, with a vulgar reproduction monkey of an orc.......」	s09a	0474
PV01_301_A	4	20	Asagi: （Bullshit......Oboro you fucker.....）	s09a	0475
PV01_301_A	4	21	Baring teeth, I resisted the hypnotism.	s09a	0476
PV01_301_A	4	22	Oboro: 「Pig, order this woman, once again to thank you」	s09a	0477
PV01_301_A	4	23	Pig: 「Y, yes, Madam. Look, I filled your womb with many of my children, tell me how delighted you are to become a mother!!」	s09a	0478
PV01_301_A	4	24	Asagi: 「Uuu……u！」	s09a	0479
PV01_301_A	4	25	Asagi: （No, absolutely not!! With a guy like this........u!）	s09a	0480
PV01_301_A	4	26	Sensing the haziness of the hypnotism, although I was being made to say thanks, I was not able to suppress it with my seething anger.	s09a	0481
PV01_301_A	4	27	They aren't human, with a lower grade of demon sex monkeys, it wasn't funny that I was being made to say thanks for possibly becoming pregnant..	s09a	0482
PV01_301_A	4	28	Asagi: 「Kuuuuu......u! Th, th, thank........」	s09a	0483
PV01_301_A	4	29	Asagi: （No, I absolutely do not want to say it!!!）	s09a	0484
PV01_301_A	4	30	Pig: 「What's wrong? Give me thanks. we'll have absolutely adorable children」	s09a	0485
PV01_301_A	4	31	Due to Oboro's hynotism, I slowly raised my face...... No, if I raise my face	s09a	0487
PV01_301_A	4	32	Asagi: 「Gu......, th......thank......」	s09a	0488
PV01_301_A	4	33	Pig: 「I'm listening.......」	s09a	0489
PV01_301_A	4	34	Asagi: 「In my womb, filling me with your children....... Thank you」	s09a	0490
PV01_301_A	4	35	Asagi: 「My, pleasure is becoming distant...... I know......... gu, that I'll be overjoyed to become a mother........!!」	s09a	0491
PV01_301_A	4	36	The hypnotism at last weakened, as I said thanks blended with hatred and anger.	s09a	0492
PV01_301_A	4	37	Pig: 「I'm not pleased with the last part, but it's passing. I'll forgive you, hahahaaha!」	s09a	0493
PV01_301_A	4	38	Oboro: 「Although, the truth was that the end wasn't very good, You said proper thanks. You're a good child, aren't you, admirable♪」	s09a	0494
PV01_301_A	4	39	While listening to the orcs and Oboro sneering regularly in the training room, I shivered with disgrace, burning in my body.	s09a	0495
PV01_301_A	4	40	Pig: 「But, since we've been here, up until now this woman has displayed insignificant gratitude!」	s09a	0496
PV01_301_A	5	1	The orcs emulated that in their gestures, breathing words that matched the manner more and more.	s09a	0497
PV01_301_A	5	2	Asagi: 「Aah......!! I absolutely.........won't allow you......」	s09a	0498
PV01_301_A	5	3	I scowled at the orcs, shivering with anger and pleasant feelings.	s09a	0499
PV01_301_A	5	4	Pig: 「Hey, you still don't understand the situation. we're going to have sex with you until you crumble」	s09a	0500
PV01_301_A	5	5	With Pig's smile, the other orcs came towards me, running out of patience.	s09a	0501
PV01_301_A	5	6	Asagi: 「.....No! I'll kill you！！」	s09a	0502
PV01_301_A	5	7	I glared at the orcs in hot haste, but they did not stop and drew near.	s09a	0503
PV01_301_A	5	8	Pig: 「Shut up! Already, you're no longer an ADN, you're only a bitch who we're going to teach more amazing pleasure to!! Ohhahhh!!!!」	s09a	0504
PV01_301_A	5	9	Asagi: 「Uahh! S, stop it..........!」	s09a	0505
PV01_301_A	5	10	The four orcs all at once swooped down upon me.	s09a	0506
PV01_301_A	5	11	There entirely was nothing I could do in my frail form, and although I refused the mighty desires of the orcs, I was not able to oppose them.	s09a	0507
PV01_301_A	5	12	Orc: 「Buhiiiiiiiiiii……！」	s09a	0508
PV01_301_A	5	13	I was being held down by the four orcs with the exception of Pig.	s09a	0509
PV01_301_A	5	14	Straddling on top of an orc on the floor, an orc turned to my back, fitting to my asshole his grotesque, wart-covered cock.	s09a	0510
PV01_301_A	5	15	Asagi: 「Uah! Th, that place is........!!」	s09a	0511
PV01_301_A	5	16	Orc: 「Tasting you, tasting the tight ass and pussy of the strongest ADN」	s09a	0512
PV01_301_A	5	17	Orc: 「Ooh, the turning and pulling with elder brother Pig, and already you're whining, aren't you, this ADN's wet, wet pussy is oohh!!」	s09a	0513
PV01_301_A	5	18	Asagi: 「Gahh!!! Ahguuuuuu!?」	s09a	0514
PV01_301_A	5	19	Asagi: (W, without warning.........u!）	s09a	0515
PV01_301_A	5	20	Without foreplay again, forcible insertions pierced the interior of my body.	s09a	0516
PV01_301_A	5	21	Asagi: 「Kaha.......u! Ah......! Ah......!?」	s09a	0517
PV01_301_A	5	22	I took the sudden attacks, surpressing my body's shivering with a climax with all of my might.	s09a	0519
PV01_301_A	5	23	Asagi: 「Guah, ahhhhhhu! So suddenly like that......n! It, it's inhuman!!」	s09a	0520
PV01_301_A	5	24	Orc: 「Hehehee, your ass and pussy are accustom to that, aren't they. Not to speak of the orcs not being human, don't you think?」	s09a	0521
PV01_301_A	5	25	The orc raped my and grated against my anus, and while the the warts spread out into my rectum, I spoke.	s09a	0522
PV01_301_A	5	26	Asagi: 「What, ........ah, ahhhhh!?」	s09a	0523
PV01_301_A	5	27	Orc: 「Look, it seems your mouth is lonely, suck my cock and lick and taste it with that cute mouth and tongue of yours!!」	s09a	0524
PV01_301_A	5	28	An orc turned to my front, holding out his wart-covered cock and jutting out his chest, coercing me to service him with my tongue.	s09a	0525
PV01_301_A	5	29	Asagi: 「.......Peroo......re.......pero, chyu.......」	s09a	0526
PV01_301_A	5	30	Oboro's hypnotism seemed to be in effect as I was called to obediently crawl my tongue along the sides of his warts.	s09a	0527
PV01_301_A	5	31	Asagi: 「Chyumuu......nn, nhaa......haa, haa........」	s09a	0528
PV01_301_A	5	32	Orc: 「Bu, buhi, buhihi, that's good. The best. This ADN Asagi feels like tasting my penis.......... kaa, you can't resist it, can you!!」	s09a	0529
PV01_301_A	5	33	Asagi: 「Reroo, re, chyuu, nn, fuuu......hamuuu, chyubuu, jyuu, jyumuu,.....jyuuu....... jyuroroo」	s09a	0530
PV01_301_A	5	34	Right after, I was servicing another with a hand job.	s09a	0531
PV01_301_A	5	35	Orc: 「Hand, your hand, it feels good. this, this slender hand and arm, what a naughty girl you are with us..........!」	s09a	0532
PV01_301_A	5	36	The orcs, so to clear away the many years of resentment that they took from me, began violating my mind.	s09a	0533
PV01_301_A	5	37	Asagi: 「Ah dir, dirty nn！？」	s09a	0534
PV01_301_A	5	38	My diaphragm trembled. while my restraints sounded with a clatter, my four limbs began dancing haphazardly.	s09a	0535
PV01_301_A	5	39	Asagi: 「Nuuuuu！！」	s09a	0536
PV01_301_A	5	40	For the first time, a sensation sprouted in my anus, indulging in it being spread out forcibly.	s09a	0537
PV01_301_A	6	1	It was almost painful to breathe. But, it was itchy..... I was feeling a need of that itch being scratched more.	s09a	0538
PV01_301_A	6	2	Asagi: （Why am I sensing this rape with an orc in my ass?）	s09a	0539
PV01_301_A	6	3	From the sheer unpleasantness of being raped by orcs, I was disgusted with the sensations of becoming a filthy harlot wanting pleasant feelings and sexual desires.	s09a	0540
PV01_301_A	6	4	Asagi: 「Lie, a lie, this ehh.......！？」	s09a	0541
PV01_301_A	6	5	The orcs peered at me with light smiles at the bewilderment on my face with the sudden change of sensations.	s09a	0542
PV01_301_A	6	6	Orc: 「The aphrodisiacs secreted from the penis of elder brother Pig are having an earnest effect...... maa, maybe the rest of us will hasten them......buhihihihi」	s09a	0543
PV01_301_A	6	7	Orc: 「Your pussy and ass that are being screwed have begun to absorb the aphrodisiacs in our cocks.......Bihii!」	s09a	0544
PV01_301_A	6	8	Asagi: 「Ngu!? Gufuuuu!」	s09a	0545
PV01_301_A	6	9	The orc struck me with his waist, going through me at once into my inner womb where Pig had ejaculated.	s09a	0546
PV01_301_A	6	10	Asagi: 「Ooh……nn！」	s09a	0547
PV01_301_A	6	11	Even I was astonished to the extent that I became aware of revealing a spicy voice, chewing my lips in hot haste obstructed that.	s09a	0548
PV01_301_A	6	12	Asagi: 「Kuu, kuuuu……」	s09a	0549
PV01_301_A	6	13	The cocks were giving me pleasure conveying to my brain pleasant feeling sensations that more and more I fought to endure.	s09a	0550
PV01_301_A	6	14	Asagi: （It, it feels good........n！）	s09a	0551
PV01_301_A	6	15	With not believing it, my body was being exploited of the intense sexual feelings from the sexual acts the orcs were carrying out.	s09a	0552
PV01_301_A	6	16	My improper body was being destroyed of its armor of my thoroughly trained mind, getting addicted to the orc's aphrodisiacs and the restructed body.	s09a	0553
PV01_301_A	6	17	Orc: 「That's a good reaction. This looking down on us like trash, we're unconcerned about breaking you with 2, 3 of our bones, that it Asagi?」	s09a	0554
PV01_301_A	6	18	Orc: 「Buhi, the same, I guess all ADN are the same, aren't they, mere female pigs.......」	s09a	0555
PV01_301_A	6	19	Orc: 「Buhihi, with piercing you with my penis, and cutting off the fart-like sounds, your anus is being turned inside out and scattering the fluids inside, buhiihiihii!!」	s09a	0556
PV01_301_A	6	20	Asagi: 「Kuuu.......! Y, you!........ahhiii!」	s09a	0557
PV01_301_A	6	21	While the orcs told obscene words with coolness, they violated me entirely.	s09a	0558
PV01_301_A	6	22	Taming with those cocks an alien female, training her, for the sole purpose of breeding and conceiving children, how is it they've grown accustom to this........	s09a	0559
PV01_301_A	6	23	The orcs were controlled by pleasant feelings, not caring about whether the female was of the same race.	s09a	0560
PV01_301_A	6	24	Now, I was surrounded by the anger of the four orcs cocks, violating me, knowing now the significance that held.	s09a	0561
PV01_301_A	6	25	Orc: 「Hehehee...... shall we gradually fuck her in seriousness. Is this woman also prepared to lose her mind in this round?」	s09a	0562
PV01_301_A	6	26	Exposing hands to my hips, the two orcs began using their waists simultaneously.	s09a	0563
PV01_301_A	6	27	Orc: 「Hmph……！」	s09a	0564
PV01_301_A	6	28	Pulling out and thrusting in with movements to that extent...	s09a	0565
PV01_301_A	6	29	Asagi: 「Ohiii!? Hiiiiiii!!」	s09a	0566
PV01_301_A	6	30	Asagi: （A, amazing........like this!?）	s09a	0567
PV01_301_A	6	31	I raised a shriek at my sphincter giving me tremendously sweet sensations.	s09a	0568
PV01_301_A	6	32	Asagi: 「Nnaaaaaaaaaaaaaau！！」	s09a	0569
PV01_301_A	6	33	In spite of my determination, I was forced into a rut, terrified with the effectiveness of the demon aphrodisiacs.	s09a	0570
PV01_301_A	6	34	No, it isn't just that alone. All of my errogenous zones in my body had been restructured, further, I wasn't able to resist Oboro's hypnotism.	s09a	0571
PV01_301_A	6	35	It was no good but to indulge in the pleasure, I could do nothing but experience it with the orcs like this.	s09a	0572
PV01_301_A	6	36	while sensing the testicles repeatedly swelling and contracting at the base of my thighs and between my butt, my senses were being crushed to death by pleasure.	s09a	0573
PV01_301_A	6	37	But....I was being caressed by the orcs opening my orifices all at once.	s09a	0574
PV01_301_A	6	38	Orc: 「Hey, take your mouth away!! My cock's aphrodisiacs, the effect is the best of any orc, look, precum has appeared, it has appeared♪」	s09a	0575
PV01_301_A	6	39	Asagi: 「Eh, eh……？」	s09a	0576
PV01_301_A	6	40	Now, I wasn't using both hands, as I stopped my tongue from caressing.	s09a	0577
PV01_301_A	7	1	Orc: 「Hey, don't you having anything to say? My aphrodisiacs are so effective that they have an immediate sexual effect, what, do you have some kind of mental problem」	s09a	0578
PV01_301_A	7	2	Asagi: 「Eh, eh……？ Immediate effect……」	s09a	0579
PV01_301_A	7	3	Orc: 「It seems, compared with other orcs, it's a 100 times effective」	s09a	0580
PV01_301_A	7	4	Asagi: 「No way.....a lie.......uuehh」	s09a	0581
PV01_301_A	7	5	In hot haste I spat out the words, not wishing it to be true.	s09a	0582
PV01_301_A	7	6	Orc: 「Useless, useless, useless. It doesn't take along before the aphrodisacs in my precum will settle and be absorbed into your stomach」	s09a	0583
PV01_301_A	7	7	The orc said seething between the legs in my hot hands.	s09a	0584
PV01_301_A	7	8	Orc: 「So, I always use condoms when I join with females」	s09a	0585
PV01_301_A	7	9	Orc: 「Noo, today it's for pleasure, any how, it's because we're fucking this ADN in seriousness!!」	s09a	0586
PV01_301_A	7	10	With finishing speaking, the orc sneered and looked down upon me.	s09a	0587
PV01_301_A	7	11	A 100 times more effective than other orc's aphrodisiacs.	s09a	0588
PV01_301_A	7	12	Moreover, an immediate effect......a lie, it's a lie.	s09a	0589
PV01_301_A	7	13	Orc: 「Maa, begin licking me with your tongue, because there's already a lot of precum and you're slow... Let's make it become effective soon, shall we? Buhihii!」	s09a	0590
PV01_301_A	7	14	Asagi: 「Higiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii！？」	s09a	0591
PV01_301_A	7	15	It was sudden. My body, without explanation, flared up and got hot rapidly.	s09a	0592
PV01_301_A	7	16	Asagi: 「Uguahhhhhh!! Such, suchahhhhh！！」	s09a	0593
PV01_301_A	7	17	Asagi: （No wayy!? What, what, is this!?? No, no.........n!!）	s09a	0594
PV01_301_A	7	18	Orc: 「Ooh, hey, that's wonderful.......! Each time you swallow aphrodisacs, your debauchery is boosted rapidly」	s09a	0595
PV01_301_A	7	19	Orc: 「Aah, but it's good you don't have a mental problem with this Buhii！！」	s09a	0596
PV01_301_A	7	20	Orc: 「It's all right, any how, you're giving us a partner, and it's not just any bitch, this female pig is the strongest ADN and since it's Miss Asagi herself!!」	s09a	0597
PV01_301_A	7	21	The orcs are all certain of it themselves!! Because they bursted into laughter.	s09a	0598
PV01_301_A	7	22	As it is, I couldn't worry about that as the orcs wholeheartedly rubbed, seeking pleasant feelings with their unforgiving penises in my anus and the flesh of my pussy	s09a	0599
PV01_301_A	7	23	Asagi: 「Kuahhhh! Ahohu! Oohh! Oooh!!」	s09a	0600
PV01_301_A	7	24	A sensation of a hot fever sprouted that was tearing me up inside.	s09a	0601
PV01_301_A	7	25	Asagi: 「Hii......! Such, noohh! Suchah!」	s09a	0602
PV01_301_A	7	26	Orc: 「Hehee. Greatly joyed, aren't you, Miss ADN........!」	s09a	0603
PV01_301_A	7	27	The movement of the orc's waists was carried to an extreme roughness.	s09a	0604
PV01_301_A	7	28	Asagi: 「Ihiiiiiii! My guts, it feels goooooood...........！！」	s09a	0605
PV01_301_A	7	29	The flesh of my vagina was congesting with hot blood, following the linkage of myself with the rugged shafts of their cocks that was catching inside me.	s09a	0606
PV01_301_A	7	30	Asagi: 「Hiiii......uhiiii...........u!」	s09a	0607
PV01_301_A	7	31	My anus was entirely like my pussy. while the intestinal fluids grew slippery inside, it also squeezed and teased with pleasure the cock.	s09a	0608
PV01_301_A	7	32	Asagi: 「So.......u, amazingggg!」	s09a	0609
PV01_301_A	7	33	Asagi: 「Fuha! Ahhaa! Kuohhhhh.......!」	s09a	0610
PV01_301_A	7	34	Orc: 「What's that? Miss ADN's voice just before orgasming!! Speaking ill about our penises like trash when you can't resist that they're making you feel good!!!」	s09a	0611
PV01_301_A	7	35	While thrusting violently into my integrity, cutting their rough breathing, the orcs cried out without imparting to anyone in particular.	s09a	0612
PV01_301_A	7	36	Orc: 「Is that so, is it good? Is it good here? Does it always feel good? After this, the whole time we're going to rape you, until we can't cum any more!!」	s09a	0613
PV01_301_A	7	37	Asagi: 「Wha, what..........!! C, cummingg!!!」	s09a	0614
PV01_301_A	7	38	Asagi: 「What........! what, orgasming is a flaw reproduction monkeys like you have......Guuohh!!」	s09a	0615
PV01_301_A	7	39	Orc: 「So, we're still not being persuasive enough, you just don't learn do you, you stupid ADN bitch, look!」	s09a	0616
PV01_301_A	7	40	Asagi: 「Fuhiiiiiiiiiiiiii！！！！」	s09a	0617
PV01_301_A	8	1	Thrusting mutually into my holes from the front and back, one of the orcs pierced me with his swelled glans in a straight line as far as my uterus.	s09a	0618
PV01_301_A	8	2	Orc: 「Good, isn't it, in spite of what you're feeling, you came forth with a stubborn, abusive attitude, I'll will it out of you!」	s09a	0619
PV01_301_A	8	3	Asagi: 「noohhhh!! My ass, my assiiiiiiii!」	s09a	0620
PV01_301_A	8	4	Spreading out with the wart-covered penis, it was disguising it as if my ass was getting narrower.	s09a	0621
PV01_301_A	8	5	Orc: 「Come again!? What about screwing your ass!? Hey, I want you to say something!!」	s09a	0622
PV01_301_A	8	6	Asagi: 「It, it's not what!! Th, this isn't a feelinggggggg.......u!!」	s09a	0623
PV01_301_A	8	7	It wasn't a sensation, it shouldn't be so to feel this way, it too wasn't the love with the orc's covetousness, my body was shivering with honest pleasure at their violent cocks.	s09a	0624
PV01_301_A	8	8	Oboro: 「Hahahaahaha, you said it wasn't a feeling........! That feeling you talk of, it's because it isn't natural!」	s09a	0625
PV01_301_A	8	9	While Oboro raised a seemingly enjoyable loud laughter from the bottom of her heart, she gazed at me loving how silly I looked writhing in agony.	s09a	0626
PV01_301_A	8	10	Oboro: 「The many your getting screwed with and your impure blood, is making you lavish your waist, appearing to feel good. It's truly vulgar.......」	s09a	0627
PV01_301_A	8	11	Oboro, with a rude sigh and a bewitching shine in her eyes, enjoyed my improper love affair.	s09a	0628
PV01_301_A	8	12	Asagi: 「Hm, hmphh!! H, how is it? when you also, relish in these, reproduction monkey's wart-covered cocks........ Higiiiii!!!!」	s09a	0629
PV01_301_A	8	13	Oboro: 「Hmph......still saying sarcastic things like that, is it. You're exceeding amazement, respectful♪」	s09a	0630
PV01_301_A	8	14	Oboro, with snorting her nose bluntly, raised her voice towards the orcs continuing to rape me.	s09a	0631
PV01_301_A	8	15	Oboro: 「What are you doing!? All of you. Asagi doesn't need any more time. Fuck her and break her mood more. Surely you can fuck? You lowly group of demon orc trash...」	s09a	0632
PV01_301_A	8	16	At first saying it casually, with Oboro's final words, she put an icy, coldhearted emphasis into them.	s09a	0633
PV01_301_A	8	17	Oboro: 「Quickly, stain this debauchery of a pig woman with your squalid semen!」	s09a	0634
PV01_301_A	8	18	Oboro, with short scolding words, ordered the orcs.	s09a	0635
PV01_301_A	8	19	Orc: 「Hii!! Certainly. Madam.......!」	s09a	0636
PV01_301_A	8	20	Orc: 「Hehe, this means, we can rape with seriousness, ADN's Miss Asagi........!」	s09a	0637
PV01_301_A	8	21	Surrounding me, the four cocks began swelling at once, the sizes, up until now raping me, were remarkably different.	s09a	0638
PV01_301_A	8	22	Asagi: 「Hii......! Gaaahhh!!」	s09a	0639
PV01_301_A	8	23	Taking it in both holes that growing, a climax assaulted my body. At that moment, my mouth opened and my jaw jutted out of place.	s09a	0640
PV01_301_A	8	24	Orc: 「Look, quickly, suck on it. I want to treat you to the fine semen I have for you」	s09a	0641
PV01_301_A	8	25	With showing a cock before my eyes, the stench of sex mingled with a vapor and tickled my nostrils.	s09a	0642
PV01_301_A	8	26	The orc's aphrodisiacs evaporated, entering inside my head.	s09a	0643
PV01_301_A	8	27	With it inside my head, a gentle, white mist eveloped me.	s09a	0644
PV01_301_A	8	28	I couldn't resist, I held the orc's dirty-looking cock in my mouth cavity.	s09a	0645
PV01_301_A	8	29	Asagi: 「Haa.....nn, fu, chyu.....rerorii, rerou........ jyuru, peroperojyubyuuroro...........」	s09a	0646
PV01_301_A	8	30	Quite entirely like a butterfly sucking nectar from a flower, I continued caressing intently the swelling cock.	s09a	0647
PV01_301_A	8	31	Asagi: 「Chyu……fu、chyupi……」	s09a	0648
PV01_301_A	8	32	Orc: 「Hee, the ADN name is a laugh」	s09a	0649
PV01_301_A	8	33	Asagi: 「Fuahh.....n, pero.......peroo, fu..........nn」	s09a	0650
PV01_301_A	8	34	The orc's scorn was no longer heard if I repeated the caressing, my face to the degree of repeating the action, was becoming a soft white.	s09a	0651
PV01_301_A	8	35	That feeling was exceedingly pleasant with me.	s09a	0652
PV01_301_A	8	36	Asagi: 「Muuahhh, ehahh! Fuguahh!」	s09a	0653
PV01_301_A	8	37	I too was entirely becoming a vulgar goblin the same with the orcs.	s09a	0654
PV01_301_A	8	38	My whole body seemed to be becoming a scattering of pleasant feelings, I raised a voice for the sake of relieving myself of that, even if it was only a little.	s09a	0655
PV01_301_A	8	39	No, maybe I wanted to convey to somebody what I'm feeling.	s09a	0656
PV01_301_A	8	40	Because it's Oboro pulling my strings, so, that was the explanation inside my head.	s09a	0657
PV01_301_A	9	1	Sure enough, with the remaining swirling pleasures, I was lusting insatiably for the pleasant feelings; is she manipulating me or.........again, I don't know.	s09a	0658
PV01_301_A	9	2	Asagi: 「Kuuu.......! I'm cumming, cum, cum, cum, cumming!! C...........gah.......ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!」	s09a	0659
PV01_301_A	9	3	Orc: 「Uoh……！ She orgasmed……！ Hehehehe」	s09a	0660
PV01_301_A	9	4	Orc: 「I'm still, we're still seriously doing it like this!」	s09a	0661
PV01_301_A	9	5	Asagi: 「Nnuuuuuuuuuuuu! Hii! Hiii!」	s09a	0662
PV01_301_A	9	6	While licking with my tongue the wart shapes that covered his cock, I began taking with honesty the sensations of being fucked in both of my holes.	s09a	0663
PV01_301_A	9	7	Orc: 「Ohhh.....! It's good, whenever I indulge in your ass, it feels like the linkage with my penis is bursting open!!!」	s09a	0664
PV01_301_A	9	8	Orc: 「Oooh, your pussy is also shivering and trembling with me inside! It feels good, heheehe」	s09a	0665
PV01_301_A	9	9	Caressing in thoroughness, the four orc's cocks used parts of my whole body. Soon, perhaps it was good that this was ending, but in what way............	s09a	0666
PV01_301_A	9	10	Asagi: 「Fumunn! Hi, hiiiiiii, cum, cum, cumming!!」	s09a	0667
PV01_301_A	9	11	Orc: 「What's that? Tell me! Yourself now, how is it? what you are doing with us reproduction monkeys!」	s09a	0668
PV01_301_A	9	12	Orc: 「Ehh!? Tell me!! Miss ADN oh!!」	s09a	0669
PV01_301_A	9	13	While both holes isolated light red, I bent my spine in a big way, like a bow, with the scraping of the seething hot wart-covered cocks.	s09a	0670
PV01_301_A	9	14	Orc: 「Ohh, ooh, ooh!! How's that!? we're not going to stop raping you until you tell us!!! 」	s09a	0671
PV01_301_A	9	15	Asagi: 「Guhiiiiiiiiiiu!」	s09a	0672
PV01_301_A	9	16	Orc: 「How is it!? What are you feeling, what are you feeling!? Oh, inside you cramped up, hahahaaha, you orgasmed」	s09a	0673
PV01_301_A	9	17	Again, I was given a violent-like climax that assailed my body.	s09a	0674
PV01_301_A	9	18	Orc: 「Fuck, how many times was that!? She orgasmed...... And still, still she hasn't answered!! what is she doing with us?」	s09a	0675
PV01_301_A	9	19	My brain was being ruined with the sensations, in a way of dissolving, and yet still the orcs enjoyed themselves tasting my body.	s09a	0676
PV01_301_A	9	20	Asagi: 「Guhiii good! It's, it's amazingly goodddddd!!」	s09a	0677
PV01_301_A	9	21	Again I orgasmed.......Already, I'm going towards an uncountable number of climaxes, as my body begins sending danger signals.	s09a	0678
PV01_301_A	9	22	The pleasant feeling of the climaxes was feeling painful now.	s09a	0679
PV01_301_A	9	23	Orc: 「How is it? ADN, ohra, ohra, ohraa!!」	s09a	0680
PV01_301_A	9	24	Already, it was useless.......not any more than this......	s09a	0681
PV01_301_A	9	25	Asagi: 「Pleasehii!! Stop it! I'm scared! I'm scared!! You're going too, farr!!」	s09a	0682
PV01_301_A	9	26	I surrendered and gave way to the reproduction monkey orcs. Soon, I was going to go mad if I was given any more pleasure than this.	s09a	0683
PV01_301_A	9	27	Orc: 「Hey, tell me. About the situation you're really in」	s09a	0684
PV01_301_A	9	28	Oboro: 「Fufufu, I also want to hear about it, huh. The strongest ADN, Asagi, is doing what with reproduction monkeys」	s09a	0685
PV01_301_A	9	29	I had an impulse their movement was somewhat slowing, piercing both of my holes.	s09a	0686
PV01_301_A	9	30	I am ready to talk with composed words. Because I want to finish the persecution that continued to go on, that was in my mind.	s09a	0687
PV01_301_A	9	31	Asagi: 「I, I'm......being raped by reproduction.......monkeys」	s09a	0688
PV01_301_A	9	32	Orc: 「Where！？」	s09a	0689
PV01_301_A	9	33	Asagi: 「You're raping the orifices of my pussy and asshole.......higuuu!」	s09a	0690
PV01_301_A	9	34	A cock pierced the orifice of my womb and integrity at once.	s09a	0691
PV01_301_A	9	35	As if fainting in agony, paralysis set in, flapping my mouth much like a fish who had been suffciently caught.	s09a	0692
PV01_301_A	9	36	Orc: 「What!? That........say it exactly, exactly!!」	s09a	0693
PV01_301_A	9	37	The blame of the angry orc wasn't forgiving the orifice of my uterus, violating it.	s09a	0694
PV01_301_A	9	38	My head had already become pure white, and therefore, I didn't even know if I was being made to say it because of Oboro's hypnotism.	s09a	0695
PV01_301_A	9	39	Nevertheless, the orgasms were too painful. All I could think in my mind was that I had to escape from these climaxes.	s09a	0696
PV01_301_A	9	40	Asagi: 「M, my throat, pussy, and ass are being raped by the bumpy cocks of these reproduction monkeys, I'm being given climaxes to the degree that I can't count them..!」	s09a	0697
PV01_301_A	10	1	Orc: 「Where！？」	s09a	0698
PV01_301_A	10	2	The voice asked a question of me with anger.	s09a	0699
PV01_301_A	10	3	Asagi: 「Every time the bumpy cocks rub the flesh of my pussy, it makes me cum many times, screwing my ass is also almost the same, the orgasms feel so good...........kuuu」	s09a	0700
PV01_301_A	10	4	While I was talking, the orc's were giving me minor pleasant feelings by the clever use of their hips so as to provoke me.	s09a	0701
PV01_301_A	10	5	Asagi: 「Hii, but........the orgasms are too, painful. Please forgive me........hiiahhuu!!!」	s09a	0702
PV01_301_A	10	6	From my mouth, such words I didn't think had come forth. Oboro had said them with her hypnotism.	s09a	0703
PV01_301_A	10	7	It seems there was no doubting that, I thought and wished that to be the case.	s09a	0704
PV01_301_A	10	8	Oboro: 「Buu, kukuu, ahuhaahahahahauha！！！！」	s09a	0705
PV01_301_A	10	9	Suddenly, Oboro burst into laugher, holding her belly.	s09a	0706
PV01_301_A	10	10	Oboro: 「Hii, th, that's hilarious!! E, even if your orgasms are too painful, hauhahahaha!!」	s09a	0707
PV01_301_A	10	11	Oboro: 「The strongest name in the ADN is sobbing. Really now, is that the same ADN Asagi that killed me?」	s09a	0708
PV01_301_A	10	12	Oboro continued laughing, holding her stomach and appearing to roll about energetically.	s09a	0709
PV01_301_A	10	13	Oboro: 「Already, it's agreeable. You orcs. Literally rape her as you like with those bumpy cocks until you wear her out, won't you♪」	s09a	0710
PV01_301_A	10	14	Asagi: 「L, like that......it's cruel!! Igii....... I won't let you.......do this........」	s09a	0711
PV01_301_A	10	15	Orc: 「Heheehe, Madam. We won't stop until this female pig dies from cumming!! Hey, cry out another orgasm for me!!」	s09a	0712
PV01_301_A	10	16	Asagi: 「Gi, ahhhhuahhuahhu! Orgasm! I orgasmed!! Ah, ah, ahh.......」	s09a	0713
PV01_301_A	10	17	My womb was jumping up and down with fright.	s09a	0714
PV01_301_A	10	18	Building an attack so as to focus on the cavity of the interior of my vagina, the nerves in my head seemed like they were burning off.	s09a	0715
PV01_301_A	10	19	Orc: 「Hehehe, you orgasmed. This pig woman. She orgasmed with ease, hehehehe」	s09a	0716
PV01_301_A	10	20	Because the orc's feelings of subjugation wrapped up in the folds of my vagina satisfied him, he raised a voice of rapture.	s09a	0717
PV01_301_A	10	21	Orc: 「Soon, I too am about ready to cum....... Hey, how about if I treat this ADN to my semen around here?」	s09a	0718
PV01_301_A	10	22	I realized the meaning behind the orc's hard cocks shaking on the tip of my tongue and in both of my holes.	s09a	0719
PV01_301_A	10	23	Orc: 「That'll be good, won't it. As a matter of fact, I seem like cumming. I'm going to dash my semen on this arrogant ADN Asagi's face!!」	s09a	0720
PV01_301_A	10	24	The source of my integrity soared before my eyes, rising and swelling out.	s09a	0721
PV01_301_A	10	25	Orc: 「Well then, it's settled. Let's soak our semen in Miss ADN with the four of our wart-covered cocks!!」	s09a	0722
PV01_301_A	10	26	Asagi: 「What! That's.......hihiiiinu!!」	s09a	0723
PV01_301_A	10	27	Orc: 「Oh, your pussy is convulsing! This woman orgasmed again, are you that happy to hear that we're ejaculating!?」	s09a	0724
PV01_301_A	10	28	Asagi: 「Fuguu! Guguu! Iu......gu....uu.......u!!」	s09a	0725
PV01_301_A	10	29	My body still continued to climax, for the sake of conveying to the orcs that I wasn't pleased to have them ejaculate, I gritted my teeth and fought frantically.	s09a	0726
PV01_301_A	10	30	Orc: 「How is it!? How do you feel, how do you feel!?」	s09a	0727
PV01_301_A	10	31	Asagi: 「Gihiiiiu! Don't want to feel, don't want to feel!! hiuhiiiiiiii!!!!」	s09a	0728
PV01_301_A	10	32	As a result of spitting out their ejaculation at my lust, the orcs, nevertheless, were using me as a disposable sex tool, stabbing my moral courage.	s09a	0729
PV01_301_A	10	33	Orc: 「Hehe, because I'm going to put it out inside your womb! Pregnating you firmly.......!」	s09a	0730
PV01_301_A	10	34	I was secluded in a fever of the orc's desires, shaking the flesh of their stomachs wildly.	s09a	0731
PV01_301_A	10	35	Asagi: 「Higiii!!! No more than that!! Please, outside!!」	s09a	0732
PV01_301_A	10	36	Orc: 「Uoohhu! It, it's tightening! Is that so, as I thought, you want my semen, don't you!」	s09a	0733
PV01_301_A	10	37	Asagi: 「That isn't it, noohh, that isn't it uuu!」	s09a	0734
PV01_301_A	10	38	while writing in agony in the pleasure, I shook my head side to side frantically. Deja vu attacked me as Pig had said the same thing when he raped me before.	s09a	0735
PV01_301_A	10	39	Orc: 「Your pussy is pressing hard as you're saying that! Gahahaha! You're not fooling anybody!!! ADN!!」	s09a	0736
PV01_301_A	10	40	Asagi: 「Noohhhhu! It's terrible, terrible pistons uu!!!!」	s09a	0737
PV01_301_A	11	1	Matching with the movements of the orcs heading towards the instance of an ejaculation, my waist swung on its own accord.	s09a	0738
PV01_301_A	11	2	Orc: 「Guoohhu! Good! I'm cumming, soon I'm cumming! I'm going to plant my semen in the rectum of this asshole I'm screwing!」	s09a	0739
PV01_301_A	11	3	Asagi: 「Stop it!! Cumming!! Please!! Aaaaaahhh!!!」	s09a	0740
PV01_301_A	11	4	Again, my pleasant feelings were my maximum priority, but my pleading was ignored by the orcs.	s09a	0741
PV01_301_A	11	5	Orc: 「Gau, right here, right here I'm cumming! Up until now, I've been saving a pack of semen to ejaculate on this ADN's face!」	s09a	0742
PV01_301_A	11	6	Asagi: 「S, stop it........! It's, it's useless, useless, useless.........!」	s09a	0743
PV01_301_A	11	7	The cocks were bursting and seeting with hotness, from the shaft to the root, and now, they swelled at once to the tip.	s09a	0744
PV01_301_A	11	8	Asagi: 「It's coming, coming, coming uuuuuuuu, the semen is coming uuuuuuu..........!!!!!!」	s09a	0745
PV01_301_A	11	9	Doing before my eyes a climax, because the glans swelled up, they turned and pulled with the membranes of my body for the sake of ushering in the cocks.	s09a	0746
PV01_301_A	11	10	Asagi: 「Muuuuu! Himuuuu! Muuuu!」	s09a	0747
PV01_301_A	11	11	While my spirit endured the seemingly violating pleasant feelings, they continued to shake my whole body, as finally that moment visited me.	s09a	0748
PV01_301_A	11	12	Because the tips of the penises continued to expand exceeding the limits, they ejaculated almost all at once with a clincher.	s09a	0749
PV01_301_A	11	13	The semen surged forth towards my whole body, beginning with my womb, as I was soaked in semen by the vulgar orcs.	s09a	0750
PV01_301_A	11	14	Asagi: 「Again......inside me!!! Higiiiiiii!!!!!!」	s09a	0751
PV01_301_A	11	15	The dirty fluid spread out into the cavity of the vicinity of my womb, as a scream was put out that overflowed from my throat, turning me inside out.	s09a	0752
PV01_301_A	11	16	That was the voice of a female that was unmistakably in deep shit trouble.	s09a	0753
PV01_301_A	11	17	Asagi: 「Ahhu! Hiyauu! Ihiiiiii!! Pussy cumming!! Ohhiricumming!! Cummingii!!!」	s09a	0754
PV01_301_A	11	18	Orc: 「Uohhu, My semen is absorbing in you!!」	s09a	0755
PV01_301_A	11	19	For the sake of stimulating the impregnation, the orc had thrust until the base so as to cum as close to my womb as possible, spitting out semen deep inside me.	s09a	0756
PV01_301_A	11	20	Oboro: 「Aah, wonderful. Your stomach is contracting and your womb is gulping down and swallowing that semen, is it tasty? The orc's wart-covered penis milk♪」	s09a	0757
PV01_301_A	11	21	Oboro hurled abusive scorn at my wretched figure that was stiffening the vagina for the benefit of digesting the loads of semen in my womb contrary to my intentions.	s09a	0758
PV01_301_A	11	22	Oboro: 「Ma, but I'm watching you, aren't I........ADN - Asagi's favorite food is penis milk........! Fufufu」	s09a	0759
PV01_301_A	11	23	Asagi: 「Cumming……、ehfuu……ah……aah☆ ……ihii……！」	s09a	0760
PV01_301_A	11	24	The semen that had spat out in a large quantity, that was pushed into by a cock the secreted cum, was enchanted with hotness in the opening of my womb.	s09a	0761
PV01_301_A	11	25	Orc: 「Hahaha, shit I put it out, wow, I put out my semen with a large quantity in this ADN's pussy.....!」	s09a	0762
PV01_301_A	11	26	With finishing the last drops of semen, the cock pulled out, making a sound, as air remained inside my vagina.	s09a	0764
PV01_301_A	11	27	It was the origin of me doing these improper things as far as here with me.	s09a	0765
PV01_301_A	11	28	Asagi: 「Aah, ahnu……！」	s09a	0766
PV01_301_A	11	29	In spite of the origin of becoming improper, nevertheless, me, now, revealed a voice, holding dear that the cocks had been pulled out.	s09a	0767
PV01_301_A	11	30	Orc: 「Hehe, because I put out a lot in your rectum, you're going to expel semen-stained shit tomorrow」	s09a	0768
PV01_301_A	11	31	The ejaculations had finished, and the orcs were staring at my improper female face, smirking.	s09a	0769
PV01_301_A	11	32	Orc: 「Hehe, because we both ejaculated, your ass hole and pussy are churning and becoming a frothy」	s09a	0770
PV01_301_A	11	33	Orc: 「Aaah, I ejaclated into your hair. Washing it too, the smell won't degenerate for awhile, because my semen is famous for smelling really badly among orcs, fuhihihihi」	s09a	0771
PV01_301_A	11	34	Asagi: 「Haa, haa, I'm finished………」	s09a	0772
PV01_301_A	11	35	Harassing me with violent pleasant feelings, I felt that I was entirely finished. At last, I can escape from these successive climaxes.	s09a	0773
PV01_301_A	11	36	Oboro: 「Oh, what are you saying? You still must keep on!? Isn't that right? Pig」	s09a	0774
PV01_301_A	11	37	Asagi: 「………………eh！？」	s09a	0775
PV01_301_A	11	38	Bewilderment with astonishment, I fixed my eyes on Oboro with that sort of facial expression.	s09a	0776
PV01_301_A	11	39	Pig: 「Naturally!! Watching these guys, I have completely recovered, hehehehehe」	s09a	0777
PV01_301_A	11	40	His posture displayed a well-ordered cock, as Pig was preparing even now with me.	s09a	0778
PV01_301_A	12	1	Asagi: 「No way……n, no………」	s09a	0779
PV01_301_A	12	2	Pig: 「Now, shall we begin......I'm worried about pregnating you earlier, you're going to give birth to my child, so I'm going to ejaculate into your womb more!!!」	s09a	0780
PV01_301_A	12	3	Pig floated a vulgar smile, rubbing intensely his cock as he approached me.	s09a	0781
PV01_301_A	12	4	Oboro: 「Hohohohoho, their plan is to truly get you pregnant, isn't it. So as much as possible, you'd better be careful huh.....soon, it'll be useless♪」	s09a	0782
PV01_301_A	12	5	I, could do nothing to resist, I could only shake my head back and forth.	s09a	0783
PV01_301_A	12	6	Asagi: 「No……no………no………aaah……」	s09a	0784
PV01_301_A	12	7	My refusal was perceived and only aroused the sexual desires of the other orcs even more......... There was more afterwards.	s09a	0785
PV01_301_A	12	8	………………………………	s09a	0786
PV01_301_A	12	9	………………	s09a	0787
PV01_301_A	12	10	Orc: 「Hey, how long are you are you going to faint! ADN!! Fuck, wake up!!!」	s09a	0788
PV01_301_A	12	11	Asagi: 「……eh, ahh…………？」	s09a	0789
PV01_301_A	12	12	I opened my eyes that were covered in darkness.	s09a	0790
PV01_301_A	12	13	With awakening, the orcs were still continuing to rape me.	s09a	0791
PV01_301_A	12	14	Asagi: 「Aah, aah……！？」	s09a	0792
PV01_301_A	12	15	In a humiliating posture like some sort of animal pushing only its butt in the air, I accepted their thorough raping rigidly.	s09a	0793
PV01_301_A	12	16	Orc: 「Oh!? She's awake, she's awake! All this trouble that I've been going through to stir up this pussy, what a bitch」	s09a	0794
PV01_301_A	12	17	Halfway swooning, my senses were hazy, the orc's sexual desires had not stopped with me.	s09a	0795
PV01_301_A	12	18	The four orcs crowded around me, alternating raping me.	s09a	0796
PV01_301_A	12	19	In the time that I had fainted, it seems they had been playing with my body.	s09a	0797
PV01_301_A	12	20	A large quantity of semen was attached throughout my body that looked like nets.	s09a	0798
PV01_301_A	12	21	Again, what had happened........ I didn't understand that I had fainted.	s09a	0799
PV01_301_A	12	22	Merely, the next orc violating me and spitting out inside my womb semen.	s09a	0800
PV01_301_A	12	23	When that had finished, the next orc would again........ and when that orc finished.......the next orc........	s09a	0801
PV01_301_A	12	24	The whole time, they had continued without tiring.	s09a	0802
PV01_301_A	12	25	Asagi: 「Wha........t uu！！」	s09a	0803
PV01_301_A	12	26	The moment my hazy senses were blown away, pleasure played an overture of climaxes once more.	s09a	0804
PV01_301_A	12	27	Orc: 「Ohu, you think you get a break if you faint!? The condition of your pussy is so nice that I just had to have it, I had to!」	s09a	0805
PV01_301_A	12	28	Asagi: 「S, stop it al, already.......ahhiiu! Aaaaahu!」	s09a	0806
PV01_301_A	12	29	The orcs had understood I had woke up and nuzzled their cocks against me, jolting their hips intensely more and more.	s09a	0807
PV01_301_A	12	30	Orc: 「Hey, more!! Quickly, give me a turn!!」	s09a	0808
PV01_301_A	12	31	Another orc spoke towards an orc that was stirring up the semen that was brimming over, thrusting his meat spear at my female anatomy.	s09a	0809
PV01_301_A	12	32	Asagi: 「Aahhu! Hii, ihiiiii!!」	s09a	0810
PV01_301_A	12	33	Terror was with the pleasant feelings, those emotions assaulted me. The other 4 orcs gazed passionately at my foolish self, all of their cocks seething hot.	s09a	0811
PV01_301_A	12	34	The orcs had kept raping me without losing interest, and after this too they were continuing to violate me, as drool dribbled from their mouths like hungry beasts.	s09a	0812
PV01_301_A	12	35	Orc: 「Your womb is becoming a tank of semen!! Every time I push into it with my penis, the end gets sloppy with the lukewarm semen collected inside.」	s09a	0813
PV01_301_A	12	36	Asagi: 「Nguuu! Ooh.......! My insides, my insides uuu!!」	s09a	0814
PV01_301_A	12	37	I thought profoundly of the importance of having the children in my womb.	s09a	0815
PV01_301_A	12	38	The semen was rampaging inside, my womb was ignoring my intentions of drinking up that, desiring the semen more and more.	s09a	0816
PV01_301_A	12	39	Asagi: （I'll, kill it………）	s09a	0817
PV01_301_A	12	40	With me killing it with pleasure, I dreaded having to kill it.	s09a	0818
PV01_301_A	13	1	Asagi: 「S, surely already this is enough? The reason...... stop these guys.......he..........igiuuaaaahhhh!!!」	s09a	0819
PV01_301_A	13	2	I sought help from Oboro as my body's freedom wasn't effective with the hypnotized state. I had done far enough as it was, being violated together with these orcs.	s09a	0820
PV01_301_A	13	3	Because I had originally thought it would have finished soon.	s09a	0821
PV01_301_A	13	4	Oboro: 「Fufufufu, maybe you're going mad with so many orgasms, huh♪」	s09a	0822
PV01_301_A	13	5	Oboro's words was only that alone. It was only a light laugh seemingly to say a single word.	s09a	0823
PV01_301_A	13	6	Oboro: 「Already I've had enough of this. Since I'm completely exhausted, I'm going to bed...... Pig, it's ok to stop when you lose interest」	s09a	0824
PV01_301_A	13	7	Seeming to say only that, Oboro left the room.	s09a	0825
PV01_301_A	13	8	Pig: 「O, okay. A first rate pussy like this, parting with something like this isn't easy!! Hehehe, Asagi-chan, I'm going to enjoy myself for a long time」	s09a	0826
PV01_301_A	13	9	Pig expressed a vulgar smile. This was becoming hopeless, dropping and kicking me to the bottom of sheer terror.	s09a	0827
PV01_301_A	13	10	Asagi: 「Stop, stop......hiu!? STOP IT!! All of you, stop it..........!」	s09a	0828
PV01_301_A	13	11	Orc: 「I wonder if I can give your womb a hard shot with my semen like before!! Ooh, I'm cumming, it's coming out」	s09a	0829
PV01_301_A	13	12	Asagi: 「Ahgii, muguuuuuuuu!!」	s09a	0830
PV01_301_A	13	13	While stirring up my hole with his penis, I shouted and cried out.	s09a	0831
PV01_301_A	13	14	Asagi: 「Fugiiiiiii！！！」	s09a	0832
PV01_301_A	13	15	The countless number of bumps with the glans swelled up at once and in the next moment........	s09a	0833
PV01_301_A	13	16	Splurt splurt splurt!	s09a	0834
PV01_301_A	13	17	In that moment I felt a dirty, hot fluid being pumped into the inside of my body, as something made a breaking sound inside me.	s09a	0835
PV01_301_A	13	18	Orc: 「It's coming out, it's coming out! Uooohu! My cock is being inhaled by your pussy with my semen!」	s09a	0836
PV01_301_A	13	19	Asagi: 「Ngooooooooooooooou!!」	s09a	0837
PV01_301_A	13	20	The lingering memory of a climax continued on inside, as the climax came around intermittently, continuing to violate me, hurling my senses and consciousness.	s09a	0838
PV01_301_A	13	21	Orc: 「And again, again I came, I came! How many orgasms is that now!?」	s09a	0839
PV01_301_A	13	22	I was only trying to control myself from the the endless orgasms. It was making me convulse my body and limbs with waves of pleasure, slouching my tongue.	s09a	0840
PV01_301_A	13	23	Asagi: 「Ah, guuuuuuu！！！」	s09a	0841
PV01_301_A	13	24	While plugging the orifice of my vagina with a cock that was spitting out dirty, cloudied liquid, I screamed out pleasant feelings inside my mind.	s09a	0842
PV01_301_A	13	25	Asagi: （Cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming with these orc cocks uuuuuuu!!!!!）	s09a	0843
PV01_301_A	13	26	I was ashamed as well as losing my honor, as I was exhausting myself relishing in the 10's of climaxes that I was putting out that shook my entire body.	s09a	0844
PV01_301_A	13	27	Asagi: 「Nguaah! Cumming! Cum cum cumming........」	s09a	0845
PV01_301_A	13	28	Already it was unimaginable. My womb wasn't connected to my intentions, squeezing the ejaculating semen from the bumpy penises.	s09a	0846
PV01_301_A	13	29	Asagi: 「Fugooooo! Ooh! Ohgooo!!」	s09a	0847
PV01_301_A	13	30	It was entirely collapsing and melting me, lingering inside like a mist.	s09a	0848
PV01_301_A	13	31	Asagi: 「Aaah, again inside me...... Ejaculating in my womb........becoming pregnant, giving birth, to a baby uuuuuu!!」	s09a	0849
PV01_301_A	13	32	All of my muscles were becoming tense, testing my training as an ADN to the limits, pouring the dirty liquid in me as I felt it dance in ecstasy within me.	s09a	0850
PV01_301_A	13	33	Asagi: 「Nbuuu! Ngu, nnn........!!」	s09a	0851
PV01_301_A	13	34	Orc: 「Fuuuuu......! That's good........! ADN - Miss Asagi..........」	s09a	0852
PV01_301_A	13	35	Orc: 「Now, I'm next.....I'm next」	s09a	0853
PV01_301_A	13	36	Pig: 「Heheehe, let's fuck her some more, just like this!! Heheehehe」	s09a	0854
PV01_301_A	13	37	Still, the orc's intentions were to keep raping me........	s09a	0855
PV01_301_A	13	38	Asagi: （It's not finished.......they aren't going to let me finish, are they.......）	s09a	0856
PV01_301_A	13	39	…………………………	s09a	0857
PV01_301_A	13	40	……………	s09a	0858
PV01_301_A	14	1	Now, I wonder how much time has passed..........?	s09a	0859
PV01_301_A	14	2	My memories were becoming distant........ yet, I knew one thing, this gang rape....... had still continued.	s09a	0860
PV01_301_A	14	3	Asagi: 「………………………」	s09a	0861
PV01_301_A	14	4	Four of the orcs had slept, tiring of raping me, Pig was still continuing to rape me, torturing severely with perseverance.	s09a	0862
PV01_301_A	14	5	Pig: 「Heheheehe, already the thing of resisting as well as breathing hard it seems you're not able to do........」	s09a	0863
PV01_301_A	14	6	Pig: 「Calling yourself exaggerated names such as ADN, peeling you of your clothes and continuing to rape you like this」	s09a	0864
PV01_301_A	14	7	To what limit does this guy resent me...........?	s09a	0865
PV01_301_A	14	8	I thought about such vague things like that inside my consciousness.	s09a	0866
PV01_301_A	14	9	Asagi: 「………………………」	s09a	0867
PV01_301_A	14	10	Pig: 「How is it? Soakng you entirely with semen by despised sex monkeys up until now, and the feeling of fainting and peeling back the whites of your eyes...!」	s09a	0868
PV01_301_A	14	11	At that moment, Oboro entered into the training room.	s09a	0869
PV01_301_A	14	12	Oboro: 「I'm amazed. You've been raping her until morning♪」	s09a	0870
PV01_301_A	14	13	Morning.....it was morning, already?	s09a	0871
PV01_301_A	14	14	Pig: 「Gehehe, I thought to make sure I pregnated her reliably. Ahu, I'm leaving」	s09a	0872
PV01_301_A	14	15	Byuri, byu, byu.......byu!!	s09a	0873
PV01_301_A	14	16	Pig spat out semen into my uterus and casted me aside like complete garbage.	s09a	0874
PV01_301_A	14	17	Lacking somewhat, the amount was scarce...........	s09a	0875
PV01_301_A	14	18	Pig: 「Hehehe, I put it out, I put it out. Soon, it'll be coming out, won't it.......hehehehe」	s09a	0876
PV01_301_A	14	19	While raising loud laughter, while Pig shook and shivered, he ejaculated for awhile then pulled out his penis.	s09a	0877
PV01_301_A	14	20	Asagi: 「nuu………ehfu……」	s09a	0878
PV01_301_A	14	21	With the cork disappearing that was plugging up my hole together with the sensation, the large quantity of semen that sprayed out from my pussy was astonishing.	s09a	0879
PV01_301_A	14	22	That is, it was entirely like water rushing forth from a hose.	s09a	0880
PV01_301_A	14	23	Asagi: 「ah……aah……aaah……」	s09a	0881
PV01_301_A	14	24	Pig: 「Gehehehee! It's coming out! Hey, there's heavy floods of it!!」	s09a	0882
PV01_301_A	14	25	Oboro: 「Ahaha! Pregnating her with so much! It's a masterpiece, isn't it♪」	s09a	0883
PV01_301_A	14	26	Pig: 「Guhihi! It's thrilling to guess what the faces of our children will look like」	s09a	0884
PV01_301_A	14	27	Pig expressed a vulgar smile, as my senses were faint as I discharged with inconstancy the viscous lukewarm liquids from only between my thighs.	s09a	0885
PV01_301_A	14	28	Oboro: 「Excellent. We'll have to give her an inspection in a short while to see whether or not she'll become pregnant」	s09a	0886
PV01_301_A	14	29	Pregnancy......me, being pregnant.........? with these reproduction monkey's.........	s09a	0887
PV01_301_A	14	30	Pig: 「That person will look forward to it........gehehe」	s09a	0888
PV01_301_A	14	31	Oboro, not being able to stand the stench of the semen from returning inside the room, pinched her nose while she approached my stupefied body.	s09a	0889
PV01_301_A	14	32	Oboro: 「Now, you'll accept working as my combatant. But only as a my puppet combatant..........fufu♪」	s09a	0890
PV01_301_A	14	33	Oboro held her hand aloft towards me.	s09a	0891
PV01_301_A	14	34	It was the hypnotism………	s09a	0892
PV01_301_A	14	35	I, stopped the matter, already resisting it. No, now, now I only thought that I wanted to be trapped by the hypnotism.	s09a	0893
PV01_301_A	14	36	…………At last, it's finished. At last, I am able to escape from here.	s09a	0894
PV01_301_A	14	37	Seeming to think that, I accepted the hypnotism.	s09a	0895
PV01_301_A	14	38	Oboro: 「Because sometime, I'll return you to your senses, won't I♪」	s09a	0896
PV01_301_A	14	39	Oboro's voice like that was heard, and my consciousness sunk into a sea of darkness...............	s09a	0897
PV01_301_A	14	40	…………………………	s09a	0898
PV01_301_A	15	1	………………	s09a	0899
