OB002A	1	1	............
OB002A	1	2	Hearing the sound of water from a shower, Oboro woke up.
OB002A	1	3	Luz: 「Uuh...... Where is, this......?」
OB002A	1	4	
OB002A	1	5	A wakeup that one couldn't call pleasant by any standard.
OB002A	1	6	While knitting her brows, she tried to get up, but for some reason, her body wouldn't move.
OB002A	1	7	Her body was dominated by a profound heaviness, which differed from a feeling of exhaustion or being half-asleep.
OB002A	1	8	Luz: （I wonder what happened......? This place is...... the bathroom of a hotel somewhere......?）
OB002A	1	9	Oboro tried to somehow grasp her situation.
OB002A	1	10	The inside of her head was still hazy, but even so, there were things which appeared, little by little.
OB002A	1	11	Lukewarm moisture and the smell of soap enveloped her surroundings――
OB002A	1	12	Furthermore, there were signs of someone on the other side of the door that she could see at the edge of her field of vision, and she could even hear humming mixing into the sound of the water.
OB002A	1	13	Luz: 「What the hell is the meaning of this......?」
OB002A	1	14	She didn't understand anything.
OB002A	1	15	Being a shrewd Taimanin, Oboro always paid the maximum attention to the condition of her mind and body.
OB002A	1	16	――In spite of that, she had fallen unconscious like this, with no memory of her actions.
OB002A	1	17	What the hell was actually......?
OB002A	1	18	Luz: 「......h?!」
OB002A	1	19	That moment――
OB002A	1	20	Suddenly, before the eyes of Oboro, who leaned against the bathroom wall, something that she could only describe as “darkness” appeared.
OB002A	1	21	? ? : 『It looks like you've woken up, hmm......?』
OB002A	1	22	A booming voice that seemed to resound directly inside her mind.
OB002A	1	23	The instant she heard that――Oboro was able to remember something important.
OB002A	1	24	Luz: 「That's right......」
OB002A	1	25	Luz: 「I was swallowed up by Edwin Black's...... by your “darkness”, and even had my body taken over......」
OB002A	1	26	After Oboro had transferred her soul into the body of a prostitute named “Ayaka” to secretly advise Asagi, on the way back to her hideout, she had encountered Black, and been engulfed by that “darkness”.
OB002A	1	27	Those were Oboro's memories right up until she lost consciousness.
OB002A	1	28	Luz: 「......So, why are you doing something like this? I don't get the point at all.」
OB002A	1	29	Oboro said, irritatedly.
OB002A	1	30	A place which seemed like a hotel bathroom.
OB002A	1	31	A man's carefree voice was audible from the next room, and for some reason, her body wouldn't move one bit.
OB002A	1	32	? ? : 『It's to save Asagi.』
OB002A	1	33	Luz: 「Huh......?」
OB002A	1	34	? ? : 『There is a control device known as “Demonseed”. It's suppressing Asagi's movements.』
OB002A	1	35	? ? : 『In order to disable it, I require a little preparation, and the assistance of an outstanding Demonologist.』
OB002A	1	36	Luz: 「So? If you're going to do that, shouldn't you do it as you please? Just give my body back.」
OB002A	1	37	? ? : 『I cannot do that.』
OB002A	1	38	? ? : 『Your body is rather handy. So much so that, if not for Asagi, I would think that you were decent, too.』
OB002A	1	39	Luz: 「......h!!」
OB002A	1	40	That was the reply that Oboro expected, yet she frowned and clicked her tongue.
OB002A	2	1	? ? : 『I am going to have you stay here for a while.』
OB002A	2	2	Luz: 「Eh? Here? That's considerate.」
OB002A	2	3	Oboro surveyed her surroundings.
OB002A	2	4	Probably a hotel room somewhere. The bathroom of it.
OB002A	2	5	? ? : 『I've injected your body with a slightly strong drug. Also, I prepared a “babysitter” so that you won't run away anywhere.』
OB002A	2	6	Luz: 「Babysitter......?」
OB002A	2	7	And then, the darkness―the presence of Black―seemed to smile pleasantly a little.
OB002A	2	8	? ? : 『It's a hopeless delinquent from this neighbourhood.』
OB002A	2	9	? ? : 『I've tampered with his memories, to make him think he plied you with drugs and alcohol. It appears that he intends to use you to shoot a porno movie.』
OB002A	2	10	Luz: 「Huh?! What was that――?!」
OB002A	2	11	With the presence still seeming to smile at Oboro, who had started to become enraged, the “darkness” faded away, little by little.
OB002A	2	12	? ? : 『Kuku. You can enjoy yourself until I return.』
OB002A	2	13	? ? : 『But, I'll warn you――He appears to be a considerable scumbag. He doesn't see women as anything but instruments of money and lust. And he uses violence without hesitation.』
OB002A	2	14	? ? : 『With you unable to move right now, I think it would be wiser not to resist.』
OB002A	2	15	Luz: 「Huh?! D, don't screw with me! Acting as you please――Wait!」
OB002A	2	16	Oboro yelled.
OB002A	2	17	But it was futile, and the “darkness” suddenly vanished, just like when it had appeared.
OB002A	2	18	And, at the same time――
OB002A	2	19	Chara man: 「Oi, Babaa! You're being noisy! Who are you talking to?!」(TL: An insulting way of referring to older women.)
OB002A	2	20	Luz: （This is my “babysitter”......?）
OB002A	2	21	Oboro sent the man who had stormed into the bathroom a bemused look.
OB002A	2	22	The man, who only had a bath towel wrapped around his waist, was clad in the frivolous air of a playboy.
OB002A	2	23	He was looking around the bathroom with atrociously bloodshot eyes.
OB002A	2	24	Luz: 「There's nobody here. Just talking to myself――Besides that.」
OB002A	2	25	Luz: 「I don't know who you are, but would you let me go? I'm not saying for free, of course.」
OB002A	2	26	Chara man: 「Huhhh?」
OB002A	2	27	The man raised his eyebrows from those words, and came right up close to Oboro, who leaned against the wall.;SE：ドカッと腹を蹴る音。;効果：クエイク
OB002A	2	28	Luz: 「Guuuh?!」
OB002A	2	29	Having been kicked in the stomach, Oboro groaned in apparent anguish.
OB002A	2	30	Chara man: 「Who do you think you are, with that condescending attitude, you old bat?! I'll kill you! Here!!」
OB002A	2	31	Luz: 「Uguh! Guuuuuh?!」
OB002A	2	32	The man kicked her stomach over and over again, with practiced movements.
OB002A	2	33	Luz: （To be able to kick a woman's stomach so readily... How much of a scumbag is he......?）
OB002A	2	34	Luz: （If my body moved, I could beat him up easily, and yet......!）
OB002A	2	35	There wasn't enough strength to inflict damage on a Taimanin's body, but he aimed at the same spot persistently.
OB002A	2	36	Unable to resist, Oboro could only groan, and, perhaps because he was satisfied after kicking her stomach for a while, the man finally lowered his leg.
OB002A	2	37	Chara man: 「Like, if you're gonna give me money, I'll take it!」
OB002A	2	38	Chara man: 「But first, before that, we've got a livestream, Babaa! All the viewers are waiting!」
OB002A	2	39	The charao said with a grin, then lifted up Oboro's body and carried her outside the dressing room. (TL: A charao is the male counterpart to the gyaru stereotype, often with tanned skin, dyed hair, tacky jewelry and a hobby of picking up women.)
OB002A	2	40	Chara man: 「Okay, like this?! Got it. Now, the stream begins〜♪」
OB002A	3	1	Chara man: 「Hi, sorry to keep you waiting, everyone〜! This is the pussy for today! As I announced in advance last time, I've captured an old lady〜♪」
OB002A	3	2	Having gotten onto a bed, the charao made an enthusiastic appeal towards a camera.
OB002A	3	3	Oboro, who had been laid down face-up, had no choice but to do as she was made to, unable to so much as resist.
OB002A	3	4	Oboro's legs were spread wide by the man's hands, and her underwear, which had become fully visible, was reflected in the camera lens.
OB002A	3	5	Chara man: 「How's that? Her sexy panties are in full view, aren't they? That's because I plied her with drugs and alcohol, as usual♪ We're gonna take the kind of super-sexy video that will end her life as a human, so enjoy!」
OB002A	3	6	Luz: 「You're always doing things like this, aren't you, you scummy man......?」
OB002A	3	7	Luz: 「Some advice...... If you stop here and apologize, I'll let you off with beating you only half to death.」
OB002A	3	8	Oboro informed him with murderous intent, despite making it so that her rage and humiliation would show on her face as little as possible.
OB002A	3	9	However, the man laughed flippantly and paid her no mind.
OB002A	3	10	Chara man: 「Did you hear that, everyone? The stupid old bat doesn't understand her situation, does she? You all like them like this, right〜? I'm confident I picked a good one♪」
OB002A	3	11	Chara man: 「And look at this sexy underwear. Putting on something like this, then saying “I'll beat you half to death”! Cracks me up!」
OB002A	3	12	Chara man: 「What's more, I asked this old lady when I was buying her a drink, and she said she teaches at an elite school! She's a teacher, a teacher! No wonder she's wearing nice clothes!」
OB002A	3	13	Luz: 「Mm?! S, stop......!」
OB002A	3	14	Her clothes were pulled on with presumptuous hand movements. Oboro raised a voice of protest, but that was all the resistance she could muster.
OB002A	3	15	Chara man: 「Wow〜, she is teacher-like, isn't she?! Everyone, please carefully watch the scene of this arrogant, self-important elite old bag being totally defeated by my dick〜♪」
OB002A	3	16	Luz: 「Say that all you like for now...... Once the drug wears off, I'll kill you immediately.」
OB002A	3	17	Chara man: 「That's good〜! Everyone's getting excited since you're going to resist♪」
OB002A	3	18	It seemed that, as far as the men were concerned, Oboro's protests were nothing more than a means to increase their enjoyment.
OB002A	3	19	On the screen that the man pointed his eyes toward, the viewing figures were increasing by the second, and a large number of comments were scrolling across.
OB002A	3	20	Chara man: 「Well! Sorry to keep everybody waiting. Let's start the usual〜♪」
OB002A	3	21	The man nodded in satisfaction at the response from the viewers, and picked up a bottle that had been placed nearby.
OB002A	3	22	He took a lot of the gooey liquid that had been put inside it onto his fingers, and his opposite hand reached out to Oboro's underwear.
OB002A	3	23	Chara man: 「Okay, the unveiling〜 ＆ finger fucking begin〜♪」
OB002A	3	24	Luz: 「S, stop! Hii...... Th, they're cold!」
OB002A	3	25	Having had her groinal fabric shifted, and fingers thrust into her vagina, Oboro reflexively made her body jolt.
OB002A	3	26	Gritting her teeth from the humiliation of having her private parts exposed and touched by the scummy man, Oboro scowled at him, but the fingers probed around the inside of her vagina relentlessly.
OB002A	3	27	Chara man: 「This cunt feels like it hasn't been used too much, huh〜? It's pretty for your age.」
OB002A	3	28	Luz: 「Kuh......! Don't mess around! If you don't want to die, take your fingers, out right now!」
OB002A	3	29	Chara man: 「Yeah yeah. Nope♪」
OB002A	3	30	His fingers moved slowly, as if searching around her vaginal folds.
OB002A	3	31	The sticky fluid, which had been plastered on heavily enough to drip off his fingers, was smeared over her insides by the movement, which cleaved through Oboro's secret flesh.
OB002A	3	32	Chara man: 「It's fiiine, it's fiiine! 'Cause it's gonna start getting hot real soon. Yeah, the people watching the video know, right? The effects are outstanding. An ultra-strong aphrodisiac lotion♪」
OB002A	3	33	Luz: 「Aphrodisiac lotion? Hmph, you can't do anything without relying on something like that? I wonder if you actually have no confidence in your technique?」
OB002A	3	34	Even if her body wouldn't move, she couldn't afford to stop resisting and get caught up in the situation.
OB002A	3	35	Oboro focused on her groin as much as possible and provoked him, making a composed smile.
OB002A	3	36	Chara man: 「Hahaha, acting tough, huh〜? Good, good〜♪ After all, the selling point of my movies is conceited women like you pathetically losing to a dick.」
OB002A	3	37	While stirring Oboro's vagina around as if to mock her opposition, the man bent and stretched his fingers inside it.
OB002A	3	38	He was trying to smear not just the lotion on the balls of his fingers, but even the stuff along their lengths, onto every single one of Oboro's vaginal folds.
OB002A	3	39	Luz: 「You're being pretty slow. I wonder if that's okay? Your friends on the other side of the screen are getting impatient, aren't they?」
OB002A	3	40	Chara man: 「That's not true, is it?〜♪ They all understand, and they're looking forward to it! Besides, even if I don't rush, I'll make you squeal right away!」
OB002A	4	1	The fingers of the man, who was calm and composed, reached the deepest part of her vagina.
OB002A	4	2	Chara man: 「Oh, everyone, my fingers hit her womb just now. This place is especially important, isn't it?♪」
OB002A	4	3	Luz: 「Fuuh, mmh, that's a delicate place...... But I think...... kuh, you'd better do it harder.」
OB002A	4	4	Having her cervix rubbed around by his fingertips, Oboro objected in a groaning voice due to the feeling of pressure.
OB002A	4	5	“I must not start feeling good――”
OB002A	4	6	She tried to calm her breathing and collect herself, but having the very depths of her body stimulated, a sweet, indistinct voice ended up being squeezed out.
OB002A	4	7	Luz: 「Mmh! Fuu, kuh......! Pull your fingers, out quickly......」
OB002A	4	8	She tried to roughen her tone, but her breaths escaped, and her speech became fragmented.
OB002A	4	9	Chara man: 「I've smeared it thoroughly on this place, so you'll start feeling super-good later. Hang on a little longer, Sensei♪」
OB002A	4	10	Luz: 「There's no student, fuuh, as poor as you among my pupils...... Mm, listen up and pull them out!」
OB002A	4	11	Chara man: 「Huh? “Pull them out, pull them out!” What a pesky old bat...... I'm saying, it'll take a little longer, get it?」
OB002A	4	12	While enjoying the protests of the agitated Oboro, the man diligently rubbed the aphrodisiac lotion into her cervix.
OB002A	4	13	Chara man: 「Okay, well, how about this, everybody?」
OB002A	4	14	Chara man: 「Hooora〜, please have a look! There's nothing on my fingers, is there? I used a larger amount than usual, and I smeared it all on〜♪」
OB002A	4	15	The man took out the fingers that he had been inserting to the hilt, in order to show them off to the camera.
OB002A	4	16	The plentiful lotion that he had squeezed out had all been wiped off on Oboro's vaginal flesh.
OB002A	4	17	Chara man: 「Hora, I pulled out my fingers, as you said, right? How is it? How do you feel about having the inside of your cunt coated with such a large amount of aphrodisiac lotion?」
OB002A	4	18	Luz: 「Terrible, to say the least...... While you're taking things out, I'd like you to disappear immediately.」
OB002A	4	19	If it was stimulation on this level, she would be fine......
OB002A	4	20	The man made a vulgar grin at the sight of Oboro trying not to throw off her undaunted attitude.
OB002A	4	21	Chara man: 「Sad to say, I can't live up to that expectation. Besides, I'm gonna make you say “Do it more” real soon!」
OB002A	4	22	The fingers that had been pulled out were placed right along her genitals.
OB002A	4	23	And then, he rubbed them back and forth slowly, just like that.
OB002A	4	24	Luz: 「Nnaah?! Ku, fuuh...... nnnh!」
OB002A	4	25	Oboro unintentionally raised a high voice due to the movement of his fingers, which was meant for sending pleasure into a woman, and was clearly different from anything before now.
OB002A	4	26	Her body unconsciously shivered, and her hot, flushed breasts spilled out from the chest of her loosened blouse.
OB002A	4	27	Chara man: 「Oh, I'm getting a nice voice all of a sudden♪ I wonder if everyone could hear that?」
OB002A	4	28	Luz: 「Kuh......!」
OB002A	4	29	Oboro immediately stifled her voice, but naturally, she couldn't hide the fact.
OB002A	4	30	Furthermore, even while he made his appeal to the camera, the movements of his fingers continuously stimulated her from the entrance of her vagina to her clitoris, without stopping.
OB002A	4	31	Luz: （Th, the movement's completely different from anything up to now......? This man's quite experienced......!）
OB002A	4	32	Chara man: 「You made light of it earlier, but my technique's pretty good, isn't it? Still, you haven't seen anything yet!」
OB002A	4	33	Luz: 「Hiah, nkuh......! Hah, doing it harder isn't...... fuuh, always better.」
OB002A	4	34	Grinning like he had seen through Oboro's mind, the man pressed his fingers down forcefully.
OB002A	4	35	Sighs tinged with a carnal tone escaped from the mouth of Oboro, who tried to endure it.
OB002A	4	36	Furthermore, noises that were mixed with a slight wetness, which was different from that of the lotion, began to resound from her vaginal entrance.
OB002A	4	37	Chara man: 「Haha! Your old lady pussy's started getting wet, huh?〜♪」
OB002A	4	38	Chara man: 「Hora, can everyone hear it squishing? This is the sound of her old lady pussy starting to feel good〜」
OB002A	4	39	Luz: 「Kuh......! Fuuh, don, don't get carried away. It's just getting wet, so that it won't...... get injured, being rubbed hard...... fuuuh!」
OB002A	4	40	Oboro desperately maintained her cocky attitude, but the wet noises from her groin were clearly audible, even to her own ears.
OB002A	5	1	However, Oboro sensed that her body had changed more than that.
OB002A	5	2	Luz: （The inside of my body, is really hot......!）
OB002A	5	3	Luz: （Is this the effect of that aphrodisiac lotion stuff......?! In particular, my womb is burning hot...... kuuuh!）
OB002A	5	4	Oboro's body was getting helplessly worked up due to an aching from the inside.
OB002A	5	5	Chara man: 「Wow〜, the old bag's way too sensitive! I wonder if everyone can tell? Her body's gotten insanely hot〜」
OB002A	5	6	Chara man: 「Her nipples are probably hard too. Shall we all look together?♪」
OB002A	5	7	Without time for Oboro to stop him, the charao moved her open blouse aside, and recklessly tore off her bra.
OB002A	5	8	Both of Oboro's breasts were completely exposed, right down to the sharply-pointed nipples.
OB002A	5	9	Chara man: 「Hooora, I knew it♪」
OB002A	5	10	Luz: 「Ahh, stop...... D, don't look!」
OB002A	5	11	Chara man: 「What're you saying, when your nipples are hard?〜 Everyone〜, these are the teacher's pointy nipples〜. They jiggle when her pussy is rubbed〜♪」
OB002A	5	12	Luz: 「Haah, aah, that place... Stop......!」
OB002A	5	13	Chara man: 「Your clit's no less hard than your nipples〜. Your hips have been jerking every time I rub it for a while. Hora, it's tingling, isn't it?」
OB002A	5	14	Luz: 「Agu, aaaah......! Grinding with your fingertips......! Clitoris, being crushed...... mmmh!」
OB002A	5	15	Having had her clitoris squashed by the balls of his fingers, Oboro made an uncouth moan.
OB002A	5	16	Chara man: 「Um-hmm〜, nice reaction♪ Hora, say it feels good, honestly.」
OB002A	5	17	His rough, unrelenting fingers went back and forth across the surface of her clitoris several times, smushing it and rolling it around.
OB002A	5	18	A tingling sensation spread out from her flesh bud, and further agitated the aching of her body.
OB002A	5	19	Luz: 「Wh, who would say something like...... Higuh?! Akuh, kuoooohh......?!」
OB002A	5	20	Luz: （H, he's...... stimulating it with strength that barely hurts......?!）
OB002A	5	21	Luz: （What's more, every time...... the heat from the aphrodisiac spreads out from my clitoris...... uuh!）
OB002A	5	22	Luz: （T, to become...... like this, even though I've only been touched a little......?!）
OB002A	5	23	Contrary to her defiant attitude, Oboro was sweating, and her thinking was lax.
OB002A	5	24	At this rate, her mind might not be able to endure.
OB002A	5	25	Due to that hunch, she was assailed by a chill which differed from that of the pleasure.
OB002A	5	26	Chara man: 「Oh, there sure are lots of requests for That now〜. Well then, to meet your expectations, I'll go for the first one!」
OB002A	5	27	Had the anxious eagerness inside Oboro's mind shown on her face and body?
OB002A	5	28	The man, who had been taking glances at the screen as he teased her clitoris, immediately sped up the movement of his fingers with exquisite timing.
OB002A	5	29	Luz: 「Higih, nhiiiiiiiiiiiih?!」
OB002A	5	30	Having had the whole of her secret flesh rubbed with violent force, Oboro raised a slutty screaming voice.
OB002A	5	31	Luz: 「Agih?! T, too strooonnng! S, stop...... Stoooohhp, hiiiiih?!」
OB002A	5	32	Chara man: 「Ora! Let's see you get off more, and send cunt juices flying!」
OB002A	5	33	Luz: 「Nnoooohh?! P, pussy's hoooht?! Rubbing's too strooonnnng!」
OB002A	5	34	The large quantity of love juices which spurted out from her vaginal opening were flicked by the movement of his fingers, and scattered all around the area.
OB002A	5	35	Chara man: 「Is it showing clearly? Yay! 『Do it harder.』 Roger〜! Here, an old lady's pussy juice sprinkler!」
OB002A	5	36	Luz: 「D, don't screw around――Guuuuuuuunnh! Juices won't stooop?! Kuh, aaah!!」
OB002A	5	37	Flicking his fingers left and right, the man scattered female juices around, and Oboro's hips rose in time with that.
OB002A	5	38	Chara man: 「Haha! Your hips are bucking, and saying they want me to do it more〜♪ Your nipples have gotten bigger than before, too. They're fully-erect nipples!」
OB002A	5	39	At the peaks of Oboro's breasts (which were horny, flushed and covered in beads of sweat), her nipples were swelling out, along with their areolae.
OB002A	5	40	Chara man: 「You realize these huge nipples are bulging out, right? Even the pores on your areolae are swollen♪ You want me to suck 'em?」
OB002A	6	1	Luz: 「D, don't say whatever you like, agih! S, stop, clitoris is gonna be torn oooooffffff!」
OB002A	6	2	The man suddenly put strength into his fingers, in order to silence Oboro, who had reacted to his humiliating words.
OB002A	6	3	Chara man: 「There's no way it's gonna come off, is there, you old bat?! Like, it got too hard because you're getting off a lot, right〜? Just from me rubbing it like this〜」
OB002A	6	4	Luz: 「Nhiiiiiiih?! Ahhh! N, no more than thisss! Nkuuuuuuuh!」
OB002A	6	5	He rubbed her flesh bud so hard that he made it sink into her body.
OB002A	6	6	Furthermore, his fingertips stimulated her vaginal entrance, and her inner and outer labia.
OB002A	6	7	One could even call his fondling aggressive, but it gave the thoroughly-horny Oboro more pleasure than anything.
OB002A	6	8	Luz: 「S, stop this right nooow! Guu, at, at this rate...... Fuuh, guuh, you'll, pay...... for thiiiiisss?!」
OB002A	6	9	Chara man: 「You're the one who's gonna pay!! Also, I wonder what's going to happen “at this rate”〜?」
OB002A	6	10	Luz: 「Th, that's...... hiuh! N, never mind that, stop moving your hand......!」
OB002A	6	11	Because I feel like I'm going to cum.
OB002A	6	12	Of course, there was no way she could say something like that, but it was clear to anyone that Oboro was going to cum any time now.
OB002A	6	13	Chara man: 「At this rate, you're gonna cum, right? Try saying, “I'm gonna cum!”」
OB002A	6	14	Luz: 「I absolutely will not say something like thaaaat! Nnah, listen up, and stop moving your ha――Higiiiiiih?!」
OB002A	6	15	Her words of defiance ended up being easily twisted by the movement of the man's hand.
OB002A	6	16	Chara man: 「Well, no matter what you say, it's already certain that you're gonna cum! Here, I'll do your clit and pussy at the same time, so cum!」
OB002A	6	17	Luz: 「D, dooonnnn't?! Ah, ahhh――!!」
OB002A	6	18	Luz: 「Nhigiiiiiiiiiih??!! Aguh, nnoooooohhhh!!!!」
OB002A	6	19	The man put exceptional strength into his fingers, and that instant, Oboro's entire stiffened body bucked a lot.
OB002A	6	20	Luz: 「B, by a guy like thiiissssh...!! Ahih, hiiiiiiiiiiih!!」
OB002A	6	21	Chara man: 「Okay, one down〜♪ This conceited old broad's pussy orgasm Number 1〜♪」
OB002A	6	22	Chara man: 「A hard, eye-rolling ahegao orgasm♪ Her cumming juices are squirting like piss! This is what everyone wanted to see, right〜?♪」
OB002A	6	23	As his vulgar laughing voice said, Oboro's face was uncouthly misshapen.
OB002A	6	24	Clear sex juices were being emitted from her groin as though a faucet had broken.
OB002A	6	25	Luz: 「D, don'd loooooook! Hiaaaaaah?! W, won't stoooohohohoooop?!」
OB002A	6	26	Chara man: 「Morrron〜, everyone's watching closely! Look, 『Serves you right, Babaa!』 Hey, Crabmuscle-san, thanks for the 3000 yen donation!」
OB002A	6	27	Luz: 「Wh, what's that?! Aaahih, ngiiiiiiih?!」
OB002A	6	28	Chara man: 「Suu-san, thanks for the ten thousand yen donation! 『Looking forward to multiple orgasms.』 Please leave it to me〜」
OB002A	6	29	Chara man: 「Ah, Tokitoki-san, thanks for subscribing to the channel♪」
OB002A	6	30	Luz: 「S, stop, agiiiih?! Stoooooop!!」
OB002A	6	31	The people watching the video were all writing comments and paying the streamer whatever amounts of money they pleased.
OB002A	6	32	Excitedly saying thanks due to those numbers, which increased one after another, the man toyed with the orgasming Oboro's groin as if to relay his gratitude.
OB002A	6	33	Each time he did, Oboro's hips bucked significantly, and she squirted over a wide area.
OB002A	6	34	Chara man: 「Well〜, thanks to everyone for donating more than usual! Hey, old bat, you say thanks too! Say “Thank you very much for watching my shameful orgasm!”」
OB002A	6	35	Luz: 「Wh, who would――Ngiiiiiiih?!」
OB002A	6	36	As if throwing in a freebie at the end, he slapped her groin, and her juices, which had decreased in force, gave one final ostentatious spurt.
OB002A	6	37	Luz: 「Haahaah...... Y, youuu...... nnu, ahih......」
OB002A	6	38	She ascended to climax over and over again, and after her last cumming squirt stopped, her rising waist finally collapsed powerlessly on the bed.
OB002A	6	39	While becoming cross-eyed and making her body twitch from the lingering feelings of her climax, which still remained, Oboro glared at the man's carefree face.
OB002A	6	40	Luz: 「J, just you wait...... Hhh, I'll definitely kill you......!」
OB002A	7	1	Chara man: 「Ha, aren't you conceited, given that you're exposing an ahegao?! Or maybe I should say, what're you thinking it's over for?」
OB002A	7	2	Excited by the higher-than-anticipated sum of revenue, the man moved his fingers away from the vagina of Oboro, who breathed wildly through her nose.
OB002A	7	3	And then, he suddenly grabbed an object that he had set by the bedside in advance.
OB002A	7	4	Chara man: 「Ta-daaa〜, now, with this thing♪ I bought it for today〜」
OB002A	7	5	The man's hand grasped a big, long dildo, which he shook in order to show it off to Oboro and the viewers on the other side of the screen.
OB002A	7	6	The size of the fake meat pole that the man held was about that of Oboro's upper arm.
OB002A	7	7	Luz: 「W, wait a sec! There's no way something like that will go in, is there?!」
OB002A	7	8	Even Oboro raised a stiff voice due to the enormous, wobbling, translucent dildo.
OB002A	7	9	Chara man: 「If I thrust in a small one, it would be boring and ordinary, wouldn't it? Well, relax. 'Cause I'll use plenty of lotion to improve its slipperiness!」
OB002A	7	10	Luz: 「L, lotion...... N, no way?!」
OB002A	7	11	Chara man: 「Hmm, you've got good memory for an old lady, don't you? Everybody, I'm adding aphrodisiac lotion, like you wished for♪」
OB002A	7	12	The man smeared aphrodisiac lotion onto the dildo.
OB002A	7	13	The amount of it was clearly large, compared to what he had put on his fingers at the beginning.
OB002A	7	14	Luz: 「Wh, what are you doing?! Putting on such a lot of――Nnaah?!」
OB002A	7	15	The shaft part of the dildo, which had been coated in lotion, was pressed against her private parts, which twitched in the afterglow of her climax.
OB002A	7	16	Oboro's cry for restraint ended up turning into a sweet moan from that alone.
OB002A	7	17	Chara man: 「Even though it's only just touched you. That's hilarious♪ It's 'cause this aphrodisiac lotion works just from smearing it on. Enjoy this major service!」
OB002A	7	18	Luz: 「I'm not asking you to... service me like that! Ah, kuu...... Don't move......!」
OB002A	7	19	Oboro's body, which had become thoroughly sensitive, reacted just from the motion of slowly smearing the lotion on, and love juices started to ooze out.
OB002A	7	20	Chara man: 「What are you saying, when you're getting off like this? Given that your eyes have been glued to it for a while, you want me to slam it into your cunt right away, don't you?」
OB002A	7	21	Luz: 「You're wrong! I'm saying, there's no way something that big will go in! Ahh, this is bad...... Aphrodisiac lotion's soaking in, kuuuh!」
OB002A	7	22	Despite breathing out words of refusal, Oboro couldn't take her eyes off the enormous fake penis.
OB002A	7	23	Pleasure was imprinted on her body every time that object, which was slimy with aphrodisiac lotion, moved back or forth.
OB002A	7	24	Luz: （To feel it this much, just from it rubbing me...... My body's becoming even more sensitive than when the aphrodisiac lotion was smeared in the first place......）
OB002A	7	25	Luz: （If he adds even more to my vagina now, when the effects of the aphrodisiac lotion and the orgasm still haven't faded...... and a super-thick dildo is put in on top of that......）
OB002A	7	26	Luz: 「Ahh...... Fuuh, d, don't......!!」
OB002A	7	27	Oboro regretted having imagined that.
OB002A	7	28	Contrary to her intentions, her body grew even more excited, and her vaginal opening squirmed like it wanted something.
OB002A	7	29	Hot breaths escaped from her lips, and a chill ran along her spine.
OB002A	7	30	Chara man: 「Eh〜? What're you saying don't for? Your cunt keeps getting off, just from being rubbed by a fake cock〜♪ Soon, you're gonna be unable to hold back.」
OB002A	7	31	Luz: 「D, don't! Ahh, the tingling hasn't faded yet! If it's put in now......!」
OB002A	7	32	Due to the words of the man, who appeared to have seen through her, Oboro half-screamed in refusal.
OB002A	7	33	However, her words were nothing more than a manifestation of her fear and unease towards the excessively strong pleasure.
OB002A	7	34	Chara man: 「Well, no matter what you say, I don't care. Now then, everyone, here we go〜」
OB002A	7	35	Maintaining a vacuous tone of voice which didn't have any eagerness in it, the man moved his hand.
OB002A	7	36	Luz: 「Nnooooooooohhhhhhh??!!」
OB002A	7	37	Oboro's throaty moan resounded.
OB002A	7	38	Chara man: 「Uha, awesome voice♪」
OB002A	7	39	The man, who had plunged the extra-thick dildo in almost to the base, laughed casually.
OB002A	7	40	Luz: 「Agah......! Kahah......! P, pussy, burst......?!」
OB002A	8	1	Oboro forced her voice out, while opening and closing her mouth like a fish that had washed ashore.
OB002A	8	2	Her flesh hole, which had been spread to its limit, squeezed the dildo hard.
OB002A	8	3	Chara man: 「You're exaggerating, Babaa. Your well-used old lady pussy isn't gonna burst from this little!」
OB002A	8	4	Luz: 「Igih?! D, don'd mooob?! Fugi, hiiiiiih!!」
OB002A	8	5	The butt of the inserted dildo was smacked, and Oboro's body bucked a lot.
OB002A	8	6	Chara man: 「I didn't think you'd be so pleased that you'd swing your hips like that〜. Your cunt's holding the dildo inside it and won't let go.」
OB002A	8	7	Luz: 「I, I'm nothing like pleased, higuh! Nnoooh! Tip's grazing the baaack?! D, don't, aaah, hiiiiiiinnh!」
OB002A	8	8	Chara man: 「Haha! Your voice is so melty♪ Everyone, you think so too, right?」
OB002A	8	9	Oboro didn't have the composure to turn her eyes toward the screen, but she could guess how the people who were watching a video like this would respond.
OB002A	8	10	Luz: 「Nnoooh, Ah'm, I'm saying, Ah'm nod pleeeeased! Hohi, ohiiiih☆」
OB002A	8	11	She mustered her willpower, thinking “Like hell am I going to do what those scummy men want,” but she had no way to hide her sweet voice and twitching body.
OB002A	8	12	If anything, since she tried to resist the pleasure, and couldn't, she fully realized how much she was getting off.
OB002A	8	13	Chara man: 「Uh-huh, just the reaction I expected♪ You think you're resisting, but your cunt is already sloppy. I'm looking forward to seeing how soon you fall〜♪」
OB002A	8	14	Luz: 「N, no matter what's done to me, I am not...... nnoooh☆ gonna fall......!」
OB002A	8	15	Contrary to her words, fear and unease grew stronger inside her body, which was getting infinitely pent-up.
OB002A	8	16	She no longer knew if the slight shaking in her voice was because of pleasure or fear.
OB002A	8	17	Chara man: 「It took me a while to realize, but when you bluff this pathetically, it actually gets funnier♪ Hora, I'll pry into your pussy more! Try saying you're not pleased by this either!」
OB002A	8	18	Luz: 「Ohoooooooonh?! Pussy's getting turned inshide ouuut! Hahih, nhiiiiih! Donnnnn'd!!」
OB002A	8	19	The dildo, which was moved in and out forcefully, sent intense pleasure into Oboro.
OB002A	8	20	A shrieking voice that pathetically broke into falsetto rushed out from Oboro's throat due to the overwhelming torrent of pleasure.
OB002A	8	21	Chara man: 「Uhah♪ Awesome reaction♪ What are you doing, saying things like “My pussy's turning inside out” like it's natural?!♪」
OB002A	8	22	Luz: 「Stop, ahih, uhoooooohhh?! Doo thick, inside of my vagina's bein ruuuuubbed!! Don, don'd moooob!」
OB002A	8	23	Chara man: 「Don't lie! Your old lady pussy's delighted. Its squeezing is way too strong! Wow〜, my arm's getting really tired〜♪」
OB002A	8	24	Luz: 「Nnoooohhh?! Hohih☆ Ohoh☆ Hoooooooonnh?!」
OB002A	8	25	Each time the man put strength into his arm, the head of the dildo gouged into her vagina forcefully.
OB002A	8	26	His hand usage appeared reckless at first glance, but the jutting end stimulated Oboro's G-spot without fail.
OB002A	8	27	Luz: 「N, not therrrre! Nnoh, rubbing all over thad place, c, cowarrrrd!!」
OB002A	8	28	Chara man: 「Coward? I don't know what you mean, Babaa! Ora, I'll make it so that I won't hear things like that again!」
OB002A	8	29	Luz: 「Nhiiiiiiiiih?! Aguh, nhiiiiiiiiih!!」
OB002A	8	30	Oboro's entire body shook over and over again from the man's tenacious G-spot teasing.
OB002A	8	31	The love juices which flooded out endlessly from inside her vagina were scraped out by the enormous glans, making squishing sounds.
OB002A	8	32	Chara man: 「No matter what you say, it's pointless, when you're leaking cunt juices like you've pissed yourself, Babaa♪ Everyone〜, from here on, we're really going for it!」
OB002A	8	33	As he stated, the man's hand immediately increased in speed.
OB002A	8	34	Luz: 「Ohoooooohhhhhh?! Oho, hoooooooooonnh!!」
OB002A	8	35	Luz: 「G, gonna bweeeak?! If you do it thish hard, it's gonna bweeeeeaaak!!」
OB002A	8	36	Chara man: 「Wow, your cunt folds keep clinging to it♪ This footage and its sloppy sounds are seriously dirty, aren't they?」
OB002A	8	37	Oboro didn't have the composure to talk back to the man, who smiled crudely.
OB002A	8	38	She could do nothing but writhe from the sensation, which felt like her internal organs were being dragged out along with the dildo.
OB002A	8	39	However, a large amount of cloudy, sticky love juices continuously overflowed from her vagina.
OB002A	8	40	Chara man: 「Can you see these gooey cunt juices properly?♪ They're super-thick and frothy. Man, the inside of the room actually smells of bitch♪」
OB002A	9	1	Before she knew it, a hot, moist air was filling the room.
OB002A	9	2	The smell of not only Oboro's love juices, but her sweat, breath, and every secretion she made, combined to form a strong sexual odour.
OB002A	9	3	Luz: 「Ahhhh! Nnooh! D, don't smell iiit! Nbuh, nnuh, oh, ooohh☆」
OB002A	9	4	The proof of her own pleasure kindled Oboro's sexual urges.
OB002A	9	5	Her body ached and grew even hotter, as though the lewd smell had directly stimulated her brain.
OB002A	9	6	Chara man: 「Ahhh〜, this old lady is getting off from the smell of her own cunt! That's too pathetic. Shall we go for the second one soon?」
OB002A	9	7	Luz: 「No......! Don't, stooop......!!」
OB002A	9	8	Oboro raised a stiff voice due to the meaning of the words, “the second one”.
OB002A	9	9	The man naturally ignored her voice, which contained no bluffing at all, and was just intended to hold him back.
OB002A	9	10	Chara man: 「Okay, the final stretch♪」
OB002A	9	11	Luz: 「Nnoooohh! Ogih, ngiiiiiih?! This is, bad! No mooooorrre!」
OB002A	9	12	Chara man: 「I'm gonna make sure to wreck her!」
OB002A	9	13	Chara man: 「See, your cunt's tightening up, isn't it?! Have another unsightly orgasm right now!」
OB002A	9	14	The dildo's pumping seemed to slam the waist of Oboro, who bucked and writhed, onto the bed.
OB002A	9	15	Oboro clenched her teeth and tried to hold on, but the moment was right in front of her eyes.
OB002A	9	16	Chara man: 「Hoi, here's the finisher!!」
OB002A	9	17	Bujuuuu! Jubuuuuuuuuh!!
OB002A	9	18	Luz: 「Oh hooooooooooooohhhhhhhhhh☆」
OB002A	9	19	Having been thrust in with all his might, the dildo was buried to the hilt, and Oboro reached her second climax.
OB002A	9	20	She bucked a lot, and squirted furiously from her stiffened groin again.
OB002A	9	21	Chara man: 「Hey, old lady! Two streaks of fuck juices are rising from your orgasm〜♪ Your cervix is twitching and holding the dildo deep inside〜」
OB002A	9	22	Luz: 「Nnoooohhh?! Ahiah, the back's bein pushed ooonnnn☆ Cumming fwom mah womb bein cruuuusssshed!!」
OB002A	9	23	With the dildo digging into her deepest place, her vaginal flesh, which fiercely climaxed, squeezed it hard.
OB002A	9	24	The mere feeling of the dildo filling her flesh cavern to capacity drove Oboro to climax over and over again.
OB002A	9	25	Luz: 「W, won't shtoooooohhhp☆ Nnooooohhh! The cummiiing, and the squirting won' shtoooohooopp!!」
OB002A	9	26	Chara man: 「The drug is working more than the first time, so your orgasm's pretty flashy, too!」
OB002A	9	27	Chara man: 「No matter how tough she acts, in the end, a woman will instantly go crazy and expose an ahegao from some pussy teasing♪」
OB002A	9	28	Luz: 「Agiiiiiiih??!! Grinding the baaack!! Stob, c, comen out agaaaiiinnnnn!!」
OB002A	9	29	The dildo was pushed in, so as to emphasize it to the camera, and the squirting from her groin increased in force again.
OB002A	9	30	The current that intermittently spurted out was scattered over a wide area, and even reached right up close to the camera.
OB002A	9	31	Chara man: 「Hey, we're capturing some intense footage, aren't we〜? Ah, but if you get any on the camera, I'll kill you, old bat! Go easy on the squirting〜♪」
OB002A	9	32	Luz: 「It, it'sh noh lie, I caaaaaaannnnn☆ Ohiah, h, how long izzit gon come ouuuut??!!」
OB002A	9	33	Chara man: 「If you squirt on the lens, I'll have to stop the stream, you know?! You gonna take responsibility if that happens?!」
OB002A	9	34	Luz: 「S, sayin somefin lie haaat?! Ahiah, no good, don't moooooob!!」
OB002A	9	35	What the man was saying was absurd, but Oboro couldn't do anything about it right now.
OB002A	9	36	She could do nothing but latch onto the dildo with her vaginal flesh, and climax while shaking her hips.
OB002A	9	37	Chara man: 「That said, you squirt too much, don't you, old lady?! What's wrong with your cunt?!」
OB002A	9	38	Luz: 「B, buhd it won'd shtop, so I can't hel――Ohooooohhhh!! Gohha squird agyaaaiiinnnnn!!」
OB002A	9	39	Oboro's squirting continued intermittently, growing in intensity to the point where the charao showed genuine concern for the camera.
OB002A	9	40	By the time the last drop ran down from her vagina, the strength had gone out from her entire body.
OB002A	10	1	Luz: 「Ahia, hahi...... nnooh......☆」
OB002A	10	2	Chara man: 「Fuu〜! Well, that was close. The camera was safe somehow, but――right now, this place is a
OB002A	10	3	The focus of the man's sneering look――
OB002A	10	4	The squirting had abated, but since all strength in her body had faded, urine was forcefully flooding out from Oboro's groin.
OB002A	10	5	A yellow puddle was spreading out beneath her ass.
OB002A	10	6	Chara man: 「Man, what a spectacular sight〜. It's really too bad I can't transmit this smell. It packs a punch♪」
OB002A	10	7	Chara man: 「Anyway, please watch the old broad's wetting scene closely, okay? If you like, please throw in donations too〜♪」
OB002A	10	8	Luz: 「S, shtop...... Don'd look...... nnh...」
OB002A	10	9	Oboro could do nothing but moan feebly as she exposed an even more humiliating appearance than the first time.
OB002A	10	10	Chara man: 「What did you say? It was the best, having them watch you cum hard and accidentally piss yourself in excitement? Oh, Oden-san says that was 『the bestest』. Thanks for donating 20 000, too♪」
OB002A	10	11	Luz: 「Sh, shut up...... It's not that I, peed out of excitement...... Nhih, nnohh...... S, shtop......!」
OB002A	10	12	Numb from the afterglow, her arms and legs wouldn't move, but Oboro mustered her shaking voice and talked back.
OB002A	10	13	Chara man: 「Ohh? This old broad is still rebellious, huh? Even though, normally, she would either be crying and saying 『Please forgive me』, or her brain would be broken.」
OB002A	10	14	Luz: 「Don, underestimate me...... There's no way, I'd lose...... to the likes of you...」
OB002A	10	15	The man made a face that said he was truly surprised that she still had the sense to resist.
OB002A	10	16	However, that face immediately twisted into a dirty smirk.
OB002A	10	17	Chara man: 「Everyone, you should look forward to this tonight! It looks like I can finally get serious!」
OB002A	10	18	Luz: 「S, serious......?」
OB002A	10	19	Chara man: 「Just about all the women so far have fallen by this point, after all. Hey, yeah, Ricky-san wants 『Babaa losing to the dick and cumming hard』. Sure thing! Thanks for the 300 yen〜」
OB002A	10	20	The character strings that the man read out were all excited and looking forward to what was going to happen after this.
OB002A	10	21	Chara man: 「K16? Oh, Keichiro-san. Thanks for the 8000 yen donation〜♪」
OB002A	10	22	Chara man: 「『With this one, put your huge dick inside.』 Yeah, like you say! Her old lady pussy is properly warmed-up!」
OB002A	10	23	Luz: 「Wh, what...... are you saying? Everything up to now was a warm...up......?」
OB002A	10	24	What had been done up to this point had only been a warmup exercise.
OB002A	10	25	The man pointed his eyes, which gleamed with excitement, at Oboro, who stiffened up from those unbelievable words.
OB002A	10	26	Chara man: 「Oh, you're making a nice face, aren't you, old lady? I messed up and broke the last woman's cunt, see? That's why I learned my lesson and bought this.」
OB002A	10	27	Chara man: 「Understand, Babaa? I slammed this thing in for the sake of fucking you hard with my mega-dick. I've warmed you up, so prepare yourself, okay?」
OB002A	10	28	Luz: 「Th, that's...... S, stop......!」
OB002A	10	29	“If I experience greater pleasure than this――”
OB002A	10	30	Oboro, who felt fear and raised a shrieking voice, had no way to resist.
OB002A	10	31	SALTAR: OB002A_2
