S003A	1	1	Several days later, Gosha Village.
S003A	1	2	Gosha Village was the headquarters of the Taimanin, which had been created by assembling the shinobi who were scattered all across the country.
S003A	1	3	“Gosha” was said to signify the five （go） elements―wood, fire, earth, metal and water―that were the basis of their ninja arts, and the pinwheels （sha） that ninja had used since ancient times―i.e., throwing stars.
S003A	1	4	Information about the hidden village was thoroughly suppressed, so outsiders had no way of knowing about it, but most of the buildings that had sprung up, and the people who lived in this village normally, were ninja-related.
S003A	1	5	Of course, that was the same for the “Academy”, too.
S003A	1	6	Despite ostensibly being operated as a normal school, Gosha Academy, which had been built on a mountainside that overlooked the town, had a hidden face as a Taimanin training institution, which would educate the next generation of ninja.
S003A	1	7	Gosha Academy, Principal's Office.
S003A	1	8	In there were the figures of Yamamoto, who also held the position of school Principal, and Asagi, who had been summoned by him.
S003A	1	9	Yamamoto: 「――What about the uniform?」
S003A	1	10	Asagi: 「That doesn't matter, does it? I don't intend to stay in a place like this for long.」
S003A	1	11	Asagi answered, bluntly.
S003A	1	12	She wasn't about to do anything bothersome, like take the trouble to get a new uniform.
S003A	1	13	What Asagi was wearing was the uniform of Joei Academy, which she had gotten used to.
S003A	1	14	Yamamoto: 「Hmm――Well, you're right.」
S003A	1	15	Yamamoto: 「It's no big deal. I will tell the people in the school for you.」
S003A	1	16	Asagi: 「As you like...... So, what are we doing? What's the reason for making me sneak into a place like this?」
S003A	1	17	Asagi asked.
S003A	1	18	Having been notified of the shocking news of 『Sakura's disappearance』, there had been no other choice for Asagi.
S003A	1	19	Cooperation with the
S003A	1	20	And, as for the details of that, what she had been instructed to perform was an infiltration mission into this Gosha Academy.
S003A	1	21	Yamamoto: 「In order to explain that...... First, I have to explain the situation in Gosha.」
S003A	1	22	Yamamoto nodded solemnly, and opened his mouth.
S003A	1	23	Yamamoto: 「I wonder how much you know about the present situation in this village?」
S003A	1	24	Asagi: 「I dunno. I have no interest in a place like this.」
S003A	1	25	Asagi shook her head.
S003A	1	26	Gosha Village was a town that the government had provided for the purpose of “Taimanin unification”.
S003A	1	27	They integrated the Taimanin, and, in return for coming under control of the government, gave them all sorts of backing and patronage.
S003A	1	28	Having opposed that course of events, Asagi had taken a few subordinates and broken away, and was living separately from Sakura, who went to Gosha Academy in order to become a “government-manufactured” Taimanin.
S003A	1	29	Consequently, she had even been informed of the serious matter of 『Sakura's disappearance』 by Yamamoto's mouth.
S003A	1	30	Yamamoto: 「I'd have to say the situation right now is...... a little fishy.」
S003A	1	31	Asagi: 「What do you mean?」
S003A	1	32	
S003A	1	33	Yamamoto: 「Even you are aware, of course, that all the shinobi in the country have migrated to this Gosha Village?」
S003A	1	34	Asagi nodded in silence.
S003A	1	35	The unification of the Taimanin――That was a project that was advanced by government officials, including Yamamoto.
S003A	1	36	Yamamoto: 「However...... Even now, when they have united on the government's side like this, the Taimanin are still not monolithic.」
S003A	1	37	Yamamoto: 「The power struggles of the influential clans have become more extreme, and they are each contesting the position of leader of the Taimanin.」
S003A	1	38	Yamamoto: 「Also, even though they've ostensibly fallen into line, there are also members who obey superficially, and whose true intentions are unknown.」
S003A	1	39	Yamamoto: 「The likes of the Fuuma clan are first on the list.」
S003A	1	40	Asagi: 「Fuuma, huh......?」
S003A	2	1	Asagi muttered, like she was displeased.
S003A	2	2	The shinobi of the Fuuma clan had a strong tendency to prioritize their own desires over Taimanin justice.
S003A	2	3	Naturally, Asagi didn't harbour any good feelings in regard to the Fuuma clan.
S003A	2	4	Asagi: 「But, what kind of connection is there between that and Sakura? Sakura disappeared in this school, right?」
S003A	2	5	Yamamoto: 「......It appears that even this Academy is not unrelated to historical ties like that.」
S003A	2	6	“Ties” referred to the infighting among fellow Taimanin, which had no sign of dying down even now.
S003A	2	7	Yamamoto: 「Young Taimanin who are affiliated with all sorts of powers go to this school.」
S003A	2	8	Yamamoto: 「It's truly regrettable, but the secret feuds, and sabotage of each other's success, are practiced even in this place.」
S003A	2	9	Asagi: 「You're saying Sakura got dragged into those stupid conflicts?」
S003A	2	10	Asagi said, like she had lost her patience.
S003A	2	11	Worthless infighting――That was one of the reasons why Asagi opposed the Taimanin unification.
S003A	2	12	Yamamoto: 「The likelihood is high...... However, there is no evidence.」
S003A	2	13	Yamamoto: 「To be frank, as things stand right now, the investigation is in a deadlock situation.」
S003A	2	14	Asagi: 「Bait to lure those guys out――You're telling me to become “bait”, right?」
S003A	2	15	If, as Yamamoto surmised, the Academy staff were connected to Sakura's disappearance, they wouldn't watch in silence when her sister Asagi, who was the head of the Igawa family, moved into the school.
S003A	2	16	They would invariably take some kind of action, so――
S003A	2	17	It seemed to be Yamamoto's intention to turn that into a foothold for rescuing Sakura.
S003A	2	18	Yamamoto: 「Will you agree to that?」
S003A	2	19	Asagi: 「That goes without saying.」
S003A	2	20	Asagi: 「No matter what kind of strategy you may have, I'll do anything if it's for the sake of saving that girl――」
S003A	2	21	They had been living apart temporarily, but Asagi considered her sister, Sakura, truly precious.
S003A	2	22	If there was even a small possibility of a rescue, she couldn't hesitate.
S003A	2	23	Yamamoto: 「I thank you for cooperating. Apart from that...... I'll dare to ask you this.」
S003A	2	24	Yamamoto: 「Do you believe that Igawa Sakura――your sister is alive even now?」
S003A	2	25	A cruel question, as if to verify Asagi's determination.
S003A	2	26	Asagi answered without hesitating even a little.
S003A	2	27	Asagi: 「Yeah. That girl is alive.」
S003A	2	28	Yamamoto: 「Why do you think so? Even though it's almost a week since she disappeared, and we can barely even get a clue as to her whereabouts?」
S003A	2	29	Asagi: 「If killing her were the objective, then her dead body would have already surfaced. There's no point in hiding it.」
S003A	2	30	Yamamoto nodded at Asagi's words.
S003A	2	31	Yamamoto: 「......I agree. I think so as well.」
S003A	2	32	Asagi: 「In that case, let's each do our best.」
S003A	2	33	Asagi: 「I'll be good “bait”. And then, I'll definitely rescue Sakura.」
S003A	2	34	Asagi: 「Old ma...... Principal, you eliminate the elements in the school who caused this worthless disturbance.」
S003A	2	35	Yamamoto: 「Understood. What will you do first?」
S003A	2	36	Yamamoto: 「I think I'll basically leave how you act in this school up to you.」
S003A	2	37	Asagi: 「I see......」
S003A	2	38	Asagi thought about it a little, and replied.
S003A	2	39	She had thought about that point in advance.
S003A	2	40	Asagi: 「First, I'm going to meet the girl she called her “best friend”.」
S003A	3	1	Sakura's “best friend” was no stranger to Asagi.
S003A	3	2	If she remembered correctly, she had been told that they were the Student Council President at this school......
S003A	3	3	Yamamoto: 「Hmm, that would be fine...... Well, finally, I shall introduce your homeroom teacher.」
S003A	3	4	Yamamoto said, and placed a hand on his intercom.
S003A	3	5	Don-don――
S003A	3	6	Mujer: 「――Excuse me, Principal Yamamoto.」
S003A	3	7	Following a gentle knocking sound, a female teacher entered the Principal's Office.
S003A	3	8	Yamamoto: 「This is Koukawa Oboro-sensei. She is the homeroom teacher for your class, and will back you up on this matter.」
S003A	3	9	Luz: 「You're Asagi-san? I've heard about you. It's nice to meet you.」
S003A	3	10	Receiving an introduction from Yamamoto, the woman smiled at Asagi.
S003A	3	11	She was a beautiful woman.
S003A	3	12	With breasts and hips that formed abundant curves, which couldn't help but draw a man's eyes.
S003A	3	13	Even from her expression, one could sense the natural composure typical of an adult woman.
S003A	3	14	However――
S003A	3	15	It was a different thing that Asagi was concerned about.
S003A	3	16	Asagi: 「Koukawa......?」
S003A	3	17	Luz: 「Fufu. Had the times not changed, we would be enemies, wouldn't we? I wonder if you're displeased?」
S003A	3	18	Asagi: 「............」
S003A	3	19	『Had the times not changed』――It was certainly as the woman said.
S003A	3	20	The Igawa and the Koukawa were distinguished families which one could call the two major ninja powers, and they had subjugated most ninja families, from the highest- to the lowest-ranking, to be their subordinates.
S003A	3	21	Like Takeda and Uesugi during the Sengoku period, for example.
S003A	3	22	Since ancient times, the two houses had been mutual enemies, who had refined their ninja arts by engaging in a bloody feud with each other.
S003A	3	23	Asagi: （That Koukawa woman is my support......?）
S003A	3	24	While harbouring misgivings, Asagi answered the woman's question.
S003A	3	25	Asagi: 「No...... It's just that I'd heard that the Koukawa weren't cooperative with
S003A	3	26	Luz: 「That's not wrong. But exceptions exist in everything. Like your little sister, right?」
S003A	3	27	Asagi: 「............」
S003A	3	28	Against the will of Asagi, who was the head of the Igawa family, Sakura had become a Taimanin who cooperated with the government.
S003A	3	29	Was this woman trying to say that she was like that too?
S003A	3	30	Asagi: 「......Thanks for your help over this little while.」
S003A	3	31	Asagi lightly bowed her head towards the female teacher.
S003A	3	32	There were too many things to be concerned about with regards to this woman...... But, there was no basis for finding fault with her right now.
S003A	3	33	Luz: 「Don't say little. I'd be pleased if we could have classes together for a long time to come♪」
S003A	3	34	Asagi: 「Haah......」
S003A	3	35	She was seemingly gentle, but her smile somehow gave the impression of bottomless ambition.
S003A	3	36	To be frank, she was the type Asagi didn't like.
S003A	3	37	Asagi: （What the hell is her intention......?）
S003A	3	38	Asagi took a fleeting glance at the expression of Yamamoto, who stood next to the woman.
S003A	3	39	To introduce a woman from the Koukawa family, which was antagonistic toward the Igawa family, just after having told her that “The Taimanin are not monolithic”――
S003A	3	40	Meant that, just speaking of possibilities, he was also considering that this woman could be the culprit who had abducted Sakura.
S003A	4	1	Yamamoto: 「............」
S003A	4	2	However, she couldn't read Yamamoto's intentions from his usual sullen face.
S003A	4	3	Asagi: （Is he saying I can trust this woman......?）
S003A	4	4	Or, was he telling her to ascertain the enemy side's movements through this woman......?
S003A	4	5	Luz: 「Fufu, Asagi-san. Do you still need something from Kouchou-sensei （Principal）?」
S003A	4	6	The woman's kind-sounding voice broke through Asagi's thoughts.
S003A	4	7	Asagi: 「No, not really......」
S003A	4	8	Luz: 「I see♪ Then, come. I'll guide you to your class.」
S003A	4	9	The woman bowed at Yamamoto, and showed Asagi out of the Principal's Office.
S003A	4	10	Asagi: （Oh well. Even if I think about it, there's no choice right now......）
S003A	4	11	Whether or not the woman was truly trustworthy――She could ascertain that in the investigation after this.
S003A	4	12	Asagi thought so, and left the Principal's Office, following behind the woman.
S003A	4	13	Luz: 「This is Igawa Asagi-san, a transfer student. Everyone, please get along with her, all right?」
S003A	4	14	Asagi: 「I'm Igawa. Pleased to meet you......」
S003A	4	15	Asagi, who had entered the classroom together with Oboro, had been introduced as a transfer student.
S003A	4	16	The name of the young head of the Igawa clan, a prestigious ninja family, was well-known among the Taimanin.
S003A	4	17	――Igawa? That's...?!
S003A	4	18	――Looks like it. That's Igawa Asagi!!
S003A	4	19	The inside of the classroom became noisy.
S003A	4	20	The students had expressions of great interest due to the sudden arrival of a celebrity.
S003A	4	21	There was no doubt that more than half the people had only heard rumours, and didn't recognize Asagi's face.
S003A	4	22	“For That head of the Igawa family to be such a beautiful girl”――Many of the male students had faces which looked like they were going to whistle at her.
S003A	4	23	Luz: 「Well then, Asagi-san, take your seat.」
S003A	4	24	Asagi: 「Yes......」
S003A	4	25	Despite being disgusted by those observant looks, Asagi headed for her seat, and――
S003A	4	26	Asagi: （This is......?）
S003A	4	27	In the middle of that, out of nowhere, she had sensed a different kind of look.
S003A	4	28	It was completely different from the curious, inquisitive looks of the students.
S003A	4	29	It didn't go as far as murderous intent, but, for example, it was like a cunning hyena waiting for its prey to weaken――?
S003A	4	30	Asagi: （Inside the classroom? Or outside......?）
S003A	4	31	Outside the classroom, she could see the figures of several teachers who were peering in, trying to see the 『celebrity』.
S003A	4	32	However, she didn't know who the owner of the crucial look was.
S003A	4	33	Just a sticky gaze which harboured an unpleasant intent――
S003A	4	34	She could definitely feel it persistently creeping along the surface of her skin.
S003A	4	35	Asagi: （『Members who obey superficially,』 huh......?）
S003A	4	36	A shiver of disgust ran along her spine.
S003A	4	37	It was as Yamamoto had told her.
S003A	4	38	There was an enemy she couldn't be careless about inside the Academy――From the unusual gaze that was focused on her, Asagi was convinced of that.
S003A	4	39	SALTAR: S004A
