S014A	1	1	After school that day, Sakura was at the Academy pool.
S014A	1	2	Sakura: 「Um〜? Sensei, you had something important to talk about?」
S014A	1	3	While students performing their club activities did stretches by the poolside, Sakura called out to a certain man.
S014A	1	4	That man was Hachiya Risuke, the phys. ed. teacher and Swim Club adviser.
S014A	1	5	Sakura had no way of knowing this, but he was the Bedroom Art user who would later attack Asagi in this pool.
S014A	1	6	Flecha de abeja: 「So you've arrived, Igawa. Sorry to call you so suddenly.」
S014A	1	7	Sakura: 「Nah〜, that's okay, but...... By any chance, is this about extra lessons or something?」
S014A	1	8	Sakura asked, fearfully.
S014A	1	9	Sakura had outstanding marks in practical skills, like battles and so forth, but she was fairly undependable where the general curriculum was concerned.
S014A	1	10	Flecha de abeja: 「Kuku, not at all, not at all. It's a more important matter than supplementary lessons――It's about a mission.」
S014A	1	11	Flecha de abeja: 「As a matter of fact, I have a task I'd like you to take care of.」
S014A	1	12	Sakura: 「Heh?! News of a mission, from Hachiya-sensei......?」
S014A	1	13	Flecha de abeja: 「Yes. Do you have an objection, or something?」
S014A	1	14	Sakura: 「I, I'm not saying that, but...... News about missions has always come from Kouchou-sensei......」
S014A	1	15	Sakura cocked her head.
S014A	1	16	This was the first time she had received a directive for a mission from someone other than Principal Yamamoto.
S014A	1	17	Flecha de abeja: 「Which means it's that important a mission, right?」
S014A	1	18	Hachiya nodded, expressing a self-important smile on his greasy face.
S014A	1	19	Flecha de abeja: 「An unofficial request has come in through a top-secret route, so that it won't be known to anyone――especially Principal Yamamoto.」
S014A	1	20	Flecha de abeja: 「The client is a certain government official who is also connected to the Taimanin organization. It's the kind of request where we absolutely cannot fail.」
S014A	1	21	Sakura: 「G, government? What is it......?!」
S014A	1	22	Sakura opened her eyes wide from his unexpected words.
S014A	1	23	Flecha de abeja: 「Now listen, Igawa...... I know that you and Principal Yamamoto have been searching for the “Chaos Arena”.」
S014A	1	24	Flecha de abeja: 「I'm told you're still barely able to obtain any clues, though, right?」
S014A	1	25	Sakura: 「Y, yeah......」
S014A	1	26	The “Chaos Arena” was an extremely cruel underground stadium. They said it made female combatants fight each other, and if they lost, it would impose a punishment game that was no better than death.
S014A	1	27	They also had intelligence that it was a source of funds for the “Nomad” crime syndicate, which made the Tokyo underworld its headquarters, and Sakura and Yamamoto had been chasing after clues to it for the past few months.
S014A	1	28	Sakura: 「What's the connection between that matter and the Chaos Arena, though......?」
S014A	1	29	Flecha de abeja: 「The truth is――it appears the son of our client, the government official, has been kidnapped by the guys from Nomad.」
S014A	1	30	Sakura: 「Ehh?! K, kidnapped?!」
S014A	1	31	Flecha de abeja: 「Idiot! Keep your voice down! I said this is a top-secret mission, didn't I?」
S014A	1	32	Sakura: 「Hah...... Th, that's right......」
S014A	1	33	Taken in by Hachiya, Sakura lowered her voice apologetically.
S014A	1	34	Flecha de abeja: 「Well, it's all right, I guess――Anyway, a demand arrived at that government official's place.」
S014A	1	35	Flecha de abeja: 「“If you want to save your son, stop the investigation into the Chaos Arena. Make the Taimanin withdraw.”」
S014A	1	36	Sakura: 「That means...... my investigation with the Principal......?」
S014A	1	37	Flecha de abeja: 「Seems like it. Those guys at Nomad are displeased with your investigation.」
S014A	1	38	Flecha de abeja: 「It seems that's why they made a demand like this...... However, Principal Yamamoto is a person who would never give in to threats.」
S014A	1	39	Flecha de abeja: 「He would carry out his own justice, without caring that a child's life depends on it.」
S014A	1	40	Sakura: 「Uh, umm......? But, no matter how stern Kouchou-sensei is, I don't think he's that bad, though......」
S014A	2	1	Flecha de abeja: 「Well, our “client” thought so. That's why this unofficial request came my way.」
S014A	2	2	Flecha de abeja: 「He said he wants us to safely rescue Ichisuke-kun――his kidnapped son.」
S014A	2	3	Hachiya said, and took out a photo of a boy to show Sakura.
S014A	2	4	This 『Ichisuke』 was Risuke's older brother, who had taken the form of a little boy, and this request itself was a cowardly trap for the purpose of luring Sakura, but――
S014A	2	5	Naturally, Sakura had no way of knowing that.
S014A	2	6	Sakura: 「Such a small boy...... Hmm, we can't allow that, can we?」
S014A	2	7	Flecha de abeja: 「Do you want to rescue him?」
S014A	2	8	Sakura: 「Of course! How helpless is he feeling about now, getting carried off by bad guys?!」
S014A	2	9	Flecha de abeja: 「Yeah, that's your mission. Go safely rescue Ichisuke-kun.」
S014A	2	10	Sakura: 「Heh......?」
S014A	2	11	Sakura made a blank face.
S014A	2	12	It looked like she had never considered that that would be the mission.
S014A	2	13	Sakura: 「W, wait a sec?! An important mission like that, for me?!」
S014A	2	14	Even though she was a Taimanin with outstanding ability, Sakura was still a student in training.
S014A	2	15	So far, Yamamoto had almost never assigned Sakura a dangerous mission like a solo infiltration.
S014A	2	16	Flecha de abeja: 「Certainly, where missions you'd give to a student are concerned, it may be going too far. But I'm counting on you, Igawa.」
S014A	2	17	Sakura: 「On me......?」
S014A	2	18	Hachiya made a theatrically sad-looking face at Sakura, who tilted her head to the side, and
S014A	2	19	Flecha de abeja: 「Because I was helped quite a lot by your father. Although I may not look like it, I'm a patron of the great Igawa family.」
S014A	2	20	Sakura: 「I feel like this is the first I've heard about something like that......」
S014A	2	21	Flecha de abeja: 「Huh?」
S014A	2	22	Sakura: 「N, no! It's nothing!」
S014A	2	23	Being sternly glared at, Sakura shook her head in a panic.
S014A	2	24	Flecha de abeja: 「Well, that being the case, I want you to mature, for your father's sake as well.」
S014A	2	25	Flecha de abeja: 「For that reason, I think that it's most important to experience a hard mission like this, and that, given your ability, you'll be able to do it satisfactorily.」
S014A	2	26	Sakura: 「Th, thank you very much......」
S014A	2	27	Flecha de abeja: 「Since this is unofficial, it's a dangerous mission, with no backup. If you refuse, there's nothing that can be done.」
S014A	2	28	Flecha de abeja: 「Just in this case, for Ichisuke-kun's sake, I want to keep this secret from Principal Yamamoto and everybody else......」
S014A	2	29	Hachiya said, and waited for Sakura's decision.
S014A	2	30	Sakura: 「Well... That's right, isn't it......?」
S014A	2	31	Sakura thought about it just a little, and immediately decided.
S014A	2	32	It certainly was a dangerous and difficult-seeming mission, but when she thought about that kidnapped child, she couldn't help but lose her nerve.
S014A	2	33	If there was someone in trouble, she couldn't overlook it. If someone was depending on her, she wanted to do something.
S014A	2	34	It was simple-minded, but that was Sakura's nature.
S014A	2	35	Sakura: 「Understood, Sensei......! But, can I be of any help?」
S014A	2	36	Flecha de abeja: 「Oh, you'll do it?! You've saved me, Igawa!」
S014A	2	37	Hachiya exaggeratedly bowed towards Sakura like he was satisfied, and
S014A	2	38	Flecha de abeja: 「Of course! Far from helping, this is a mission that can't be done by anyone but you!」
S014A	2	39	Flecha de abeja: 「I'll have you infiltrate the Chaos Arena as a female combatant.」
S014A	2	40	Sakura: 「Hey?! W, wait a sec! The Chaos Arena...... Does Sensei know its location?!」
S014A	3	1	The whereabouts of the Chaos Arena had not been discovered, even by Sakura and Yamamoto's all-out investigation.
S014A	3	2	This gym teacher knew something like that......?
S014A	3	3	Flecha de abeja: 「It's not me that knows, but the “client”, the government official.」
S014A	3	4	Flecha de abeja: 「After all, the Chaos Arena is like a distasteful sports show for the rich.」
S014A	3	5	Flecha de abeja: 「It's hidden by wealth and power. Through the normal way of doing things, its location won't be discovered no matter how much you search. However――」
S014A	3	6	Hachiya grinned, and continued talking.
S014A	3	7	Flecha de abeja: 「Our “client” has wealth and power too.」
S014A	3	8	Flecha de abeja: 「He has gathered information from contacts among his colleagues, and has finally squeezed the location of the Chaos Arena out of them.」
S014A	3	9	Flecha de abeja: 「And, the fact that a guy called Zokuto, a slave trader attached to the Chaos Arena, is searching for female combatants.」
S014A	3	10	Sakura: 「So......? I meet that person and sneak into the Chaos Arena......?」
S014A	3	11	Flecha de abeja: 「Exactly. It appears that Ichisuke-kun is being held captive inside the Chaos Arena.」
S014A	3	12	Flecha de abeja: 「Our “client” will prolong the bargaining with them to buy time, so during that, you will find Ichisuke-kun and rescue him.」
S014A	3	13	Flecha de abeja: 「A solo infiltration will make for a difficult mission, though...... Will you do it, Igawa?」
S014A	3	14	Sakura: 「Roger, Hachiya-sensei! Please leave it to Igawa Sakura!」
S014A	3	15	Sakura enthusiastically replied.
S014A	3	16	There was no time to think about it.
S014A	3	17	To rescue a kidnapped child―a person who had been tyrannized―was a natural act for a Taimanin.
S014A	3	18	Also, if she became able to infiltrate the Chaos Arena, she would also be useful to Principal Yamamoto and her sister――
S014A	3	19	――About half a day after that exchange.
S014A	3	20	Sakura: （I never thought I'd be able to infiltrate it this easily〜）
S014A	3	21	The illegal underground stadium, the Chaos Arena.
S014A	3	22	Considering the time and effort she had spent searching for its location, it was so easy as to be a letdown.
S014A	3	23	Having met with the slave trader named Zokuto in a Shinminato-ku back street, Sakura had been blindfolded and loaded into a car, just like that.
S014A	3	24	And when the blindfold was taken off, she was already in the waiting room for fighters in the Chaos Arena.
S014A	3	25	Sakura: （But...... This is a more unpleasant place than I imagined......）
S014A	3	26	Amid loud booing, Sakura was standing in the centre of the Arena.
S014A	3	27	Even for Sakura, who had witnessed many gruesome scenes on missions, this stadium was extraordinary.
S014A	3	28	A battle which was the very picture of gruesomeness, and an audience who watched that with delight.
S014A	3	29	Towards the top, there were stands which seemed to be VIP seating, and rich people who hid their faces with ostentatious masks could be seen chatting with wine in hand.
S014A	3	30	The outcome of the match―and, naturally, even the survival of the competitors―were the subject of gambling.
S014A	3	31	Sakura: （It's right that Onee-chan and Kouchou-sensei would try to shut down a place like this......）
S014A	3	32	This was certainly an establishment where it appeared that all the rotten parts of humanity had been brought together.
S014A	3	33	It was not just filled with vice and corruption, but was also a source of funds for the Nomad crime syndicate.
S014A	3	34	Sakura, who had a strong sense of justice, could not let this be.
S014A	3	35	Nonetheless――
S014A	3	36	Sakura: （But for now, I have to quietly win their confidence as a female fighter here, right?）
S014A	3	37	According to Hachiya's story, it seemed the boy was being held captive somewhere in this Arena facility.
S014A	3	38	Given that――a chance to investigate the inside of the establishment would probably come around after she had won here a few times.
S014A	3	39	In front of Sakura, who was secretly thinking about things like that, her “opponent”, Big Gogo the ogre slave, had come along, making loud footsteps.
S014A	3	40	Byg Gogo: 「Oi, pig bitch?! You're my opponent?!」
S014A	4	1	Sakura: 「That's right. Any complaints?」
S014A	4	2	
S014A	4	3	The large ogre slave gazed at Sakura's body, which was dressed in a battle suit, as if licking her from top to bottom.
S014A	4	4	Byg Gogo: 「Ororo, complaint?! Nothing like that!」
S014A	4	5	Byg Gogo: 「I think it would be a waste to fuck such a fine woman to death in one go, though!」
S014A	4	6	And then, vulgar lip-licking, which seemed like he was saying he couldn't help but look forward to that moment.
S014A	4	7	Inside his head, there was already an image of him raping Sakura as he pleased.
S014A	4	8	Sakura: 「Haah〜, dear, dear. Looks like I'll be able to fight without the slightest pity for you.」
S014A	4	9	Sakura sighed, with a composed attitude.
S014A	4	10	Because she had been watching the gruesome match just before, Sakura also knew about the danger and ferocity of the ogre slave.
S014A	4	11	Nevertheless, she couldn't be something like a Taimanin if she flinched from that.
S014A	4	12	Moderador: 『Now, everyone!! The introduction of his poor challenger!!』
S014A	4	13	Seeing that Sakura and the ogre slave had appeared on the stage, the Master of Ceremonies raised his voice.
S014A	4	14	Moderador: 『A rookie fighter, who has sold herself and joined the Chaos Arena to pay the costs of an operation for her sister, who is suffering from a serious disease! Her name is Sakura Lady!』
S014A	4	15	Moderador: 『Isn't that a touching reason?! A warm hand, everyone――And, let's hope for a miserable manner of death for Sakura Lady!』
S014A	4	16	Loud cheering arose.
S014A	4	17	Audiencia 1: 「Hihihi! Sakura Lady's nice, isn't she?! If you look closely, she's got a pretty cute face!」
S014A	4	18	Audiencia 2: 「Rape her, Big Gogo! Let's see you pierce right through that woman's cunt and kill herrr!!」
S014A	4	19	Her face was being concealed by a mask, but it seemed that Sakura's pretty features were coming across.
S014A	4	20	It looked like the spectators who had been booing her had also changed their minds, and were starting to look forward to the scene of the sweet, beautiful girl being slaughtered by the ogre.
S014A	4	21	Moderador: 『Now, everyone, please bet eagerly! What will the result of this battle be――?!』
S014A	4	22	The MC spurred on the spectators, pointing out the odds, which had been displayed on a huge monitor.
S014A	4	23	There were hardly any people betting on Sakura's victory.
S014A	4	24	They were concentrating and voting on how soon Sakura would be raped by the ogre, and how soon she would tragically die.
S014A	4	25	In a situation where she was surrounded by enemies on all sides, Sakura――
S014A	4	26	Sakura: 「Uhh〜, that profile seems like it would get me scolded by Onee-chan...... Even though I asked Zokuto-san to make it something else...」
S014A	4	27	Had a calm, utterly nonchalant attitude.
S014A	4	28	Byg Gogo: 「That's a cocky attitude, pig bitch!! Did I drive you crazy with fear?!」
S014A	4	29	Sakura: 「Mmm? You're my opponent, so I'm not concerned at all.」
S014A	4	30	Byg Gogo: 「What?! What does that mean?!」
S014A	4	31	Sakura: 「I'm saying, it'll be an easy win. So I don't suppose there's any need to be afraid.」
S014A	4	32	Sakura said, plainly, and a brutal glint appeared in the ogre's dimwitted-seeming eyes.
S014A	4	33	Byg Gogo: 「How dare you, pig bitch?! You made me angry!!」
S014A	4	34	Byg Gogo: 「I won't kill you easily!! I'm gonna rip off your arms and legs and turn you into a daruma doll, and then I'm gonna thrust my cock into your womb and mess it up――That's my favourite way to kill a bitch!」
S014A	4	35	Sakura: 「Ugh. That's siiick!」
S014A	4	36	Sakura displayed a fed-up expression due to the ogre, who howled with laughter.
S014A	4	37	In the meantime, it looked like the wagering on the battle had also been cut off.
S014A	4	38	Moderador: 『Now, at last, it's the start of the match!! Both players, are you ready?!――Begin!!』
S014A	4	39	Amid the loud, excited cheering, the gong for the start of the match was rung.
S014A	4	40	And, at the same time――
S014A	5	1	Byg Gogo: 「Oooohhhhhhhhhhhh!!」
S014A	5	2	Sakura: 「Uwaah?!」
S014A	5	3	Dogooohh!!
S014A	5	4	Quick and agile movements, which did not suit his huge build.
S014A	5	5	The fist of the ogre, who had started charging at her at the same time that the match started, rushed towards Sakura.
S014A	5	6	Sakura: 「That was close!」
S014A	5	7	Sakura just barely managed to avoid the ogre's attack.
S014A	5	8	The ogre's fist, which had been held up in the air, crashed into the Arena floor. It dug into that part of the floor so greatly that debris shot up, and a cloud of dust arose.
S014A	5	9	Sakura: 「Hieh〜?! Amazing power!!」
S014A	5	10	Byg Gogo: 「Don't run around! Oraa!! Oraaaah!!」
S014A	5	11	The ogre immediately reset his posture and chased Sakura down.
S014A	5	12	His log-like arm made a whooshing sound as it was thrust out at Sakura. However――
S014A	5	13	Sakura: 「Nyaha! Too slow, too slow〜♪」
S014A	5	14	For Sakura, who was flourishing as a student and as a Taimanin, its speed wasn't much.
S014A	5	15	Though that was also because she was used to seeing the speed of her sister, who was a Falcon Art master.
S014A	5	16	Sakura: 「Okaaay〜!! This time, I'll come from over here〜!!」
S014A	5	17	Bashu!! Zubaaah!
S014A	5	18	Byg Gogo: 「Ogoohh?!」
S014A	5	19	She launched a counterattack on the ogre, who had headed towards her with terrific speed.
S014A	5	20	The two ninja kodachi that Sakura held had cut the ogre's boulder-like body apart.
S014A	5	21	Byg Gogo: 「Uguuuhh!! How, how dare youuu?!」
S014A	5	22	The ogre's face contorted, and a spray of blood rose up.
S014A	5	23	――Oooohhhhhhhhhhh?!
S014A	5	24	The stadium grew noisy.
S014A	5	25	The young girl, who should have been helplessly massacred by Big Gogo, was showing them a battle that exceeded their expectations.
S014A	5	26	The audience raised voices of surprise and excitement――
S014A	5	27	Mixed into them were the screams of the poor spectators who had bet that 『Big Gogo will slaughter Sakura Lady in 10 seconds』.
S014A	5	28	Moderador: 『Whoooa〜, this is a surprise! Whether by chance or some kind of divine miracle, Sakura Lady has survived Big Gogo's fierce attack!』
S014A	5	29	Sakura: 「Hey〜, that's no accident, it's skill!」
S014A	5	30	While jauntily replying to the MC, Sakura took a distance from the ogre.
S014A	5	31	Although she had dealt him blows with her excellent two-blade style, it appeared that not much damage had been conferred.
S014A	5	32	Sakura: （Hmm〜, looks like it might be tough to take him down without my Shadow Escape Arts......）
S014A	5	33	It would be difficult to inflict a serious wound on the ogre's body, which was covered in tough muscle, with her shortswords alone.
S014A	5	34	Nevertheless, Sakura had infiltrated the place as an ordinary fighter.
S014A	5	35	She couldn't risk the danger of using her ninja arts and being exposed as a Taimanin.
S014A	5	36	Sakura: 「My, my〜? You're pretty tough, aren't ya〜?!」
S014A	5	37	Thus, Sakura decided to deliberately provoke the ogre.
S014A	5	38	Her intention was to aim for his crotch once he had lost his composure.
S014A	5	39	Sakura: 「But, with such a slow punch, it's no use at all〜. You can't beat me with that〜!」
S014A	5	40	Byg Gogo: 「Shut uuuuuuup!! Damn biiiiiitch!!」
S014A	6	1	The ogre roared, burning with anger.
S014A	6	2	And then, it carried out a fierce charge attack towards Sakura――
S014A	6	3	Byg Gogo: 「I'll kill you!! Kill you!! Kill youuuuuuuuuuuu!!」
S014A	6	4	It was a full-strength attack, making the muscles he boasted swell to their limits.
S014A	6	5	That seemed to be an instinctive choice, but it was correct.
S014A	6	6	Sakura, who was clearly inferior in terms of strength, and also lacking in firepower, was not good at dealing with power plays.
S014A	6	7	But――
S014A	6	8	Sakura: 「Okay! Another strike here!!」
S014A	6	9	Pushaaaa!!
S014A	6	10	A new wound had been carved into the ogre's muscles, and fresh blood spurted out.
S014A	6	11	Byg Gogo: 「Gunuuuuuhh?!」
S014A	6	12	A fierce attack by the ogre――However, its speed was far too mediocre.
S014A	6	13	Sakura easily avoided it. Another counter-strike.
S014A	6	14	Sakura: 「Nyahaha〜! Oji-san, if you're gonna give up, do it right now〜♪」
S014A	6	15	Byg Gogo: 「D, don't make light of me, soooooooowwwww!!!」
S014A	6	16	A large swing of his fist with all his anger behind it, which left him vulnerable to attack.
S014A	6	17	That slipped past Sakura and slammed into the stadium floor.
S014A	6	18	Sakura: （Great!! With this opening――）
S014A	6	19	It was as Sakura planned.
S014A	6	20	Aiming for the ogre's crotch, which was open to attack, she thrust her shortswords out, and――
S014A	6	21	Sakura: 「Heeh?!」
S014A	6	22	Byg Gogo: 「Gehi! Gotcha, pig biiitch!!」
S014A	6	23	Big Gogo's record of having butchered four female combatants was not just for show.
S014A	6	24	The fist that he had brought down ostentatiously blew up dirt and rubble, and Sakura and the ogre's surroundings were covered by a cloud of dust.
S014A	6	25	The ogre, who had grown accustomed to combat, had been pretending to lose control of himself in anger, cunningly aiming for a chance at a knockout blow.
S014A	6	26	If he blocked her field of vision, Sakura wouldn't be able to see the ogre's attacks.
S014A	6	27	He, on the other hand, could make use of his physique to charge at her recklessly.
S014A	6	28	Byg Gogo: 「Uoooooohhhhhhhh!!」
S014A	6	29	As if saying “Now!”, the ogre charged in the direction where he presumed Sakura was, swinging his burly arm.
S014A	6	30	The stands grew noisy.
S014A	6	31	The spectators made excited cries. They would finally get to see the impertinent woman's blood and disgraceful appearance.
S014A	6	32	Sakura: 「Hieeeh?!――――Juuust〜 kidding!!」
S014A	6	33	However, Sakura dealt with this surprise attack in an instant.
S014A	6	34	She used the dust that obstructed her vision to slip into the shadows with her superhuman-type “Shadow Escape” ninja arts, and evaded the ogre's charge――
S014A	6	35	And then, she cut around behind him.
S014A	6	36	Sakura: 「――Anti-Demon Killing Art “Two-Sword Style・Twin True Blade”!!!」
S014A	6	37	Zushaaaah!!
S014A	6	38	Byg Gogo: 「Agyaaaaaaaaaaaaah?!」
S014A	6	39	Fresh blood spurted out from the ogre's arm.
S014A	6	40	Having jumped out from a shadow behind him, Sakura had cleanly cut off the ogre's arm.
S014A	7	1	Byg Gogo: 「A, arm?! My aaaarrrrrrmmmmm?!!」
S014A	7	2	Byg Gogo: 「Uuu, so cruuuel!! What did you do, you damn whorrre?!!」
S014A	7	3	Sakura: 「Don't complain! After all, you did some pretty cruel things too――Ei!!」
S014A	7	4	Gaaahh!!
S014A	7	5	Sakura's roundhouse kick was delivered to the ogre, who screamed in shock and pain, and fainted to the ground with a thud.
S014A	7	6	Moderador: 『M, my goodness!! In a huge upset, an extraordinary situation has arisen!! Our Big Gogo has been knocked out!!』
S014A	7	7	The Master of Ceremonies shouted, making his voice shake in amazement.
S014A	7	8	Moderador: 『Sakura Lady wins!! It's a victory for the challenger, Sakura Lady!!!』
S014A	7	9	The end-of-match gong was rung.
S014A	7	10	Sakura: 「Fuu〜, that's about right! Meet Taima...... I mean, Sakura Lady!!」
S014A	7	11	On the stage, Sakura had been declared the winner.
S014A	7	12	The slave ogre fighter, Big Gogo, had had the strong arm of which he boasted cut off, and been knocked out――
S014A	7	13	It would also have been possible to slaughter the ogre by lopping off his head, but Sakura hadn't done that.
S014A	7	14	Big Gogo was a brutal, hardened killer, who had taken the lives of many female fighters.
S014A	7	15	“Even so, to go so far as to kill him”――Thinking so, Sakura had decided to merely get rid of his fighting ability.
S014A	7	16	That was because of Sakura's naivete. He would pay her back for that another day, but――that was still a long way off.
S014A	7	17	Audiencia 1: 「You're kidding me!! How did YOU win, you damn whore?!!」
S014A	7	18	Audiencia 2: 「I lost a ton, you bitch!! I won't forgive you!!」
S014A	7	19	After a few moments of silence, loud booing arose from the stands.
S014A	7	20	Sakura: 「Oh〜, amazing odds! If I'd bet on myself, I would have made a huge amount, wouldn't I?」
S014A	7	21	Showing no concern at all towards that heckling, Sakura made a composed expression as she viewed the odds chart.
S014A	7	22	It looked like that was making the spectators who had lost big increasingly annoyed.
S014A	7	23	Audiencia 1: 「Next one, quickly!! Kill that damn conceited whore!!」
S014A	7	24	Audiencia 2: 「Yeah!! Go all out, management!! We won't forgive you if you send out a half-asser!!」
S014A	7	25	Moderador: 『Certainly, everyone!! The next challenger is already standing by in the green room!!』
S014A	7	26	Responding to the spectators' voices, the MC was about to call in the next challenger.
S014A	7	27	What was taking place right now was a knockout competition.
S014A	7	28	Since Sakura had triumphed over Big Gogo, that naturally led to the entrance of the next opponent.
S014A	7	29	Moderador: 『Her brawny, bulging muscle is proof that she has the strongest power! That's right, it's her! Power La...... Eh, what?』
S014A	7	30	Perhaps because some kind of message had come in, the MC once again placed his hand on his earphone and confirmed something.
S014A	7	31	Moderador: 『Ohh〜?! This is a surprise!! All of a sudden, Sakura Lady's opponent has been changed!!』
S014A	7	32	Moderador: 『It seems there will be an appearance by “That Person”!!』
S014A	7	33	Sakura: 「Huh? That Person......?」
S014A	7	34	Sakura tilted her head.
S014A	7	35	And then, the audience reacted to the words “That Person” by making loud cheers.
S014A	7	36	Moderador: 『Everyone, please welcome her with a big hand! The next competitor is the Chaos Arena's manager, and its strongest fighter!』
S014A	7	37	Moderador: 『Entering the stage, our “Madam”, Snake Lady!!!』
S014A	7	38	SALTAR: S015A
