S016A	1	1	Downtown Shinminato-ku.
S016A	1	2	Led by Byg, the orc information dealer, Asagi had reached an area lined with enormous business buildings.
S016A	1	3	Unlike the slums, where Joei Academy (which the Igawa clan that Asagi led made its stronghold) was located,
S016A	1	4	Around this area, foreign-owned corporations were lined up in rows, and there were places that select upper-class people frequented.
S016A	1	5	Asagi: 「The Chaos Arena's...... in a place like this......?」
S016A	1	6	Asagi looked up at the building in front of her eyes like she was a little surprised.
S016A	1	7	What Byg had guided her to was an enormous building in the heart of the business district.
S016A	1	8	She couldn't believe that they were hiding an incredibly illegal facility under the appearance of a sophisticated, state-of-the-art business building.
S016A	1	9	But according to Byg, the Chaos Arena was in the basement of this building.
S016A	1	10	Byg: 「Surprised, aren'tcha? Heh heh...... It's 'cause it's supposed to be a secret party venue where the Almighty enjoy themselves.」
S016A	1	11	Asagi: 「How nauseating.」
S016A	1	12	Asagi spat out, with an irritated face.
S016A	1	13	Asagi: （It's because rotten places like this exist that we'll always have unhappy people......）
S016A	1	14	Indeed――
S016A	1	15	That was the reason why Asagi had been pursuing the Chaos Arena.
S016A	1	16	An underground show business which was said to abduct the residents of Shinminato-ku's slums, set them up as combatants to fight in an illegal stadium, and make them kill each other in bloody battles.
S016A	1	17	Unable to allow the existence of that, Asagi had been conducting an investigation independently.
S016A	1	18	Asagi: （Well...... For a hiding place, it might be appropriate.）
S016A	1	19	If the people who enjoyed the show were the “Almighty”, then she could understand the Chaos Arena being hidden in the basement of an enormous, foreign-owned building.
S016A	1	20	Asagi wouldn't have found it, no matter how much she searched the shady neighbourhoods.
S016A	1	21	Asagi: 「But that, too, ends today――」
S016A	1	22	Asagi muttered, looking up at the enormous building.
S016A	1	23	Her purpose in having come here was to rescue Sakura, but, of course, she had no intention of letting it end with just that.
S016A	1	24	The Taimanin existed to help the weak people of the world.
S016A	1	25	She was going to teach that to the miscreants who dwelled in this building――
S016A	1	26	Byg: 「Uh, um...... Asagi-no-danna? Did you say something?」
S016A	1	27	Asagi: 「It's nothing. Anyway, lead me in quickly.」
S016A	1	28	Asagi said coldly, and pointed at the entrance of the enormous building, whereupon
S016A	1	29	Byg: 「Y, yes! Right away!」
S016A	1	30	Byg bowed his head subserviently as he took out his entry ID.
S016A	1	31	Shinminato-ku, foreign corporate building, entrance.
S016A	1	32	Asagi: 「.....................」
S016A	1	33	Asagi: （Honestly. They're thoroughly-prepared, aren't they......?）
S016A	1	34	Asagi was proceeding through the deserted entrance.
S016A	1	35	Everyone had probably been ordered to leave. In spite of it being such a gigantic building, there were no signs of people around.
S016A	1	36	It was strangely silent, without the figures of guides or security guards or whatnot.
S016A	1	37	Judging from the fact that they had sent Byg as an envoy, Asagi's opponents already had full knowledge that she would come here.
S016A	1	38	Which meant that all of this was prepared for her “welcoming”.
S016A	1	39	Asagi: 「Byg, are the stairs up ahead all right?」
S016A	1	40	Byg: 「Y, yeah. That way's no problem......」
S016A	2	1	Glancing at Byg, who answered subserviently, Asagi went up the front stairway.
S016A	2	2	Since they grasped her movements, there was no point in being stealthy.
S016A	2	3	And then――
S016A	2	4	Asagi: 「............Shown up, huh?」
S016A	2	5	Clacking footstep noises resounded from the entrance.
S016A	2	6	Before Asagi ascended the staircase, a woman with captivating looks appeared.
S016A	2	7	Señora Serpiente: 「――Welcome, “Igawa Asagi”♪」
S016A	2	8	Señora Serpiente: 「Thank you for accepting my invitation. I welcome you.」
S016A	2	9	The woman smiled bewitchingly, narrowing her eyes, which gave off a cold glint.
S016A	2	10	Asagi didn't even need to hear those words.
S016A	2	11	From the air she was clad in, and her strange aura,
S016A	2	12	Asagi immediately gathered that the woman in front of her eyes was “Madam”――the proprietress of the Chaos Arena.
S016A	2	13	Asagi: 「......A reception from the boss herself? What hospitality.」
S016A	2	14	Señora Serpiente: 「Yes. That's because you're my precious “guest”.」
S016A	2	15	The woman halted ten steps ahead of Asagi.
S016A	2	16	Issoku-ittou range―― (TL: Literally "one-step-one-cut". A kendo term for the distance at which one can cut through an opponent after a single step.)
S016A	2	17	It was a distance where they could each shift to attack at any time.
S016A	2	18	Asagi: 「That's a bad joke. Entrapping my little sister――Is that any treatment for a “guest”?」
S016A	2	19	Señora Serpiente: 「Ahaha! There's no need to worry.」
S016A	2	20	Señora Serpiente: 「Your sister, Piglet-chan, is safe and alive――for now.」
S016A	2	21	Sakura was “alive”, but she couldn't guarantee anything except that.
S016A	2	22	They were words which implicitly insinuated that.
S016A	2	23	Asagi: 「I see―― Well, as thanks, I'm going to kill you.」
S016A	2	24	Asagi, whose mind shook with silent rage, pulled out and readied “Akkirokumon”, which was a memento of her father.
S016A	2	25	The woman who stood before her eyes was no ordinary person.
S016A	2	26	More than that, it seemed that she wasn't even human.
S016A	2	27	She was probably a being positioned fairly high up in hell.
S016A	2	28	This was a shrewd opponent who had even captured a Taimanin of Sakura's calibre.
S016A	2	29	――Since that was the case, Asagi would go all out from the beginning.
S016A	2	30	Señora Serpiente: 「Ara ara? That's an amazing bloodthirst, isn't it?」
S016A	2	31	The woman facing Asagi looked down at her with an expression that was filled with composure, and
S016A	2	32	Señora Serpiente: 「But didn't you hear from that orc over there? Your precious sister is my hostage.」
S016A	2	33	Asagi: 「So......?」
S016A	2	34	Señora Serpiente: 「It's settled, isn't it? Hand your weapon over to Byg. Otherwise――」
S016A	2	35	――Sakura's life would be gone.
S016A	2	36	It was a hackneyed means of threatening.
S016A	2	37	However, there was no way that Asagi was going to draw back.
S016A	2	38	If she drew back here, Sakura and Asagi herself would go down together.
S016A	2	39	Asagi: 「I refuse. If you want to disarm me, how about doing it by your own power?」
S016A	2	40	Señora Serpiente: 「Well! What an unexpected――and marvellous decision! To try and take me down without regard for your sister's life――」
S016A	3	1	At that moment, the figure of Asagi disappeared.
S016A	3	2	Byg: 「A, Asagi-no-danna?!」
S016A	3	3	At least, it looked that way to Byg, who was standing a short distance back.
S016A	3	4	Asagi had vanished like smoke.
S016A	3	5	And then, the next moment――
S016A	3	6	Asagi's high-speed charge forward, by means of her “Falcon Arts”――
S016A	3	7	Señora Serpiente: 「Ahaha!」
S016A	3	8	Gakiiih!!!
S016A	3	9	Somehow, the woman had stopped that deadly blow, which was too fast for the eye to catch, with the palm of her outstretched hand.
S016A	3	10	Superhuman strength competed with superhuman strength――
S016A	3	11	Cracks developed in the flooring from the shock of the pair's clash, and fragments of rock shot up.
S016A	3	12	The glass that had been fitted to the entry gate and the windows was breaking in a chain reaction.
S016A	3	13	Asagi: 「Haaaaaaaah!!」
S016A	3	14	But Asagi still didn't stop her charge, and put strength into both hands, which gripped Akkirokumon.
S016A	3	15	Bagigigigiginnnn!!!
S016A	3	16	That instant――
S016A	3	17	The palm of the woman's hand made a harsh noise, like that of metal being scratched.
S016A	3	18	Señora Serpiente: 「――h?!」
S016A	3	19	Bushuuuuuuu!!
S016A	3	20	A spray of blood arose from the woman's outstretched palm.
S016A	3	21	Asagi: 「Fufu――」
S016A	3	22	Smiling slightly, Asagi narrowed her eyes.
S016A	3	23	The skin of the woman's palm, which Akkirokumon had pierced through――Beneath that, a hard shine peeked out, like that of a reptile's scales.
S016A	3	24	Asagi: 「As I thought――」
S016A	3	25	Asagi: 「That form is temporary, right? Your true nature is some kind of monster.」
S016A	3	26	Señora Serpiente: 「Guuh!」
S016A	3	27	
S016A	3	28	Señora Serpiente: 「The likes of a little human...... to my skin......」
S016A	3	29	Asagi: 「If you're going to do something, you'd better do it seriously.」
S016A	3	30	Asagi: 「If you don't, then at this rate――you're going to lose to “the likes of a human”.」
S016A	3	31	Looking up at the woman, who shook with rage, Asagi curved her lips.
S016A	3	32	Señora Serpiente: 「Haha! What an annoying little girl――!!」
S016A	3	33	Asagi: 「Wha?!!」
S016A	3	34	All of a sudden, a storm of fighting intent raged between Asagi and the woman.
S016A	3	35	It was released from the woman's body without limit, and rushed toward Asagi, who readied Akkirokumon.
S016A	3	36	Señora Serpiente: 「Now, vomit blood and repent!」
S016A	3	37	Asagi: （Th, this is...... bad!!）
S016A	3	38	The fissures in the surrounding structure spread out even further due to the torrent of overwhelming power.
S016A	3	39	Asagi promptly turned around, and――
S016A	3	40	Was sent flying by the fantastic energy that the woman had given off, and was going to crash into a wall――
S016A	4	1	Just before it seemed like that would happen, Asagi parried the force by kicking off the surface of the wall, and nimbly landed on the ground.
S016A	4	2	Asagi: 「Fuuh――」
S016A	4	3	A cold sweat went along her spine.
S016A	4	4	If she hadn't avoided that at the last moment, she would probably have sustained a fatal wound.
S016A	4	5	Señora Serpiente: 「I'm surprised, Asagi! For you to make me go all-out♪」
S016A	4	6	The woman excitedly exclaimed.
S016A	4	7	An ominous serpentine aura was swirling around her.
S016A	4	8	Asagi: 「......That snake god tribe I've heard about, huh?」
S016A	4	9	There were lots of people among the mazoku who used their demonic abilities to emanate supernatural power.
S016A	4	10	And in this woman's case――That was the aura of some gigantic snakes.
S016A	4	11	The woman's demonic power had manifested in the form of a large snake, which was her true nature.
S016A	4	12	Señora Serpiente: 「Ahaha, that's right! I will tell you my true name!」
S016A	4	13	Señora Serpiente: 「I am Kaliya, of the Naga tribe! Kaliya, matriarch of the Naga tribe!」
S016A	4	14	Asagi: 「......h!!」
S016A	4	15	Asagi: （Looks like she was a more outrageous opponent than I expected, huh......?）
S016A	4	16	A clan of snake gods referred to as the Naga tribe.
S016A	4	17	Its matriarch class were even deified as gods in religions all over the world.
S016A	4	18	In other words, despite being mazoku, they possessed godhood.
S016A	4	19	Why was such a high-ranking mazoku amusing herself in the human world, acting as something like a Nomad executive?
S016A	4	20	And why was she fixated on Asagi......?
S016A	4	21	Señora Serpiente: 「Ufufu, wonderful. You “pass” for now, Igawa Asagi.」
S016A	4	22	Kaliya, the divine snake woman, descended the stairway in a good mood.
S016A	4	23	Asagi had intended to launch an attack if she got the chance, but――No matter what, she couldn't find an opportunity for that.
S016A	4	24	Señora Serpiente: 「But, finally...... I have to make sure, don't I?」
S016A	4	25	Asagi: 「Of, of what......?」
S016A	4	26	Asagi asked, making her voice shake, and the woman turned her eyes toward the entrance, where debris was strewn around.
S016A	4	27	Señora Serpiente: 「All right. Now――Byg! Take that out!」
S016A	4	28	Byg: 「Y, yes! Got it, Madam!」
S016A	4	29	The small-time orc miscreant crawled out from under the rubble like a caterpillar.
S016A	4	30	Even though he had been blown away by the shock of the pair's clash, it appeared that he had stubbornly remained alive beneath the wreckage.
S016A	4	31	Byg: 「Well...... This video's okay, right......?」
S016A	4	32	Byg ingratiatingly took out his smartphone, and displayed on the screen was――
S016A	4	33	Sakura: 『Hahii...... ohh...... hiah...... h...... aah......』
S016A	4	34	A video of her beloved sister, Sakura, being displayed in an appalling state.
S016A	4	35	Asagi: 「......h?! S, Sakura......?!」
S016A	4	36	The blood drained from Asagi's head.
S016A	4	37	A miserable facial expression that looked like Sakura had half-fainted, baring the whites of her eyes.
S016A	4	38	Her entire body was soiled by gooey, cloudy-white fluid, and Asagi especially wanted to avert her eyes from the state of her groin.
S016A	4	39	Sakura's stomach bulged out roundly like a pregnant woman's, urine was being expelled from her groin, and what looked to be an enormous dildo was sticking very deeply into her genitals.
S016A	4	40	Asagi had braced herself in advance, but――
S016A	5	1	The appearance of the captured Sakura was dozens of times more horrible than she had expected.
S016A	5	2	Señora Serpiente: 「――Now, choose, Asagi.」
S016A	5	3	The woman said softly, curving her lips bewitchingly.
S016A	5	4	Señora Serpiente: 「Do battle with me like this and have your little sister executed, or become my prisoner, like her.」
S016A	5	5	Asagi: 「Guuh......?!」
S016A	5	6	Asagi went stiff due to the excessively harsh choice.
S016A	5	7	She could hardly remain normal, being shown the extremely cruel video of Sakura.
S016A	5	8	Asagi: 「I, I did tell you...... Even if you take a hostage, it's pointless...... I'll fight......」
S016A	5	9	Señora Serpiente: 「Really? In that case, I'll just kill your little sister, then.」
S016A	5	10	Señora Serpiente: 「After all, that girl had served her purpose by the time you were summoned here.」
S016A	5	11	Asagi: 「......h!! Th, that's......」
S016A	5	12	――Her bluff wasn't going to work.
S016A	5	13	Since she had presumed that Sakura had been taken hostage, Asagi was trying to get out of this predicament by putting on a bluff that 『Sakura's life would not be a bargaining chip』.
S016A	5	14	However――
S016A	5	15	Even though she could get her own way with a hoodlum of Byg's calibre using that, it wouldn't work on the woman before her eyes――the divine mazoku, Kaliya.
S016A	5	16	This woman would readily execute Sakura as if stepping on an ant at her feet.
S016A	5	17	Señora Serpiente: 「Show me your seriousness, Asagi.」
S016A	5	18	Señora Serpiente: 「Which do you choose? What does your heart truly desire――?」
S016A	5	19	Asagi fell silent.
S016A	5	20	After having thought about it enough for the inside of her head to wear down,
S016A	5	21	Asagi: 「......Understood. I surrender.」
S016A	5	22	She said quietly, and stood down.
S016A	5	23	She placed Akkirokumon in its scabbard, and threw it over to Byg, nearby.
S016A	5	24	Asagi: 「Is this satisfactory? After this, do whatever you want with――」
S016A	5	25	Asagi stopped her words midway.
S016A	5	26	The woman's reaction was the complete opposite of what Asagi had been expecting.
S016A	5	27	Señora Serpiente: 「――Huh??? What? Are you serious?」
S016A	5	28	The woman, who had been in a good mood, was clearly disappointed.
S016A	5	29	And the aura of the huge snakes, which had been surrounding her, suddenly vanished in the blink of an eye.
S016A	5	30	Señora Serpiente: 「That's your reply...... You've disappointed me.」
S016A	5	31	Asagi: （Disappointed? What does she mean......?）
S016A	5	32	Hadn't the woman used Sakura as a hostage in order to capture her?
S016A	5	33	Byg: 「M, Madam?! What are you gonna do with this woman?! Are you gonna kill her?!」
S016A	5	34	Señora Serpiente: 「Ara, Byg? You've become lively all of a sudden, hmm?」
S016A	5	35	Byg: 「Heh heh――Of course, Madam!」
S016A	5	36	Byg: 「That's 'cause you said I'd get the chance to finally be able to pay back this damn whore.」
S016A	5	37	And then, Byg brought his ugly pig face toward Asagi, who had become unarmed.
S016A	5	38	Byg: 「Oi, Asagi?! You don't think you can just do whatever you want and go home alive, do ya?!」
S016A	5	39	Asagi: 「............」
S016A	5	40	Cold sweat went along Asagi's cheeks.
S016A	6	1	The stupid orc aside, her problem was Kaliya.
S016A	6	2	This was a gamble for Asagi.
S016A	6	3	Since the woman had gone out of her way to summon Asagi, she wasn't going to kill her――Asagi judged so, but it wasn't like she had conclusive proof.
S016A	6	4	If she died, the chance to rescue Sakura would be lost forever.
S016A	6	5	No matter what it took, that, at the very least――
S016A	6	6	Señora Serpiente: 「No, Byg. We're not going to kill this woman.」
S016A	6	7	Byg: 「Ehh?! Really......?」
S016A	6	8	
S016A	6	9	Señora Serpiente: 「There's a more effective use for her than killing her, you know?」
S016A	6	10	Señora Serpiente: 「I'm going to have this disappointing garbage woman make a lot of money with her little sister. Starting with the cost of the repairs for this place, of course.」
S016A	6	11	The woman lifted the edges of her lips, looking at the destroyed entrance.
S016A	6	12	Byg: 「Geheh! I get it! Good idea!! Understood!」
S016A	6	13	Asagi: 「............h.」
S016A	6	14	Asagi surreptitiously let out a sigh of relief.
S016A	6	15	It appeared that she wasn't going to be killed here and now, but――
S016A	6	16	Byg: 「Oraaa?! Did you hear Madam's words, you shit woman?!」
S016A	6	17	Dokaaah!!
S016A	6	18	Asagi: 「Aguh?!」
S016A	6	19	Suddenly feeling intense pain in her lower abdomen, Asagi doubled over.
S016A	6	20	Grinning, Byg had driven a kick into her solar plexus with all his strength.
S016A	6	21	Byg: 「Gehihi, prepare yourself, Asagi!! 'Cause I'm gonna give a lot of love to both you sisters!!」
S016A	6	22	And then, he raised Akkirokumon, which he had picked up, over the head of Asagi, who had bent over.
S016A	6	23	Gatsuh!!
S016A	6	24	Asagi: 「Guh...... uuh......」
S016A	6	25	Her world became tinted red.
S016A	6	26	Having been dealt a heavy blow to the back of the head with the handle of her sword, Asagi's consciousness promptly cut off.
S016A	6	27	SALTAR: S017A
