S020B	1	1	2 weeks later.
S020B	1	2	An enormous building owned by the GN Group, a foreign corporation.
S020B	1	3	The GN Group was a shady corporation which acted as a front for Nomad, a wide-ranging crime syndicate, but most of the people who worked there didn't know that fact.
S020B	1	4	The employees were making money at a business which, on the surface, was like a typical corporation.
S020B	1	5	But sometimes, strange things happened at this company.
S020B	1	6	Like the entrance to the building being destroyed, as if there had been a bombing or something. And, it being tidily repaired overnight.
S020B	1	7	And――
S020B	1	8	Empleado 1: 「Oi, look. Those statues...... It's “Them”, isn't it?」
S020B	1	9	A few employees were looking up at some objets.
S020B	1	10	Two sculptures, which hadn't been there before the previous day, had been installed in a corner of the entrance.
S020B	1	11	Empleado 2: 「Yeah. “Them” from that time, huh?」
S020B	1	12	Empleado 1: 「Kuku...... Never thought “They” would become like this, right......?」
S020B	1	13	The men surreptitiously exchanged looks and laughed.
S020B	1	14	Among the super-elites who worked at this building, there were some regular spectators of the Chaos Arena.
S020B	1	15	They knew exactly what these statues signified.
S020B	1	16	Empleado 1: 「All the same, what shabby statues. Honestly, who put things like these here?」
S020B	1	17	Two shabby-looking works of art had been displayed at the entrance.
S020B	1	18	The elites, who had looked up at them and theatrically feigned ignorance, were going back to their respective jobs with sneering smiles on their lips.
S020B	1	19	A further week had passed.
S020B	1	20	Late at night, two figures trespassed into the deserted entrance of the enormous building.
S020B	1	21	Murasaki: 「You mean Asagi-sama and Sakura are really here......?! In a building like this?!」
S020B	1	22	The one who asked that, sharply but whisperingly, was Gosha Academy's Student Council President, Murasaki.
S020B	1	23	She was wearing her Taimanin suit, and making sure to hide herself in the darkness as she moved forward.
S020B	1	24	Byg: 「Of, of course! Please believe me!」
S020B	1	25	The one who was guiding her was Byg, the orc “information dealer”.
S020B	1	26	Murasaki was pursuing the whereabouts of Sakura and Asagi, who had disappeared after heading for the Chaos Arena.
S020B	1	27	However, clues were scarce, and no news of the pair came to light at all.
S020B	1	28	About a month had passed like that.
S020B	1	29	The lead that she had finally obtained was this “information dealer”, Byg.
S020B	1	30	Murasaki: 「I'll say this just to make sure, but the Igawa clan will attack this place after one call from me.」
S020B	1	31	Murasaki: 「If you're deceiving me, or something happened to Asagi-sama――」
S020B	1	32	On Asagi's instructions, Murasaki had assembled the best of the best, who had been scattered around in various places.
S020B	1	33	Based on Byg's suggestion that standing out would be disadvantageous, she was marching into this building alone, but if her partner had any intention of double-crossing her, she was prepared to teach him a lesson.
S020B	1	34	Byg: 「It's all right! Those sisters are certainly “alive”, hihii!」
S020B	1	35	Byg said, strangely cockily.
S020B	1	36	Murasaki felt some kind of unease from the orc's expression, but――
S020B	1	37	Murasaki: 「h?!」
S020B	1	38	More importantly than that, she had discovered something that concerned her in the entranceway.
S020B	1	39	Murasaki: 「Oi?! What's that......?!」
S020B	1	40	Byg: 「Ah, well...... You see......」
S020B	2	1	Without even waiting for Byg's response, Murasaki rushed over to the objects that adorned the entrance of the enormous building.
S020B	2	2	Murasaki: 「Wh...... What is this......?」
S020B	2	3	Murasaki was unable to move, dumbfounded, and even forgot that she was stealthily trespassing.
S020B	2	4	Decorating the entrance were sculptures of two women.
S020B	2	5	They were statues of the naked bodies of Asagi and Sakura, who Murasaki knew well.
S020B	2	6	Murasaki: 「Isn't that exactly like Asagi-sama?! And Sakura, too......?!」
S020B	2	7	They possessed intricacy which didn't seem like they had been sculpted by human hands at all.
S020B	2	8	Despite their unladylike, completely naked appearance, Asagi and Sakura had sharp expressions, and were looking ahead as if opposing something.
S020B	2	9	However, the pair's limbs had been cruelly broken,
S020B	2	10	And carved into their respective lower abdomens were the characters for “Reject”, and the mark which was the symbol of a Slave Prostitute.
S020B	2	11	Murasaki: 「Wh, what's the meaning of this?! Are they insulting Asagi-sama by making stone statues like this?!」
S020B	2	12	The sculptures of the pair were beautiful.
S020B	2	13	However, precisely because of their beautiful modelling, they had the unconcealable aura of poor defeated losers.
S020B	2	14	Byg: 「Uh, umm, good question...... I'm an outsider, so I don't know what that's about at all......」
S020B	2	15	Byg: 「Well, I don't think there's that deep a meaning to it, though. Heh heh......」
S020B	2	16	Byg gave a vague answer, smiling subserviently.
S020B	2	17	Murasaki: 「Kuh, this is out of the question――!」
S020B	2	18	Thousands, tens of thousands of people worked at this building.
S020B	2	19	There was no way she could allow them to expose such appalling statues of the pair to those people's eyes.
S020B	2	20	Murasaki raised her special weapon overhead to destroy the statues, but――
S020B	2	21	Murasaki: 「I can't break them......! Because, a statue so much like Asagi-sama......」
S020B	2	22	Her axe, which she had raised high overhead, stopped mid-swing.
S020B	2	23	Unable to destroy the pair's statues, no matter what, Murasaki grimaced and pointed her face downward.
S020B	2	24	Byg: 「Gehihi. Well, that might be better...... for “those two”.」
S020B	2	25	Murasaki: 「Ahh?! What did you say?!」
S020B	2	26	Byg: 「N, no! It's nothing!」
S020B	2	27	Byg shook his head, and shut his mouth in a panic.
S020B	2	28	Byg: 「It seems they're planning for a “new” statue to stand next to them pretty soon, though. Well, that's not important――」
S020B	2	29	Byg: 「Now, this way, Murasaki Ojou-sama. The Chaos Arena is in the basement.」
S020B	2	30	Murasaki: 「Yeah...... I know......」
S020B	2	31	Murasaki: （Please hold on...... Asagi-sama, Sakura...... Murasaki's coming right now......）
S020B	2	32	Without knowing the tragic fate that awaited her after that――
S020B	2	33	Led by her guide, Byg, Murasaki set foot into the darkness of the Chaos Arena.
