S021A_2	1	1	Sakura: 「Higyaaaaaaaaaaaaah!! Oggoooh...... oh, ah...... ohh...... Like always, Gogo-sama's cock is too thick......」
S021A_2	1	2	His enormous pillar of flesh had been buried in Sakura's body.
S021A_2	1	3	Her cervix was squashed hard, and spit out cloudy-white juices.
S021A_2	1	4	Sakura: （T, tiiiight〜〜〜!! There's no way a human can withstand something like this!!）
S021A_2	1	5	Sakura: 「Uguh, ooohh, id, hurds......! Guoh, ohh, ohhhh belly's gonna breeeak......!」
S021A_2	1	6	Cliente VIP B: 「Ohhh! Her stomach's bulging out in the shape of his cock!」
S021A_2	1	7	One person shouted, enthusiastically. The VIP Room became excited by the tragic state of Sakura.
S021A_2	1	8	Cliente VIP A: 「Most women would scream, having their cunts torn apart by this, though......」
S021A_2	1	9	Sakura: 「Ahh, belly's filled up by Gogo-samaaa! Pig cunt's, happy to take, kuooh, Gogo-sama's robust oni penis into her belly!」
S021A_2	1	10	Cliente VIP D: 「Not to mention, there's not even any blood coming out, ufufu. It looks painful, but I wonder if that piggy is actually pleased?」
S021A_2	1	11	A brutal sight, which looked like another leg had sprouted between hers.
S021A_2	1	12	Tenderness still remained in her fissure of flesh, which had spread out as much as it could.
S021A_2	1	13	Sakura: 「Haah, haah, thanks to Gogo-sama's training, nnaah, I've now reached the point where I can take it without fainting, with my nipples and clit hard!」
S021A_2	1	14	Sakura: 「Nguoh, I feel happy to have my belly, m, made the shape of Gogo-sama......」
S021A_2	1	15	It didn't look like there was room, but, as she said, Sakura's body had become one that could take an insertion from Big Gogo.
S021A_2	1	16	Byg Gogo: 「Gefufu! Once I get a hold of them, all pigs turn out like this!」
S021A_2	1	17	Big Gogo showed Sakura (who was still powerlessly being penetrated) off to the audience.
S021A_2	1	18	And what they saw there was defeat and submission from Sakura which hadn't existed on That Day.
S021A_2	1	19	Sakura: （The inside of my pussy is hot...... This guy's “That” is...... his cock is inside it......）
S021A_2	1	20	Sakura: （Once this is put in, it's no use, my body remembers getting messed up......!）
S021A_2	1	21	In terms of thickness alone, the dildo from when she had been defeated by Snake Lady was larger than Big Gogo's cock.
S021A_2	1	22	The reason Sakura was frightened of Big Gogo's cock was also because of the life of hell that she had experienced over the last two days.
S021A_2	1	23	Whether because he understood that or in order to show off, Big Gogo deliberately made his cock pulsate.
S021A_2	1	24	Sakura: （Ahh, it's going to be done to me again...... Even though it's scary, my body is starting to look forward to it......）
S021A_2	1	25	Cliente VIP C: 「Even if she is an Ex-Taimanin, for her to be able to turn into Big Gogo's cock sheath...... My expectations are rising.」
S021A_2	1	26	Cliente VIP D: 「She really is precious, giving her all in such a tragic state. I want to see her get wrecked right away!」
S021A_2	1	27	Even though she was taking it and getting off, it was a pitiful sight, like a shrike's prey impaled on a thorn.
S021A_2	1	28	Her Slave Prostitute body would convert pain and anguish into pleasure, but that didn't mean that the strain on her body would be light.
S021A_2	1	29	Her loosely-dangling limbs and agonized expression were because of her body receiving that much damage and strain from the insertion.
S021A_2	1	30	Sakura: 「Gogo-sama, please use this pig's body in place of an onahole, and l, let her service you with gratitude!」
S021A_2	1	31	Sakura: 「P, p, please, ohhh, thrash this sinful livestock with your wonderful oni penis, and let it apologize for its rudeness to Gogo-sama!」
S021A_2	1	32	She lost control of her body, and her consciousness nearly ended up giving rise to panic.
S021A_2	1	33	Even in a situation like this, Sakura didn't stop the speech of allegiance that she had been trained to give.
S021A_2	1	34	Byg Gogo: 「Ororoh! Big Gogo's a great fighter!! You're a pig!! My property!!」
S021A_2	1	35	Still holding Sakura's body in place, Big Gogo put all his might into his cock.
S021A_2	1	36	Countless “barbs” that it was endowed with spread out, preventing it from escaping, and his brutal cock, which had swollen almost a full size bigger, pointed straight up.
S021A_2	1	37	Sakura: 「Nnooh, that's, riiight! I'm a pig, I'm Gogo-sama's pet! Ohh, being churrrned......!!」
S021A_2	1	38	Big Gogo started moving Sakura, whom he had grabbed hold of.
S021A_2	1	39	Sakura: 「Mmhhh oooooohhhhh, cunnnt, being dug intooooo!!!」
S021A_2	1	40	Sakura: 「Hih iiiih, igiiiiiiih, hiih, hiih, nhiiiiiiiih!」
S021A_2	2	1	Having her vaginal flesh gouged into by the meat spear's barbs, Sakura made her dangling limbs shake.
S021A_2	2	2	Sakura: （Being scraped away at! Gouged intooo! Pussy's gonna be destroyyyed......!!）
S021A_2	2	3	If she were a normal person, her pussy would be torn to shreds, and she would reach the point where she started desperately begging for her life.
S021A_2	2	4	Cliente VIP B: 「That's no problem?!」
S021A_2	2	5	Sakura continuing to cry out her allegiance, even as her body was destroyed, and she lost her life――
S021A_2	2	6	The VIPs had been anticipating a spectacle like that, but, surprisingly, not a single drop of blood escaped from the place where they combined.
S021A_2	2	7	Sakura: 「Sa, Sakura's pussy, hiih, hiiih, has been torn to shreds over and over again, but, igi, iih, because of reconstruction every time, kufuuuuu!」
S021A_2	2	8	Sakura: 「And the remodelling, that goes with, becoming a Slave Prostitute, it's become a stroking hole, a commodity optimized for, guhiiin!」
S021A_2	2	9	Sakura: 「Go, Gogo-sama's, Cock-sama to be able, kuuh, to enjoy and thrash over and over againnn! Ah, as you can seeeeee!!」
S021A_2	2	10	Sakura: 「Ugih, ugiiin! Iguiiih, tender remodelled flesh, being scraped away by Cock-sama!!」
S021A_2	2	11	Big Gogo moved Sakura in short strokes, and scraped her vaginal flesh intensively with his barbs.
S021A_2	2	12	Even though she was being drilled into with short, repeated movements, at a speed that didn't go easy on her, Sakura's body wouldn't break.
S021A_2	2	13	Sakura: 「Nniaaaaah, aaaah! It's acutely sensitive, so, kihii, I can enjoy myself without ever getting sick of it, hiiiiin!」
S021A_2	2	14	Once Sakura had finished desperately explaining, Big Gogo stopped moving.
S021A_2	2	15	Sakura: 「Hiiih, hiiih, pussy gonna break, it's gonna breeeak, and yet, the tingling's amazing! Ahiih, this is bad, it's baaad......」
S021A_2	2	16	Her Slave Prostitute mask had slipped for a moment.
S021A_2	2	17	Byg Gogo: 「Gufuu!」
S021A_2	2	18	Sakura: 「Nhih!!」
S021A_2	2	19	But Sakura's complaints receded just from him thrusting his hips up slightly.
S021A_2	2	20	This brutal cock was the reason he had made Sakura this obedient in a mere two days.
S021A_2	2	21	Cliente VIP A: 「I see. So Big Gogo, who's broken and cruelly murdered countless women, is torturing her without allowing her to die?」
S021A_2	2	22	Cliente VIP C: 「Definitely. Torturing that eyesore of a Taimanin, like this, is him trying to vent his anger.」
S021A_2	2	23	She wasn't allowed to die from this deadly torture.
S021A_2	2	24	Having become aware of that cruelty, the looks in the VIPs' eyes had changed.
S021A_2	2	25	Sakura still wasn't completely broken. But her figure had been battered this badly in a short space of time. This torture had caused that.
S021A_2	2	26	Byg Gogo: 「Pig.」
S021A_2	2	27	Big Gogo prompted her to start the show proper.
S021A_2	2	28	Sakura: 「Yeh, ss......」
S021A_2	2	29	Sakura: （It's gonna start again, no......! But, if I don't do it, this won't end with me merely getting raped......）
S021A_2	2	30	Fear filled her, having flashbacks of herself being torn apart and leaking blood like a waterfall.
S021A_2	2	31	Sakura: （Even though I don't want that...! Don't be pleased to remember it, my body!）
S021A_2	2	32	Dark anticipation of being held down and violated without any way to resist burned in her heart.
S021A_2	2	33	All Sakura could do was obey orders, flirt with him, and guard her mind so that it wouldn't get broken.
S021A_2	2	34	Even if she had been remodelled and optimized, that only meant that her body wasn't going to break.
S021A_2	2	35	Sakura: （Have to, hold on, I need to hold on until Onee-chan comes......!）
S021A_2	2	36	Sakura: 「W, well then, now that you've, gotten the gist, please enjoy...... the sex show, where Gogo-sama will pummel me relentlessly!」
S021A_2	2	37	Dojuuuuuunnn!!!
S021A_2	2	38	Sakura: 「Nnhh goooohhh, oh, in, intennnse! Oh, w, womb......! Ooohhhh, oh, ohooooh, gummiiing!!」
S021A_2	2	39	The pillar of meat was buried inside her, with force that was incomparable to when it was inserted.
S021A_2	2	40	Her consciousness flickered white over and over again.
S021A_2	3	1	She was given a shock which felt like she was going to spew the entire contents of her body out from her mouth.
S021A_2	3	2	From just one blow, her face, which was twisted from having her vaginal flesh gouged into, lost its strength, and her eyes started to roll back.
S021A_2	3	3	Then――
S021A_2	3	4	Byg Gogo: 「Guhhgaah!!」
S021A_2	3	5	Dojun!! Dojun!! Dojuun!!
S021A_2	3	6	She was dealt three consecutive blows with his ogre strength, which he did not hold back.
S021A_2	3	7	With every blow, her womb was crushed and spewed out bodily fluids, and the noise of it (and the surrounding organs) being struck resounded from Sakura's stomach.
S021A_2	3	8	Sakura: 「Uu oh!! Ohh hoh!! Nnhh hooohh!! It's doing iiit!! Insides, oohhh, being crushed!! Fungoooh!!」
S021A_2	3	9	Guchuguchuguchuguchuguchu!!
S021A_2	3	10	After thrusting, merciless womb gouging. He crammed his cock inside, then swung her body violently and churned the inside of her womb.
S021A_2	3	11	It was certainly an act of violence strong enough to take a person's life. In Sakura's case, that death transformed into pleasure, and ran amok.
S021A_2	3	12	Sakura: 「Stomach...! Uboh, unnoooobooooah! Fuooooh〜〜! Being churrrned! Gumming from bein churned!!」
S021A_2	3	13	Bikubikubikubikuuu――!
S021A_2	3	14	Sakura's body was shaking and reaching climax every time she was churned, had her internal organs crushed, and was given “death”.
S021A_2	3	15	Cliente VIP A: 「I can clearly tell that she's being churned by the cock that's bulging out on her stomach. I've never seen anything like this!」
S021A_2	3	16	Cliente VIP D: 「Uufufufu! She truly is an onahole, isn't she? To be getting off, even though something like this is being done to her!」
S021A_2	3	17	Byg Gogo: 「Gufufuu! There's more to come!」
S021A_2	3	18	Put in a good mood by the VIPs' reactions, Big Gogo pulled Sakura off him and swung her downward again, over and over.
S021A_2	3	19	Dojuu!! Dojuuu!! Dojuuu!!
S021A_2	3	20	Sakura: 「Nguoh! Oh buh! Gogo-sama, fuoah, ah! Abuoh! How does it feel, egueh?!」
S021A_2	3	21	Every time it was swung downward, Sakura's body stiffened up and twitched.
S021A_2	3	22	The rate at which he pulled her off and swung her downward increased.
S021A_2	3	23	Doju, doju, doju, doju!!
S021A_2	3	24	Sakura: 「Fubuh, bubeh! Gogo-samaa, Gogo-samaaa, nn heah, nheeh! Fuhooh, how does it feel to use my pig hole?!」
S021A_2	3	25	Sakura: 「Does it feel, good enough, hoeeh, to have your precious sperm go whoosh-whoosh out from Cock-sama?!」
S021A_2	3	26	The strength drained from Sakura's body, which was stiffening up and bucking every time it was swung downward.
S021A_2	3	27	Moisture and stickiness increased in the slapping noise that resounded from inside her belly.
S021A_2	3	28	Dojuuuuuh!!
S021A_2	3	29	Sakura: 「Hoheeeeeehh☆」
S021A_2	3	30	Her body, which had been battered and lost its strength, was swung downward even harder, as if for the finishing blow.
S021A_2	3	31	Sakura: 「Hyuwaaaa〜aaa〜aaah〜〜, the inside of my belly's, been turned to mush〜」
S021A_2	3	32	A slutty voice arose, with a different tone from that of the moans which had been squeezed out of her until just before.
S021A_2	3	33	Her arms and legs were not just weak, but limp, and her mind and body had softened tenderly, like pounded mochi.
S021A_2	3	34	Sakura: 「Sakura's〜, aheeh〜, been beaten up by Cock-samaaa, it's a total defeat now〜☆ Fuhoheeh〜」
S021A_2	3	35	Big Gogo stopped pumping Sakura.
S021A_2	3	36	He tilted the body of Sakura, whose brains had melted, backward.
S021A_2	3	37	The end of the cock was distinctly visible on her stomach, which had bulged out under the pressure.
S021A_2	3	38	Still pressing Sakura's body onto his cock, Big Gogo started to stir it, as if to mix her internal organs around with his dick.
S021A_2	3	39	Gujugujuguju, gujugujugujugujugujuuuu!!
S021A_2	3	40	Sakura: 「Fuhyooooh, pain, ful?! Nnoh, fuheooh! Oh, what's this?! Ubeh! Nnoh!」
S021A_2	4	1	A more intense wet sound than when he slammed her down onto himself. The end of his cock made the flesh and skin of her belly stretch and undulate slightly.
S021A_2	4	2	It was extremely brutal treatment towards the groggy Sakura, but the VIPs became very excited and noisy because of that.
S021A_2	4	3	Sakura: 「Ngooohh, gonna break, ohhh, Gogo-sama, stomaaach! Hey, oboooh, stomach's gonna breeeak!!」
S021A_2	4	4	Byg Gogo: 「What's wrong with that?! You're gonna cum from this! Isn't that so?!」
S021A_2	4	5	Sakura: 「Ohoooh, ooohh, nnoooooh! Ohh bu, nnbuhooh!」
S021A_2	4	6	Sakura: 「Yeh, sss! I'm cumming! Cumming from this, ngooh, cumming, cumming! Gubuh! Sakura's, cumming from you churning her insides!」
S021A_2	4	7	Her owner was telling her to cum.
S021A_2	4	8	If that was the case, then she would have to cum. A Slave Prostitute was someone who could cum because of that.
S021A_2	4	9	Excited by the order to cum, her trained body was about to burst from the raging pleasure.
S021A_2	4	10	Byg Gogo: 「Cum! Pig! Cum!」
S021A_2	4	11	The strength with which he was churning Sakura was reflected in his urging voice.
S021A_2	4	12	He continued moving Sakura's body, and grinding his glans against her as if to caress her.
S021A_2	4	13	Gujujujujujujujujuuu!!
S021A_2	4	14	Byg Gogo: 「Cuuummmm!!」
S021A_2	4	15	Sakura: 「Aguaaaaaah, aaaah, aaah, oaaaaaahhhhh!!」
S021A_2	4	16	Sakura: 「Stirring my bellyyy, insides being pushed and churned by Cock-sama, cumming cumming cumming, pig's cummiiiiing, aaaaahh, aaaaaaaaahhh!!」
S021A_2	4	17	Sakura howled, having especial strength put into churning her.
S021A_2	4	18	Even during that, Big Gogo continued moving Sakura in short, quick movements, and teasing the inside of her womb.
S021A_2	4	19	Sakura: 「Nnh hooooo〜〜ooo〜oooohh〜〜〜, churning, cumming, gumming, gyummiiiing〜〜〜」
S021A_2	4	20	Sakura cried happily. Her womb had been crushed, and the large amount of pussy juices that had spurted out of it escaped from the place where they combined.
S021A_2	4	21	Sakura: 「Huoon, nnoh oh oh, oh ah! Cum, ming! Uho! Oh! Oh! Cummiiing!」
S021A_2	4	22	Sakura: 「Gogo-samaaa〜, Pig caaame! Id ohgashmmm〜, orgasmmmed〜☆」
S021A_2	4	23	Cliente VIP B: 「She climaxed......」
S021A_2	4	24	Cliente VIP D: 「She's still doing it......」
S021A_2	4	25	Even the VIPs had never seen something like this before.
S021A_2	4	26	Figures begging for forgiveness, covered in tears, snot, blood and entrails. And, their lives fruitlessly disappearing at the utmost limit of inhumanity.
S021A_2	4	27	They had watched that kind of death and destruction, enveloped by supreme excitement.
S021A_2	4	28	However, they had never even considered that someone would climax from brutal sexual intercourse with Big Gogo, which had caused horrible deaths up to this point.
S021A_2	4	29	Cliente VIP C: 「How magnificent. To turn that Taimanin into a creature which suits the words “pig bitch” that much...」
S021A_2	4	30	The VIPs were once again astonished by the fiendish act, and grew excited from the two days' worth of exclusive Slave Prostitute time that had changed Sakura this much.
S021A_2	4	31	Byg Gogo: 「This still isn't all. Gufu gufu, I still have a lot of strength left! It's nothing like this! That's right, isn't it, pig?!」
S021A_2	4	32	Big Gogo pressed Sakura, agitatedly.
S021A_2	4	33	In addition to sadism and the excitement of domination, the eyes that looked at Sakura were burning with a fierce desire.
S021A_2	4	34	Sakura: 「Y, yessh〜, Gogo-sama's power〜, is nooothing〜 like this♪」
S021A_2	4	35	Sakura: 「I'm sorry I can't, nhaah, make Gogo-sama ejaculate, and demonstrate his power, since I'm not good enough, mmh, mmh♪」
S021A_2	4	36	Sakura gave in, while stifling the lingering feelings of her climaxes.
S021A_2	4	37	Perhaps because he liked Sakura's attitude, Big Gogo made his cock swell out ferociously.
S021A_2	4	38	Sakura: （Kuhiin! Ahhh〜, at last, That's coming! Merciless cock stroking, with me as an unresisting onahole, where no strength will enter my body at all......!）
S021A_2	4	39	The strength of Big Gogo's hand, which seized Sakura, increased.
S021A_2	4	40	Her bones creaked. All-out onahole treatment was coming.
S021A_2	5	1	Sakura: 「G, Gogo-sama, please use Sakura―who's been beaten and become a total onahole, with no power to resist―to feel really good!」
S021A_2	5	2	Sakura screamed, due to the shock and pleasure that were going to run amok after this.
S021A_2	5	3	Sakura: 「Please use her enough to break her, feel good, and ejaculate!」
S021A_2	5	4	Dojudojudojudojudojudojudojuuu!!
S021A_2	5	5	Sakura: 「Ki hyuaaaaaaaaaaaaaah〜〜〜!! Aweshome, ohh, aweshooome, Gogo-sama's cock's aweshommme!!」
S021A_2	5	6	Big Gogo began his all-out cock stroking, using Sakura.
S021A_2	5	7	Her limbs, which had lost their strength due to the extreme violence, shook up and down just like her breasts.
S021A_2	5	8	Immediately after that, her head, which she had thrown back from the shock and pleasure, swung back and forth so much that it almost seemed like her neck was going to snap.
S021A_2	5	9	Cliente VIP B: 「That sow is delighted, even when it's this rough?」
S021A_2	5	10	Gruesome pummelling noises resounded, which were incomparable to anything before now.
S021A_2	5	11	Byg Gogo: 「Guooonh! Guoaah!! Guah guah, guooaaah!!」
S021A_2	5	12	Big Gogo spewed saliva and roared from the pleasure of the sex and violence.
S021A_2	5	13	The bitch who had lopped off his arm while making a calm smile was going mad, being helplessly skewered by his cock.
S021A_2	5	14	Byg Gogo: 「My bitch!! My pig, my slave!! Guooonh!!」
S021A_2	5	15	Sakura: 「That's riiiight! Kuhihihihi, ku hiiiiih! Sakura isss, Gogo-sama's slaaave!!」
S021A_2	5	16	He had never been able to get sexually excited by any of the bitches he had killed before now. They had all ended up dying easily.
S021A_2	5	17	Sakura engendered a feeling of domination and superiority which satisfied the male instincts of Big Gogo, for whom dominance had hitherto meant taking his opponents' lives.
S021A_2	5	18	She was a symbol of his freedom, and a symbol of his strength.
S021A_2	5	19	Sakura: 「Beat me up as much as you like, please make me your plaything with Cock-samaaa〜!!」
S021A_2	5	20	And he was the supreme ruler over the body of Sakura, who had been beaten up and turned into a Slave Prostitute.
S021A_2	5	21	Sakura: 「Oooooaaaaoaaaah! Inside of my belly's, a mess! Nhoooh, Cock-sama's good! Cock-sama'sh amaziiing!」
S021A_2	5	22	Sakura: 「Gogo-samaaa! Please beat Sakura enough to cripple her, with Cock-shamaaaa!!」
S021A_2	5	23	Sakura: （This really is bad! If it's done like thiiis, I'll become unable to think about anything but feeling good anymore, I'll be unable to turn baaack!）
S021A_2	5	24	The VIPs' masks as Ladies and Gentlemen had slipped off due to the outrageous sight of the two animals.
S021A_2	5	25	The VIP Room was enveloped by excitement similar to when they were watching the brutal shows in which female fighters were violated and massacred.
S021A_2	5	26	Cliente VIP A: 「Ohh, it's the first time I've seen such a ferocious rape! Do it, thrash the conceited Taimanin!」
S021A_2	5	27	Cliente VIP B: 「That's right, impale her and make her cum! Teach her that she's just a bitch in the end!」
S021A_2	5	28	The VIPs unanimously yelled for him to beat up Sakura, to thoroughly destroy the Taimanin.
S021A_2	5	29	Byg Gogo: 「Guhahahaa! In that case, here!!」
S021A_2	5	30	Big Gogo tilted her backward slightly once again.
S021A_2	5	31	His cock was rubbed against the vaginal walls adjacent to her stomach, albeit not to the same extent as before.
S021A_2	5	32	Sakura: 「Muoh?!」
S021A_2	5	33	Without dropping Sakura, who had been pulled upwards in that state, he moved in a short, quick motion with the barbs of his cock.
S021A_2	5	34	Sakura: 「Huhaaaaaaah, G-spot teasiiing!! Ohh, concentrating your fire on the slutty spot of my pussy, which has been trained by Gogo-samaaa!!」
S021A_2	5	35	Sakura: 「Hoah, hoah, hoaaaaah! G-spot, constant light climaxes won't stop, one after anotherrr! Again, again, oooh cumming over and overrr!」
S021A_2	5	36	Sakura: 「Rubbing against the frenulum, ohh, ku hoh......! Nn, aah! Are you enjoying Sakura'sh pig cunt?」
S021A_2	5	37	Sakura: 「Hahoooh, Sakura keeps lightly cumming, fuhiin! Frenulum at my G-spot, barbs at the entrance of my vagina, Sakura is full of happiness because of Cock-samaaa!」
S021A_2	5	38	Byg Gogo: 「You're useful, pig! Gufuhahaha, you're my bitch!!」
S021A_2	5	39	Sakura: 「Oh, huoooooh! Pussy's pleased by your joyous worrrds!! Ahih, ahih, Gogo-samaaanh!! Haah haah, nhiiiii!!」
S021A_2	5	40	Receiving Big Gogo's words, a tingle of pleasure ran down Sakura's spine.
S021A_2	6	1	Her womb was twitching, deeply moved by her dominator's pleasure.
S021A_2	6	2	Byg Gogo: 「I won't allow you to orgasm again!!」
S021A_2	6	3	Dojun!!
S021A_2	6	4	Sakura: 「Fugoooh! Ooohoh, I, I'm shorreeeh, I was too happeh, fuhi, and anxious to, ohgashm as I pleeeashed〜」
S021A_2	6	5	Sensing from the twitching of her womb that a large climax was about to visit her, Big Gogo gave her an order.
S021A_2	6	6	Her body, which had turned into limp flesh, trembled, having its womb struck hard on the brink of climax.
S021A_2	6	7	Byg Gogo: 「Orgasm after I let it out. From here on, I won't allow you to cum ahead of me!」
S021A_2	6	8	Sakura: 「Y, yeh, yessh! Thank you very much, nhih, for teaching, a moron who orgashms without discipline, to, hold baack......!」
S021A_2	6	9	Sakura: 「Sha, Shakura, will hol baaack......! She'll hold back a lot, with her moronic head, until she can receive, your shperm!」
S021A_2	6	10	She seemed to be resisting her climax. Sakura's voice slurred, and stiffened from the convulsions of her womb, which demanded that she let it cum.
S021A_2	6	11	Byg Gogo: 「Ororo! If you orgasm before me, I'll slam it in through your mouth again, got it?」
S021A_2	6	12	Big Gogo announced happily. Sakura nodded with a pitiful expression, making her face, which twisted with pleasure, turn pale.
S021A_2	6	13	Sakura: 「W, will absolutely not, have a proper orgasm, until I receive Gogo-shama's precioush shperrrm! Shakura is, a flesh onahole for Gogo-shamaaa!」
S021A_2	6	14	Sakura: 「Hehih, hehihi, please use Shakura, to enjoy yourshelf a lot, please use and break herrr, feel good and creampie herrr!」
S021A_2	6	15	Sakura: 
S021A_2	6	16	Even while she was doing so, Sakura pled needfully, and Big Gogo started swinging his arms violently to respond to that.
S021A_2	6	17	Dojudojudojudojudojudojudojuuu!!
S021A_2	6	18	Sakura: 「Ahiiiiiiiiiiiihh! Gogo-shama's amazhiiing!」
S021A_2	6	19	Sakura: 
S021A_2	6	20	The speed and forcefulness could not be compared to the initial stroking.
S021A_2	6	21	From his cock, which swelled up and twitched, she could surmise that he was also close to climax.
S021A_2	6	22	Sakura: 「If my pig bitch womb is jabbed this much by burly Cock-shamaaa, nhoooh, it'sh gonna cum straight away, gonna orgasmmm!」
S021A_2	6	23	Byg Gogo: 「No! I won't let you!」
S021A_2	6	24	Sakura: 「Ahiin! Thah'sh... Gonna go crazhy fwom holdin back doo muush! Uhiih, uiiih!!」
S021A_2	6	25	Byg Gogo: 「Gufuu! In that case, go crazy and die! Die from my cock, pig!」
S021A_2	6	26	Big Gogo spit out, making his eyes bloodshot, and put strength into the hand gripping Sakura.
S021A_2	6	27	Sakura: 「Ogooh, Cock-shama's stronnng! Scrapinnng, uuuuhiii, getting off from having my body pared awaaay!」
S021A_2	6	28	Sakura: 「Fuhoh, hooonh, more! Pummel Shakura more! Wreck her, Cock, sha, maa......!!」
S021A_2	6	29	Her flesh screamed, her bones creaked, and the feeling of her organs being squashed grew stronger. The pleasure of the writhing Sakura kept on stimulating Big Gogo's cock.
S021A_2	6	30	Byg Gogo: 「Gugaaaah! Guooh, gugooon!!」
S021A_2	6	31	Big Gogo bellowed. The speed of his stroking increased.
S021A_2	6	32	Sakura: 「Uuh, iah! Ahi, ahii! Feel gooh, Gogo-shamaaa! Aaah, ahhh!」
S021A_2	6	33	His cock strained, and its flesh parasol spread out.
S021A_2	6	34	The barbs also spread, and gouged deeper into her vaginal folds.
S021A_2	6	35	Sakura: 「Cock-shamaaa, scratching, scraping, kuhooon, oohhh, ohh!」
S021A_2	6	36	Sakura: 「Aweshooome, ohhh! Ooohh, doo aweshomme! Geddin off doo mussh, Shakura-Onahole's, gohha breeeak!!」
S021A_2	6	37	Sakura: 「Am Ah usheful, Gogo-shamaaa?! Isss, ohhh! Cock-shama, able to feel good in Pig'sh onahole cunnnt?!」
S021A_2	6	38	Sakura: 「Nfuoooh, too muuuch! Shakura can't take ih anymoaah! Doo amazhinn, I like thish, doo mush, kuoooonnh, can't take it anehmooore!」
S021A_2	6	39	She started squirting from her pussy in short spurts.
S021A_2	6	40	Her body was squeezing Big Gogo's cock with greater strength than he was using to hold her.
S021A_2	7	1	Sakura: 「Hohyaah, wanniiiid! Gogo-shamaaa, Ah wan, wan, wand shemeeennn, fuhiiii, hiiiiin!!」
S021A_2	7	2	Byg Gogo: 「Mm, guuuh!! I'm letting it out, pig! Squeeze it out! Milk my cock, with your pig hoooole!!」
S021A_2	7	3	Had her intense squeezing been the trigger? An unendurable tingle of pleasure had filled Big Gogo's cock, and a tremendous urge to ejaculate had welled up.
S021A_2	7	4	His testicles, which had amassed super-rich cum, rose up.
S021A_2	7	5	Sakura: 「Haaaaaah, this feeliiing!! It'sh comiiing, Gogo-shama's, extra-thick Goshujin-shama milllllk!!」
S021A_2	7	6	Sakura: 「Hot shtuff, ooohhhh, please come come come come coooommmmme!」
S021A_2	7	7	Byg Gogo: 「Gufuu, gufu, guoooooooohhhh!!!」
S021A_2	7	8	Sakura: 「Hyaaaaaaaaaah, shemen's coming uuuuhhhp!! Comin, comin, cominnn, shemen's comiiinnn!!」
S021A_2	7	9	Sakura: 「Fukyah――――Aaaaaaaaaaaahhh!!」
S021A_2	7	10	Byuguguguguguuu, bububububuryuu, bubyu bubyu bubyu, bubyubububububuuu!!
S021A_2	7	11	Sakura: 「Oah, oah, oah☆ Shemennn, spurtiiiiing☆ Hyaaah, hooohht, huoh, cumming cumming cumming cumming cyummiiiinnng♪」
S021A_2	7	12	Extraordinary cum had been released inside Sakura's body from his meat spear, which had been thrust in very deep.
S021A_2	7	13	That cum―the volume, richness and heat of which couldn't be compared to a human's―had seriously devastated Sakura's insides.
S021A_2	7	14	It seemed like she would even feel anguish from the heat and quantity, but when she received it, and climaxed from having her womb expand, she squirted a large quantity of fluid.
S021A_2	7	15	Sakura: 「Ohh, hoooohh♪ Ooohhhh♪ Spurrrrrt, spurrrrrt, shemen's aweshoome♪ Gogo-shama's ejaculation's aweshomme♪」
S021A_2	7	16	Sakura: 「It'sss... Orgasssm, nhoooooooh, orgasm won'd shtooohhp〜〜! Ahiinh, gumming, gumming, gumming again!!」
S021A_2	7	17	Byg Gogo: 「Guguuu, guoh, guooh, it's still coming out! Take it! Make your womb swell ouuut!!」
S021A_2	7	18	Sakura: 「Fu hiih☆ Yesssh! Fill id, make mah womb burrrsht!!」
S021A_2	7	19	Big Gogo held down Sakura, who orgasmed wildly, as if to say he wouldn't allow her to let the semen leak out.
S021A_2	7	20	Her womb expanded from the cum that was fired in, and Sakura's belly was swollen as if she had reached the last month of pregnancy.
S021A_2	7	21	Byg Gogo: 「Guooh, oh, fuuuuh, fuuuuh, squeeze it out! Pig! Pig bitch!」
S021A_2	7	22	Sakura: 「Oh, oooohhh! Yehsh, yehssh, fire id all into, Shakura's, Onahole's womb, enough foh it to burrrsht......!!」
S021A_2	7	23	Sakura: 「Ahhhh〜 gummiiing, womb swelling out, gumming, huaaaah〜, too habbyyy, this orgasm, doo happyy〜♪」
S021A_2	7	24	Sakura: 「Hoaaaaaa〜aaaaaah〜〜, happyyy〜, Pig Bitch is happyyy〜〜, thiiis, aheeeh〜〜〜♪♪♪」
S021A_2	7	25	As her stomach swelled out, Sakura continued accepting Big Gogo's semen like it felt good.
S021A_2	7	26	There was no panic on her face (which drooled, and moaned 『I'm happy, I'm happy,』 with a slovenly expression), but it was also lacking intelligence and humanity.
S021A_2	7	27	Sakura: 「Ohh, heeeeeeeh〜〜〜〜〜......」
S021A_2	7	28	Big Gogo's long ejaculation ended, and then, after a while, Sakura came back from her climax.
S021A_2	7	29	Her abdomen was bulging to an unbelievable degree, packed full of Big Gogo's cum.
S021A_2	7	30	Her head slumped forward.
S021A_2	7	31	Her eyes rolled back completely. She was twitching, and moaning something or other, but no meaningful words could be heard.
S021A_2	7	32	Asagi: 
S021A_2	7	33	Sakura: 「Uu...... ohh, oheh...... heh...... oah, aah......」
S021A_2	7	34	Only Sakura's moans were emitted in the VIP Room, which had gone silent.
S021A_2	7	35	Clientes VIP: 「......h......」
S021A_2	7	36	Someone gasped. The VIPs, who had been excited by the pair's tremendous insemination climax, were lost for words.
S021A_2	7	37	Compared to the slaughter shows, it seemed like a simple one, with no death, and no blood, flesh or death throes present.
S021A_2	7	38	But there was another, different vileness to the sex show of Sakura and Big Gogo, which one would hesitate to call a sex act, or even animal copulation.
S021A_2	7	39	Sakura's condition was too pitiful to call it sex, and if she were an ordinary person, there was no telling how many times over she would have died.
S021A_2	7	40	It turned death into pleasure, and thoroughly desecrated and belittled her life, soul, dignity, and existence as a human. It was that kind of vileness.
S021A_2	8	1	Byg Gogo: 「Gururuu...... Oi, pig.」
S021A_2	8	2	Sakura: 「Nhih☆」
S021A_2	8	3	Being shaken by Big Gogo, Sakura let out a short, strange voice.
S021A_2	8	4	The VIPs shuddered.
S021A_2	8	5	Sakura: 「F, fank you〜, kuhi☆ V, vereh mush, foh ejagu, ladin〜, in Sha, Shakura-Onahoah〜♪」
S021A_2	8	6	Sakura: 「Uu, uheeh〜♪ Ah looove...... I love...... feewin good♪ Ah love, Cock-shamaaa...... Nheeh〜♪」
S021A_2	8	7	A shiver ran through Sakura from the legs up.
S021A_2	8	8	Judging from the fact that his cock had throbbed, was she still trying to service him, even in a state like this?
S021A_2	8	9	Cliente VIP D: 「Fufu, ufufufu, this is wonderful. She really has been trained this well.」
S021A_2	8	10	Cliente VIP B: 「Hmm. I suppose this sow is the only one who could be that Big Gogo's partner.」
S021A_2	8	11	Cliente VIP D: 「Yes, they're husband and wife now. They're a good match. Ufufufu.」
S021A_2	8	12	Cliente VIP A: 「Truly magnificent. I wonder if I should put this up on social media or something in commemoration.」
S021A_2	8	13	The VIPs, who had been watching the two animals and their sex act, unanimously made a racket, and the VIP Room was filled with excitement again.
S021A_2	8	14	Sakura: 「Nheh☆ Eheheh, habbyyy, fuheh, heh......」
S021A_2	8	15	Byg Gogo: 「Pig! Address the guests!」
S021A_2	8	16	Sakura: 「Nhyaan, y, yesss〜♪」
S021A_2	8	17	Sakura: 「Fuheh♪」
S021A_2	8	18	Sakura raised both of her shaking hands and made peace signs.
S021A_2	8	19	She was trying to somehow make a charming smile, but it looked like it was stiffening from pleasure even now.
S021A_2	8	20	Sakura: 「I, Ah'm Igawa Sak......ura, aheh☆ Did, you enjoy, mah sex show wif, hah, hah, Gogo-shama?♪」
S021A_2	8	21	Due to Sakura's words, the VIPs gave them an unsparing ovation.
S021A_2	8	22	Cheers and applause filled the VIP Room.
S021A_2	8	23	The applause was sent without holding back even slightly, and then stopped suddenly, without lingering.
S021A_2	8	24	Sakura: 「Fuheeh, fuheeeh, S, Shakura'sh also, oho♪ habby that yoh pleashed!」
S021A_2	8	25	Sakura: 「Ah, Ah will, heh, heh, nheh, continue to, s, serve ash yoh hoshtessh, foh tonigh☆」
S021A_2	8	26	Applause was sent to Sakura and Big Gogo again.
S021A_2	8	27	The MC praised Big Gogo's training, insulted Sakura (who tried to make up for her sins as a Taimanin), and lowered the curtain on the extra performance.
S021A_2	8	28	Señora Serpiente: 「That was a splendid performance, Sakura♪」
S021A_2	8	29	The Slave Prostitutes were about to shift to entertaining the VIPs, when.
S021A_2	8	30	A woman appeared, while clapping gracefully.
S021A_2	8	31	Señora Serpiente: 「You liked that orc's cock quite a bit, didn't you? You're making a face that's reflecting on the joys of womanhood♪」
S021A_2	8	32	It was the Chaos Arena's proprietress and “Madam”, Snake Lady.
S021A_2	8	33	Sakura: 「Nheeh, h, happyyy〜〜♪ Oho, I lub, Cock-shama☆ Fuhi!」
S021A_2	8	34	Señora Serpiente: 「Ara ara♪」
S021A_2	8	35	Snake Lady sadistically curved her lips, which were expressing an elegant smile, and brought her face up close to Sakura.
S021A_2	8	36	She whispered in a voice that only Sakura could hear.
S021A_2	8	37	Señora Serpiente: 「That's no good, is it? You have to stick at it until Onee-chan comes to save you.」
S021A_2	8	38	Señora Serpiente: 「No matter how miserable you feel, you'll survive to punish us together with your Onee-chan, who will definitely come, right?♪」
S021A_2	8	39	Señora Serpiente: 「That's how you protected your mind when you were turned into a Slave Prostitute. And when you were defeated by me, and when you prostrated yourself before that ogre, crying and screaming, and when you were made to stand right here.」
S021A_2	8	40	Señora Serpiente: 「Did you forget that you were resisting, propped up by your beloved Onee-chan?」
S021A_2	9	1	Sakura: 「――――h.」
S021A_2	9	2	The light of reason burned in Sakura's dull eyes.
S021A_2	9	3	Sakura: （That's right, I won't give up......! Onee-chan will definitely come for me, so I have to keep on living......!）
S021A_2	9	4	Sakura: 「That's, right...... I definitely, definitely won't lose, to the likes of you guys......」
S021A_2	9	5	Señora Serpiente: 「Ufufu. Indeed. That's good. Splendid, Sakura-chan♪ Now, to that end, serve a customer as a Slave Prostitute.」
S021A_2	9	6	Telling her so, Snake Lady moved away, and gave the order to release Sakura.
S021A_2	9	7	Her collar was removed, and she finished her duty as Big Gogo's exclusive Slave Prostitute.
S021A_2	9	8	Señora Serpiente: 「This way.」
S021A_2	9	9	Sakura: （Slave Prostitute...... Right now, I have to behave like a Slave Prostitute......）
S021A_2	9	10	Sakura followed after Snake Lady with shaky steps.
S021A_2	9	11	She held back from almost climaxing on the spot due to the semen that leaked out from her pussy and ran along her thighs, and became conscious of the prostitute mannerisms for seducing men that she had been trained in.
S021A_2	9	12	She looked unsightly in her present condition, with her legs and loins numb, but because she was the leading part in the extra performance, she had gathered vulgar interest from those around her.
S021A_2	9	13	Señora Serpiente: 「Over here is today's most special VIP. Offer to clean his cock as sokushaku. He's built up a lot of dick cheese for your sake.」
S021A_2	9	14	Sakura: （Truly the lowliest woman...... And that most-special VIP guy, too.）
S021A_2	9	15	She turned her gaze from Snake Lady, whose eyes seemed wholeheartedly pleased, to a man who sat on a sofa right next to them.
S021A_2	9	16	Sakura: 「I, I am Igawa Sakura, the Slave Prostitute who will serve as your partner for today.」
S021A_2	9	17	Clientes VIP especiales: 「Kukuku, well then, shall I leave it to you?」
S021A_2	9	18	The man nodded relaxedly, and pointed to his groin, which was already erect and pushing up his trousers.
S021A_2	9	19	Clientes VIP especiales: 「Shall I have you put those obscene breasts to use at the same time?」
S021A_2	9	20	Sakura: 「Yes......」
S021A_2	9	21	Sakura bowed, and was about to kneel down when he gave her an order.
S021A_2	9	22	Sakura nodded, and knelt (for sure, this time), removed the man's belt, took out his erect cock, and enveloped it in her two masses of soft flesh.
S021A_2	9	23	SALTAR: S021A_3
