SK002A	1	1	Having suffered defeat in the Chaos Arena, Sakura had been reduced to a Slave Prostitute prospect.
SK002A	1	2	Sakura would definitely meet her sister safe and sound, and would bravely continue to endure any kind of training――Ten-odd days had already passed.
SK002A	1	3	She still hadn't yielded her mind.
SK002A	1	4	However, something was definitely changing inside of Sakura's body, which had piled on the obscene training.
SK002A	1	5	And so, on this day as well――
SK002A	1	6	Sakura: 「You're...... kuuh, my partner again......?」
SK002A	1	7	Byg: 「What? Did you want to do a taste comparison with another guy's dick or somethin'?」
SK002A	1	8	Sakura: 「Y, you're wrong...... nhaah! I just thought, “I'm going to train, only doing it with the same partner?”......」
SK002A	1	9	Sakura said, while swaying her hips, and rubbing her pussy against Byg's uncovered cock through her outfit.
SK002A	1	10	Sakura's pose was a humiliating one, in which she stood on all fours in front of Byg (who brazenly sat on a sofa and spread his legs) and sluttishly stuck her ass out at him.
SK002A	1	11	Her suit, which symbolized justice, had been cruelly turned into an obscene costume, in which the chest section was cut out and her boobs were fully exposed.
SK002A	1	12	Naturally, Sakura's face was filled with humiliation and chagrin.
SK002A	1	13	Sakura: 「Mmh, ah...... haa...... ku, uu......」
SK002A	1	14	However, her body, which had undergone Slave Prostitute training countless times, had reached the point where she got horny and ended up letting out gasps even now, in a situation like this.
SK002A	1	15	Before long, love juices permeated her outfit, and she was fully prepared to serve Byg's huge orc cock.
SK002A	1	16	Byg: 「I see. Once you've gotten hooked on my cock, it might hinder your Slave Whore work, right?」
SK002A	1	17	Sakura: 「Uuu, shut up! It's nothing like that!」
SK002A	1	18	Having what she was unconsciously afraid of pointed out, Sakura smoothed over that in a panic.
SK002A	1	19	Sakura: 「After all, if I weren't in this situation, someone like you wouldn't even be able to lay a finger on me, would you?」
SK002A	1	20	Sakura: 「Be grateful that you can even have sex with me like this......!」
SK002A	1	21	Byg: 「That again? You really don't learn, do ya, pig? Even though you're always half-crying and pissing yourself with joy at the end!」
SK002A	1	22	Sakura: 「Shut up! I'm saying, I won't lose today!」
SK002A	1	23	Hearing the words of Sakura, who acted tough, Byg made a wry smile.
SK002A	1	24	That was because he knew that those words, which had been her true feelings at first, were becoming a mere bluff these days.
SK002A	1	25	Sakura: 「So then, I'm going to put it in now, okay......? Nn, ah......」
SK002A	1	26	Sakura: 「......h...... Kuh, haah...... Oh, it's absurdly thick...... nnh, ah......」
SK002A	1	27	Sakura slowly lowered her hips toward Byg's cock.
SK002A	1	28	She was assailed by the feeling of it being fully buried, cleaving open and stretching her vaginal hole.
SK002A	1	29	Sakura: （No matter, how many times I do this, I don't get used to it at all......! The pain of being spread out, or the pleasure of it rubbing me......）
SK002A	1	30	A little hole had already been opened in the groinal cloth of the Taimanin suit she was wearing now, making insertion possible while she still had it on.
SK002A	1	31	Byg's cock was so thick that the hole spread to its limit, and seemed like it would tear apart any time now.
SK002A	1	32	Sakura: 「Ah, hah...... haa, haa...... uuuuuh〜」
SK002A	1	33	She didn't even have to tighten her vagina, as Byg's orc meat pole put heavy pressure on it.
SK002A	1	34	Sakura brought it in, keeping in close contact with him, and it rubbed all of her sensitive spots as it invaded her.
SK002A	1	35	That act, which had been nothing but repulsive at first, now felt irresistibly good.
SK002A	1	36	Sakura: 「Mmm...... ah, ah...... haah......」
SK002A	1	37	Byg: 「Oi oi, what are you doing, getting off, when this is supposed to be service training?」
SK002A	1	38	Sakura: 「What are, y...... you say, ing? I'm not, getting...... ahih...... off at all......」
SK002A	1	39	Sakura: 「Never mind that, shut up and keep still......! Kuhiih, ahh...... 'Cause I'll make a cock like this ejaculate right away...... Hiaah!」
SK002A	1	40	Even so, Sakura, whose reason still remained, couldn't show weakness, and took a composed-seeming attitude.
SK002A	2	1	However, an attitude like that inadvertently created another opportunity for Byg to take advantage.
SK002A	2	2	Byg: 「You're not getting off? That's farfetched, though, isn't it? After all, you're making your nipples so hard......」
SK002A	2	3	Sakura: 「Ahhh, stop, uuuuuh!」
SK002A	2	4	Byg: 「And you're rattling your legs like this, aren'tcha?」
SK002A	2	5	Sakura: 「Hiiiinh! Why, just from having my leg rubbed......?! Ahhh!」
SK002A	2	6	Byg had reached his hands out, pinching her engorged nipple and stroking her thigh.
SK002A	2	7	Sakura experienced so much pleasure that it felt like her lower body was melting, and her mask of composure was ripped off in the blink of an eye.
SK002A	2	8	Sakura: 「Ah, ahhh...... Don't, my legs will...... uu, kuuuuuh!」
SK002A	2	9	Sakura: 「Oah! Oh hooh☆」
SK002A	2	10	Just like that, Sakura, who had faltered halfway through due to Byg's teasing, let her hips fall straight down, and brought the meat pole in to the hilt all at once.
SK002A	2	11	Having the back of her vagina jabbed, Sakura made an uncouth voice and displayed an enraptured face.
SK002A	2	12	Byg: 「Ah〜, you've become like this again? The more service training you do, the shittier you get at it, don'tcha?」
SK002A	2	13	Byg: 「But hey, as you'd expect after I loosened it so much, your hole's gotten pretty nice, though.」
SK002A	2	14	Sakura: 「Uguh, kahaah......! D, don't shake your hips...... The back's, being rubbed...... nhoohh...」
SK002A	2	15	Byg made his meat pole squirm in order to enjoy the feeling of her vaginal flesh, and precum flowed out from his glans.
SK002A	2	16	The orc bodily fluid, which contained an aphrodisiac, was rubbed into her cervix, which was in close contact with his glans, and Sakura felt that place becoming more sensitive.
SK002A	2	17	Sakura: 「Haah, haah...... nnh...... ah, ahh...... nhiiih......」
SK002A	2	18	Sakura: （Ahhh, no good...... If this is done, I'm gonna break......）
SK002A	2	19	When her cervix was dug into by the glans that had been pressed against it, Sakura's head went blank, and she became unable to think about anything.
SK002A	2	20	Pleasure so captivating that, if she were a normal woman, she would probably have just given herself over and greedily indulged in it.
SK002A	2	21	However, despite even her brain being steeped in pleasure, Sakura swung her head and shook that off.
SK002A	2	22	Sakura: （I have to move...... But, if I move right now, it'll be too much...... Mmm, even so, at this rate, I really will go crazy, so......!）
SK002A	2	23	Sakura: 「W, well then......」
SK002A	2	24	Byg: 「Oh?」
SK002A	2	25	Sakura: 「Perverted Slave Prostitute Sakura, will service you...... nnh...... with her, pussy hole...... kuuuuh...」
SK002A	2	26	Byg: 「Gehi, you're going for it, aren'tcha? That's why you're worth training. So then, I'll leave you to get on with it, okay?」
SK002A	2	27	Sakura delivered the speech that she had been trained to by Byg with a shaking voice, and put strength into her legs.
SK002A	2	28	Sakura: 「Uuh, uuuuuuh!」
SK002A	2	29	Sakura: 「Nnh, gu...... anh! Ah...... nn! Uuh, ku, aaah......」
SK002A	2	30	Byg: 「What's wrong? I can't feel good at all from worthless movement like that!」
SK002A	2	31	Sakura: （Saying whatever he pleases...... But today, I'm gonna make him cum first for sure......!）
SK002A	2	32	Sakura: 「......Nnh! Hiunnn! Nnnh...... uunh! Haah, haah, haah!」
SK002A	2	33	While complaining inside her mind, Sakura held her mouth shut and desperately swung her hips.
SK002A	2	34	However, even though Byg still had a composed expression, Sakura's face was already twisted with pleasure.
SK002A	2	35	The large amount of fluids that dripped from the place where they joined were all her own pussy juices.
SK002A	2	36	Sakura: 「Oh, mmh! Mmh, aah! Ohi, hiiiaaah! Nhiih☆」
SK002A	2	37	Sakura: （Precum is being spread, inside That Place, by his orc cock......!）
SK002A	2	38	Sakura: （Hot, hot, hot, hot hot...... Pussy's so hot it's melting!）
SK002A	2	39	Sakura: （But, but......! I won't give in......! Taimanin Sakura won't lose to a sex monkey like this!）
SK002A	2	40	Sakura: 「Ku, nnh! Uuh, guuuh! Oah! Ah, kuuuuuuuuh!」
SK002A	3	1	Byg: 「Oho, ohh. That's good. Not too bad.」
SK002A	3	2	In the knowledge that she was feeling it as well, Sakura put strength into her vagina to tighten up, wiggled her hips, and rubbed the meat pole.
SK002A	3	3	Byg reflexively moaned and twitched his cock from the feeling of her parted vaginal folds latching onto it and sucking on it.
SK002A	3	4	Sakura: 「Nguuuh! Haah, haah! Uuh, ah, uuuuuuh! Nhaaaah!」
SK002A	3	5	Having sensed that this was a critical moment right now, Sakura increased the speed of her pistoning, and kept on stroking his cock.
SK002A	3	6	When she did, the twitching of his cock grew increasingly intense, his glans became engorged, and its ridge spread out.
SK002A	3	7	Sakura: 「Ahhh, aaaaahhh! Being dug into...... Being ruuubbed! But, buuut......」
SK002A	3	8	Copious Cowper's fluid also gushed out, and Sakura became unable to feel anything but that, as if her entire body had now become a pussy.
SK002A	3	9	Her consciousness flickered on and off, over and over again. If she lost focus, even slightly, she would crumple down and gracelessly collapse onto the floor.
SK002A	3	10	But even so, Sakura was gritting her teeth and grinding her hips around.
SK002A	3	11	Sakura: （Ahh, come on! Quickly...... Ejaculate quickly! Spew out your smelly cum at once!）
SK002A	3	12	Sakura: （Cum, semen! Spew it out of this fat cock......）
SK002A	3	13	Sakura: （It's twitching, becoming burning hot...... I know you want to let it out, so...! Let it out...... without holding baaack!）
SK002A	3	14	Sakura screamed in her mind, while feeling her climax slowly building up.
SK002A	3	15	It was also for the sake of making the training a success, but her body, which wallowed in pleasure, was instinctively craving semen.
SK002A	3	16	Sakura was swinging her hips up and down in order to finish him off, as her sense of duty and her female instincts commanded......
SK002A	3	17	Sakura: 「Kahaah?!」
SK002A	3	18	Sakura: 「Ah......? Oh, eh......? Hahii☆」
SK002A	3	19	All of a sudden, together with a squishing sound, Sakura's field of vision blurred, and her head was struck by a tingling sensation.
SK002A	3	20	Sakura turned her unsteady, shaking eyes in the direction the sound had come from...... the lower half of her body.
SK002A	3	21	Sakura: 「Oh, ah...... Wh, yy......? Bud, Ah'm, servishin you......」
SK002A	3	22	Byg: 「Sorry. It felt too good, so my hips bucked on their own.」
SK002A	3	23	What had caught Sakura's eye was Byg's cock, which had been thrust out at her lowered waist as if to deal a counterattack.
SK002A	3	24	The noise just now, which sounded like flesh being squashed, had been the sound of her cervix, which had loosened up from the pleasure, yielding to the strong impact and being pierced through by his glans.
SK002A	3	25	The instant she realized that, a surge of pleasure, which seemed to engulf everything, advanced on Sakura and roasted her brain.
SK002A	3	26	Sakura: 「C, cu, gumming...... Mustn't, gumm...... Oah, gummming! Cumming, cumming, cumming cumming!」
SK002A	3	27	She immediately grit her teeth and stiffened up to try and endure it, but that conversely ended up amplifying the pleasure.
SK002A	3	28	And then, a torrent of climaxes that she had no way to resist swallowed Sakura's body whole.
SK002A	3	29	Sakura: 「Gumminnng, gum gum gummiiing, gugugiiiiiiiiiiaaaaah!」
SK002A	3	30	Sakura uncouthly threw her head back, stuck her tongue out, panted, and raised a loud cumming voice.
SK002A	3	31	She was making her arms, legs, and entire body convulse, and was about to collapse at any time.
SK002A	3	32	Byg: 「Ohhh, you're tightening up......! Relax, 'cause I'm gonna let out a lot right away!」
SK002A	3	33	And then, Byg, who was headed for an ejaculation, began pumping her fiercely.
SK002A	3	34	Sakura: 「Ohoooh☆ Don'd pull mah womb aroun! You mussn't thrust when you're still inshiiide!」
SK002A	3	35	Sakura: 「Ho hoaaah! Womb bein churrrned! The entrance is stretchin oud to its limiiiit!」
SK002A	3	36	With his glans being made to thrash around inside her uterus, Sakura was being toyed with to the point where she started slurring.
SK002A	3	37	However, her body, which reacted sensitively and convulsed, also gave strong pleasure to Byg's cock.
SK002A	3	38	Byg: 「Uuuu, your cervix and vagina are tightening up, and you're sucking on the head with your womb flesh......!」
SK002A	3	39	Byg: 「Good! Let's respond to that admirable service......! Guuuuuuooh!! I'm gonna let it out, pig!」
SK002A	3	40	Sakura: 「Ngih hiii?!」
SK002A	4	1	Dobyu! Dobyuruuuuuuuuuuuuu!! Byuruuu!
SK002A	4	2	Sakura: 「Uaah ah! Ah, hot! Nn gih! Gumming! Gumming agaaaaaiiinnn!」
SK002A	4	3	Semen was spewed out so as to directly strike the walls of her vulnerable uterus.
SK002A	4	4	Having the lining of it roasted by the heat of the juices, which contained a strong aphrodisiac component, Sakura's climax intensified even further, and her head turned pure white.
SK002A	4	5	Sakura: 「Nhooohhh! Stomach, hurts...... Gonna bursht...... Ohhhhh...... C, cumming...... Cummiiing!」
SK002A	4	6	In the blink of an eye, her little uterus was filled up by a huge amount of cum, and exceeded its maximum capacity.
SK002A	4	7	However, it was corked by Byg's fat cock, and the cum had nowhere to escape to.
SK002A	4	8	Her womb was audibly swelling to its limit due to the force of the semen that kept being pumped in.
SK002A	4	9	Sakura's body, which had completely degraded from pleasure, ended up reaching orgasms over and over and over again just from the feeling of that.
SK002A	4	10	Sakura: 「Eheh, eheah...... ohoh, ooooooohhhh......」
SK002A	4	11	And then, at last, along with a shameful voice, golden drops leaked out from Sakura's groin.
SK002A	4	12	Even the sensation of urine travelling along her urethra was an unbelievably lewd feeling to her now, and she ended up cumming from that alone.
SK002A	4	13	Not even a bit of sense remained in Sakura anymore, and she had become a mere bitch indulging in the pleasure of the ejaculation.
SK002A	4	14	Byg: 「Keh, I think you've gotten a little better, but in the end, it's the same as always. You're a girl who doesn't improve at all, aren'tcha......? Fuu.」
SK002A	4	15	Byg (who had continued ejaculating for a long, long time) squeezed it out into Sakura's womb until the last drop.
SK002A	4	16	And then, he breathed out a pleasured-sounding sigh, and roughly yanked his cock out as if to say that he had finished relieving himself now.
SK002A	4	17	Sakura: 「Nyaah! Don't pull on mah wooomb! Bein pulled ouuut, ahiih, nhaaaah!」
SK002A	4	18	Sakura, who had now gotten used to cumming no matter what was done to her, screamed while making her entire body shake.
SK002A	4	19	But it wasn't like Byg had any need to be concerned about her.
SK002A	4	20	Sakura: 「Aaaaahhhhhh! Nn gyuuu! It came out......!」
SK002A	4	21	By twisting his cock, he extracted his glans from her cervix, and then pulled it out of her vagina.
SK002A	4	22	That place, which had had an excessively thick penis buried in it, wouldn't close, and stayed gaping-open even after it had been pulled out.
SK002A	4	23	However, because it had been let out extremely deep inside, the cum didn't flow out from her vagina, which exposed its pretty, smooth, pink-coloured lining flesh to the air.
SK002A	4	24	Sakura: 「Haheeeh...... ahaah...... Over? Are you finished?」
SK002A	4	25	Byg: 「Oi, how long are you gonna be out of it for......?!!」
SK002A	4	26	Sakura: 「Gi hiiiiiiiih?!!! Aih, gih, ngiih?! Id hurrrrts!」
SK002A	4	27	The meat pole and its ejaculation, which had continued to torment her body, had disappeared, and Sakura had breathed a sigh of relief.
SK002A	4	28	Byg slapped her ass hard with both hands, as if to reprimand her.
SK002A	4	29	And not just once, but twice, and thrice...... She was being struck repeatedly, as if she were a percussion instrument or something.
SK002A	4	30	Sakura: 「H, hey, hooh?! Whaad?! Whahyy? Stop, ahih, nn hiiiih!」
SK002A	4	31	Sakura: 「Stohp! I'm still sensitive right nohoowww! If I'm spanked like thah, I'll go crazy, so shtooohhp!」
SK002A	4	32	Sakura, who was still out of it, woke up and protested to Byg while darting her eyes around in surprise.
SK002A	4	33	Sakura: 「Nhoh hoohoooooooooohhhhh!」
SK002A	4	34	However, the only answer that came back to her was a particularly big slap.
SK002A	4	35	Sakura: 「Ahiee, did cum, buhd I did it to the end, din'n I?! Why something like this, hoooh?!」
SK002A	4	36	Even so, Sakura was in a state where she couldn't comprehend why she was receiving this treatment at all.
SK002A	4	37	Though disgusted, Byg finally opened his mouth.
SK002A	4	38	Byg: 「Haven't I taught you this at length? What was it that you do once the customer finishes ejaculating? Eh?」
SK002A	4	39	Sakura: 「Ah, ahh! Thah'ssh...... S, shorryyy! Ah fohgoht! Iggih, id hurrrtsh!」
SK002A	4	40	Having finally realized her mistake, Sakura reflexively and meekly spoke apologetic words, even though it was to her contemptible orc partner.
SK002A	5	1	However, even though Byg had accepted the apology, he still didn't stop his hands from slapping her buttocks.
SK002A	5	2	Sakura: 「Ah'll do it, I'll do id now, so! Ow! Stop your haaaannnndsh!」
SK002A	5	3	Byg: 「Don't mind this, say it right now!」
SK002A	5	4	Sakura: 「Yeeeeeessssssss!」
SK002A	5	5	Sakura: 「Thank you very musssh, for using the cock-stroking hole of Slave Prostitute Sakura, who has no skills except squeezing out shemennn.」
SK002A	5	6	Sakura: 「As a toilet hole, I am overjoyed to have you excrete a lot in mehhh...... kuuuh...」
SK002A	5	7	Sakura: 「Taking responsibility is completely unnecessary if I get pregnant. The responsibility for my fertilized eggs is entirely by your own choice......!」
SK002A	5	8	While shedding tears from the pain of her ass, Sakura delivered her speech, expressing the most flirtatious look she could manage on her face.
SK002A	5	9	Hearing that all the way to the end, Byg finally moved his hands away from her buttocks.
SK002A	5	10	Sakura: 「Haah, haah............ uuh, ah...」
SK002A	5	11	At that moment, the semen that had been crammed into her uterus finally started overflowing from her vagina.
SK002A	5	12	That made Sakura, who had returned to sanity because of the pain, fully realize that it had been let out in her vagina by an orc, and even more tears arose.
SK002A	5	13	Byg: 「All right, seems good. Remember, absolutely do not forget during a real performance.」
SK002A	5	14	Byg: 「'Cause, if you've got a short-tempered, violent customer, it wouldn't be strange if you lost an arm or two.」
SK002A	5	15	Sakura: 「Uuh, uu...... You're pretty short-tempered and violent too......」
SK002A	5	16	Byg: 「Did you say something?」
SK002A	5	17	Sakura: 「N, nothinnng!」
SK002A	5	18	Sakura: （Uuu, Onee-chan. Come save me quicklyyy〜......）
SK002A	5	19	Sakura, who was worn out from the intense training, reflexively whined, albeit in her mind.
SK002A	5	20	However, that wasn't just because her days of repeated training were agonizing.
SK002A	5	21	Sakura: （If you don't, I...... I......）
SK002A	5	22	Cum kept pouring out from her gaping-open vaginal hole.
SK002A	5	23	Mixing into that, transparent juices were trickling out from the depths of her pussy.
SK002A	5	24	Those were the love juices of Sakura, who had reached the point where she ended up getting off even from the spanking, which should have merely hurt.
SK002A	5	25	The young Taimanin girl's body was becoming lewder by the day, little by little――
SK002A	5	26	The day when Sakura would become a Slave Prostitute was soon approaching.
