S007A	1	1	―――The next day.	ms07a	0000
S007A	1	2	Lab Worker: 「Kiryuu-sama. The preparations have been completed.」	ms07a	0001
S007A	1	3	Kiryuu: 「Good...... Shit, that monster......」	ms07a	0002
S007A	1	4	After making Murasaki and Sakura his prisoners, Kiryuu had kept working through the night, in an underground room that had been custom-built for the sake of his research.	ms07a	0003
S007A	1	5	Of course, he had prepared the best “welcome” he could for Murasaki. Kiryuu had been trusted to deal with Murasaki and Sakura by Black, but......	ms07a	0004
S007A	1	6	Kiryuu: 「Hmph, I didn't need to be ordered......!」	ms07a	0005
S007A	1	7	Kiryuu: （After all, that was my intention from the start.）	ms07a	0006
S007A	1	8	Lab workers, who were subordinates under Kiryuu's direct supervision, were all silently proceeding with their work. The fact that his best assistant―the name slipped his mind―had been killed by Murasaki was a heavy loss, but...	ms07a	0007
S007A	1	9	Kiryuu: 「Well, good. The project is still outside the margin of error.」	ms07a	0008
S007A	1	10	The “Project”―the plan that Kiryuu had devised― was proceeding as scheduled.	ms07a	0009
S007A	1	11	Even the preparation for this welcome was an important component of that.	ms07a	0010
S007A	1	12	Assistant: 「Kiryuu-sama. There's something you'll want to hear.」	ms07a	0011
S007A	1	13	A lab worker, whom he had ordered to help him in his lost assistant's place, approached Kiryuu and whispered into his ear in a low voice.	ms07a	0012
S007A	1	14	Kiryuu: 「What, what? I'm busy...... What is it?」	ms07a	0013
S007A	1	15	Assistant: 「There's no mistake. There is movement concerning some kind of investigation of Kiryuu-sama's research.」	ms07a	0014
S007A	1	16	Kiryuu: 「Hmph, her. Ingrid......」	ms07a	0015
S007A	1	17	Given that Black's aide, Ingrid, had had a dog-and- monkey relationship with Kiryuu from the beginning, he knew she wanted to have him removed from the Chaos Arena if possible.	ms07a	0016
S007A	1	18	Thus, the arrogant conduct of Ingrid, who snooped around Kiryuu, was normal...... But Kiryuu could not laugh it off right now.	ms07a	0017
S007A	1	19	Kiryuu: 「Edwin Black......」	ms07a	0018
S007A	1	20	―――『Don't betray me, Kiryuu Sabato.』	ms07a	0019
S007A	1	21	Kiryuu: 「Oooh, knock on wood.」	ms07a	0020
S007A	1	22	Yesterday's words had gone in through Kiryuu's ears, dug into a deep part of his mind, and remained there like a tumour.	ms07a	0021
S007A	1	23	Kiryuu: （Has that man already realized......?）	ms07a	0022
S007A	1	24	This man, Kiryuu Sabato, who didn't have even a bit of loyalty, could never be a faithful subordinate.	ms07a	0023
S007A	1	25	Kiryuu pledged allegiance only to his enthusiasm for hellish medical treatment.	ms07a	0024
S007A	1	26	Even living in the basement of the Chaos Arena and belonging to Nomad, which controlled the Arena, was all for the sake of his research.	ms07a	0025
S007A	1	27	As long as they offered an opportunity for research, he was okay with any sponsor, and there was no reason to limit himself to one.	ms07a	0026
S007A	1	28	Kiryuu: 「Call “Ryuumon”. Tell them that in a little while, they might have to repay the favour.」	ms07a	0027
S007A	1	29	Assistant: 「Yes, certainly.」	ms07a	0028
S007A	1	30	Ryuumon was one of the crime syndicates hostile to Edwin Black.	ms07a	0029
S007A	1	31	Even having inflicted a deep wound on Black was the doing of a “warrior” that Ryuumon possessed, and Kiryuu, of course, had intimately participated in the development of those “warriors”.	ms07a	0030
S007A	1	32	Assistant: 「So, what should we do about Ingrid?」	ms07a	0031
S007A	1	33	Kiryuu: 「Oh, I forgot, Ingrid. Hmm......」	ms07a	0032
S007A	1	34	Black's sycophant was an eyesore, but strong. He couldn't be negligent.	ms07a	0033
S007A	1	35	SELECCIONAR 1: S007B
S007A	1	36	SELECCIONAR 2: S007C
