SB014B	1	1	Murasaki: 「Puah, hah, haah, haah, haaaa......」	ms14a	0064
SB014B	1	2	After they had exchanged a long, passionate kiss, Murasaki breathed out heavily.	ms14a	0065
SB014B	1	3	Her head had become hot and her consciousness hazy from the sweet sensation of her tongue being sucked on, and the inside of her mouth being licked around.	ms14a	0066
SB014B	1	4	The feeling of Kiryuu's fleshy tongue still remained inside her mouth. When she remembered that, she ended up unconsciously licking her lips.	ms14a	0067
SB014B	1	5	Kiryuu: 「Seems you were feeling pretty good, weren't you?」	ms14a	0068
SB014B	1	6	Looking at Murasaki, whose cheeks were still flushed, Kiryuu made a dirty smile.	ms14a	0069
SB014B	1	7	Murasaki: 「Ah, I......」	ms14a	0070
SB014B	1	8	She had exposed an obscene appearance in front of Kiryuu. Murasaki's whole body became flaming hot from shame and humiliation.	ms14a	0071
SB014B	1	9	Kiryuu: 「Well then, I wonder what kind of teasing you want next?」	ms14a	0072
SB014B	1	10	Kiryuu brought his face towards Murasaki's own flushed face.	ms14a	0073
SB014B	1	11	Murasaki: 「D, don't look...... Please...... don't look......」	ms14a	0074
SB014B	1	12	Murasaki hid her face, as if unable to bear the shame, and murmured in a frail voice.	ms14a	0075
SB014B	1	13	SALTAR: SUB_START_CHK
