SS014E	1	1	As if to reflect Kiryuu's intentions, tentacles, which had grown out from the lower half of his body, started to twine around Murasaki.	ms14a	0597
SS014E	1	2	Murasaki: 「Hii, iah...... Hah, haah, wh, what are...... aaaaah!」	ms14a	0598
SS014E	1	3	The tentacles that had coiled around Murasaki's limbs elevated her body, just like that. Murasaki's body rose into the air, face-down.	ms14a	0599
SS014E	1	4	Kiryuu: 「Kukuku, that's a pretty nice view, isn't it?」	ms14a	0600
SS014E	1	5	Murasaki was lifted up to exactly chest-height, and her lower parts came into view.	ms14a	0601
SS014E	1	6	Her legs were spread by the tentacles, and her groin became exposed. A stain had started to appear on the thin piece of fabric which concealed that important place.	ms14a	0602
SS014E	1	7	Murasaki: 「Nooooo...... Don't...... look...... Don't look......!」	ms14a	0603
SS014E	1	8	Murasaki made an ashamed voice, like she had forgotten that she was a Slave Prostitute.	ms14a	0604
SS014E	1	9	It seemed that she felt his eyes concentrating on her groin. The face that looked back at him was blushing out of shame.	ms14a	0605
SS014E	1	10	She struggled, trying to escape from the tentacles, but they had no intention of releasing their prey.	ms14a	0606
SS014E	1	11	Kiryuu: 「Kuku, what are you doing, getting embarrassed from this little?」	ms14a	0607
SS014E	1	12	He brought his face toward the place where the stain had been made, and inhaled in order to sniff its stench.	ms14a	0608
SS014E	1	13	Murasaki: 「Hah?! Hah, haah, haaaa...... D, don't sniff...... the smell...... ah...... yaaaah!」	ms14a	0609
SS014E	1	14	Seeing her crotch being noisily sniffed, Murasaki twisted her body again.	ms14a	0610
SS014E	1	15	Kiryuu: 「In spite of not liking it, it looks like this spot is getting bigger, though?」	ms14a	0611
SS014E	1	16	The spot over her groin was gradually spreading out. When he informed Murasaki of that fact, she bucked her hips, and then stopped moving.	ms14a	0612
SS014E	1	17	Kiryuu: 「You're feeling it, aren't you? Exposing a disgraceful appearance like this feels good, right?」	ms14a	0613
SS014E	1	18	He breathed hot breaths toward the spot, and Murasaki's toes twitched.	ms14a	0614
SS014E	1	19	Murasaki: 「Nfuu, fu, haah, hafuuuuh...... N, no good... Don't...... breathe...... on......」	ms14a	0615
SS014E	1	20	Kiryuu: 「I see. Breathing on it's no good? Well then......」	ms14a	0616
SS014E	1	21	He reached his hand out towards her underwear, on which the stain had been made, and traced her slit through it.	ms14a	0617
SS014E	1	22	Murasaki: 「Hiah?! Hah, haah, ah, haaaaaaah! T, touching......?」	ms14a	0618
SS014E	1	23	Kiryuu: 「That's right. I'm touching it...... Kuku, when I apply pressure like this...... the spot gets larger again, doesn't it?」	ms14a	0619
SS014E	1	24	While pushing the underwear into her cleft, he dug into her vaginal flesh with his fingers.	ms14a	0620
SS014E	1	25	The stain that had been made on her underwear became even larger, and Murasaki's hips began trembling in delight.	ms14a	0621
SS014E	1	26	A sweet, ecstatic voice escaped from the lips of Murasaki, who could not control her sexual excitement. As he listened to that voice, his fingers moved, searching for her clitoris.	ms14a	0622
SS014E	1	27	Murasaki: 「Huah! Hah, haah, aaaah, hih, ahi, nhiiiiih!」	ms14a	0623
SS014E	1	28	Murasaki started gasping in a sweet voice, as if she had cast away the shame she had been displaying until just before.	ms14a	0624
SS014E	1	29	Kiryuu: 「Kukukuu, here. Here it is.」	ms14a	0625
SS014E	1	30	He found her clitoris, then pressed against her underwear and confirmed its swollen state.	ms14a	0626
SS014E	1	31	Kiryuu: 「It's gotten bigger, yearning to be pinched. You want me to touch this place, don't you?」	ms14a	0627
SS014E	1	32	He asked Murasaki, who looked at him, still making her cheeks blush and her eyes moist, and	ms14a	0628
SS014E	1	33	Murasaki: 「Kufu, fu, fuu...... haah, hah, aah, nfuuuuuu!」	ms14a	0629
SS014E	1	34	Murasaki did not answer. She just let out a gasping voice, without saying yes or no.	ms14a	0630
SS014E	1	35	However, her face, which was steeped in ecstasy, was yearning for strong stimulation to her clitoris.	ms14a	0631
SS014E	1	36	Kiryuu: 「Should I pinch or should I squash......? Kukuku, there's no need to rack my brain. I should try both!」	ms14a	0632
SS014E	1	37	He pinched her erect clitoris, which made her underwear rise up.	ms14a	0633
SS014E	1	38	Murasaki: 「Hyah?! Hih, iah! Ih, ihiiiiiiii! Ah, aaaah!」	ms14a	0634
SS014E	1	39	Murasaki's body, which was suspended in midair, jumped like an electric current had flowed through it. She gave off screams of pleasure, and began to drool, her mouth still slobbishly open.	ms14a	0635
SS014E	1	40	Murasaki indulged in the pleasure, like she had given up fighting against the rapturous feelings that surged toward her.	ms14a	0636
SS014E	2	1	Kiryuu: 「Kukuku, next, I'll squash it!」	ms14a	0637
SS014E	2	2	Murasaki: 「Haah, aah, n, no use...... Hiih, ih, iih, my body is...... flying...... flying...... kuu......」	ms14a	0638
SS014E	2	3	Momentarily washed away by the waves of pleasure that surged toward her, Murasaki emitted a gasping voice.	ms14a	0639
SS014E	2	4	Even though they were held back by her carnal voice, which was moist from the pleasure, that had merely stimulated her seething arousal. His fingers let go of her clitoris, which they had been pinching, and gently stroked it through her underwear.	ms14a	0640
SS014E	2	5	Perhaps because even that faint stimulation turned into strong pleasure, Murasaki once again stiffened her body and let out gasps of ecstasy.	ms14a	0641
SS014E	2	6	While seeing that the stain was gradually spreading out again, this time, he squashed the clitoris as hard as he could.	ms14a	0642
SS014E	2	7	Murasaki: 「Kihiii! Hih, hih, noo, ihiiiiiiii!!」	ms14a	0643
SS014E	2	8	Murasaki gave off a scream while bending her head and spine backwards, and dishevelled her hair as she shook her head.	ms14a	0644
SS014E	2	9	The endlessly-overflowing honey juices were making the stain even bigger, and her underwear had already become so slimy that it barely fulfilled its purpose.	ms14a	0645
SS014E	2	10	Murasaki continued making obscene gasps, as if she had ended up forgetting everything due to the stimulation of her clitoris.	ms14a	0646
SS014E	2	11	It seemed that she had gotten carried away from the pleasure, and had even forgotten that she was entwined by tentacles and exposing a shameful appearance.	ms14a	0647
SS014E	2	12	If her obscene appearance were pointed out, she might regain her senses and try to stifle her carnal feelings again.	ms14a	0648
SS014E	2	13	Kiryuu: 「That would be boring......」	ms14a	0649
SS014E	2	14	Forcefully teasing a resisting Murasaki would be good too, but right now he wanted to thoroughly enjoy the sight of Murasaki falling.	ms14a	0650
SS014E	2	15	Giving Murasaki even more pleasure, exciting her sexual desire more and more and more, and, all at once......!	ms14a	0651
SS014E	2	16	The image of Murasaki writhing violently drifted through his mind, and strength seemed to fill his tentacles and meat pole.	ms14a	0652
SS014E	2	17	Murasaki: 「Hah, hah, haah, haah, hiah, nfuuuuuh...... haaaah!」	ms14a	0653
SS014E	2	18	While looking at Murasaki, who was basking in the afterglow of the strong stimulation to her clitoris, he took his fingers away from it for a moment.	ms14a	0654
SS014E	2	19	Kiryuu: 「For it to get this slimy... This is a deluge, isn't it?♪ I'd better cork it, then.」	ms14a	0655
SS014E	2	20	Though it didn't seem like Murasaki, who was wallowing in pleasure, understood the meaning of his words, Kiryuu said so to her, then......	ms14a	0656
SS014E	2	21	Shifted her sopping underwear to the side, and her dripping-wet slit was exposed before his eyes.	ms14a	0657
SS014E	2	22	He pushed open her slit, which was greedily oozing with honey juices, and thrust his middle finger and ring finger inside.	ms14a	0658
SS014E	2	23	Murasaki: 「Hyahii! Hii! Ihii, nhiiih, heah, heaaaaaaah!」	ms14a	0659
SS014E	2	24	The two fingers felt strong pressure. Her vaginal flesh was undulating as it clung to the intruders.	ms14a	0660
SS014E	2	25	Murasaki's vaginal flesh was burning hot, as if to demonstrate the level of her excitement.	ms14a	0661
SS014E	2	26	He was thrusting his fingers into the very depths of her vaginal walls, which coiled around them. Murasaki's body jerked every time the fingers moved.	ms14a	0662
SS014E	2	27	Kiryuu: 「Kukuku, looks like they're in up to the root. You see? My fingers are going into your depths.」	ms14a	0663
SS014E	2	28	His hand had already become sticky with honey juices, which overflowed from inside her vagina. While soaked to the wrist with the honey juices, which flowed along his hand, he looked at Murasaki, and	ms14a	0664
SS014E	2	29	Murasaki: 「Hiih, ih, iah...... Going in...... uu...... Going...... insiiide! Ah, ahiih! Ahiiiii!」	ms14a	0665
SS014E	2	30	A face that was surprised by having the inside of her vagina violated by his fingers came into view.	ms14a	0666
SS014E	2	31	He rubbed his fingers against her flesh walls, which were slimy-wet with honey juices, and ascertained their flexibility.	ms14a	0667
SS014E	2	32	Bending his middle finger slightly, he grazed the flesh walls as if clawing at them, and the undulation of her vaginal flesh became greater from that alone.	ms14a	0668
SS014E	2	33	Murasaki: 「Iih! Ih, iiiiih! Hioh, nfuuuu, being rubbed...... Bein rubbed! Rubbing, the inside!」	ms14a	0669
SS014E	2	34	He thrust his fingers in to the base, and moved them.	ms14a	0670
SS014E	2	35	The stronger the stimulation of her flesh walls grew, the louder Murasaki's voice became as well.	ms14a	0671
SS014E	2	36	Murasaki's labia twitched, her legs stiffened up, and her body convulsed like she had cum a little.	ms14a	0672
SS014E	2	37	Kiryuu: 「Kukuku, you're going to get to feel better and better... The place where you feel it the most is......」	ms14a	0673
SS014E	2	38	He pulled his fingers, which had been crammed all the way in, out a little, and moved them toward her vaginal opening.	ms14a	0674
SS014E	2	39	Murasaki: 「Haah, hahi, hi, heaaah, hieaaaaaaah!」	ms14a	0675
SS014E	2	40	While looking at Murasaki, who displayed a reaction each time the fingers moved, he was searching for her vagina's most sensitive spot.	ms14a	0676
SS014E	3	1	Kiryuu: 「Kukuku, is it here......?」	ms14a	0677
SS014E	3	2	He gently touched that place, and Murasaki's body bucked conspicuously hard.	ms14a	0678
SS014E	3	3	Kiryuu: 「This is the G-spot. Ohh, pussy juice is overflowing just from rubbing it!」	ms14a	0679
SS014E	3	4	Murasaki: 「Hiaa?! Th, that place isssss......?!」	ms14a	0680
SS014E	3	5	Murasaki: 「Kyahiiiiiiii! Heh, heh, ehiiiiiii!」	ms14a	0681
SS014E	3	6	He moved his fingers up and down over that place, almost enough for her honey juices to froth.	ms14a	0682
SS014E	3	7	He had found the place where Murasaki got off the most, and the stimulation from having it relentlessly rubbed against had gotten her lust worked up in an instant.	ms14a	0683
SS014E	3	8	Murasaki gave off a slutty voice every time he rubbed her vaginal flesh with his middle finger. The quantity of honey juice increased even further, formed a spray, and began to scatter around.	ms14a	0684
SS014E	3	9	Murasaki: 「Ihi, hi, ihiiih! Ah, naaaaaah! Oh, huoooooh!」	ms14a	0685
SS014E	3	10	Murasaki opened her eyes wide while raising a bestial scream, and made her body jerk over and over and over again.	ms14a	0686
SS014E	3	11	Kiryuu: 「How is it?! Do you feel like cumming?! Kukuku, or, have you cum already?!」	ms14a	0687
SS014E	3	12	He asked, sneering as he watched Murasaki indulge in pleasure. Even during that, his fingers continued to incessantly rub her vaginal flesh, and give her unparalleled pleasure.	ms14a	0688
SS014E	3	13	The face of Murasaki, who had gotten worked up to her limit, contorted sluttishly, and drool continued to stream out from her lips, which kept giving off cries of pleasure.	ms14a	0689
SS014E	3	14	Murasaki: 「Ihii, ihiiii! No ushe, no uuuuushe! Bein ruhhhbbed! Oh, ohh! Oooohhhh!」	ms14a	0690
SS014E	3	15	It seemed that Murasaki no longer even realized that she was shrieking in a shameful voice.	ms14a	0691
SS014E	3	16	Murasaki was just indulging in pleasure and heading towards her climax.	ms14a	0692
SS014E	3	17	Kiryuu: 「Kukukuu......」	ms14a	0693
SS014E	3	18	The moment that Murasaki was about to reach climax, the fingers that had been digging into her vaginal flesh were pulled out.	ms14a	0694
SS014E	3	19	Murasaki: 「Huheh......? Heaaah......」	ms14a	0695
SS014E	3	20	The moment that she had gotten worked up to her limit and started to cum, the stimulation from the inside of her vagina being dug into stopped.	ms14a	0696
SS014E	3	21	Her face still flushed, Murasaki looked at Kiryuu in a stupor, like she couldn't understand what had happened.	ms14a	0697
SS014E	3	22	Kiryuu: 「Kukuku, that's all.」	ms14a	0698
SS014E	3	23	Kiryuu licked his fingers, which had gotten wet with honey juices, then pointed a sadistic smile towards Murasaki.	ms14a	0699
SS014E	3	24	Murasaki: 「It's o.....ver...... hah, ah, the end...... h...... That's...... aah, it's...... ah......」	ms14a	0700
SS014E	3	25	Murasaki instinctively let out a pained-sounding voice, while making her labia twitch.	ms14a	0701
SS014E	3	26	Kiryuu: 「That's right. Now it's over. Kukuku, I hope you were able to enjoy it well enough.」	ms14a	0702
SS014E	3	27	Honey juices stretched strings from her twitching genitals as they oozed out.	ms14a	0703
SS014E	3	28	Murasaki: 「Uah, haah, haa, aah...... afuuu, nh, nfuuuuuh...」	ms14a	0704
SS014E	3	29	Carnal breaths kept being exhaled by Murasaki, who made her entire body writhe in frustration.	ms14a	0705
SS014E	3	30	SALTAR: SB014E
