S004A	1	1	Mercenary: "Boss, we've arrived. Boss?"	s04a	0000
S004A	1	2	Gagoze: "Huh?"	s04a	0001
S004A	1	3	Being called, I slowly opened my eyes.	s04a	0002
S004A	1	4	Mercenary: "We're in Alraune."	s04a	0003
S004A	1	5	Gagoze: "Is that so...."	s04a	0004
S004A	1	6	It was a sight that was all too familiar to me.	s04a	0005
S004A	1	7	Gagoze: "Hah......."	s04a	0006
S004A	1	8	I stepped down from the transport, and looked at the city.	s04a	0007
S004A	1	9	Alraune.	s04a	0008
S004A	1	10	It was the name of a city in the Union of Guilds, the 3rd most powerful territory on the Celtoana continent.	s04a	0009
S004A	1	11	Several hundred years ago, the countless guilds united, creating a rather unique country of sorts.	s04a	0010
S004A	1	12	Up until about 200 years ago, they were the source of materials and craftsmen of Celtoana.	s04a	0011
S004A	1	13	But about 2 generations ago, oil, and the way to use it, was discovered..	s04a	0012
S004A	1	14	With that discovery, the guilds, who already had vast amounts of natural resources, became even more powerful.	s04a	0013
S004A	1	15	They now export drache tanks to both the Empire and Alliance.	s04a	0014
S004A	1	16	It could be said that the Union of Guilds is the newest power on the Celtoana continent.	s04a	0015
S004A	1	17	A glance at their cities reveals as much.	s04a	0016
S004A	1	18	Gagoze: "Well....I guess there's a little more to it than that..."	s04a	0017
S004A	1	19	Looking at the gigantic walls that had been built to surround the city, I set out towards the center of it.	s04a	0018
S004A	1	20	The place I was familiar with was a certain back alley that hardly anyone walked.	s04a	0022
S004A	1	21	Gagoze: "No....."	s04a	0023
S004A	1	22	It's not that hardly anyone walked it, it was that only those who had a reason to could be found using it.	s04a	0024
S004A	1	23	Man: "What's this? Why, it's Gagoze."	s04a	0025
S004A	1	24	Gagoze: "Hey."	s04a	0026
S004A	1	25	I came to the building I was looking for, and a man with a face I knew called out to me.	s04a	0027
S004A	1	26	Gagoze: "You-know-who called for me. Is she here?"	s04a	0028
S004A	1	27	Man: "Yes. But, unfortunately she is attending to a client at the moment..."	s04a	0029
S004A	1	28	Gagoze: "Well then, I'll wait inside."	s04a	0030
S004A	1	29	I entered the door behind the man.	s04a	0031
S004A	1	30	Then I began descending the stairs that lead down underground.	s04a	0032
S004A	1	31	………	s04a	0033
S004A	1	32	……	s04a	0034
S004A	1	33	…	s04a	0035
S004A	1	34	After a moment, my eyes adjusted to their surroundings.	s04a	0036
S004A	1	35	At the same time, a stench filled my nose.	s04a	0037
S004A	1	36	Girl: "Hah....ahyi....ohh, hahn.... N-no, please don't.......ah....."	s04a	0038
S004A	1	37	Man: "What are you saying? Heh heh.  Look at how wet you are!"	s04a	0039
S004A	1	38	Girl: "No....agh.....please......ahyiii!"	s04a	0040
S004A	1	39	Gagoze: "I see this place is still exactly the same."	s04a	0041
S004A	1	40	There was nothing surprising about the scene before me. I exhaled.	s04a	0042
S004A	2	1	Woman: "Hagh...kah...Master~..... Please...more...give me more cock..."	s04a	0043
S004A	2	2	Man: "Ahaha! You're a good girl, aren't you? Okay then, I'll take you home with me!!♪	s04a	0044
S004A	2	3	Woman: "Yes....Please, buy me. Buy me and make me your cock slave!!"	s04a	0045
S004A	2	4	Cries of delight were heard all around me.	s04a	0046
S004A	2	5	Girl: "No, no more! Let me go! Let me go back home!!"	s04a	0047
S004A	2	6	As well as cries of fear.	s04a	0048
S004A	2	7	The sound of malesand females coupling heard throughout the room, and it's stench permeated the area.	s04a	0049
S004A	2	8	This was the hidden side of the Union of Guild's Alraune.	s04a	0050
S004A	2	9	Girl: "Hahh....hikyah....ahii! No, I'll go crazy....I'll.... I'm going crazy!!!"	s04a	0051
S004A	2	10	These were the slaves that had been either taken or stolen from the Empire and Alliance territories.	s04a	0052
S004A	2	11	And then there were the ones who were here to "sample" or perhaps buy some of the merchandise on display.	s04a	0053
S004A	2	12	Race, religion, nationality, none of it mattered here.	s04a	0054
S004A	2	13	looking around, you'd find anyone  from a noble of Fuluakia to a member of parliament from the Alliance.	s04a	0055
S004A	2	14	Even if they tried to hide it, they all had an insatiable greed.	s04a	0056
S004A	2	15	They were pigs, albeit insanely wealthy, who were fat from that greed.	s04a	0057
S004A	2	16	And then there were the slaves, lower than pigs, who could either service them or wait to be made to service them.	s04a	0058
S004A	2	17	This was a gathering to evaluate those slaves.	s04a	0059
S004A	2	18	Girl: "Ahyi....No, no! Please stop! Let me go home!!"	s04a	0060
S004A	2	19	The ones who screamed might still have had some hope left in them.	s04a	0061
S004A	2	20	Girl: "Ahn....ah....hah.....hyi.....ah, ah, ah"	s04a	0062
S004A	2	21	But the ones who could no longer make anything but "noises" were, in a  way, perhaps the happiest.	s04a	0063
S004A	2	22	The entire continent's corruption and scum gathered here.	s04a	0064
S004A	2	23	The "customers" who came here usually avoided entering directly. Instead they were brought from the edge of the city by transports.	s04a	0065
S004A	2	24	But it wasn't just this place. This entire city served as the brothel of the Union of Guilds.	s04a	0066
S004A	2	25	Gagoze: "Haha, guess I'm just old fashioned...."	s04a	0067
S004A	2	26	I too often sold "merchandise" in this city.	s04a	0068
