S011A	1	1	The Fuluakia emperor's imperial villa.	s11a	0000
S011A	1	2	It was a place were only the royal family and one other person was permitted to enter.	s11a	0001
S011A	1	3	Fuluakian Emperor: "Haha, you don't have to be so nervous."	s11a	0002
S011A	1	4	The youthful emperor smiled.	s11a	0003
S011A	1	5	The one he was smiling at was Noa.	s11a	0004
S011A	1	6	Fuluakian Emperor: "So...how are the peace talks going?"	s11a	0005
S011A	1	7	Noa: "Sir, both Anastasia and Daness are making favorable progress."	s11a	0006
S011A	1	8	She didn't even hesitate.	s11a	0007
S011A	1	9	Noa: "Danesss from the Alliance and Anastasia are handling the talks as if they were old friends."	s11a	0008
S011A	1	10	Fuluakian Emperor: "Is that so...Haha, It seems what Anastasia was talking about was right."	s11a	0009
S011A	1	11	The young emperor recalled what Anastasia had confessed to him and smiled once more.	s11a	0010
S011A	1	12	Fuluakian Emperor: "I suspect from here on out it will be a critical point for the talks, but could you please tell Anastasia to continue to do her best?"	s11a	0011
S011A	1	13	Noa: "Y-Yes sir!"	s11a	0012
S011A	1	14	Seeing his smile, Noa let out a nervous reply.	s11a	0013
S011A	1	15	Fuluakian Emperor: "I told you Noa, relax. If these talks go well, this world will finally know peace once again."	s11a	0014
S011A	1	16	Noa: "........."	s11a	0015
S011A	1	17	Noa's expression slightly paled as the empreror spoke those words.	s11a	0016
S011A	1	18	Fuluakian Emperor: "Hm? What's wrong?"	s11a	0017
S011A	1	19	Noa: "N-Nothing..."	s11a	0018
S011A	1	20	She looked as if she couldn't say something she wanted to.	s11a	0019
S011A	1	21	Noa: "U-Um, your majesty..."	s11a	0020
S011A	1	22	But even so, she tried to say it.	s11a	0021
S011A	1	23	Fuluakian Emperor: "Hm? What is it?"	s11a	0022
S011A	1	24	Noa: "Ah...N-....no, Never...mind. That's...all I have to report."	s11a	0023
S011A	1	25	She swallowed back the words that had almost escaped her throat, and saluted.	s11a	0024
S011A	1	26	Fuluakian Emperor: "Thank you. I won't be able to meet with Anastasia until the talks are over, but please send her my greetings."	s11a	0025
S011A	1	27	Noa: "Yes sir..."	s11a	0026
S011A	1	28	How Noa's reply must have pained her.	s11a	0027
S011A	1	29	………	s11a	0028
S011A	1	30	……	s11a	0029
S011A	1	31	…	s11a	0030
S011A	1	32	If you went beyond the modern roads of the Celtoana continent, you'd find yourself surrounded by forests.	s11a	0031
S011A	1	33	No matter how far technology had come, nature was still something it could not control.	s11a	0032
S011A	1	34	Within that forest, a single armored vehicle was on the move.	s11a	0033
S011A	1	35	It's emblem was that of the Fuluakia Empire.	s11a	0034
S011A	1	36	Having departed for the imperial palace a few days before, it was now headed to Union territory.	s11a	0035
S011A	1	37	...	s11a	0036
