S012B	1	1	Gagoze: "Yeah, I'll do that..."	s12b	0000
S012B	1	2	Unfortunately, I have no interest in beastiality.	s12b	0001
S012B	1	3	It'd just be something else for me to have to deal with. I'll just get Jean to take care of it.	s12b	0002
S012B	1	4	Making that decision, I turned on my heel and went the way I had come from.	s12b	0003
S012B	1	5	………	s12b	0004
S012B	1	6	……	s12b	0005
S012B	1	7	…	s12b	0006
S012B	1	8	Jean: "I was just getting ready for bed... You know a good rest is vital to maintaining beautiful skin, don't you?"	s12b	0007
S012B	1	9	Gagoze: "I said I'm sorry."	s12b	0008
S012B	1	10	I gave an honest apology to Jean, even though I could never tell how honest Jean was being.	s12b	0009
S012B	1	11	Gagoze: "So, have the arrangements been made?"	s12b	0010
S012B	1	12	Jean: "Take a look for yourself♪"	s12b	0011
S012B	1	13	Jean gestured into her room.	s12b	0012
