S013A	1	1	？？: "Oi."	s13a	0000
S013A	1	2	Gagoze: "Hm?"	s13a	0001
S013A	1	3	While walking around the city without any particular aim, someone called to me.	s13a	0002
S013A	1	4	Looking back I saw Anastasia.	s13a	0003
S013A	1	5	Gagoze: "What do you think? This city is pretty easy to live in, right?"	s13a	0004
S013A	1	6	Anastasia: "Hmph."	s13a	0005
S013A	1	7	Anastasia just frowned at my words.	s13a	0006
S013A	1	8	Anastasia: "Not when you're being watched every hour of the day."	s13a	0007
S013A	1	9	Anastasia knew that everyone in this city had connections to the slave market.	s13a	0008
S013A	1	10	She was still frowning.	s13a	0009
S013A	1	11	Gagoze: "Hey, don't say that. This is just your preperation for becoming 'merchandise.'"	s13a	0010
S013A	1	12	Anastasia: "You...!!"	s13a	0011
S013A	1	13	Her pretty face twisted at my simple jab to her honor.	s13a	0012
S013A	1	14	But, only for a fleeting moment.	s13a	0013
S013A	1	15	Anastasia: "Sorry to ask, but do you know where Noa is?"	s13a	0014
S013A	1	16	Gagoze: "Huh? Oh, that dog?"	s13a	0015
S013A	1	17	Yeah, I knew where she was. But pretending I didn't, I faked ignorance.	s13a	0016
S013A	1	18	Anastasia: "Yes, Noa. I haven't seen her for the past few days..."	s13a	0017
S013A	1	19	Gagoze: "I have no idea."	s13a	0018
S013A	1	20	I shrugged.	s13a	0019
S013A	1	21	Anastasia: "...Honestly?"	s13a	0020
S013A	1	22	Her doubt was clear as she met my eyes with hers.	s13a	0021
S013A	1	23	Man: "Ah, you're here! Boss!!"	s13a	0022
S013A	1	24	Suddenly someone else called to me.	s13a	0023
S013A	1	25	It was one of my subordinates. He was almost out of breath as he drew near.	s13a	0024
S013A	1	26	Gagoze: "What's the matter?"	s13a	0025
S013A	1	27	Man: "It's...It's serious-... ah..."	s13a	0026
S013A	1	28	Catching sight of Anastasia behind me, the man stopped in the middle of his sentence.	s13a	0027
S013A	1	29	Anastasia: "...?"	s13a	0028
S013A	1	30	Man: "I need to tell you something..."	s13a	0029
S013A	1	31	It seems it was something he didn't want Anastasia to hear.	s13a	0030
S013A	1	32	He leaned in and whispered.	s13a	0031
S013A	1	33	………	s13a	0032
S013A	1	34	Gagoze: "What!?"	s13a	0033
S013A	1	35	I couldn't believe it.	s13a	0034
S013A	1	36	Gagoze: "........."	s13a	0035
S013A	1	37	I turned back to Anastasia.	s13a	0036
S013A	1	38	Anastasia: "What's wrong?"	s13a	0037
S013A	1	39	Gagoze: "It seems I have to take care of something. I'll have to have this little chat with you later."	s13a	0038
S013A	1	40	I replied to the confused Anastasia, and then looked back at the man.	s13a	0039
S013A	2	1	Gagoze: "Take this one back to her room. Lock the door."	s13a	0040
S013A	2	2	Man: "Yes sir!!"	s13a	0041
S013A	2	3	As the man saluted in confirmation, I started running towards my destination.	s13a	0042
S013A	2	4	Gagoze: "Damn it..."	s13a	0043
S013A	2	5	………	s13a	0044
S013A	2	6	……	s13a	0045
S013A	2	7	…	s13a	0046
S013A	2	8	Anastasia: "........."	s13a	0047
S013A	2	9	Anastasia stood there in silence.	s13a	0048
S013A	2	10	Man: "O-Oi! This way! You're going back to your room!!"	s13a	0049
S013A	2	11	Anastasia: "...Fine."	s13a	0050
S013A	2	12	Man: "Hn..."	s13a	0051
S013A	2	13	The man held his breath as Anastasia's sharp gaze turned on him.	s13a	0052
S013A	2	14	Anastasia: "But I'm not going back to my room by way of your orders. I'm going of my own will."	s13a	0053
S013A	2	15	With that, Anastasia started out to return to her room.	s13a	0054
S013A	2	16	Her face at that moment was that of the 'Silver Valkyrie.'	s13a	0055
S013A	2	17	………	s13a	0056
S013A	2	18	……	s13a	0057
S013A	2	19	…	s13a	0058
S013A	2	20	Gagoze: "What happened here!?"	s13a	0059
S013A	2	21	I arrived at my destination.	s13a	0060
S013A	2	22	I yelled as I looked around the empty cell.	s13a	0061
S013A	2	23	It was Daness' cell.	s13a	0062
S013A	2	24	But Daness was not in it.	s13a	0063
S013A	2	25	Gagoze: "I told you to watch her!!"	s13a	0064
S013A	2	26	Man: "B-...But..."	s13a	0065
S013A	2	27	Man２: "Apologies, boss!!"	s13a	0066
S013A	2	28	As the man in front of me stood looking ashamed, the younger man behind him lowered his head in apology.	s13a	0067
S013A	2	29	Man２: "As he was using the restroom, I took over for him and..."	s13a	0068
S013A	2	30	Looking at his face, I was already starting to guess what happened.	s13a	0069
S013A	2	31	Man２: "...I couldn't resist the temptation. And she acted like she wanted it too, so..."	s13a	0070
S013A	2	32	Gagoze: "...And so then you opened the cell."	s13a	0071
S013A	2	33	Man２: "Ah...Y-Yes."	s13a	0072
S013A	2	34	As the young mercenary felt the silent rage in my words and gaze, he shrunk back a few steps.	s13a	0073
S013A	2	35	Daness had used the young mercenary's own lust against him, and escaped.	s13a	0074
S013A	2	36	I was training her how to please men, but she used that to find a way to escape.	s13a	0075
S013A	2	37	Gagoze: "Clever girl..."	s13a	0076
S013A	2	38	Man２: "I-It was all my fault! What should be done?"	s13a	0077
S013A	2	39	Gagoze: "At least she can't get out of the city. We'll tell Jean about it and search for Daness with her men. You idiot."	s13a	0078
S013A	2	40	Man２: "Y-Yes sir!!"	s13a	0079
S013A	3	1	The young mercenary was trembling. With those orders, I headed for Jean's office.	s13a	0080
S013A	3	2	………	s13a	0081
S013A	3	3	……	s13a	0082
S013A	3	4	…	s13a	0083
S013A	3	5	Anastasia: "........."	s13a	0084
S013A	3	6	Anastasia sat in silence as she looked out through the metal lattice that covered the window.	s13a	0085
S013A	3	7	She could see many different men running around as if confused.	s13a	0086
S013A	3	8	It seemed they weren't quite sure where they were going.	s13a	0087
S013A	3	9	In other words, they were searching for something.	s13a	0088
S013A	3	10	She had seen nothing like this since she had been taken prisoner here.	s13a	0089
S013A	3	11	It seemed they were in a state of emergency.	s13a	0090
S013A	3	12	Coming to that conclusion, Anastasia looked to where the man gaurding her room was standing.	s13a	0091
S013A	3	13	Anastasia: "...Is something going on outside?"	s13a	0092
S013A	3	14	As she spoke she started walking towards the man.	s13a	0093
S013A	3	15	Man: "I don't know."	s13a	0094
S013A	3	16	He kept his answer ambiguous.	s13a	0095
S013A	3	17	Anastasia: "Has something happened?"	s13a	0096
S013A	3	18	As she asked, she started to quicken her steps.	s13a	0097
S013A	3	19	Man: "I don't know."	s13a	0098
S013A	3	20	He repeated the same answer.	s13a	0099
S013A	3	21	Anastasia: "I see..."	s13a	0100
S013A	3	22	Anastasia nodded and clenched her hand into a fist.	s13a	0101
S013A	3	23	Man: "Wh-!?"	s13a	0102
S013A	3	24	Anastasia: "I guess I'll have to see for myself then..."	s13a	0103
S013A	3	25	A strike followed.	s13a	0104
S013A	3	26	Anastasia's fist found it's mark, and the man standing gaurd crumpled to the floor.	s13a	0105
S013A	3	27	Anastasia: "Thanks for all your hard work. From here on though, I'll act without your orders."	s13a	0106
S013A	3	28	Quickly snatching the key ring that was attached to the man's belt, Anastasia stood up.	s13a	0107
S013A	3	29	Anastasia: "When I was brought here, my weapons were taken somewhere on this floor..."	s13a	0108
S013A	3	30	The keys would probably prove to be useful.	s13a	0109
S013A	3	31	Anastasia, the 'Silver Valkyrie' hadn't been simply biding time as a prisoner.	s13a	0110
S013A	3	32	Nor had she just been enduring the humiliation thrust upon her.	s13a	0111
S013A	3	33	She didn't know what was going on, but now the entire city was in a panic.	s13a	0112
S013A	3	34	Anastasia: "Now's my chance...!"	s13a	0113
S013A	3	35	An opportunity will always present itself to those who do not give up.	s13a	0114
S013A	3	36	Seeing such an opportunity arise, Anastasia began to move.	s13a	0115
S013A	3	37	………	s13a	0116
S013A	3	38	……	s13a	0117
S013A	3	39	…	s13a	0118
S013A	3	40	Man: "Did you find her!!?"	s13a	0119
S013A	4	1	Man２: "N-Not yet, sir!!"	s13a	0120
S013A	4	2	It would be dark soon.	s13a	0121
S013A	4	3	Man: "Just keep looking. If we don't find her, who knows what the boss will do to us."	s13a	0122
S013A	4	4	Man３: "Ahh...We're as good as guinea pigs for Jean's experiments..."	s13a	0123
S013A	4	5	Man２: "Let's just keep looking!!"	s13a	0124
S013A	4	6	The men were terrified as they ran along the streets.	s13a	0125
S013A	4	7	Man: "Just find her!"	s13a	0126
S013A	4	8	Deciding there was nothing to be found along this road, the men ran onto the next.	s13a	0127
S013A	4	9	The road was now deserted.	s13a	0128
S013A	4	10	Daness: "Looks like the coast is clear..."	s13a	0129
S013A	4	11	A figure came out of the shadows.	s13a	0130
S013A	4	12	It was Daness.	s13a	0131
S013A	4	13	On her belt was a gun and a few other weapons.	s13a	0132
S013A	4	14	Along with a few grenades.	s13a	0133
S013A	4	15	Daness: "...Good thing there was someone who had the same models. At least I'm familiar with these."	s13a	0134
S013A	4	16	She smiled as she counted the grenades and ammunition that she took from a few men she ran into while on the run.	s13a	0135
S013A	4	17	Daness: "Not as much as I would have liked, but guess it'll have to do."	s13a	0136
S013A	4	18	Daness seemed confident in her chances.	s13a	0137
S013A	4	19	Daness: "But who can say for sure..."	s13a	0138
S013A	4	20	Suddenly a sense of doubt crossed her face.	s13a	0139
S013A	4	21	Daness: "It seems the amount of men on the search has gone down... No, perhaps they're just spread wider and thinner now."	s13a	0140
S013A	4	22	When she had first escaped her cell, the stream of pursuers seemed to have no end.	s13a	0141
S013A	4	23	They had probably been restricting their search to the areas around her cell.	s13a	0142
S013A	4	24	But it seems they had started to spread out more since then.	s13a	0143
S013A	4	25	But if they were spreading out, that would only make it easier for Daness to escape.	s13a	0144
S013A	4	26	Daness: "Even that idiot's subordinates can't really be this stupid, can they...?"	s13a	0145
S013A	4	27	There was one other possible explanation.	s13a	0146
S013A	4	28	Daness: "Are they searching for someone else as well?"	s13a	0147
S013A	4	29	That must have been it.	s13a	0148
S013A	4	30	It was right at the moment that Daness reached that conclusion.	s13a	0149
S013A	4	31	She sensed someone sneaking up on her from behind.	s13a	0150
S013A	4	32	Daness: "Fuck!"	s13a	0151
S013A	4	33	Cursing herself for dropping her gaurd, Daness released a backfist at whoever had gotten the better of her.	s13a	0152
S013A	4	34	Daness: "Hn...!!"	s13a	0153
S013A	4	35	But right as she did, her opponent's fist dug into her.	s13a	0154
S013A	4	36	Daness: "Heh, smarter than I thought."	s13a	0155
S013A	4	37	Summing up her opponent's strength, the dark elf jumped back.	s13a	0156
S013A	4	38	Then...	s13a	0157
S013A	4	39	Daness: "...Ah."	s13a	0158
S013A	4	40	Then Daness, seeing her opponent through the shadows, let out a gasp of surprise.	s13a	0159
S013A	5	1	It was easy to understand why.	s13a	0160
S013A	5	2	Her opponent had a look of surprise to match Daness'.	s13a	0161
S013A	5	3	Daness: "An...Imperial knight?"	s13a	0162
S013A	5	4	Anastasia: "You're wearing an Alliance uniform..."	s13a	0163
S013A	5	5	It was Anastasia.	s13a	0164
S013A	5	6	After breaking out of her room, Anastasia had fled into the city, avoiding her would-be captors.	s13a	0165
S013A	5	7	She had come to the same conclusion as Daness.	s13a	0166
S013A	5	8	The people of this city were looking for someone else in addition to her. That person was probably in the same situation as she was.	s13a	0167
S013A	5	9	She had planned to find whoever it was they were looking for, and join forces with them to escape these pursuers.	s13a	0168
S013A	5	10	And then...	s13a	0169
S013A	5	11	Anastasia: "Would you happen to be...'The Flame Rapier,' commander Daness?"	s13a	0170
S013A	5	12	She wasn't particularly interested in her rank.	s13a	0171
S013A	5	13	Daness: "'The Silver Valkyrie,' Anastasia, commander of the Fuluakia knights..."	s13a	0172
S013A	5	14	She already knew.	s13a	0173
S013A	5	15	There was no way she couldn't have.	s13a	0174
S013A	5	16	They were the head of the Faizland family and the Azrael family, who's ancestors had parted ways over 100 years ago.	s13a	0175
S013A	5	17	And the ones who fought each other on the battlefield, almost as if it were a game of chess where they themselves were the pieces.	s13a	0176
S013A	5	18	At this very moment, 100 years later, they had happened to find each other.	s13a	0177
S013A	5	19	Daness: "Hn, Ha ha ha!"	s13a	0178
S013A	5	20	Anastasia: "Ha ha!"	s13a	0179
S013A	5	21	The two elven commanders began to laugh at the peculiarty of the entire situation.	s13a	0180
S013A	5	22	Anastasia: "It is a pleasure to meet you... Or perhaps 'nice to see you again' would be more appropriate, commander Daness."	s13a	0181
S013A	5	23	Daness: "Heh, I like that better. By our ancestor's vows, we are old friends, after all."	s13a	0182
S013A	5	24	They shook hands.	s13a	0183
S013A	5	25	And even though that handshake would end, the unity that it represented would last much, much longer.	s13a	0184
S013A	5	26	SALTAR: S014A
