S018D	1	1	Jean: "No, I told you, it's disgusting."	s18d	0000
S018D	1	2	She voiced her displeasure at just the thought.	s18d	0001
S018D	1	3	Jean: "I hate coffee. Even drinking an Ork's semen would preferable to drinking that horrid stuff."	s18d	0002
S018D	1	4	Gagoze: "...How could you say that?"	s18d	0003
S018D	1	5	I couldn't believe what I was hearing.	s18d	0004
S018D	1	6	Perhaps something had happened in her past that made her hate coffee. I wasn't sure.	s18d	0005
S018D	1	7	But oh well.	s18d	0006
S018D	1	8	Gagoze: "Well, if I ever get my hands on even better tasting coffee, I'm bringing it over here."	s18d	0007
S018D	1	9	As soon as I said that, I could almost feel a dark energy fill the entire room.	s18d	0008
S018D	1	10	Jean: "Gagoze... are you trying to anger me?"	s18d	0009
S018D	1	11	I didn't expect that.	s18d	0010
S018D	1	12	In that moment, I felt like I had gotten a glimpse at the real Jean.	s18d	0011
S018D	1	13	SALTAR: S019A
S018D	1	14	SALTAR: S019A
