S002D	1	1	Towako: 「Wha-?!」	s02d	0001
S002D	1	2	Towako immediately freezes up. Her expression stiffens and beads of sweat appear on her forehead.	s02d	0004
S002D	1	3	Towako: 「Re-Reika will probably not care about this!」	s02d	0005
S002D	1	4	Kondo: 「"Call me if you get bullied for no reason", she said. Just you wait and see!」	s02d	0006
S002D	1	5	Kondo takes out a mobile phone and a memo from his inner pocket and shows them to Towako.	s02d	0007
S002D	1	6	Towako: 「Wh-! Where did you get this number?!」	s02d	0008
S002D	1	7	The girl's voice trembles in surprise: the handwriting definitely belongs to Reika.	s02d	0010
S002D	1	8	Kondo: 「Heh, who cares? All it matters is that I have this number!」	s02d	0011
S002D	1	9	Towako: 「Are you serious?!」	s02d	0012
S002D	1	10	Kondo: 「Oh, Tow-wy? Do you think Rei-chi will be mad when she hears how you treated me and my guys just because you were in a bad mood?」	s02d	0013
S002D	1	11	Towako: 「Grrrrr.」	s02d	0014
S002D	1	12	The girl groans, unable to even object.	s02d	0016
S002D	1	13	Kondo: 「Let's just call her and find out. I'll say little Tow-wy was bullying us.」	s02d	0017
S002D	1	14	Towako: 「Don't you mafia have any pride?!」	s02d	0018
S002D	1	15	Towako's shoulders drop when she sees Kondo dialing a number.	s02d	0019
S002D	1	16	Towako: 「Aww, fine! FINE! What do you want? Name your price!」	s02d	0020
S002D	1	17	Kondo: 「A da-date!」	s02d	0021
S002D	1	18	Towako: 「Say what?!」	s02d	0022
S002D	1	19	The girl shouts in surprise.	s02d	0023
S002D	1	20	Kondo: 「A date! Please date me for finding out Yuyami's whereabouts!」	s02d	0024
S002D	1	21	Towako: 「Say what? Date!?」	s02d	0025
S002D	1	22	Towako: 「A date like THAT kind of date? Where a man and a woman flirt and go to the movies, eat rice and that kind of junk?」	s02d	0026
S002D	1	23	Towako is still puzzled. This was the first time she was asked out on a date since junior high school.	s02d	0028
S002D	1	24	Kondo: 「That's the one. With me.」	s02d	0029
S002D	1	25	Kondo nods enthusiastically.	s02d	0030
S002D	1	26	Towako: 「Fine by me...But just holding hands with Issy? Are you sure that's all you want?」	s02d	0031
S002D	1	27	Kondo: 「Yep, no other payment is neccessary.」	s02d	0032
S002D	1	28	Towako: 「Huh, what's up with that...」	s02d	0033
S002D	1	29	Such a wish is unbefitting a mafia boss. More like something a teenager would ask for.	s02d	0034
S002D	1	30	Towako: 「Tch, fine. A date it is, then!」	s02d	0035
S002D	1	31	She replies with a tinge of embarrassment.	s02d	0036
S002D	1	32	Kondo: 「Hahaha. I promise I'll protect little Towako♪」	s02d	0037
S002D	1	33	Looking at Kondo's cheerful face, the girl cannot help but sigh.	s02d	0038
S002D	1	34	Towako: 「Yes, yes. Now start working on my request.」	s02d	0039
S002D	1	35	Just as Towako is about to leave, Kondo stops her.	s02d	0040
S002D	1	36	Kondo: 「Yo, hold on, Tow-wy. I still need to tell you something.」	s02d	0041
S002D	1	37	Towako: 「What now?」	s02d	0042
S002D	1	38	Kondo: 「Umm, "Dinner is getting cold, so please hurry up and get back home, milady".」	s02d	0043
S002D	1	39	Kondo reads out loud the mail he just received and Towako freaks out.	s02d	0044
S002D	1	40	Towako: 「Ho-Ho-How did she know I was here?!」	s02d	0045
S002D	2	1	Kondo: 「"Butler's intuition", it says.」	s02d	0046
S002D	2	2	Towako: 「Did she forsee even THAT?!」	s02d	0047
S002D	2	3	Kondo: 「So typical of Reika. You'd better hurry home if you don't want to be scolded, Towako.」	s02d	0048
S002D	2	4	Towako: 「Z-Zip it! I can go on a rampage without my butler's permission!!」	s02d	0049
S002D	2	5	Despite the retort, it looks like all strength drained from her body. No longer was she the same brave person who tore down the place.	s02d	0050
S002D	2	6	Kondo: 「Hehe, the mafia could use a defence mechanism like Reika. Especially if you are our opponent.」	s02d	0051
S002D	2	7	Towako: 「Tsk! Dang!」	s02d	0052
S002D	2	8	Kondo: 「Pass my thanks to Rei-chi!」	s02d	0053
S002D	2	9	Towako: 「Aw, zip it already, ya fool!」	s02d	0054
S002D	2	10	Towako leaves the mafia hideout with the tail between her legs.	s02d	0055
S002D	2	11	SALTAR: S003A
