S009A	1	1	...	s09a	0000
S009A	1	2	......	s09a	0001
S009A	1	3	Towako: （...?）	s09a	0002
S009A	1	4	How much time had passed?	s09a	0003
S009A	1	5	When she woke up, Towako was still in the dark.	s09a	0004
S009A	1	6	Towako: （This is...?）	s09a	0005
S009A	1	7	She thought groggily.	s09a	0006
S009A	1	8	Towako: (Pitch-black...darkness...）	s09a	0007
S009A	1	9	Indeed, as far as Towako could see, there was only darkness. Not a single ray of light anywhere.	s09a	0010
S009A	1	10	She tries to wave a hand in front of her eyes, but it doesn't move. It's like something is binding her body.	s09a	0012
S009A	1	11	Or maybe that feeling means she no longer has a body? If she is dead, that would certainly explain it...	s09a	0014
S009A	1	12	Towako: (No way. Could this really be the afterlife?）	s09a	0015
S009A	1	13	A lone soul, drifting in the nothingness...	s09a	0016
S009A	1	14	Towako: (If that's the case...That's not funny at all.）	s09a	0017
S009A	1	15	Without a positive outlook, hanging around in this deathly darkness will only instil fear into her.	s09a	0019
S009A	1	16	Towako: （Papa...Mama...）	s09a	0020
S009A	1	17	Towako suddenly thinks about her late parents. Could they be somewhere in here too? If that is true...	s09a	0023
S009A	1	18	Towako: （I want to see you again...）	s09a	0024
S009A	1	19	Fear and sorrow creep into her mind, when-	s09a	0026
S009A	1	20	*Ka-chung!*	s09a	0027
S009A	1	21	-Suddenly, the darkness opens up, allowing the light to pour in.	s09a	0028
S009A	1	22	Towako: （Ugh...）	s09a	0030
S009A	1	23	It sounds like someone entered.	s09a	0031
S009A	1	24	Towako: (Footsteps...?）	s09a	0032
S009A	1	25	The lights got switched on after the door closed.	s09a	0033
S009A	1	26	Towako: (*Gasp*!）	s09a	0034
S009A	1	27	The girl instinctively shuts her eyes from the sudden brightness.	s09a	0036
S009A	1	28	Towako: （So, that means I'm alive after all?）	s09a	0037
S009A	1	29	Towako: （I wasn't in the afterlife or anything?...Man, I'm such an idiot...）	s09a	0038
S009A	1	30	Towako slowly opens her eyes, laughing at herself in her mind.	s09a	0039
S009A	1	31	Towako: 「...」	s09a	0040
S009A	1	32	Once her eyes become accustomed to the light, she can finally see her surroundings.	s09a	0041
S009A	1	33	Bare, cold concrete floor, walls and ceiling. Something smells  unpleasant in the damp air of the room. Illuminated only by a dim  fluorescent lamp, everything in it feels unreal.	s09a	0044
S009A	1	34	She is probably somewhere underground.	s09a	0045
S009A	1	35	Except for a western-styled toilet located further in the room, there is no other furniture.	s09a	0047
S009A	1	36	A typical setup for a prison cell and being bound by a rope on the floor is a natural part of being imprisoned.	s09a	0049
S009A	1	37	Towako: 「Ghh!!!」	s09a	0050
S009A	1	38	Towako applies force to her bonds. If it were a regular rope or even a steel wire, she would've broken it by now. But this restraint does not budge at all.	s09a	0050
S009A	1	39	Towako: （Guess I got captured...）	s09a	0051
S009A	1	40	Towako: 「Nn...Guh...Huff...」	s09a	0052
S009A	2	1	She twists her body to face whomever just entered through the door and a woman's high-heeled shoe comes into view.	s09a	0054
S009A	2	2	Towako: （Damn...It really is true.）	s09a	0055
S009A	2	3	Towako: 「Geh...」	s09a	0056
S009A	2	4	The young diviner glances upwards with an annoyed look.	s09a	0057
S009A	2	5	Yuyami: 「Hehe...」	s09a	0058
S009A	2	6	Sure enough, Yuyami is looking down on Towako with a faint smile on her lips.	s09a	0059
S009A	2	7	Yuyami: 「How are you feeling, I wonder?」	s09a	0060
S009A	2	8	Towako: 「Didn't I kill you already?」	s09a	0061
S009A	2	9	Both ladies glare at each other.	s09a	0062
S009A	2	10	Yuyami: 「I know you really want me dead, but I'll have to disappoint you♪.」	s09a	0063
S009A	2	11	Yuyami responds to the girl's murderous intent.	s09a	0064
S009A	2	12	Towako: 「You may come to regret not killing me when you had the chance.」	s09a	0065
S009A	2	13	Yuyami: 「Aha. How cliche. But thank you for your concern♪.」	s09a	0066
S009A	2	14	Towako: 「Grr.」	s09a	0067
S009A	2	15	The fact remains that Towako lost and got herself captured. She is all bark and no bite now. Although she is fully aware of it, she cannot help but rebel.	s09a	0069
S009A	2	16	Yuyami: 「Do you understand where you are?」	s09a	0070
S009A	2	17	Towako: 「Who knows?」	s09a	0071
S009A	2	18	She replies sarcastically.	s09a	0072
S009A	2	19	Yuyami: 「You're in my shop, in a brothel run by my organisation. The 'Tower of pleasure', an entertainment venue where female pigs fulfil the gentlemen's lewd desires.」	s09a	0073
S009A	2	20	Yuyami grins from ear to ear, as if saying "Do you understand what it means?".	s09a	0075
S009A	2	21	Towako: 「What are you implying?」	s09a	0076
S009A	2	22	Yuyami: 「Hey, listen. If you reflect on your actions and swear to live on as my sow, I'll keep you alive.」	s09a	0077
S009A	2	23	Towako: 「Wanna hear what I have to say on this?」	s09a	0078
S009A	2	24	Yuyami: 「But of course. Tell me what you really want, Towako.」	s09a	0079
S009A	2	25	Towako: 「Screw you, you damn crone!」	s09a	0080
S009A	2	26	Towako replies with seething anger. She doesn't care if she will die now.	s09a	0081
S009A	2	27	Although the woman was expecting this answer, she still cannot help but laugh.	s09a	0083
S009A	2	28	Yuyami: 「Ahahaha! Wonderful! You are truly a wonderful lass, Towako♪.」	s09a	0084
S009A	2	29	Yuyami: 「Making perfect whores out of saucy girls like you is my hobby♪.」	s09a	0085
S009A	2	30	Yuyami absent-mindedly runs her hands along her body and the young diviner can suddenly smell her pheromones.	s09a	0087
S009A	2	31	Towako: （Th-That hag! She's aroused?!）	s09a	0088
S009A	2	32	The girl is disgusted.	s09a	0089
S009A	2	33	Towako: 「I'll definitely kill you!!!」	s09a	0090
S009A	2	34	Yuyami: 「Hehehe, I wonder if you can. Hey, listen. You have never slept with a man before, right?」	s09a	0091
S009A	2	35	Towako: 「Wh-What of it?!」	s09a	0092
S009A	2	36	Towako's voice trembles slightly.	s09a	0093
S009A	2	37	Yuyami: 「Since you had never experienced that pleasure, my training should prove most entertaining.」	s09a	0094
S009A	2	38	Yuyami: 「But do not worry. I won't make it easy for you to lose your mind.」	s09a	0095
S009A	2	39	Yuyami: 「For opposing me, I'll tenderly and carefully train you into the. Best. Whore. Out there♪.」	s09a	0096
S009A	2	40	Towako: 「Guh...」	s09a	0097
S009A	3	1	Yuyami smiles faintly.	s09a	0098
S009A	3	2	This is the first time Towako felt scared. No, she doesn't fear her enemy. She fears how her own inexperienced body will react to this.	s09a	0100
S009A	3	3	Towako: 「I-I won't turn into a sow! ESPECIALLY if that's what you hope to achieve!!」	s09a	0101
S009A	3	4	Yuyami: 「Everyone says this. But in the end, you are only human♪.」	s09a	0102
S009A	3	5	Towako: 「SHUT UP!」	s09a	0103
S009A	3	6	Koso: 「I applaud your determination.」	s09a	0104
S009A	3	7	With these words Koso enters through the heavy iron door.	s09a	0105
S009A	3	8	Towako: 「And you, you traitor!!!」	s09a	0106
S009A	3	9	The girl lashes out. But given her position, all she can do is yell and rage.	s09a	0107
S009A	3	10	Koso: 「...」	s09a	0108
S009A	3	11	The diviner doesn't flinch from the insult and simply looks down on her.	s09a	0109
S009A	3	12	Koso: 「This woman, Yuyami, is an upcoming mafia boss in these parts. She has her ways of changing any female into a faithful slave. You'll see.」	s09a	0111
S009A	3	13	Koso: 「The prostitutes working in the shop are of the lowest rank. Her elite whores are very popular with the upper class citizen.」	s09a	0112
S009A	3	14	Koso: 「You can say that the girls earned her favours with the businessmen and the politicians, as well as a few powerful benefactors.」	s09a	0113
S009A	3	15	Towako: 「Oh dear me!」	s09a	0114
S009A	3	16	Koso: 「That is why the executive board of the 'Onmyo Agency' deemed you beyond rescuing.」	s09a	0115
S009A	3	17	Towako: 「Are you done talking yet?」	s09a	0116
S009A	3	18	Koso: 「Your life is over. You're as good as dead.」	s09a	0117
S009A	3	19	Koso indifferently replies to Towako's sarcasm.	s09a	0118
S009A	3	20	Koso: 「As a final act of mercy, Yuyami promised not to revive you, should you choose to take your own life now.」	s09a	0119
S009A	3	21	Towako: （This old fart calls it mercy? Hah, I'm not buying it!）	s09a	0120
S009A	3	22	Towako: （They could've killed me already when they had a chance, yet they bring me here instead. Now, why would you do that?）	s09a	0121
S009A	3	23	Towako: 「Why did you betray the 'Agency'?!」	s09a	0122
S009A	3	24	The girl shouts loudly.	s09a	0123
S009A	3	25	Koso: 「I betrayed nobody. I use Yuyami and, in turn, she uses me. That's the business relationship between us.」	s09a	0124
S009A	3	26	He answers without batting an eye.	s09a	0125
S009A	3	27	Towako: 「What business does the 'Agency' have with a pile of crap that turns women into slaves?」	s09a	0126
S009A	3	28	Koso: 「The 'Agency's' ethics are outdated. I wish to reform them.」	s09a	0127
S009A	3	29	Towako: 「That cliche garbage again! You just have 'illusions of grandeur' written all over you!」	s09a	0128
S009A	3	30	Koso: 「Say what you will. In order to reform the 'Onmyo Agency' befitting this new world, I have to get rid of you. That is why I joined forces with Yuyami.」	s09a	0129
S009A	3	31	Towako: 「I'm in your way...?」	s09a	0130
S009A	3	32	Towako involuntarily asks, surprised by these words.	s09a	0132
S009A	3	33	Koso: 「My foster father, to be exact. Your grandfather.」	s09a	0133
S009A	3	34	An emotion crossed Koso's face for the first time. Was it jealousy...or self-loathing?	s09a	0135
S009A	3	35	Towako: 「Gramps and me cut ties. We are hardly related.」	s09a	0136
S009A	3	36	Koso: 「That may be so, but as long as he refuses to admit this fact, you two are still relatives.」	s09a	0137
S009A	3	37	Koso: 「Was it only 3 months ago? He suddenly told me to surrender my post as a secretary of Abe family and declare you the next head of the family.」	s09a	0138
S009A	3	38	Towako: 「Huh?! First time I hear about it. But I still refuse.」	s09a	0139
S009A	3	39	Koso: 「Even if you don't intend to succeed him, if the current head said so, his will must be done.」	s09a	0140
S009A	3	40	Koso: 「I endured the disgrace and humiliation of abandoning my family to get adopted into the Abe house. And then the oldtimer denies me in the end!」	s09a	0141
S009A	4	1	Koso tries to get his emotions in check, but he doesn't quite succeed. Although this is the first time Towako heard about his grudge, she still fails to care.	s09a	0144
S009A	4	2	Towako: 「Basically, you don't have the guts to face the old man himself, so you targeted me instead? You make me laugh!」	s09a	0145
S009A	4	3	Koso: 「I'll get to him eventually. I've made up my mind.」	s09a	0146
S009A	4	4	Koso: 「In order to reform the 'Agency' and free it of the Abe family's rule, both the old head and everyone with his blood in their veins must die.」	s09a	0147
S009A	4	5	Koso: 「Then only I shall remain at the top! We, the Ashiyake family, will lead the diviners into the new future!」	s09a	0148
S009A	4	6	Towako: 「You will do what? Bullshit! You are boring, stubborn and stupid.」	s09a	0149
S009A	4	7	Towako snorts coldy and Yuyami giggles behind Koso's back.	s09a	0152
S009A	4	8	Koso: 「This is the last bit of mercy I can offer. I would rather not see you become a slave and a men's urinal. Pick a honourable death instead.」	s09a	0154
S009A	4	9	The diviner says with an air of superiority.	s09a	0156
S009A	4	10	Towako: 「I refuse.」	s09a	0157
S009A	4	11	Koso: 「Don't be stubborn.」	s09a	0158
S009A	4	12	Towako: 「At least I've got balls...Something you appear to be lacking.」	s09a	0159
S009A	4	13	Koso: 「As stubborn as your grandfather. You foolishly wasted your last chance!」	s09a	0160
S009A	4	14	Koso said dramatically and turned on his heel to leave.	s09a	0161
S009A	4	15	Towako: 「Again, grandpa has nothing to do with it. I am me, Towako Yagyu.」	s09a	0162
S009A	4	16	The girl tells to his back.	s09a	0163
S009A	4	17	Koso: 「Don't let her escape.」	s09a	0164
S009A	4	18	The man orders Yuyami before he leaves.	s09a	0165
S009A	4	19	Towako: （Geez...）	s09a	0166
S009A	4	20	Yuyami: 「Not even prepared to dirty his own hands. What a tight-assed guy.」	s09a	0168
S009A	4	21	Towako: （Totally.）	s09a	0169
S009A	4	22	Although she completely agrees, Towako decides not to voice her thoughts.	s09a	0170
S009A	4	23	Yuyami: 「Ufufu. The idea was to have you commit suicide. But I am glad it didn't go as planned. You have my thanks.」	s09a	0171
S009A	4	24	Towako: 「And you stay out of this too...」	s09a	0172
S009A	4	25	Yuyami: 「Heeey, do you understand what you did? You just signed your contract of slavery♪.」	s09a	0173
S009A	4	26	Towako: 「Don't forget the next part.」	s09a	0174
S009A	4	27	The young diviner glares Yuyami in the eyes.	s09a	0175
S009A	4	28	Yuyami: 「Which is?」	s09a	0176
S009A	4	29	Towako: 「Your heart, hag.」	s09a	0177
S009A	4	30	Yuyami: 「?!?!」	s09a	0178
S009A	4	31	Towako: 「You will be living in fear as long as I am alive. Afraid to be stabbed through the heart with a knife.」	s09a	0179
S009A	4	32	Towako: 「You will not be able to sleep at night. "What if she escapes?". You will keep thinking about it. The fear will always haunt you.」	s09a	0180
S009A	4	33	Towako: 「As long as I am alive, as long as I draw breath, you will always live in fear for your life.」	s09a	0181
S009A	4	34	Towako: （Even if you hope to train me.）	s09a	0182
S009A	4	35	Towako: （It is best to take advantage of my anger.）	s09a	0183
S009A	4	36	Towako could feel the passion rising in her, something that Koso failed to make her feel. This catfight with Yuyami could still get messy.	s09a	0187
S009A	4	37	Towako: （This is my enemy...）	s09a	0188
S009A	4	38	Yuyami: 「Oh, I love this intense passion of yours♪.」	s09a	0189
S009A	4	39	Yuyami: 「That fighting spirit, willpower and intelligence burning in your eyes...Oh how I long to see that change into a look of lust and submission!」	s09a	0190
S009A	4	40	Yuyami: 「Begging me for mercy over and over again, yet still indulging in miserable, indecent pleasure.」	s09a	0191
S009A	5	1	Towako: 「I'll definitely kill you!」	s09a	0192
S009A	5	2	Yuyami: 「Ahahaha! I'm looking forward to it!」	s09a	0193
S009A	5	3	Yuyami leaves, still laughing out loud, and the cell descends into darkness once again.	s09a	0195
S009A	5	4	Towako: （I shall not give up hope.）	s09a	0196
S009A	5	5	Towako: （Even if I'll be violated, I shall endure.）	s09a	0197
S009A	5	6	Towako: （If I do, a chance to strike at the enemy will present itself.）	s09a	0198
S009A	5	7	Towako: （I'll bet on it when the time comes.）	s09a	0199
S009A	5	8	Towako: （And I count on my loyal butler to get me there!）	s09a	0201
S009A	5	9	Towako: （I shall survive...）	s09a	0202
S009A	5	10	Towako: （I'll keep on living!）	s09a	0203
S009A	5	11	Towako convinces herself more and more.	s09a	0204
S009A	5	12	Were it just the dreams of a weak woman or an indomitable warrior? Only time would tell...	s09a	0206
S009A	5	13	SALTAR: S010A
