S017D	1	1	Kondo: 「Don't mind me. The great diviner and a scary lady-diviner took over my turf. Me and my guys are just humans, what can we possibly do?」	s17c	0007
S017D	1	2	Kondo starts making excuses to appease the girl.	s17c	0008
S017D	1	3	Towako: 「...」	s17c	0009
S017D	1	4	Kondo: 「W-Well, with you being advertised as her slave and all that, I might hire you.」	s17c	0010
S017D	1	5	Towako: 「Is this why you became that perverted hag's lackey? The old man must be turning in his grave right now.」	s17c	0011
S017D	1	6	Towako spits out. He's a mobster, he cannot be good. Plus he has the hots for her.	s17c	0012
S017D	1	7	But to be willing to pay for the woman he invited on a date? Now that's just low!	s17c	0014
S017D	1	8	Towako: (He wants to take me. By force if needed, that twisted bastard!)	s17c	0015
S017D	1	9	Kondo: 「Hey, don't bully me! You are just like Reika-」	s17c	0016
S017D	1	10	Towako: 「Reika?! How is she?!」	s17c	0017
S017D	1	11	Kondo: 「You, you don't know? She'd been dominated by some kind of demon. Probably the one that got you too. My guys can't fight them. Well? Try to understand my situation.」	s17c	0018
S017D	1	12	Towako: 「Shut up! Is it really an incubus?! Are you certain?!」	s17c	0019
S017D	1	13	Kondo: 「Y-Yeah...I think he's called Shutendoji of the incubus tribe.」	s17c	0020
S017D	1	14	Towako: 「Grrr...」	s17c	0021
S017D	1	15	Towako bites her lip.	s17c	0022
S017D	1	16	Towako: 「Reika is the same as me...」	s17c	0023
S017D	1	17	Did she also receive a brand and undergo a training?	s17c	0025
S017D	1	18	Towako: 「Damn it!」	s17c	0026
S017D	1	19	Kondo: 「W-Well, probably...We wouldn't merge with the likes of Yuyami's organisation without sufficient leverage and threats.」	s17c	0027
S017D	1	20	Kondo: 「I even needed a special permission to come visit you. But man, you are going to be quite something...」	s17c	0028
S017D	1	21	Towako: 「-Eh?」	s17c	0029
S017D	1	22	The diviner glares at Kondo, who winces and looks away.	s17c	0031
S017D	1	23	Kondo: 「O-Oooh. About that. See, when you become a full-fledged sex slave, I'll be your number one client.」	s17c	0032
S017D	1	24	Kondo: 「What I'm trying to say is hang in there and wish me luck as well.」	s17c	0033
S017D	1	25	Having said that, Kondo turns his back to Towako.	s17c	0034
S017D	1	26	Towako: (What does he mean "Good luck"? That clown.)	s17c	0035
S017D	1	27	But then a switch flips in her mind.	s17c	0036
S017D	1	28	Towako: (That guy still owes me a favour. Now is as good a time as any to collect.)	s17c	0037
S017D	1	29	The diviner calls out in a deliberately feeble voice.	s17c	0038
S017D	1	30	Towako: 「Hey, Issy. Thanks for cheering me on...But I'd like to ask for a parting gift instead.」	s17c	0039
S017D	1	31	Kondo: 「Eh?! Hey, hey, stop it! The lady-boss will find out! No matter the relationship between us, I cannot rescue you.」	s17c	0040
S017D	1	32	Kondo quickly rattles an excuse before even hearing her out. He seems to be quite frightened of Yuyami.	s17c	0042
S017D	1	33	Towako: 「You won't get into trouble. You only need to deliver a message to a certain man.」	s17c	0043
S017D	1	34	Kondo: 「An-And I'm telling you I cannot! I am not allowed to help you.」	s17c	0044
S017D	1	35	The mafioso breaks into cold sweat and attempts to flee.	s17c	0045
S017D	1	36	Towako: (I'm in trouble if he leaves!)	s17c	0046
S017D	1	37	There is only one thing that might work on the scared mobster. Towako makes up her mind and steels herself.	s17c	0048
S017D	1	38	Towako: 「Ho-Hold on!」	s17c	0049
S017D	1	39	The woman staggers to her feet.	s17c	0050
S017D	1	40	Towako: 「I don't know when you will be able to come again. So take a good look for your trouble.」	s17c	0051
S017D	2	1	She uncovers her outfit, fully revealing her breasts and crotch.	s17c	0053
S017D	2	2	Kondo: 「Toh-Towako...」	s17c	0054
S017D	2	3	Kondo swallows loudly at the sight of her miserable, yet seductive appearance.	s17c	0055
S017D	2	4	Towako: (That's right. Come closer.)	s17c	0056
S017D	2	5	Towako: 「This is all I can do for now. I don't have the strength to oppose Yuyami. I am but a mere sow. Surely a single message won't matter?」	s17c	0057
S017D	2	6	Kondo: 「Bu-But you see...This too...」	s17c	0058
S017D	2	7	Kondo is still undecided, alternatively looking at her chest and groin.	s17c	0059
S017D	2	8	Towako: (Tch, what a spineless wimp. Make up your mind already, will you?)	s17c	0060
S017D	2	9	The slave's mark on her chest leaves Towako no choice but to act like a sex slave would.	s17c	0061
S017D	2	10	Towako: 「If it is alright with you, Issy, I would like to show you my whorish greeting.」	s17c	0062
S017D	2	11	Kondo: 「Eh?」	s17c	0063
S017D	2	12	Kondo looks up and their eyes meet. The young diviner grins in her mind.	s17c	0066
S017D	2	13	Towako: 「Hehe. I haven't done it for anyone yet. Issy would be my first. Wanna see? A sow's greeting?」	s17c	0067
S017D	2	14	She nailed him to the ground! While it is hard to believe she said it all on her own, Kondo is shaking from head to toe like an idiot.	s17c	0070
S017D	2	15	Towako: 「Then, take a goood~ look.」	s17c	0071
S017D	2	16	Towako: 「Ngh.」	s17c	0073
S017D	2	17	Towako greatly spreads her legs and squats, showing off her secret spot. She puts her arms behind her head and puffs out her chest, displaying the erect nipples.	s17c	0074
S017D	2	18	A submissive pose in the clothes that leave nothing to imagination. That is a "sow's greeting".	s17c	0075
S017D	2	19	Kondo twitches and his eyes grow as large as saucers.	s17c	0077
S017D	2	20	Towako: (Hehe...)	s17c	0079
S017D	2	21	Towako: 「I'm a l-lowly rookie female pig Towako...」	s17c	0080
S017D	2	22	Towako: 「To repay the kindness Yuyami showed to this cheeky girl, I shall strive to become a top-class female pig, even if it kills me.」	s17c	0081
S017D	2	23	Towako: 「So, sex slave Towako is l-looking forward to working with you in the future...」	s17c	0082
S017D	2	24	Although she stuttered a bit in the end, Towako made an otherwise perfect introduction.	s17c	0083
S017D	2	25	Kondo: 「Awwwww, guh.」	s17c	0084
S017D	2	26	The woman's words and her new appearance give Kondo an erection.	s17c	0085
S017D	2	27	Towako: 「Well? Did you like it?」	s17c	0087
S017D	2	28	Towako returns to her usual posture.	s17c	0088
S017D	2	29	Kondo: 「Ah, yeah. That was awesome!」	s17c	0089
S017D	2	30	The mobster hunches, trying to suppress his excitement.	s17c	0090
S017D	2	31	Towako: 「With that in mind...If you think of it as just an ordinary farewell message...It's okay, right?」	s17c	0091
S017D	2	32	Kondo: 「Y-Yeah. Got it.」	s17c	0092
S017D	2	33	Towako: 「Thank you kindly. Then please tell a guy called Rodrigo at the 'Onmyo Agency' "Let's meet sometime. My regards".」	s17c	0093
S017D	2	34	The girl draws close to his ear and whispers.	s17c	0094
S017D	2	35	Kondo: 「Le-Let's meet sometime?! With a g-g-guy?!」	s17c	0095
S017D	2	36	Towako chuckles when Kondo nearly bursts into tears.	s17c	0096
S017D	2	37	Towako: 「Rodrigo is my best pal and a gay.」	s17c	0097
S017D	2	38	Kondo: 「Ah, I see!」	s17c	0098
S017D	2	39	The mobster's face immediately lights up. What a simple guy!	s17c	0099
S017D	2	40	Towako: 「I'll be busy for a while...Tr-Training, you see. Just tell Rodrigo "Let's meet sometime. My regards", that's all.」	s17c	0100
S017D	3	1	She checks if Kondo understood his task.	s17c	0101
S017D	3	2	Kondo: 「But, but! I absolutely cannot tell that person your whereabouts.」	s17c	0102
S017D	3	3	Towako: 「I understand. I don't intend to involve Rodrigo. So there.」	s17c	0103
S017D	3	4	She eases his anxiety.	s17c	0104
S017D	3	5	Towako: 「Please, Issy.」	s17c	0105
S017D	3	6	Along with a whisper, she pats his manhood through the pants.	s17c	0107
S017D	3	7	Towako: 「And then, when I become a full-fledged sex slave...get it?」	s17c	0108
S017D	3	8	Kondo: 「Uuu.」	s17c	0109
S017D	3	9	Kondo groans.	s17c	0110
S017D	3	10	Kondo: 「G-Got it! Pass the message "Let's meet sometime. My regards". I'll be sure to tell, for your sake! Leave it to me!」	s17c	0111
S017D	3	11	Kondo: 「Whoops! Someone is coming. See ya!」	s17c	0112
S017D	3	12	With the look of an obedient puppy, her dashes out, still hiding his erection.	s17c	0113
S017D	3	13	Towako: 「*Spit*...」	s17c	0114
S017D	3	14	She spits in disgust.	s17c	0115
S017D	3	15	SALTAR: S017F
