S005B	1	1	Ichiro: （Lily, I guess...?）	s05a	0957
S005B	1	2	... certainly, Yuko-sensei is very attractive. Also, without a doubt I have always admired her from the bottom of my heart.	s05a	0958
S005B	1	3	;※※Original used "without a doubt" here AND in previous line, I changed to "without regrets" on this one. Just a little while ago, perhaps only just a few hours ago, I would have declared my love to Yuko-sensei with no regrets.	s05a	0959
S005B	1	4	However, currently I can't ignore the emotions I feel towards Lily.	s05a	0960
S005B	1	5	Although Lily personally created the whole mess, she practically sacrificed her frail body to... take care of me. I have to say I really appreciate that.	s05a	0961
S005B	1	6	Ichiro: （Moreover...）	s05a	0962
S005B	1	7	This is a really selfish aspect and is quite obvious at this point, but Lily is really famous in the school for being extremely cute... and that means bragging rights.	s05a	0963
S005B	1	8	Her pride might be just a tiny little bit high and her tongue tends to be sharp and nasty but...	s05a	0964
S005B	1	9	Ichiro: （I guess with her, I just get a good feeling...）	s05a	0965
S005B	1	10	SALTAR: S005D
