S014C	1	1	In a fit of rage, I dash towards Faust.	s14c	0000
S014C	1	2	Ichiro: 「Daaaaaaaaamn youuuu!!!」	s14c	0001
S014C	1	3	With my body brimming with power, my mind can barely even keep up with the speed of my dash.	s14c	0002
S014C	1	4	I close the distance between us in a flash and raise my hand with the intent to drive my fist into Faust at full power.	s14c	0003
S014C	1	5	But, people do not suddenly just turn into heroes.	s14c	0004
S014C	1	6	Even with a blazing fast, powerful punch coming at his way, Faust just laughs. He doesn't seem disturbed in the least.	s14c	0005
S014C	1	7	Faust: 「Young man, you wasted the chance your lover especially made for you.」	s14c	0006
S014C	1	8	;※※※嫌味な iyamina?: "disagreeable/gaudiness/sarcasm", used haughty. Added some to the end of the sentence. Faust says it like a haughty teacher who discovered a mistake in the exam of his most hated student.	s14c	0007
S014C	1	9	Ichiro: 「Shut up! I will defeat you!!」	s14c	0008
S014C	1	10	Faust: 「Kukuku, you understand nothing.」	s14c	0009
S014C	1	11	The very moment my fist was right in front of Faust's face――	s14c	0010
S014C	1	12	Ichiro: 「Guaaaaaaah!!!!!」	s14c	0011
S014C	1	13	Like I was tied with invisible chains, my body becomes unable to move.	s14c	0012
S014C	1	14	Ichiro: （Move! Mooooooove!!）	s14c	0013
S014C	1	15	;※※Let me honest here, I was bored so I heavily freeformed this. My fist is right at his nose. Just a little bit more and I can wipe that smirk off his face!	s14c	0014
S014C	1	16	But my body ignores my will and doesn't even twitch.	s14c	0015
S014C	1	17	Ichiro: 「Guh! Uoooooooh!!」	s14c	0016
S014C	1	18	I put all of my strength into breaking these invisible chains.	s14c	0017
S014C	1	19	Faust: 「You should learn when to give up. It is pointless.」	s14c	0018
S014C	1	20	Laughing with a fist right in front of his face, Faust's gaze turns to the collapsed Lily and Yuko-sensei.	s14c	0019
S014C	1	21	Faust: 「Kuku, this is a fine opportunity. Why won't I put up a funny show for you?」	s14c	0020
S014C	1	22	Ichiro: 「Guh... ghh... w-what... are... you... ... going... to... do...」	s14c	0021
S014C	1	23	Faust: ;※※Young man added. 「It would be good for you to lament your inability to live up to your lover's expectations. And grieve your powerlessness, young man.」	s14c	0022
S014C	1	24	As soon as he finishes saying so, Faust slowly starts to approach Lily.	s14c	0023
S014C	1	25	Ichiro: 「H-Hold iiiiit!」	s14c	0024
S014C	1	26	Laughing with a broad grin on his face, Faust stands next to the limp Lily. The Lily who tried to save me by sacrificing her own body.	s14c	0025
S014C	1	27	Faust: 「What's wrong? Hmm? You won't help your lover?」	s14c	0026
S014C	1	28	;※※踏みつけた fumitsuketa?: "to trample down/to tread on/to ignore/to spurn" Once he is done laughing at me, Faust suddenly stomps on Lily.	s14c	0027
S014C	1	29	;※※整った totonotta? means "well-featured" etc, translated as "pretty" here. Also 踏みにじる fuminijiru?: "to trample underfoot/to tread on/to crush with a foot" Faust places his foot on Lily's pretty face and grinds his heel on it.	s14c	0028
S014C	1	30	Ichiro: 「Oooooooooooooo!!」	s14c	0029
S014C	1	31	My body becomes hot from my anger and I howl but――	s14c	0030
S014C	1	32	Even then, my body doesn't move at all.	s14c	0031
S014C	1	33	Faust: 「Kukuku, just a scream? You won't help? Hmm?」	s14c	0032
S014C	1	34	Whack!!	s14c	0033
S014C	1	35	Using the foot he was using to grind on Lily's face, Faust kicks Lily's stomach.	s14c	0034
S014C	1	36	Lily had already lost her consciousness so she doesn't even groan in pain. She is as limp as a puppet whose strings have been cut.	s14c	0035
S014C	1	37	;※※責任 sekinin?: "duty/responsibility/liability/onus" Even though it's my fault that Lily ended up like that...	s14c	0036
S014C	1	38	I can't do anything for her. I can only look.	s14c	0037
S014C	1	39	My own helplessness is irritating. And my anger for Faust turns into hatred, filling my chest.	s14c	0038
S014C	1	40	Ichiro: 「Stop iiiiit! O-Oooooooooo!!」	s14c	0039
S014C	2	1	Faust: 「Hmph, she's a lost cause anyway. Shall I finish her off!」	s14c	0040
S014C	2	2	Whack!!!! Whack!!	s14c	0041
S014C	2	3	Faust kicks Lily's abdomen again and again.	s14c	0042
S014C	2	4	;※※What sort of hearing ability does this "completed body" have!?! The dull sound of bones breaking and Lily's internal organs being smashed pierce my hearing.	s14c	0043
S014C	2	5	Faust: 「Looks like this is the end. Kukuku, now, this will set you free of this world.」	s14c	0044
S014C	2	6	Faust kicks Lily again and her trampled, dirt and blood stained face turns towards me.	s14c	0045
S014C	2	7	Ichiro: （Lily!! Lilyyyy!!!）	s14c	0046
S014C	2	8	There was no vitality in that face. It already looks like a dead person's face.	s14c	0047
S014C	2	9	Even then, the slightest amount of breathing could still be heard.	s14c	0048
S014C	2	10	Faust: 「Hmph, isn't she tenacious!!」	s14c	0049
S014C	2	11	Whack!!	s14c	0050
S014C	2	12	Intending to finish Lily off, Faust kicks her so hard that her body lifts off the ground, then slams back on the floor and rolls for a while.	s14c	0051
S014C	2	13	Faust: 「Kukuku, it looks like she went on ahead of you. Don't worry, you'll catch up with her soon enough.」	s14c	0052
S014C	2	14	Faust walks up to where Lily's body rolled and pulls the dagger out of her body.	s14c	0053
S014C	2	15	Blood drips down on the ground from the extracted dagger.	s14c	0054
S014C	2	16	Ichiro: 「I won't forgive you!! I'll never... forgive you...!!」	s14c	0055
S014C	2	17	Faust: 「Kukuku, not being forgiven is fine with me. I won't ever meet you again, I'd think.」	s14c	0056
S014C	2	18	He points the bloody dagger at the left side of my chest.	s14c	0057
S014C	2	19	As the tip pierces me, I feel slight pain and blood starts to flow out of me.	s14c	0058
S014C	2	20	My blood and Lily's blood mix in the downward flow.	s14c	0059
S014C	2	21	Faust: 「Goodbye, young man. Make merry with your lover in the afterlife.」	s14c	0060
S014C	2	22	With an unpleasant sneer on his face, Faust buries the dagger without any hesitation.	s14c	0061
S014C	2	23	Stab!!	s14c	0062
S014C	2	24	I feel the cold metal as it sinks into my flesh.	s14c	0063
S014C	2	25	The moment the burning pain spreads in my body――	s14c	0064
S014C	2	26	;※※※As far as I can tell, this is supposed to be a heartbeat sound. Ba-dump!	s14c	0065
S014C	2	27	The moment that the dagger's tip reaches my beating heart, everything blacks out.	s14c	0066
S014C	2	28	A deep, deep darkness swallows me and my despair.	s14c	0067
S014C	2	29	Ichiro: ;※※Considering how famous Lilith is for their bad ends, you're getting off easy, chump. At least you CAN win. （It can't end like this!）	s14c	0068
S014C	2	30	Such an outcry is futile, of course. My consciousness is completely extinguished.	s14c	0069
S014C	2	31	SALTAR: ＢＡＤＥＮＤ２
S014C	2	32	SALTAR: END
