PV01_2001_A	1	1	Beatrice: 「Haaaa, Hah, Haaaa, Hah」	s21a	0009
PV01_2001_A	1	2	Kila: 「Haaaa, Haaaa, Haaaa, Haaaa」	s21a	0010
PV01_2001_A	1	3	The Kushan mother and daughter were in agony.	s21a	0011
PV01_2001_A	1	4	I couldn’t see their faces at all today.	s21a	0012
PV01_2001_A	1	5	Both of them were standing in front of me while bending forward,  with their asses pushed backward, and their torsos had been stuck  inside the maintenance-machine.	s21a	0013
PV01_2001_A	1	6	Obviously, the consciousness of both the women had been snuffed  out with drugs, as usual.	s21a	0014
PV01_2001_A	1	7	Bohgan: 「Are we focusing on their anal-maintenance today?」	s21a	0015
PV01_2001_A	1	8	The mother’s huge ass and her daughter’s petite ass were facing  me, as if the pig-sluts were inviting me to penetrate them from the  back in a standing posture.	s21a	0016
PV01_2001_A	1	9	Beatrice: 「Haaaa, Haaaa, Haaaaaa, Haaaaaa」	s21a	0017
PV01_2001_A	1	10	A circular hole had been cut into the trousers of Beatrice’s attire  and even into her panties underneath it, merely exposing her anus.	s21a	0018
PV01_2001_A	1	11	Her light-brown anus was twitching by itself and looked to be past  its prime.	s21a	0019
PV01_2001_A	1	12	Kila: 「Hah, Haaaaaa, Haaaa, Hah, Haaaaaa」	s21a	0020
PV01_2001_A	1	13	The skirt of Kila’s attire had been rolled up over her waist and  a circular hole had been cut into her panties, exposing her anus as  well.	s21a	0021
PV01_2001_A	1	14	Her anus looked very youthful, as expected, with its dazzling pink  colour and even its wrinkles had a delicate look about them.	s21a	0022
PV01_2001_A	1	15	However, it was twitching entirely like her mother’s, as if it was  fearful even of the atmosphere within the Brainwashing Laboratory.	s21a	0023
PV01_2001_A	1	16	Beatrice: 「Uha, Aaah, Haaa...」	s21a	0024
PV01_2001_A	1	17	Kila: 「Haaaa, Haaaa, Haaaa」	s21a	0025
PV01_2001_A	1	18	Gyururuuu, Gyururururuuu!!	s21a	0026
PV01_2001_A	1	19	Grumbling sounds echoed out from the bellies of both the women, who  had been lined up alongside each other.	s21a	0027
PV01_2001_A	1	20	Beatrice: 「Nguuuh!!」	s21a	0028
PV01_2001_A	1	21	Kila: 「Kuhuuu!!」	s21a	0029
PV01_2001_A	1	22	The mother and her daughter stiffened up and stifled their breaths  simultaneously, the moment those sounds echoed out of both them.	s21a	0030
PV01_2001_A	1	23	The pleasure-meter monitoring the brains patterns of both the women  rose slightly, before coming back down immediately.	s21a	0031
PV01_2001_A	1	24	Currently, the degree of pleasure was at 0%.	s21a	0031
PV01_2001_A	1	25	Beatrice: 「Haaaaaa, Uuuuuuh, Huuuuuu」	s21a	0032
PV01_2001_A	1	26	Kila: 「Fuuuuh, Haaaaaa, Haaaaaa」	s21a	0033
PV01_2001_A	1	27	Bohgan: 「Did the sounds echoing out of their bellies actually make the  pleasure-meter rise?」	s21a	0034
PV01_2001_A	1	28	Hans: 「However, even that is already enough to push it to a level which  would be unbearable for an average woman. It is a sign that their  brainwashing and remodelling process has progressed well.」	s21a	0035
PV01_2001_A	1	29	Hans approached me, while explaining that.	s21a	0036
PV01_2001_A	1	30	Bohgan: 「What is the state of these pigs now?」	s21a	0037
PV01_2001_A	1	31	Hans: 「It is progressing very well. The degree of their brainwashing has  progressed to 75%, and in two more days we will be able to completely  erase their original personalities.」	s21a	0038
PV01_2001_A	1	32	Bohgan: 「Two more days, is it...?」	s21a	0039
PV01_2001_A	1	33	I folded my arms and muttered to myself and just then Magnus spoke  up.	s21a	0040
PV01_2001_A	1	34	Magnus: 「Now that the brainwashing has advanced to such a degree, it should  begin affecting even their original personalities. In other words,  they will be pigs even during the day.」	s21a	0041
PV01_2001_A	1	35	Magnus: 「That is to say, all their moral barriers will have been torn  down and they will have lost all their former prejudices against  sex. And from tomorrow onwards, they will unconsciously abide with  the Captain’s orders, as if it is the natural thing to do.」	s21a	0042
PV01_2001_A	1	36	Bohgan: 「If the effects are manifesting even at 75% completion, then that  means that the desired “Convenient Personality” should be attained  quite soon.」	s21a	0043
PV01_2001_A	1	37	I came to that conclusion, based on my prior experience.	s21a	0044
PV01_2001_A	1	38	Magnus: 「It is as you say, my Lord. Of course, they will still recognize  themselves as per their original personalities for now.」	s21a	0045
PV01_2001_A	1	39	Bohgan: 「That is perfect. Let us conduct a small experiment tomorrow, shall  we? Olov! Report the progress on the remodelling of their bodies.」	s21a	0046
PV01_2001_A	1	40	Olov: 「Y-Yes! By means of further administration of drugs, their  Erogenous Framework remodelling has been solidified even more  and has reached a stage which is, now, irreversible.」	s21a	0047
PV01_2001_A	2	1	Olov: 「Medical treatment is completely impossible and, now, even the  mere weight of each and every bone in their bodies will make them  experience pleasure.」	s21a	0048
PV01_2001_A	2	2	Olov: 「From tomorrow onwards, even if they move they will go into heat,  and if they ever try to fight they will simply end up orgasming.  These women can’t engage in combat anymore. Uhi! Uhihi!」	s21a	0049
PV01_2001_A	2	3	It seemed like Olov had been waiting to explain all this, as he  continued to blabber on and on without a pause.	s21a	0050
PV01_2001_A	2	4	Magnus cut in amidst Olov’s high-spirited talk.	s21a	0051
PV01_2001_A	2	5	Magnus: 「Captain, their urethral remodelling has almost reached the  completion stage as well, and the data of their brain patterns  shows that they derive immense pleasure from the mere act of  urination.」	s21a	0052
PV01_2001_A	2	6	Magnus: 「And on top of all that, if we progress with this remodelling,  leading normal lives will be quite difficult for these women,  won’t it...?」	s21a	0053
PV01_2001_A	2	7	Bohgan: 「Don’t be like that, Magnus. This is completely appropriate for  them. An entire life’s worth or orgasmic hell will suit these pigs  just fine.」	s21a	0054
PV01_2001_A	2	8	Bohgan: 「These pigs are quite dangerous though. We need to completely  disarm them of their abilities.」	s21a	0055
PV01_2001_A	2	9	The smile of a mad-scientist was etched across Magnus’ face as he  pretended to care about them, while in reality he was simply waiting  for my go-ahead.	s21a	0056
PV01_2001_A	2	10	Magnus: 「Roger that.」	s21a	0057
PV01_2001_A	2	11	Bohgan: 「I am looking forward to their reaction tomorrow. No matter how  amusing their physical condition becomes, they are bound to simply  put the blame on their clit-rings... Kukuku」	s21a	0058
PV01_2001_A	2	12	Beatrice: 「Ahaaaa, Ahaaa, Haaaa, Nnnngh」	s21a	0059
PV01_2001_A	2	13	Kila: 「Hah, Hah, Hah, Hah, Hah, Haaaaaa」	s21a	0060
PV01_2001_A	2	14	Their breathing had become increasingly agonized during the time we  had been gossiping amongst ourselves.	s21a	0061
PV01_2001_A	2	15	Appalling grumbling sounds were echoing out of their bellies and  their anuses were twitching uncontrollably.	s21a	0062
PV01_2001_A	2	16	Bohgan: 「Begin!!」	s21a	0063
PV01_2001_A	2	17	Olov: 「Uhihi! I will start it off!」	s21a	0064
PV01_2001_A	2	18	Olov responded on behalf of everyone present and switched on the  machine excitedly.	s21a	0065
PV01_2001_A	2	19	Whiiiirrrr―― Piccch!	s21a	0066
PV01_2001_A	2	20	Beatrice: 「Kuhiii!!」	s21a	0067
PV01_2001_A	2	21	Kila: 「Higuuuh!!」	s21a	0068
PV01_2001_A	2	22	Both their voices echoed out from inside the machine.	s21a	0069
PV01_2001_A	2	23	The injection arms came forth and pierced thick needles into  Beatrice’s right ass-cheek and Kila’s left ass-cheek.	s21a	0070
PV01_2001_A	2	24	The light-brown anus of the mother and the pink anus of her daughter  contracted simultaneously.	s21a	0071
PV01_2001_A	2	25	Beatrice: 「Aha... Uhu... Guh... Uhuhuuu...」	s21a	0072
PV01_2001_A	2	26	Kila: 「Nhuuu... Kuh... Uh... Uh... Uhuuu...」	s21a	0073
PV01_2001_A	2	27	A liquid drug was injected into them from the thick needles.	s21a	0074
PV01_2001_A	2	28	Their soft and round ass-cheeks stiffened up.	s21a	0075
PV01_2001_A	2	29	Beatrice: 「Guuuh... Uh... Uh... Ahiii... Ngh, Nnnnh...」	s21a	0076
PV01_2001_A	2	30	Kila: 「Uguh... Uh... Uh... Nnnnh... Kuh... Nguuuh...」	s21a	0077
PV01_2001_A	2	31	I could almost picture both of their faces, as they bit their lips  while trying to endure the pain.	s21a	0078
PV01_2001_A	2	32	Bohgan: 「What are you injecting into them?」	s21a	0079
PV01_2001_A	2	33	Hans: 「I have been controlling their defecation. Now, we are injecting  them with nano-machines which will allow them to do it again」	s21a	0080
PV01_2001_A	2	34	Bohgan: 「Are you planning to have them defecate here, in order to collect  and store their shit?」	s21a	0081
PV01_2001_A	2	35	Hans: 「No. However, we had stopped their bowel-movements with drugs  for the sake of their anal remodelling and if they get clogged  up with it, there is a risk of it flowing back into their small  intestines.」	s21a	0082
PV01_2001_A	2	36	Hans: 「On top of that, I have also buried shit-dildos inside them for  the sake of training them in the pleasures of defecation.」	s21a	0083
PV01_2001_A	2	37	Hans: 「Either way, it is the perfect time to train these women in  defecation-orgasms, now that they are going to have such huge  bowel-movements.」	s21a	0084
PV01_2001_A	2	38	After the completion of this process, their anal-rectums would be  completely remodelled, all the way to their large intestines, and  make them orgasm even during defecation.	s21a	0085
PV01_2001_A	2	39	It was a pure form of the demonic medical treatment.	s21a	0086
PV01_2001_A	2	40	Bohgan: 「Kukukuku!! So, if we force them to store up their shit, their own  large intestines will end up raping them and lead them towards an  orgasm, is it!?」	s21a	0087
PV01_2001_A	3	1	Bohgan: 「Record this properly. We will compile it all and send it to dear  Mr. Lucius at a later date. His wife and daughter are about to take  a huge shit together after all!!!」	s21a	0088
PV01_2001_A	3	2	Hans: 「You are a truly evil man, Captain.」	s21a	0089
PV01_2001_A	3	3	All the mad scientists sneered together.	s21a	0090
PV01_2001_A	3	4	Beatrice: 「Hngh, Guuuh, Urgggh... Urgggh... Ngh, Nhuuu...」	s21a	0091
PV01_2001_A	3	5	Kila: 「Ahaaa, Uguuuh... Uh, Urrrrrggh, Nnnnnnh」	s21a	0092
PV01_2001_A	3	6	The drug took effect immediately and both the women’s groaning  became even more agonized.	s21a	0093
PV01_2001_A	3	7	Their swollen bellies began to grumble and play a wonderful melody  together.	s21a	0094
PV01_2001_A	3	8	Their anuses were opening and closing energetically, as their farts  leaked out with obscene sounds and a disgusting odour began to waft  through the atmosphere.	s21a	0095
PV01_2001_A	3	9	Beatrice: 「Nhuuu, Uh, Uhuhuuu, Ugh, Nnnnnnnnnnh」	s21a	0096
PV01_2001_A	3	10	Kila: 「Ngh, Kuh, Aha, Urgh, Uhu, Uhuuuuun!」	s21a	0097
PV01_2001_A	3	11	Bohgan: 「Both of you, squeeze it out with all your strength! Lucius is  going to be delighted to see this!!」	s21a	0098
PV01_2001_A	3	12	Puuuh, Puuuh, Puuuh, Pupuuuh――	s21a	0099
PV01_2001_A	3	13	Beatrice: 「Nhnhnhnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnn!!」	s21a	0100
PV01_2001_A	3	14	Kila: 「Kuhuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuh!!」	s21a	0101
PV01_2001_A	3	15	In the end, they were a mother-daughter pair. Both of them ended up  straining themselves together.	s21a	0102
PV01_2001_A	3	16	Buryuuu!!	s21a	0103
PV01_2001_A	3	17	Both their anuses swelled up with amusing popping sounds and, as it  reached the top, their puckered up holes spread open like a mouth.	s21a	0104
PV01_2001_A	3	18	Beatrice: 「Ngh, Ngh, Nnnhuuuuuuuuuuuuuu!!」	s21a	0105
PV01_2001_A	3	19	Kila: 「Guhuhuhuhuuuuuuuuuuuun!!」	s21a	0106
PV01_2001_A	3	20	Their anuses continued to spread open until their wrinkles stretched  to their limits.	s21a	0107
PV01_2001_A	3	21	And then, the heads of the shit-dildos, which were stuffed inside  them in order for their defecation-orgasm training, slithered out  from the dark depths of their anal-rectums and appeared forth.	s21a	0108
PV01_2001_A	3	22	Beatrice: 「Higuuuh!!」	s21a	0109
PV01_2001_A	3	23	Kila: 「Aghaaa!!」	s21a	0110
PV01_2001_A	3	24	The pleasure-meters besides both the women beeped and began to  rise.	s21a	0111
PV01_2001_A	3	25	They rose up to around 10%... before coming to a halt.	s21a	0112
PV01_2001_A	3	26	Beatrice: 「Fuhuuun, Kufuhuhuhuuuum!!!」	s21a	0113
PV01_2001_A	3	27	Kila: 「Unnngh, Unghhh, Uguuuhuhuhuuum!!」	s21a	0114
PV01_2001_A	3	28	Bohgan: 「Kukukuku... It really is most difficult to squeeze out the initial  part when constipated after all.」	s21a	0115
PV01_2001_A	3	29	The glans of the shit-dildos, which were their thickest parts, had  probably gotten stuck behind their anuses.	s21a	0116
PV01_2001_A	3	30	Now that the shit-dildos had gotten stuck in their stretched open  anuses and were simply peeking out without being able to come out  or go back in, both of them started trembling uncontrollably.	s21a	0117
PV01_2001_A	3	31	Beatrice: 「Kufuguuuh!! Uh, Uh, Mhmhmhmhmmmmm!!」	s21a	0118
PV01_2001_A	3	32	Kila: 「Higuhuuu!! Nhuuuuuu!! Fuguhmhmhmmmm!!」	s21a	0119
PV01_2001_A	3	33	I could picture their faces grotesquely distort in agony while  knitting their eyebrows, as they put as much strain on themselves  as they could to push out the shit-dildos one way or another.	s21a	0120
PV01_2001_A	3	34	Even though they were trying really hard to expel the shit-dildos,  their anuses had already spread unnaturally beyond their limits and  even their stretched insides were beginning to push out now, as they  continued to apply pressure.	s21a	0121
PV01_2001_A	3	35	Beatrice: 「Mugummmuhuhuhuuuh!!」	s21a	0122
PV01_2001_A	3	36	Kila: 「Aguhuguhuuuuun!!」	s21a	0123
PV01_2001_A	3	37	Bohgan: 「Oh! Are they coming out? Are they coming out already!?」	s21a	0124
PV01_2001_A	3	38	All the staff members, including me, leaned forward in anticipation,  and the very next moment,	s21a	0125
PV01_2001_A	3	39	Buryuryuuuuuuu!!	s21a	0126
PV01_2001_A	3	40	A wonderful popping sound echoed out and, finally, the glans of the  shit-dildos slithered out of their anuses.	s21a	0127
PV01_2001_A	4	1	Beatrice: 「Nhuuuuuhuhuuu!!」	s21a	0128
PV01_2001_A	4	2	Kila: 「Kufuuuhuhuhuuu!!」	s21a	0129
PV01_2001_A	4	3	The groans of anguish, that Beatrice and Kila had been giving out,  changed to enraptured moans of lewd bitches.	s21a	0130
PV01_2001_A	4	4	Beatrice: 「Nhuhahiii!!! Nhiii!! Nhuhuhu, Kuuuh!!!」	s21a	0131
PV01_2001_A	4	5	Kila: 「Kufuuuh!! Nkuh!! Fuhun!! Nh, Nnnnh!!」	s21a	0132
PV01_2001_A	4	6	The shit-dildos slid out smoothly having gotten past the initial  difficult part.	s21a	0133
PV01_2001_A	4	7	Each time they strained themselves, their anuses, which had been  spread out in perfect circles, twitched obscenely.	s21a	0134
PV01_2001_A	4	8	Following which, the shit-dildos smoothly slid out of them while  giving off appalling farting sounds.	s21a	0135
PV01_2001_A	4	9	Beatrice: 「Nhuuuuu, Mufuhuuu, Nnnh, Mmmmmmh...」	s21a	0136
PV01_2001_A	4	10	Kila: 「Nhuhu, Ungh, Ungh, Ungh, Fumuhuhuuuuuuuuuu!!」	s21a	0137
PV01_2001_A	4	11	20 centimetres had already come out of their anuses so far.	s21a	0138
PV01_2001_A	4	12	The shit-dildos dangling out of their anuses looked entirely like  their tails.	s21a	0139
PV01_2001_A	4	13	Moreover, it was clear to see that the mother and her daughter were  feeling pleasure from the act of defecation, as they began to swing  their asses around.	s21a	0140
PV01_2001_A	4	14	The pleasure-meter was proof of that.	s21a	0141
PV01_2001_A	4	15	As it rose up to 20%, Beatrice’s trousers and Kila’s panties  became dark on soaking up their pussy-juices, which were leaking  out.	s21a	0142
PV01_2001_A	4	16	Beatrice: 「Fuuumuuuh, Uhuhuhun, Nnnnnnnnh!!」	s21a	0143
PV01_2001_A	4	17	Kila: 「Nh, Nh, Nnnnnnnnh! Kufuh, Nnnnnnnnh!!」	s21a	0144
PV01_2001_A	4	18	Bohgan: 「Olov. Will their bodies be remodelled, once they push out these  shit-dildos?」	s21a	0145
PV01_2001_A	4	19	Olov: 「Yes. It is theoretically similar to the urethral remodelling,  however, the process involves repeatedly inserting and extracting  the shit-dildos, which I have specially crafted myself―― Uhihi」	s21a	0146
PV01_2001_A	4	20	Bohgan: 「Oho!」	s21a	0147
PV01_2001_A	4	21	Beatrice: 「Fuhummmuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuun!」	s21a	0148
PV01_2001_A	4	22	Kila: 「Nguhuhuuuuuuuuuun!!」	s21a	0149
PV01_2001_A	4	23	Both of them strained themselves severely, as if they wanted to put  a stop to Olov’s explanation.	s21a	0150
PV01_2001_A	4	24	Buryuryuryuryuryuuu!!	s21a	0151
PV01_2001_A	4	25	Bohgan: 「Ohooo!!」	s21a	0152
PV01_2001_A	4	26	Olov: 「Uhihihi!!」	s21a	0153
PV01_2001_A	4	27	Their anuses turned inside-out remarkably.	s21a	0154
PV01_2001_A	4	28	About 20 centimetres of the shit-dildos, covered with their slimy  intestinal-juices, slithered out of them in one swoop and ended up  rolling over their anuses.	s21a	0155
PV01_2001_A	4	29	Beatrice: 「Nhohohohoho! Hoh, Hoooooooooh!」	s21a	0156
PV01_2001_A	4	30	Kila: 「Ohohohooooooooooo!!」	s21a	0157
PV01_2001_A	4	31	They let out breaths on feeling intense sexual pleasure in their  anuses, which were completely different to the ones they had been  letting out while straining themselves to defecate.	s21a	0158
PV01_2001_A	4	32	The pleasure meters of both the women rose up to 40% as well.	s21a	0159
PV01_2001_A	4	33	Beatrice: 「Hihaaa, Hiha, Hihaha... Hah, Hah... Haaa...」	s21a	0160
PV01_2001_A	4	34	Kila: 「Haaa... Hih, Hah... Haha... Kaha... Hah... Hah, Hah...」	s21a	0161
PV01_2001_A	4	35	The pleasure they had derived from drawing out 20 centimetres of the  dildo seemed to be absolutely terrific.	s21a	0162
PV01_2001_A	4	36	Both of them had begun to wheeze while letting out their breaths, as  their dangling shit-tails reached down up to their knees.	s21a	0163
PV01_2001_A	4	37	As the shit-dildos stretched out to almost 40 centimetres in length,  their intestinal-juices began to pour out of their perfectly circular  anuses incessantly and drop down onto the ground after sliding off  the entire length of the dildos.	s21a	0164
PV01_2001_A	4	38	Bohgan: 「Hmmm...?」	s21a	0165
PV01_2001_A	4	39	Beatrice: 「Nguuuh... Kuh, Guh, Ngh, Nhuuuu, Nnnnnn...」	s21a	0166
PV01_2001_A	4	40	Kila: 「Kuh, Nnnnh, Ngh, Uhuuuuun!!」	s21a	0167
PV01_2001_A	5	1	Both the women clamped down on the shit-dildos with their anuses,  causing it to wobble back and forth.	s21a	0168
PV01_2001_A	5	2	Looking at their clamping, it seemed like they were trying to sever  the shit-dildos dangling out of them, unconsciously.	s21a	0169
PV01_2001_A	5	3	Bohgan: 「Kukukuku... That is a pointless effort.」	s21a	0170
PV01_2001_A	5	4	Olov: 「Yes. They will never be able to sever the shit-dildos, however,  Uhihihi―― Uh-oh, I guess you will see what I was about to explain  very soon.」	s21a	0171
PV01_2001_A	5	5	Bohgan: 「I thought you said that this is exactly the same as their urethral  remodelling.」	s21a	0172
PV01_2001_A	5	6	Olov: 「Yes. We are shaving off the cells on the surfaces of their large  intestines and anal-rectums, by repeatedly inserting and extracting  these shit-dildos. Following which, we are transplanting erogenous  cells in their stead.」	s21a	0173
PV01_2001_A	5	7	The slithering sounds of the women squeezing out the shit-dildos  were audible in between the intervals of our talk.	s21a	0174
PV01_2001_A	5	8	And then――	s21a	0175
PV01_2001_A	5	9	Beatrice: 「Ngh, Nnnnnnnnnnnnh!! Ohohoooo! Kah, Hah, Muhyaaahaaa!!」	s21a	0176
PV01_2001_A	5	10	Kila: 「Kuh, Fuh, Fuuuh! Nmoooh, Oh, Oh, Ohiii!! Hah, Hah... Nhuuuu!!!」	s21a	0177
PV01_2001_A	5	11	Bohgan: 「I see. So, is this the result?」	s21a	0178
PV01_2001_A	5	12	Olov: 「The result is the completion of the pigs, who feel sexual pleasure  during defecation, Uhihihi!」	s21a	0179
PV01_2001_A	5	13	Kila and Beatrice were no longer letting out anguished groans while  defecating, rather they were raising their lovely voices on getting  their anuses stimulated by the shit-dildos.	s21a	0180
PV01_2001_A	5	14	Beatrice: 「Ooooh, Ngh!! Nnnnnnnnh, Kuh, Guuuh... Kuhaaa!! Oh... Ohoho...」	s21a	0181
PV01_2001_A	5	15	Kila: 「Nnnnnnnngh!! Ngh, Ngh, Hnnnngh!! Hahihihiii!!!」	s21a	0182
PV01_2001_A	5	16	Their anuses had spread out in perfect circles and were chomping  down on the shit-dildos, causing the shit-dildos to slither out  every time they did so, as if they were completely different  creatures altogether.	s21a	0183
PV01_2001_A	5	17	Both the women began to swing their asses in a circular motion as  the glans of the shit-dildos reached the floor, which caused their  intestinal-juices to give off sputtering sounds.	s21a	0184
PV01_2001_A	5	18	Beatrice: 「Kuhuuun, Ngh... Nhuuu!! Nhoho, Oho, Ohohohooo!!」	s21a	0185
PV01_2001_A	5	19	Buryuryuryuuu!!	s21a	0186
PV01_2001_A	5	20	Beatrice: 「Kuhihiiiiiii!!!」	s21a	0187
PV01_2001_A	5	21	The mother raised a scream amidst her panting, as it squeezed out,	s21a	0188
PV01_2001_A	5	22	Kila: 「Ofuhun, Ngh, Nh, Nh, Nhuuun!!」	s21a	0189
PV01_2001_A	5	23	Buryuryuburyuburyuryuuu!!	s21a	0190
PV01_2001_A	5	24	Kila: 「Ohohohooooooo!!」	s21a	0191
PV01_2001_A	5	25	And the daughter indulged herself, while squeezing it out as well.	s21a	0192
PV01_2001_A	5	26	Beatrice: 「Nguhuuu, Oh, Ohooo, Uh, Uh, Uhuhuuu!!」	s21a	0193
PV01_2001_A	5	27	Kila: 「Ungh, Ungh, Ungh... Uuuuh, Kuhaaa, Ahahaaa...!!」	s21a	0194
PV01_2001_A	5	28	Their pleasure-meters rose up, as if both the women were competing  with each other.	s21a	0195
PV01_2001_A	5	29	The speed of the rise didn’t slow down whatsoever, even as it  crossed the 50% mark.	s21a	0196
PV01_2001_A	5	30	Beatrice: 「Kufuuuh, Uh, Uh... Ofuh, Oh, Oh, Ohohohoho!!」	s21a	0197
PV01_2001_A	5	31	Kila: 「Nguuuh, Kuh, Uh, Hnnngh... Kuhi, Hih, Uh, Uhuhuuuuuuuun!!!」	s21a	0198
PV01_2001_A	5	32	Their wild panting became louder and louder, as the pleasure from  their defecation increased.	s21a	0199
PV01_2001_A	5	33	The pleasure-meters rose up to 85%, as the length of the shit-dildos  which they had squeezed out, reached up to 1 metre.	s21a	0200
PV01_2001_A	5	34	Beatrice: 「Nhuuuhun, Ngh, Ngh, Kuuuh, Uuugh, Uhuuun...」	s21a	0201
PV01_2001_A	5	35	Kila: 「Hngh, Hngh, Aaaah, Uhu, Nnn～～～～nnh!!」	s21a	0202
PV01_2001_A	5	36	For a while now, Beatrice and Kila had been swinging their asses, as  if drawing a circle, while defecating the shit-dildos.	s21a	0203
PV01_2001_A	5	37	That uncouth yet lewd ass movement was causing the shit-dildos to  coil around as it dropped on the floor.	s21a	0204
PV01_2001_A	5	38	Bohgan: 「Ohooo! They are swinging their asses diligently despite being  unconscious. Has that been programmed into them!?」	s21a	0205
PV01_2001_A	5	39	Hans: 「No, Captain. We have done no such thing. They seem to be doing  it by themselves. I think this type of ass movement is a habit they  have picked up from their natural past defecation experience.」	s21a	0206
PV01_2001_A	5	40	Bohgan: 「Kuhahahahaha!!! Coiling up one’s shit was something people did in  the days of yore!! I can’t believe these pig-sluts!!」	s21a	0207
PV01_2001_A	6	1	Beatrice: 「Nhuuun, Ngh, Kufuh, Fuhaaa, Oho, Oh, Hoho, Nfuh, Ohohoho!!!!!」	s21a	0208
PV01_2001_A	6	2	Kila: 「Ahooo, Oh, Uh... Kuh, Fuuuh, Nhuuu, Ungh, Unnnnnngh... Fuh,  Fuhohooooo!!」	s21a	0209
PV01_2001_A	6	3	And then, both the women began to howl like wild beasts.	s21a	0210
PV01_2001_A	6	4	It looked like their anal-rectums were about to roll over inside-out,  however, the end parts of the shit-dildos, which had gotten stuck  behind their completely spread open anuses, were resisting it.	s21a	0211
PV01_2001_A	6	5	Bohgan: 「It looks like the other end of the dildos have become stuck. Are  they supposed to be stuck like that?」	s21a	0212
PV01_2001_A	6	6	Olov: 「No, Captain. It should be any moment now.」	s21a	0213
PV01_2001_A	6	7	Olov: 「I have already made them defecate like this 20 times before you  arrived, Captain.」	s21a	0214
PV01_2001_A	6	8	Olov: 「Both of them let out the shit-dildos completely every single time,  however, their pleasure-meters never reached 100% regardless, and  they couldn’t attain the perfect defecation-orgasms.」	s21a	0215
PV01_2001_A	6	9	Bohgan: 「Will they attain it this time?」	s21a	0216
PV01_2001_A	6	10	Olov: 「Uhihihihi... They will!!」	s21a	0217
PV01_2001_A	6	11	Beatrice: 「Nhuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu!!!」	s21a	0218
PV01_2001_A	6	12	Kila: 「Fuh, Fuh, Fuuuhuuuuumuuuh!!!!」	s21a	0219
PV01_2001_A	6	13	We continued to observe the asses of the Kushan mother and daughter  attentively as they put as much strain as they could, causing them  to tremble uncontrollably.	s21a	0220
PV01_2001_A	6	14	Zyuguuu, Pooooooooop!!!	s21a	0221
PV01_2001_A	6	15	Beatrice: 「Ohooo, Keeeeeeeeeeeeeh!!!」	s21a	0222
PV01_2001_A	6	16	Kila: 「Nhoho, Nhoho, Nhohohohooooo!!!」	s21a	0223
PV01_2001_A	6	17	Both the women let loose magnificent screams, as they hit their  tremendous anal-orgasms simultaneously.	s21a	0224
PV01_2001_A	6	18	Both of their anuses turned inside-out completely,	s21a	0225
PV01_2001_A	6	19	And, their intestinal-juices gushed out.	s21a	0226
PV01_2001_A	6	20	They had managed to squeeze out the end parts of the shit-dildos in  one swoop.	s21a	0227
PV01_2001_A	6	21	Beatrice: 「Ohooo, Hooo, Hoh, Hoh, Hohohohohohoho!!」	s21a	0228
PV01_2001_A	6	22	Kila: 「Hyuuuh, Ooooh, Oheeeheeeheeeee!!!」	s21a	0229
PV01_2001_A	6	23	And their anuses had been left gaping wide open.	s21a	0230
PV01_2001_A	6	24	Their fully expanded anuses overflowed with their intestinal-juices,  as their completely exposed pink anal-rectums twitched lewdly.	s21a	0231
PV01_2001_A	6	25	Beatrice: 「Hiyaaahaaa, Ah, Ah, Ahahaha, Ahahaaannn...」	s21a	0232
PV01_2001_A	6	26	Kila: 「Kuhihi, Kuhihi, Hih, Ah, Hihahahahaaaaa!!」	s21a	0233
PV01_2001_A	6	27	Both of them were experiencing an unmistakeable defecation-orgasm.	s21a	0234
PV01_2001_A	6	28	Even though I couldn’t see their faces, they had undoubtedly  peeled the whites of their eyes and had to be drooling out of  their trembling lips, while being stuck inside the machine.	s21a	0235
PV01_2001_A	6	29	The only thing that I could see from this side were the asses of the  mother and her daughter, which they were swinging together. They drew  their trembling legs together at their knees due to the orgasms and  spouted a magnificent tide out of their crotches as well.	s21a	0236
PV01_2001_A	6	30	Beatrice: 「Hyahaaa, Haaahaaahaaahuuum!!」	s21a	0237
PV01_2001_A	6	31	Kila: 「Ahihuuuuuuuuuuun!!!」	s21a	0238
PV01_2001_A	6	32	Beatrice was in her trousers and Kila in her panties, which is why  the tides they were spouting didn’t scatter all over the place.	s21a	0239
PV01_2001_A	6	33	That part of their attire became completely soaked with the shameful  juices that they were spouting, before trickling down onto the floor  along both their legs.	s21a	0240
PV01_2001_A	6	34	Moreover, the long shit-dildos that both the women had squeezed out  had coiled up neatly on the floor.	s21a	0241
PV01_2001_A	6	35	Beatrice: 「Haaahahahaaahahahaaaaaaa!!」	s21a	0242
PV01_2001_A	6	36	Kila: 「Hahuuuhahahaaaaahuuuun!!!」	s21a	0243
PV01_2001_A	6	37	The shit-dildos were no longer stuffed up their anal-rectums.	s21a	0244
PV01_2001_A	6	38	Despite that, both the mother, Beatrice, and her daughter, Kila,  continued to raise screams while having an anal-orgasm as their  anuses continued to twitch intermittently.	s21a	0245
PV01_2001_A	6	39	Bohgan: 「Is their pleasure-meter now at 100%?」	s21a	0246
PV01_2001_A	6	40	Olov: 「Yes. This is the first time that they have experienced a perfect  defecation-orgasm. Uhihi, Uhihihihi!!」	s21a	0247
PV01_2001_A	7	1	Bohgan: 「Wonderful! This was the best! Both these women have transformed  into unimaginably perverted pig-sluts now, haven’t they!?」	s21a	0248
PV01_2001_A	7	2	Hans: 「After their orgasms calm down, I will be stuffing the shit-dildos  back inside them and make them repeatedly experience these perfect  defecation-orgasms over and over again.」	s21a	0249
PV01_2001_A	7	3	Hans: 「That way, they will learn, from their asses all the way up to their  brains, that it is natural to orgasm while defecating. I plan to do  that 100 times before the morning.」	s21a	0250
PV01_2001_A	7	4	Hans displayed his sadistic nature in a different manner to Olov, by  keeping his composure until the end as usual.	s21a	0251
PV01_2001_A	7	5	Bohgan: 「Very well!! The officers who have sworn loyalty to the Kushan  Armed Forces will surely desert them, if they come to realize  that the Empress and the Grim Reaper orgasm while defecating!!」	s21a	0252
PV01_2001_A	7	6	I looked at the uncouth figures of both the women in satisfaction.	s21a	0253
PV01_2001_A	7	7	There had been no problems in today’s Public Relations Missions or  the brainwashing and remodelling process whatsoever.	s21a	0254
PV01_2001_A	7	8	And it was going to get even better.	s21a	0255
PV01_2001_A	7	9	Now then, which one should I choose for tomorrow?	s21a	0256
PV01_2001_A	7	10	The Empress Beatrice and the Grim Reaper Kila.	s21a	0257
PV01_2001_A	7	11	Which of these would I enjoy more?	s21a	0258
PV01_2001_A	7	12	SELECCIONAR 1: S021B
PV01_2001_A	7	13	SELECCIONAR 2: S021C
