PV01_101_A	1	1	Bohgan: 「Well, well...」	s10a	0136
PV01_101_A	1	2	I smiled in satisfaction.	s10a	0137
PV01_101_A	1	3	The detestable mother-daughter witch-duo of Beatrice and Kila had  been imprisoned miserably in front of my eyes.	s10a	0138
PV01_101_A	1	4	Bohgan: 「Welcome to my Brainwashing Laboratory. I will be sure to give  you a proper welcome... Kukuku」	s10a	0139
PV01_101_A	1	5	Beatrice: 「――――――」	s10a	0140
PV01_101_A	1	6	Kila: 「――――――」	s10a	0141
PV01_101_A	1	7	I greeted both of them, however they didn’t respond to me.	s10a	0142
PV01_101_A	1	8	Both of them had been restrained by the brainwashing-remodelling  device and had been put in a state of induced paralysis, through  the use of drugs.	s10a	0143
PV01_101_A	1	9	Bohgan: 「Kuku. What an excellent sight.」	s10a	0144
PV01_101_A	1	10	Beatrice and Kila had been forced into a bow-legged posture by  spreading their legs apart, and both their arms had been tied  behind their backs.	s10a	0145
PV01_101_A	1	11	The mother and her daughter had been lifted up as they were, and had  been suspended in mid-air with the help of the arm of the machine,  which stretched all the way to the back.	s10a	0146
PV01_101_A	1	12	They had been neatly dressed up in their attires, of course.	s10a	0147
PV01_101_A	1	13	Beatrice in the attire of the Commodore and Kila in the attire of  the Lieutenant, perhaps the appearances with which they associated  themselves the most.	s10a	0148
PV01_101_A	1	14	However, care had been taken to make certain that they would be  exposing themselves uncouthly.	s10a	0149
PV01_101_A	1	15	The fabric covering Beatrice’s crotch had been cut off, and her  pussy-lips had been spread wide open with the use of clips pulling  them outward.	s10a	0150
PV01_101_A	1	16	Beatrice: 「――――――」	s10a	0151
PV01_101_A	1	17	Bohgan: (So this is Empress’s pussy, huh? It looks the stench of semen has  already permeated it before.)	s10a	0152
PV01_101_A	1	18	I thought so, while looking at the pussy of the woman who had  already been impregnated with and pushed out her daughter, Kila,  who was dangling beside her.	s10a	0153
PV01_101_A	1	19	Her face and body still looked youthful, but her pussy was  extremely ripe.	s10a	0154
PV01_101_A	1	20	Her pussy looked extremely obscene under the lights of the  Brainwashing Laboratory, and it was twitching as her crimson  meat-folds contracted and relaxed intermittently.	s10a	0155
PV01_101_A	1	21	Even though nothing had been done to her yet, her female juices  were dripping out regardless.	s10a	0156
PV01_101_A	1	22	Bohgan: (And, this is her daughter, huh...?)	s10a	0157
PV01_101_A	1	23	Kila: 「――――――」	s10a	0158
PV01_101_A	1	24	Kila’s skirt, a part of her military attire, had also been rolled  up, similar to Beatrice. Her slutty black panties had been cut open,  and her pussy had also been completely exposed using clips.	s10a	0159
PV01_101_A	1	25	She looked young as expected, and her cunt, which was gaping as it  had been spread wide open, was giving off a fresh hue which wasn’t  even comparable to her mother’s.	s10a	0160
PV01_101_A	1	26	I didn’t know whose daughter Kila was to have inherited it, but her  lustrous dark-brown skin, which had been spread open, was exposing  her lavender-coloured female meat, which was so alluring that it  would make anyone forget her true nature.	s10a	0161
PV01_101_A	1	27	Bohgan: (And... Kuku, could you possibly be a virgin...?)	s10a	0162
PV01_101_A	1	28	It was easy to infer that, since her trembling and transparent  hymen membrane was still visibly intact without even needing to  probe into the depths of her cunt, which was a size smaller than  her mother’s.	s10a	0163
PV01_101_A	1	29	I had assumed that 『The beloved daughter of the Empress』 was a  raunchy girl, who would have been chewing up and spitting out the  men loyal to her, however surprisingly enough, she looked to be  nothing more than a naive girl who knew only how to kill.	s10a	0164
PV01_101_A	1	30	Bohgan: (I will be able to take the virginity of the daughter while her own  mother looks on, huh...? That is one more pleasurable act to look  forward to.)	s10a	0165
PV01_101_A	1	31	While I peered into Beatrice’s pussy, who had given birth, and  Kila’s pussy, who was still a virgin, they both continued to sleep  with a tranquil yet comical look on their faces, oblivious to the  fact that I was observing them.	s10a	0166
PV01_101_A	1	32	Needles had been pierced all over their bodies and sleeping drugs  were being administered to them continuously. The fact that they  were sleeping like this was evidence of the fact that the drugs  were working perfectly.	s10a	0167
PV01_101_A	1	33	The sleeping drugs were so powerful that they would never wake up  from the induced paralysis without an antidote.	s10a	0168
PV01_101_A	1	34	It was impossible to brainwash, remodel and rewrite a person’s  personality without the use of such drugs, all steps which were  essential to convert a normal body into that of a sex-doll.	s10a	0169
PV01_101_A	1	35	Bohgan: 「Kukuku, When the time for payback comes, I will carefully apply  all my time and effort in completely ravaging you witches.」	s10a	0170
PV01_101_A	1	36	After enjoying myself going over the uncouth figures of the two  women, I called over one of the members of the staff, who was busy  preparing for their brainwashing and remodelling process.	s10a	0171
PV01_101_A	1	37	Bohgan: 「Captain Ingeborg!」	s10a	0172
PV01_101_A	1	38	Ingeborg: 「Yes!」	s10a	0173
PV01_101_A	1	39	The man, who had been diligently monitoring the devices until now,  saluted me. He was my Deputy Major, Ingeborg.	s10a	0174
PV01_101_A	1	40	He was a practitioner of photography, and would carefully record  the sexual abuse of brainwashed and remodelled subjects and take  their photographs in uncompromising situations for use as feedback,  in order to further his brainwashing research.	s10a	0175
PV01_101_A	2	1	This man was the acknowledged authority when it came to data  collection and it could be said that he was a prodigy of this  science, which is why he had been well-supported by the Director  of the Brainwashing Laboratory, Hans.	s10a	0176
PV01_101_A	2	2	Bohgan: 「What is the situation report?」	s10a	0177
PV01_101_A	2	3	Ingeborg: 「It is going well, Captain. The nano-machines administered to them  have stabilized within their brains.」	s10a	0178
PV01_101_A	2	4	Bohgan: 「What about the memory processing?」	s10a	0179
PV01_101_A	2	5	Ingeborg: 「Yes. Although some brain cells were destroyed in the process, the  memories of tonight’s events have been successfully erased.」	s10a	0180
PV01_101_A	2	6	Bohgan: 「What about their accompanying guard?」	s10a	0181
PV01_101_A	2	7	Ingeborg: 「One of their soldiers was killed, but the remainder have all been  processed as well. And of course, the memories of the dead soldier  have been converted to “Not being on-board from the beginning of  the voyage”.」	s10a	0182
PV01_101_A	2	8	Ingeborg responded confidently with a cheerful face.	s10a	0183
PV01_101_A	2	9	Bohgan: 「Very well. Lieutenant Olov!」	s10a	0184
PV01_101_A	2	10	Olov: 「Y-Yo!」	s10a	0185
PV01_101_A	2	11	In contrast to Ingeborg, Lieutenant Olov saluted me while floating  a vulgar smile.	s10a	0186
PV01_101_A	2	12	He had a bestial appearance, however, he held a Ph. D. degree in  chemistry and was considered to be the one genius born every 100  years.	s10a	0187
PV01_101_A	2	13	However, his research leaned towards subjects like sexual abuse of  women, increasing virility, control of sexual desires, and he was  especially infatuated with researching the effects of aphrodisiacs,  all of which had hindered his career.	s10a	0188
PV01_101_A	2	14	I didn’t know how many women Olov had ruined before being banished  by the scientific community, after which I had taken him under my  wing when he had no one left to turn to.	s10a	0189
PV01_101_A	2	15	Bohgan: 「Is there any problem in the remodelling procedure?」	s10a	0190
PV01_101_A	2	16	Olov: 「N-No problem. We are all set to commence with the initial stage  of the remodelling process. Uhihi!」	s10a	0191
PV01_101_A	2	17	Bohgan: 「Failure isn’t an option anymore. I am asking you to be cautious  and reliable, similar to how you dealt with the renowned Maya and  Alicia. Don’t jeopardize this process by succumbing to your wicked  fetishes.」	s10a	0192
PV01_101_A	2	18	Olov: 「U-Understood. For the sake of the Captain, I have taken a lot more  care than usual. Be rest assured, Uhihi!」	s10a	0193
PV01_101_A	2	19	Bohgan: 「Very well. Army-Surgeon Captain Magnus!」	s10a	0194
PV01_101_A	2	20	Magnus: 「Reporting!」	s10a	0195
PV01_101_A	2	21	The aging man, Army-Surgeon Captain Magnus, responded with a  brilliant salute, suitable from someone his age.	s10a	0196
PV01_101_A	2	22	He was a doctor with a Ph. D. in brain specialization, who operated  on the brains and manipulated memories of the subjects,	s10a	0197
PV01_101_A	2	23	He was a man who had developed a device, that separated all the  personality traits from the brain for the purpose of storage.	s10a	0198
PV01_101_A	2	24	Bohgan: 「Is the program for the new personality working perfectly?」	s10a	0199
PV01_101_A	2	25	Magnus: 「Captain, as per your demands, I have built a program that will  convert these women into the most wretched pig-sluts, who will be  perfectly suitable as whores.」	s10a	0200
PV01_101_A	2	26	Magnus: 「The brainwashing process is scheduled to take approximately two  weeks, in order to attain 100% progression.」	s10a	0201
PV01_101_A	2	27	Bohgan: 「I see. My hopes rest with you.」	s10a	0202
PV01_101_A	2	28	Magnus: 「Yes, leave it to me!」	s10a	0203
PV01_101_A	2	29	Magnus, who considered and made use of people’s personalities  as his own personal playthings, saluted me while floating a smile  suitable for a mad-doctor.	s10a	0204
PV01_101_A	2	30	Hans: 「Captain, we can finally commence with the brainwashing and  remodelling process.」	s10a	0205
PV01_101_A	2	31	Bohgan: 「Major Hans, you have come at an opportune time.」	s10a	0206
PV01_101_A	2	32	Hans: 「Excuse me.」	s10a	0207
PV01_101_A	2	33	I gave a broad grin to the man, who had been working diligently  on monitoring all the preparations within the Brainwashing  Laboratory.	s10a	0208
PV01_101_A	2	34	He was the Director of the Brainwashing Laboratory and my Deputy,  who had a huge fixation for widows.	s10a	0209
PV01_101_A	2	35	These were men who tempered their intellect with their varied  fetishes and desires, which had enabled the Brainwashing Laboratory  to function at 100% efficiency.	s10a	0210
PV01_101_A	2	36	Bohgan: 「Fufu」	s10a	0211
PV01_101_A	2	37	My trustworthy brainwashing staff looked at me intently.	s10a	0212
PV01_101_A	2	38	All of them were waiting for my signal.	s10a	0213
PV01_101_A	2	39	Bohgan: 「Commence with the brainwashing!」	s10a	0214
PV01_101_A	2	40	Brainwashing Staff: 「Yes Sir!!」	s10a	0215
PV01_101_A	3	1	Huuuuuum!	s10a	0215
PV01_101_A	3	2	Two mechanical arms rose up from under the floor with dull humming  sounds.	s10a	0216
PV01_101_A	3	3	Cylindrical parts, which looked like penlights of about 5 mm in  diameter and about 30 cm in length, had been attached on the tips  of the arms.	s10a	0217
PV01_101_A	3	4	The mechanical arms aimed those cylindrical parts at the pussies of  the two women, similar to how a viper targets its prey.	s10a	0218
PV01_101_A	3	5	Bohgan: (Hmmm... Are they aiming at the upper part of their cunts?)	s10a	0219
PV01_101_A	3	6	Bohgan: 「What is happening?」	s10a	0220
PV01_101_A	3	7	Olov responded to my question.	s10a	0221
PV01_101_A	3	8	Olov: 「L-Lately, I have become fixated on developing sexual feelings in  the urethra.」	s10a	0222
PV01_101_A	3	9	Bohgan: 「Ohooo! Are you progressing with the urethra first?」	s10a	0223
PV01_101_A	3	10	Olov: 「I am trying to really pervert their bodies so that these whores  will orgasm every time they urinate, making it impossible for them  to lead normal lives... Uhihi!」	s10a	0224
PV01_101_A	3	11	Bohgan: 「That is wonderful, please continue!」	s10a	0225
PV01_101_A	3	12	Olov: 「Hahihi!」	s10a	0226
PV01_101_A	3	13	Olov chuckled with satisfaction and advanced with the mechanical  arms.	s10a	0227
PV01_101_A	3	14	Gubuh.	s10a	0228
PV01_101_A	3	15	Olov was extremely proud of his invention of these mechanical arms  and screwed them into the urethras of the women without hesitation,  something which they weren’t prepared for.	s10a	0229
PV01_101_A	3	16	Beatrice: 「Unn...」	s10a	0230
PV01_101_A	3	17	Kila: 「Kih...」	s10a	0231
PV01_101_A	3	18	Both the women lightly groaned in their sleep.	s10a	0232
PV01_101_A	3	19	The mother and her daughter knit their eyebrows.	s10a	0233
PV01_101_A	3	20	The restrained bodies of both the women stiffened up, even though  they had only been shallowly penetrated in their urethras.	s10a	0234
PV01_101_A	3	21	Their spread apart thighs began to twitch slightly, something which  wasn’t too apparent to everyone but me, as I observed their sultry  postures minutely.	s10a	0235
PV01_101_A	3	22	Beatrice: 「Kuh... Uuuun...」	s10a	0236
PV01_101_A	3	23	Kila: 「... Nnh... Kiiih...」	s10a	0237
PV01_101_A	3	24	Bohgan: 「They seem to be in pain, from the manner in which they are moving  their bodies.」	s10a	0238
PV01_101_A	3	25	Olov: 「Obviously, Captain.」	s10a	0239
PV01_101_A	3	26	Even though it was a bit slenderer than their urethras, having it  thrust in there all of a sudden was bound to transmit sharp pain  to their bodies.	s10a	0240
PV01_101_A	3	27	However, as the sleeping drugs were working perfectly both of them  didn’t wake.	s10a	0241
PV01_101_A	3	28	Their bodies were feeling a steady stream of pain but there was  no way for them to comprehend what was happening to them.	s10a	0242
PV01_101_A	3	29	Before they would even realize what was happening to them, their  normal bodies would be completely destroyed. That was the real  beauty of the brainwashing and remodelling process.	s10a	0243
PV01_101_A	3	30	Beatrice: 「Kuh... Ugh... Uuuun...」	s10a	0244
PV01_101_A	3	31	Kila: 「Nhh... Uuuun... Kuuuh... Hiii...」	s10a	0245
PV01_101_A	3	32	Bohgan: 「Olov, what are going to do?」	s10a	0246
PV01_101_A	3	33	Olov: 「Now, the pointed tips of the mechanical arms will be used to slice  off the inner surface of the urethras of these whores, and erogenous  cells will be transplanted in its place, for which I have already  done the preparations, Uhihi」	s10a	0247
PV01_101_A	3	34	Bohgan: 「That sounds really painful.」	s10a	0248
PV01_101_A	3	35	Olov: 「I conducted this experiment on five women while they were conscious,  and one of them went in shock and ended up dying instantly while two  others went insane due to the pain, Uhihi」	s10a	0249
PV01_101_A	3	36	I recalled the remaining two women who Olov had added to his  collection, and issued him a warning.	s10a	0250
PV01_101_A	3	37	Bohgan: 「You might feel like trying it out on both of these women while they  are conscious, however in this case, you need to show restraint.」	s10a	0251
PV01_101_A	3	38	Olov: 「Oh well, I guess it can’t be helped. I will transplant the  erogenous cells on these whores repeatedly, until the assimilation  is perfected and, after that, I will spend time in strengthening  those erogenous feelings. Is that more to your liking?」	s10a	0252
PV01_101_A	3	39	Bohgan: 「Of course. Get to it.」	s10a	0253
PV01_101_A	3	40	Olov: 「Hahahi!」	s10a	0254
PV01_101_A	4	1	Beatrice: 「Nnnnguh!」	s10a	0255
PV01_101_A	4	2	Kila: 「Kuhuuun!」	s10a	0256
PV01_101_A	4	3	The inner surfaces of their urethras were being sliced off and  transplanted with new erogenous cells. The demonic remodelling  continued, as the remodelling tip of the mechanical arm entered  further into their depths.	s10a	0257
PV01_101_A	4	4	It was thrust in deep enough for both the women to feel it vividly  and they ended up knitting their eyebrows even more due to the pain,  while their moaning became louder.	s10a	0258
PV01_101_A	4	5	Bohgan: 「You seem to burying it in them quite slowly.」	s10a	0259
PV01_101_A	4	6	The remodelling tip was stopping repeatedly after being buried a  little and, in that manner, it was being penetrated bit by bit into  their urethras.	s10a	0260
PV01_101_A	4	7	Olov: 「It is being done like that based on the experimental results.  After all, the urethra is an organ which is particularly sensitive,  Uhihi」	s10a	0261
PV01_101_A	4	8	Bohgan: 「I see.」	s10a	0262
PV01_101_A	4	9	Beatrice: 「Nguuuh...!! Nnnnnh...!! Kuuuuh...!!」	s10a	0263
PV01_101_A	4	10	Kila: 「Fukuuuh...! Uuuun... Nnnnnh!!」	s10a	0264
PV01_101_A	4	11	It was a time-consuming process, peeling off the cells of the inner  surface of their urethras and transplanting erogenous cells in their  place.	s10a	0265
PV01_101_A	4	12	Both of them wound up bouncing their entire bodies, as if struck by  lightning, every time the remodelling tip was screwed deeper into  them, while leaking out groans of pain.	s10a	0266
PV01_101_A	4	13	Beatrice: 「Nnnngh...! Kuuuuh!! Ngh... Nnnnnnh!!」	s10a	0267
PV01_101_A	4	14	Kila: 「Uh... Kuuuh... Argh...!! Nnnh, Kuh... Huguuuh!!」	s10a	0268
PV01_101_A	4	15	Ingeborg: 「Captain, isn’t this a pleasant duet?」	s10a	0269
PV01_101_A	4	16	Ingeborg, who idolized Marquis de Sade, was cheerfully staring at  them with narrowed eyes.	s10a	0270
PV01_101_A	4	17	Bohgan: 「Indeed, it is. Olov, how long does it take to complete the  remodelling process?」	s10a	0271
PV01_101_A	4	18	Olov: 「It will take about one week. Once the assimilation is complete,  it will be impossible for them to remove the erogenous feelings  from their urethras.」	s10a	0272
PV01_101_A	4	19	Bohgan: 「And then, my slaves with erogenous urethras will be born.」	s10a	0273
PV01_101_A	4	20	Olov: 「Yes. These whores will be transformed into perverted women who  orgasm every time they urinate, for the entirety of their miserable  lives. Uhihi!」	s10a	0274
PV01_101_A	4	21	Bohgan: 「That is wonderful.」	s10a	0275
PV01_101_A	4	22	The remodelling tips slowly buried themselves completely inside the  urethras of both the witches, as we engulfed their bodies with our  cheerful stares.	s10a	0276
PV01_101_A	4	23	Beatrice: 「Uuuh... Uuuh... Kuuuh... Uuuh... Uuuh... Uuuuuun...」	s10a	0277
PV01_101_A	4	24	Kila: 「Nnnnh... Kuh... Uh... Kuuuh... Uuuuh... Nnnnnh...」	s10a	0278
PV01_101_A	4	25	Their urethral openings had stretched open due to the intrusion of  the remodelling tips and had started to tremble increasingly, which  was apparent even by observing it from outside.	s10a	0279
PV01_101_A	4	26	And at the same time, the erogenous cells were being assimilated  into the depths of their urethras.	s10a	0280
PV01_101_A	4	27	It was a sight that a man couldn’t help but get excited about.	s10a	0281
PV01_101_A	4	28	Bohgan: 「Come to think of it... Hans, apart from this, I would like to try  a new type of remodelling on these women as well.」	s10a	0282
PV01_101_A	4	29	Hans: 「Okay! Lieutenant Olov, are we ready for that?」	s10a	0283
PV01_101_A	4	30	Olov: 「Are you talking about the Erogenous Framework remodelling? Then,  of course we are. Uhihihi」	s10a	0284
PV01_101_A	4	31	Magnus: 「Ohooo. Are you going to carry that out? I have heard that it is  quite a complex procedure.」	s10a	0285
PV01_101_A	4	32	Bohgan: 「I have heard that as well. Is it safe to do it?」	s10a	0286
PV01_101_A	4	33	Hans: 「Captain, be rest assured. I have carefully prepared a series of  teleportation injections for this very purpose.」	s10a	0287
PV01_101_A	4	34	Bohgan: 「Teleportation injections?」	s10a	0288
PV01_101_A	4	35	Hans: 「The process involves administering drugs from phase space, which  doesn’t injure the body at all. It is the latest technology that  is still undergoing research but has already been tested on guinea  pigs. It is a practical use of the shielding technology.」	s10a	0289
PV01_101_A	4	36	Beatrice: 「Uuuh... Kuh... Uh... Uuuuun... Kuuuh...」	s10a	0290
PV01_101_A	4	37	Kila: 「Nghhh... Kuhuuu... Fukuuuh... Uh... Kuuuh...」	s10a	0291
PV01_101_A	4	38	The faces of both the witches started showing the gradual increase  in pain.	s10a	0292
PV01_101_A	4	39	Bohgan: 「Excellent, go ahead then.」	s10a	0293
PV01_101_A	4	40	Hans: 「Yes. Lieutenant Olov, you may begin.」	s10a	0294
PV01_101_A	5	1	Olov: 「Understood. Uhihi」	s10a	0295
PV01_101_A	5	2	Two rifle-like mechanical arms emerged.	s10a	0296
PV01_101_A	5	3	Each of them aimed at the centres of both of their bodies.	s10a	0297
PV01_101_A	5	4	Mechanical sounds resonated as energy filled up in those arms, after  which the serial injections were administered to them.	s10a	0298
PV01_101_A	5	5	Beatrice: 「Uuuuugh!!」	s10a	0299
PV01_101_A	5	6	Kila: 「Guhiii!!」	s10a	0300
PV01_101_A	5	7	The mother and her daughter groaned loudly and their bodies jolted  up with a start.	s10a	0301
PV01_101_A	5	8	Bohgan: 「Hooo」	s10a	0302
PV01_101_A	5	9	I gazed at them with wide eyes,	s10a	0303
PV01_101_A	5	10	Long, thin glass phials had pierced through the flesh of both of  their necks, the centres of their chests and the area just under  their chests.	s10a	0304
PV01_101_A	5	11	The insides of the glass phials were filled with a fluorescent drug  that was sparkling brightly.	s10a	0305
PV01_101_A	5	12	Beatrice: 「Mmmmmmmmh, Ugh, Kuuuh!」	s10a	0306
PV01_101_A	5	13	Kila: 「Kuuuuuuh, Hih, Hiiin!」	s10a	0307
PV01_101_A	5	14	Beatrice and Kila couldn’t open their eyes as expected, however,  their bodies started trembling due to the shock of having three  drug-filled phials pierced through them.	s10a	0308
PV01_101_A	5	15	Bohgan: 「I see. So, this is the teleportation injection, huh?」	s10a	0309
PV01_101_A	5	16	I observed this practical use of the shielding technology with  amusement, as the bodies of the women were skewered suddenly.	s10a	0310
PV01_101_A	5	17	Hans: 「Framework remodelling nano-machines with special aphrodisiacal  properties are ready to be injected and stored in their bones,  Lieutenant Olov.」	s10a	0311
PV01_101_A	5	18	Olov: 「Injecting♪」	s10a	0312
PV01_101_A	5	19	Beatrice: 「Uhuuuh... Kuh, Uuuuh... Uh, Kuh... Uuuh...」	s10a	0313
PV01_101_A	5	20	Kila: 「Kuh... Fuh... Uh... Kuuuh... Nnnh, Kuuuuh...」	s10a	0314
PV01_101_A	5	21	The drugs were injected into them from the three phials, which had  pierced through their bodies.	s10a	0315
PV01_101_A	5	22	Unlike an injection―― it looked like it was being sucked into  their bodies against their will.	s10a	0316
PV01_101_A	5	23	The chemical solution started decreasing, as I looked on.	s10a	0317
PV01_101_A	5	24	Beatrice: 「Uuuun... Kuh, Uh... Uh... Guuuh... Uh... Kuuuh...」	s10a	0318
PV01_101_A	5	25	Kila: 「Kufuuuh... Uguh... Uuuh... Kuh... Mmmmh... Ngh, Nnnnnnnnh!!」	s10a	0319
PV01_101_A	5	26	Even though they were unconscious, they were clearly in a lot of  pain.	s10a	0320
PV01_101_A	5	27	Both of them moaned over and over again.	s10a	0321
PV01_101_A	5	28	Their trembling bodies, which had been skewered with the drug  phials, went into convulsions.	s10a	0322
PV01_101_A	5	29	Beatrice: 「Nnnguh... Guuuh... Uh... Kuh... Keh... Ugh...」	s10a	0323
PV01_101_A	5	30	Kila: 「Nnnnnh... Kuh, Uh... Gah... Uuuh, Nnnhiii!」	s10a	0324
PV01_101_A	5	31	Hans: 「If we keep this up for one week, their entire skeletal framework  will be completely eroticized.」	s10a	0325
PV01_101_A	5	32	Hans: 「Initially, it will simply feel like tantalizing pleasure. Following  that, they will go into heat, and very soon, they will just end up  having an orgasm, if they ever move vigorously.」	s10a	0326
PV01_101_A	5	33	Olov: 「And when it is complete... their athletic capabilities will be  completely restricted... In other words, their combat abilities  will be thoroughly nullified... Uhihi!」	s10a	0327
PV01_101_A	5	34	Olov continued Hans’s explanation while twitching his shoulders,  as if he couldn’t control his excitement.	s10a	0328
PV01_101_A	5	35	Bohgan: 「This mother-daughter witch-duo is powerful enough to match a  thousand soldiers. We must bury it completely... without them  even realizing it... Kukuku」	s10a	0329
PV01_101_A	5	36	Beatrice: 「Guuuh... Ugh... Guuuh... Fuuun... Uh, Kuuuh...」	s10a	0330
PV01_101_A	5	37	Kila: 「Nhaaaa... Uuuh... Kuh... Uh, Uuuuuuh, Uuuuuh...」	s10a	0331
PV01_101_A	5	38	The chemical solution of the drugs stored in the three phials  was injected into their two bodies at an unbelievable speed in  one swoop, with the use of mechanical forces.	s10a	0332
PV01_101_A	5	39	As expected, their reaction was dramatic enough to match that  development.	s10a	0333
PV01_101_A	5	40	Beatrice: 「Kuhaaa... Aaaah, Haaa... Aaahiii... Aaahiii...」	s10a	0334
PV01_101_A	6	1	Kila: 「Hiii... Hah, Hah, Hiyaaa... Hih, Hih... Hahiii... Hiii...」	s10a	0335
PV01_101_A	6	2	The appearance of the mother and her daughter changed drastically.	s10a	0336
PV01_101_A	6	3	All of a sudden, their faces flushed a deep scarlet, their breathing  became wild and they started panting, as sweat began oozing out of  their bodies.	s10a	0337
PV01_101_A	6	4	Beatrice: 「Hahiii... Higuh... Higuh... Kah, Hah... Kaaah... Hah, Hah...」	s10a	0338
PV01_101_A	6	5	Kila: 「Hih... Hah, Hih... Hah, Hah... Hih... Wahiii... Hih... Kuh...  Hih...」	s10a	0339
PV01_101_A	6	6	The empty drug phials, which had been pierced through their torsos,  wobbled up and down furiously.	s10a	0340
PV01_101_A	6	7	I couldn’t help but get excited while looking over the agonized  faces of the witches, as they suffered difficulty in breathing.	s10a	0341
PV01_101_A	6	8	Bohgan: 「It is wonderful, this technology which you call the teleportation  injection.」	s10a	0342
PV01_101_A	6	9	Hans: 「Yes. It injects the aphrodisiac directly into their bones, which  permeates all the way to the marrow, causing an alteration to their  skeletal framework, transforming it into a pleasure-inducing one.」	s10a	0343
PV01_101_A	6	10	Bohgan: 「I am looking forward to its completion. Are those drug phials  still supposed to be stuck in them like that?」	s10a	0344
PV01_101_A	6	11	Hans: 「No need to worry about it.」	s10a	0345
PV01_101_A	6	12	―― Whoosh.	s10a	0346
PV01_101_A	6	13	The teleportation mechanism was activated again and the glass phials,  which had contained the drugs, disappeared in an instant.	s10a	0347
PV01_101_A	6	14	Never mind any injuries, there wasn’t even even a single mark left  on both of their bodies.	s10a	0348
PV01_101_A	6	15	And then,	s10a	0349
PV01_101_A	6	16	Beatrice: 「Kuaaah!!」	s10a	0350
PV01_101_A	6	17	Kila: 「Hiyaaah!!」	s10a	0351
PV01_101_A	6	18	Moans of pleasure echoed out.	s10a	0352
PV01_101_A	6	19	The two bodies jolted up and twisted remarkably even though they  were restrained.	s10a	0353
PV01_101_A	6	20	Bubyubyuuu!!	s10a	0354
PV01_101_A	6	21	Beatrice: 「Kuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuh!!」	s10a	0355
PV01_101_A	6	22	Kila: 「Kafuuuuuuuuuuuuuh!!」	s10a	0356
PV01_101_A	6	23	Bohgan: 「Ooooh!!」	s10a	0357
PV01_101_A	6	24	I stared at them with wide eyes.	s10a	0358
PV01_101_A	6	25	Honey-juices spurted out of their pussies, as if a dam had broken.	s10a	0359
PV01_101_A	6	26	And the very next moment, their boobs squeezed tightly and their  nipples became comically erect.	s10a	0360
PV01_101_A	6	27	Beatrice: 「Hiyaaah, Waaah, Haahaa, Hah, Kuaaah!!」	s10a	0361
PV01_101_A	6	28	Kila: 「Eyaaah, Hah, Hih, Kuhiii, Hiii!!」	s10a	0362
PV01_101_A	6	29	They started breathing wildly, as the agonizing feelings raced  through their bodies without a pause.	s10a	0363
PV01_101_A	6	30	Drool overflowed out of the openings of their mouths and began  trickling out.	s10a	0364
PV01_101_A	6	31	Bohgan: 「Fufu... This is beautiful.」	s10a	0365
PV01_101_A	6	32	Even for me, someone who had trained numerous women so far by means  of brainwashing, this contrast of them going completely into heat  in an instant was visually stunning.	s10a	0366
PV01_101_A	6	33	Olov: 「Uhihihi! It seems like the moment the teleportation injections  disappeared the recoil from the phase space struck their pleasure  core.」	s10a	0367
PV01_101_A	6	34	Bohgan: 「I see. So, that is why they reacted like that? Interesting.」	s10a	0368
PV01_101_A	6	35	Beatrice: 「Waaahiii, Uhiii, Hih, Hih, Hahiii, Kuhiii, Hahiii」	s10a	0369
PV01_101_A	6	36	Kila: 「Hah, Haha, Hah, Hah, Hih, Hah, Uhaaa」	s10a	0370
PV01_101_A	6	37	Magnus: 「It is certainly interesting. However, leave their brains to me.  Is that alright, Captain?」	s10a	0371
PV01_101_A	6	38	Magnus turned his gaze to me, while twiddling his fingers together  excitedly.	s10a	0372
PV01_101_A	6	39	He had become unable to control his excitement while observing the  magnificent remodelling of their bodies, including the urethral  remodelling and the Erogenous Framework remodelling, which was ironic  considering the fact that he was a brain specialist.	s10a	0373
PV01_101_A	6	40	Bohgan: 「Certainly. Army-Surgeon Captain Magnus, that is your area of  expertise after all. I entrust that task to you.」	s10a	0374
PV01_101_A	7	1	Magnus: 「Yes!」	s10a	0375
PV01_101_A	7	2	―― Ghuuuun	s10a	0376
PV01_101_A	7	3	A pleasant whirring sound echoed out and the heads of Beatrice and  Kila were completely covered up by the brainwashing helmets.	s10a	0377
PV01_101_A	7	4	Numerous electrodes had been connected to those helmets through  which the program of their new personalities would be installed  onto the micro-chips, which had already been embedded inside their  brains.	s10a	0378
PV01_101_A	7	5	Beatrice: 『Aaah, Kih, Kah, Hah, Hiii, Kiiih!』	s10a	0379
PV01_101_A	7	6	Kila: 『Fuuuh, Hih, Kuh, Fuh, Higuh, Hah, Hah...』	s10a	0380
PV01_101_A	7	7	The thick and bulky equipment had covered their faces entirely,  causing their wild breathing to sound muffled.	s10a	0381
PV01_101_A	7	8	Magnus: 「I will start their brainwashing process right away.」	s10a	0382
PV01_101_A	7	9	Magnus: 「As you know, once the brainwashing process progresses to 100%,  we will be able to switch over to their completed Convenient  Personalities. In other words, they will have transformed into  completely different people.」	s10a	0383
PV01_101_A	7	10	Magnus: 「The setting of the new personality is of a whore whose only goal  in life is to be the most wretched pig-slut.」	s10a	0384
PV01_101_A	7	11	Magnus: 「Moreover, since it is an extremely potent personality, it will  change their original personality bit by bit, however, they will  never even realize that fact.」	s10a	0385
PV01_101_A	7	12	Magnus continued to methodically explain the process that everyone  already knew, befitting of a doctor.	s10a	0386
PV01_101_A	7	13	Beatrice: 『Kuuuuh, Fuuuuh, Kiiiih, Hiiiiii』	s10a	0387
PV01_101_A	7	14	Kila: 『Ahiii, Ahiii, Hih, Hih, Hifuuuh, Hih』	s10a	0388
PV01_101_A	7	15	Both of them started to breathe in an increasingly agonized manner  from under the helmet.	s10a	0389
PV01_101_A	7	16	It was amusing to listen to.	s10a	0390
PV01_101_A	7	17	Bohgan: 「Very well. You may begin.」	s10a	0391
PV01_101_A	7	18	Magnus: 「Okay. I will begin the installation.」	s10a	0392
PV01_101_A	7	19	Magnus pushed the buttons deftly.	s10a	0393
PV01_101_A	7	20	―― Buzz Buzz Buzz Buzz!	s10a	0394
PV01_101_A	7	21	Beatrice: 『Nguuuuuuuuuuuuuuuh!!!』	s10a	0395
PV01_101_A	7	22	Kila: 『Ehiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii!!!』	s10a	0396
PV01_101_A	7	23	Sparks flew from the electrodes, which had been connected directly  to their brains.	s10a	0397
PV01_101_A	7	24	Both their bodies trembled furiously and they went into convulsions  yet again.	s10a	0398
PV01_101_A	7	25	Finally, the brainwashing process had commenced.	s10a	0399
PV01_101_A	7	26	Beatrice: 『Ughighighighiguuuuuh!!』	s10a	0400
PV01_101_A	7	27	Kila: 『Aghiii!! Geeeh!! Gughighighighiii!!』	s10a	0401
PV01_101_A	7	28	The electric current wasn’t really assaulting them directly.	s10a	0402
PV01_101_A	7	29	However, their tormented voices echoing from underneath the  brainwashing helmets were so severe, that it made it seem like  they really were being directly struck by lightning.	s10a	0403
PV01_101_A	7	30	Bohgan: (Oh dear... When your new personalities completely reform your  original personalities, the pain you will feel will be way more  than actually being struck by lightning... Kukuku)	s10a	0404
PV01_101_A	7	31	Beatrice: 『Guhguguuuh, Geeeh, Giiiiih!!』	s10a	0405
PV01_101_A	7	32	Kila: 『Agaagaagaagh!! Agaaah!! Aaaaaaaaaaah!!』	s10a	0406
PV01_101_A	7	33	Their anguished screams escalated and became louder and the  convulsions of their bodies became even more intense.	s10a	0407
PV01_101_A	7	34	Their honey-juices squirted out in magnificent tides from their  exposed crotches, while they were kept suspended in a bow-legged  posture.	s10a	0408
PV01_101_A	7	35	Bohgan: 「That was fast. Has their pain started transforming into pleasure  already?」	s10a	0409
PV01_101_A	7	36	I knew of such developments already due to my experience with the  brainwashing and remodelling process until now.	s10a	0410
PV01_101_A	7	37	Magnus: 「Indeed, it looks like the effect of their bodily remodelling has  already taken effect, no doubt due to our new technology. Shall I  develop their “Orgasm” neural network right now, Captain?」	s10a	0411
PV01_101_A	7	38	Bohgan: 「Go for it.」	s10a	0412
PV01_101_A	7	39	Magnus: 「Well then, Beatrice Kushan, Kila Kushan. It is time to make you  memorize the feeling of a real pig-slut’s orgasm.」	s10a	0413
PV01_101_A	7	40	Magnus began operating the control-panel by smoothly drifting his  fingers over it.	s10a	0414
PV01_101_A	8	1	And, the very next moment――	s10a	0415
PV01_101_A	8	2	Beatrice: 『Ohohooooooooooooooooo!!!』	s10a	0416
PV01_101_A	8	3	Kila: 『Hihihiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii!!!』	s10a	0417
PV01_101_A	8	4	Their groans of agony transformed into moans of pleasure, in an  instant.	s10a	0418
PV01_101_A	8	5	An electric signal depicting the act of orgasming had been sent  directly to their brains using the brainwashing device, and they  had been forced to orgasm just like that.	s10a	0419
PV01_101_A	8	6	Of course, it wasn’t just their orgasms.	s10a	0420
PV01_101_A	8	7	The experience of an orgasm was being firmly planted inside their  bodies, by forcefully pumping the orgasm-signal through their nervous  system repeatedly. The signal was ten-fold in strength to a normal  orgasm, which was causing their brains to melt in ecstasy.	s10a	0421
PV01_101_A	8	8	Beatrice: 『Nhohooo, Oho, Hooohiii, Haaahyaaa, Hohooooooooooooooo!!』	s10a	0422
PV01_101_A	8	9	Kila: 『Ahiii, Hiiihiiiiin, Uhihihihihiiiiin!!!』	s10a	0423
PV01_101_A	8	10	Even though they had been fixed in a bow-legged posture, they began  trembling uncontrollably and their dangling legs began wobbling back  and forth.	s10a	0424
PV01_101_A	8	11	It looked like they were trying to draw in a dick situated in the  space under them, and thrust it into their pussies by themselves.	s10a	0425
PV01_101_A	8	12	Their twitching cunts, which had been stretched wide open to their  limits with the use of the clips, went into convulsions and started  spouting out their thick female tide all over the place.	s10a	0426
PV01_101_A	8	13	Beatrice: 『Ooohohohohooo!!!! Nhhh, Hooohohohooo!!』	s10a	0427
PV01_101_A	8	14	Kila: 『Hiyooooooooooo!! Ah, Ah, Ahaaa, Ohoooooooon!!!』	s10a	0428
PV01_101_A	8	15	Bohgan: 「Kuhahahahahaha!! So this is how these witches orgasm, huh?  The mother and her daughter look like absolute fools!」	s10a	0429
PV01_101_A	8	16	Magnus: 「Kila Kushan has been scanned and is confirmed to be a virgin,  which is precisely why she is showing off her orgasm, just as a  virgin would.」	s10a	0430
PV01_101_A	8	17	Captain Magnus, the Army-Surgeon, said so in a cold-hearted but  calm tone, as only a doctor could.	s10a	0431
PV01_101_A	8	18	Kila: 『Nhiiiii!! Hih, Ahiiiiiiiiiiiiin!!!』	s10a	0432
PV01_101_A	8	19	Bohgan: 「Her cunt has experienced and memorized an orgasm way more powerful  than a normal one despite not even knowing how it feels to hold a  cock. And what of her mother?」	s10a	0433
PV01_101_A	8	20	Beatrice: 『Hiiiyaaah!! Aheheeeh!! Nhaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!!』	s10a	0434
PV01_101_A	8	21	Magnus: 「The experience of the orgasm seems to be less potent for her.  However, the condition of her pussy and her womb is like that of  a teenager since she hasn’t had any sexual-intercourse at least  for the past year, which I have confirmed from the scans.」	s10a	0435
PV01_101_A	8	22	Bohgan: 「Kuhahahahahaha!!! Do this mother-daughter pair know nothing else  but war? It really will be worthwhile to plant the memories of a  whore in these bloody women.」	s10a	0436
PV01_101_A	8	23	Magnus: 「This is why I was born, to brainwash women.」	s10a	0437
PV01_101_A	8	24	Bohgan: 「Army-Surgeon Captain Magnus, finish them off by giving them the  most magnificent orgasm possible.」	s10a	0438
PV01_101_A	8	25	Magnus: 「Maximizing their orgasms.」	s10a	0439
PV01_101_A	8	26	Beatrice: 『Ahnnnghiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii!!!』	s10a	0440
PV01_101_A	8	27	Kila: 『Hogyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!!!』	s10a	0441
PV01_101_A	8	28	The screams of the two women echoed out inside the Brainwashing  Laboratory.	s10a	0442
PV01_101_A	8	29	Beatrice: 『Nhaaa, Aaah, Aaah, Aaaaah!!! Higiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii!!!』	s10a	0443
PV01_101_A	8	30	Kila: 『Oghnooo, Oooh, Oooh, Oooooh!!! Ooooooooooooooooooooooohnnn!!!』	s10a	0444
PV01_101_A	8	31	Ingeborg: 「The orgasm has now been maximized and it is ongoing even as we  speak.」	s10a	0445
PV01_101_A	8	32	The bodies of Beatrice and Kila twisted and squirmed around  aimlessly, like broken dolls.	s10a	0446
PV01_101_A	8	33	The force with which the two women were thrashing about seemed  enough to break the mechanical arms, which were being used to  restrain them.	s10a	0447
PV01_101_A	8	34	They were suffering the most potent orgasm that they possibly could  with their bodies and their brains.	s10a	0448
PV01_101_A	8	35	Ingeborg: 「They are orgasming magnificently, Captain.」	s10a	0449
PV01_101_A	8	36	Bohgan: 「Indeed. I expected nothing less from these demonic women of Mars.  They will entertain us aplenty!!!」	s10a	0450
PV01_101_A	8	37	Pushaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!!!	s10a	0451
PV01_101_A	8	38	Olov: 「Uhihi! Look at that, it came out!!」	s10a	0452
PV01_101_A	8	39	Beatrice: 『Ahyaaaaah, Bhyaaa, Ah, Ah, Aaaaaaaaahin!!!』	s10a	0453
PV01_101_A	8	40	Kila: 『Ibibibibibibibibibih, Ihiiiyuuun!!』	s10a	0454
PV01_101_A	9	1	It looked like the urethral remodelling, which had been bestowed  upon the two women a while back, was beginning to show its effects  now.	s10a	0455
PV01_101_A	9	2	They started urinating and their urine burst out with tremendous  force, because of the remodelling tip which was still buried inside  their urethral openings.	s10a	0456
PV01_101_A	9	3	Ingeborg: 「They are magnificent. I expect them to be the best pig-sluts we  have ever had the pleasure of training.」	s10a	0457
PV01_101_A	9	4	Hans: 「Congratulations, Captain.」	s10a	0458
PV01_101_A	9	5	Beatrice: 『Ah, Hah, Ah, Aaaaaaaaaaaahin!!!』	s10a	0459
PV01_101_A	9	6	Kila: 『Ighiiiiiiiiiiih, Uuuuuuuuuuuuhuuun!!!』	s10a	0460
PV01_101_A	9	7	I couldn’t even hear the words of my subordinates over their loud  orgasmic screams.	s10a	0461
PV01_101_A	9	8	Besides, this was simply the first wave of their brainwashing and  remodelling process.	s10a	0462
PV01_101_A	9	9	Bohgan: 「Gentlemen, the cruellest enemies make the best prey!!」	s10a	0463
PV01_101_A	9	10	Bohgan: 「Let us be sure to carve our marks onto them without mercy, which  will come to signify the end of their miserable lives! It shall be  our tribute to the tens of thousands of soldiers that these witches  have murdered!」	s10a	0464
PV01_101_A	9	11	My Men: 「Aye Aye, Sir!!!」	s10a	0465
PV01_101_A	9	12	Beatrice And Kila: 『Aaah, Aaah, Aaah, Aaahuuun, Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahun!!!』	s10a	0466
PV01_101_A	9	13	They continued to scream uncouthly, while orgasming over and over  again.	s10a	0467
PV01_101_A	9	14	Without even knowing about it, the two witches of Mars had fallen  from being humans into mere pig-sluts.	s10a	0468
PV01_101_A	9	15	Bohgan: (Kukukuku... I will accept the gratitude of the Kushan mother and  daughter very soon.)	s10a	0469
PV01_101_A	9	16	At long last, I got the actual feeling of a hotly contested battle  and I felt truly alive as I listened to the orgasmic screams of both  the women.	s10a	0470
PV01_101_A	9	17	SALTAR: S011A
