PV01_1201_A	1	1	Beatrice: 「Kuh...」	s18a	0111
PV01_1201_A	1	2	I took of Beatrice’s mantle and touched her breasts, causing her  to leak out a moan tinged with annoyance.	s18a	0112
PV01_1201_A	1	3	Beatrice: 「I suppose... only the breasts will do...」	s18a	0113
PV01_1201_A	1	4	Bohgan: 「Yes, Madam. I have no intention of earning your wrath by lying  to you.」	s18a	0114
PV01_1201_A	1	5	Beatrice: 「Somehow... I feel you won’t be satisfied... just with this...」	s18a	0115
PV01_1201_A	1	6	Bohgan: 「Well, after this, if you allow me──」	s18a	0116
PV01_1201_A	1	7	Beatrice: 「NO sex... Nnngh, I already told you...」	s18a	0117
PV01_1201_A	1	8	Bohgan: 「Well then, Commodore, let me enjoy myself to my heart’s desire  with these voluptuous boobs of yours, which are enough to drive any  man crazy.」	s18a	0118
PV01_1201_A	1	9	Beatrice: 「Ukuuuh... Hih... Seriously, the animal that is a man...」	s18a	0119
PV01_1201_A	1	10	Beatrice’s cheeks were already flushing as she complained.	s18a	0120
PV01_1201_A	1	11	Small drops of sweat adorned her sexy and beautiful face.	s18a	0121
PV01_1201_A	1	12	It was proof of the fact that her body was already getting hot  inside.	s18a	0122
PV01_1201_A	1	13	Beatrice: 「Uh... Kuuuh... Fuh... Ugh...」	s18a	0123
PV01_1201_A	1	14	She was desperately trying to hide her wild breathing.	s18a	0124
PV01_1201_A	1	15	Bohgan: (Kukuku... The Empress is feeling it nicely. I will make your true  self completely expose your shameful figure to me!)	s18a	0125
PV01_1201_A	1	16	This is exactly what I had wanted from Beatrice.	s18a	0126
PV01_1201_A	1	17	The opportunity to caress these woman’s breasts as I pleased.	s18a	0127
PV01_1201_A	1	18	In return, I was to keep the fact, that her clitoris had been  furnished with a ring, a secret and cooperate with her in its  removal.	s18a	0128
PV01_1201_A	1	19	Bohgan: 「These boobs of yours are irresistible. They are so soft even  though I have grabbed them from above your attire.」	s18a	0129
PV01_1201_A	1	20	Beatrice: 「Kuguh... Shut your trap...! Ngh... Don’t humiliate me!」	s18a	0130
PV01_1201_A	1	21	Bohgan: 「I am not humiliating you. I honestly meant that. This is the  reason why I can’t get over you. I have been consumed by the  excitement of our time together.」	s18a	0131
PV01_1201_A	1	22	Beatrice: 「Ahaaa... Kuuuh... Just forget what happened that time...!」	s18a	0132
PV01_1201_A	1	23	Bohgan: 「It is impossible. It would be the same for you if you were in my  position. I can’t help but recall that time vividly when I caressed  your voluptuous boobs like this.」	s18a	0133
PV01_1201_A	1	24	Beatrice: 「D-Don’t say that... Kuh...」	s18a	0134
PV01_1201_A	1	25	Bohgan: 「You might say that that one-night stand was a mistake, however,  for me it was a dream-like night. A man and woman, entwined together  like beasts... It was so passionate.」	s18a	0135
PV01_1201_A	1	26	Beatrice: 「Ahiii... Stop it...」	s18a	0136
PV01_1201_A	1	27	I placed my hands under her armpits and grabbed her boobs from  the sides, which were sticking out towards me lewdly, after which  I began to squash them together, causing her meaty balloons to get  crushed by each other.	s18a	0137
PV01_1201_A	1	28	Gunyuriii, Gunyuriii――	s18a	0138
PV01_1201_A	1	29	Beatrice: 「Kufuuuh...!? Uhuuu... Ungh...」	s18a	0139
PV01_1201_A	1	30	The female Commodore frowned while trying to endure it and suppressed  her voice, as if she was trying to stifle it completely.	s18a	0140
PV01_1201_A	1	31	Her body had conformed itself to the remodelling that had been done  on her, which was giving her so much pleasure that an average woman  would have orgasmed instantly by now.	s18a	0141
PV01_1201_A	1	32	On noticing that I had realized that, she quickly averted her gaze  from mine.	s18a	0142
PV01_1201_A	1	33	Bohgan: 「Doesn’t it feel good, Commodore?」	s18a	0143
PV01_1201_A	1	34	Beatrice: 「Fuh... What are you talking about...? Kuh... Me? And feeling  good...?」	s18a	0144
PV01_1201_A	1	35	Bohgan: 「Aren’t you feeling it?」	s18a	0145
PV01_1201_A	1	36	Beatrice: 「Fuh... What a stupid question...!」	s18a	0146
PV01_1201_A	1	37	Bohgan: 「That is disappointing. That night you were experiencing pleasure  with my touch, like a virginal girl.」	s18a	0147
PV01_1201_A	1	38	Beatrice: 「Sh-Shut your mouth already...! Don’t bring it up again and  again!」	s18a	0148
PV01_1201_A	1	39	The Empress’s face blushed a deep scarlet, exactly like a virginal  girl.	s18a	0149
PV01_1201_A	1	40	All I wanted was to erase the strong sense of virtue of this woman  and replace it with the fake memories, which I had prepared just for  her.	s18a	0150
PV01_1201_A	2	1	And so, in order to humiliate her even more I continued caressing  her.	s18a	0151
PV01_1201_A	2	2	Bohgan: (I will continue to torment your mind, while you still retain your  consciousness!)	s18a	0152
PV01_1201_A	2	3	Bohgan: 「You may be calm since you aren’t feeling it, Commodore. However,  I am so aroused that I can't be like that.」	s18a	0153
PV01_1201_A	2	4	Beatrice: 「Wha...!? Kuh, Stop it...」	s18a	0154
PV01_1201_A	2	5	I ran my hand over the buttons of her military attire while  unbuttoning them one by one.	s18a	0155
PV01_1201_A	2	6	And──	s18a	0156
PV01_1201_A	2	7	Beatrice: 「Uhiii...!?」	s18a	0157
PV01_1201_A	2	8	Her boobs swayed heavily on being released from the confines of her  tight attire before coming to a halt.	s18a	0158
PV01_1201_A	2	9	Even though she was wearing her brassiere, it was clear to see  that they were extremely taut and elastic in nature and alluringly  soft.	s18a	0159
PV01_1201_A	2	10	Bohgan: (I can’t believe that these beauties provided milk for that bloody  impertinent little brat of a daughter of yours, Kukukuku)	s18a	0160
PV01_1201_A	2	11	An alluring scent typical of a woman, mingled with the stench of her  sweat, wafted out from her exposed breasts, which was unlike that of  any soldier’s.	s18a	0161
PV01_1201_A	2	12	Bohgan: 「Ooooh! This scent of yours is so arousing! Not just your body,  even your scent is fascinating me!」	s18a	0162
PV01_1201_A	2	13	Beatrice: 「Y-You bastard!? Going so far as to take in... my scent! You  pervert!」	s18a	0163
PV01_1201_A	2	14	Her breasts became even hotter and got dyed with a lewd rosy-pink  colour.	s18a	0164
PV01_1201_A	2	15	In addition to that, the scent of a sultry bitch-in-heat seducing  a man began emanating from her.	s18a	0165
PV01_1201_A	2	16	Bohgan: 「This rich scent of yours is what did me in.」	s18a	0166
PV01_1201_A	2	17	Beatrice: 「Uhiii... Don’t... say that...」	s18a	0167
PV01_1201_A	2	18	Bohgan: 「It looks to me like the Commodore is getting excited every time  I say that.」	s18a	0168
PV01_1201_A	2	19	Beatrice: 「How ridiculous! I think... you have started hallucinating things...  due to your extreme arousal...」	s18a	0169
PV01_1201_A	2	20	Bohgan: 「There is no way I can stop my arousal now. Especially after seeing  the Commodore in her brassiere like this!」	s18a	0170
PV01_1201_A	2	21	I held out both my hands out towards her.	s18a	0171
PV01_1201_A	2	22	Beatrice: 「Kuh!? W-Wait...」	s18a	0172
PV01_1201_A	2	23	Bohgan: 「It is such a cute brassiere with a number of ribbons hanging  out, however, it is see-through in some places as well giving you  a extremely sultry appearance.」	s18a	0173
PV01_1201_A	2	24	Beatrice: 「W-What...!?」	s18a	0174
PV01_1201_A	2	25	Bohgan: 「Despite having a formidable reputation throughout the universe,  you still wear such cute brassieres. This gap is really turning me  on!」	s18a	0175
PV01_1201_A	2	26	Beatrice: 「You bastard! You better control your mouth or... Ngh, Aaaah!?」	s18a	0176
PV01_1201_A	2	27	Acting as if I had gotten completely worked up, I grabbed a tight  hold of a big chunk of Beatrice’s lewd boobs, which were covered  up with her brassiere.	s18a	0177
PV01_1201_A	2	28	Bohgan: 「Aaaah... They are so amazingly soft...! Shall I squash them even  harder?」	s18a	0178
PV01_1201_A	2	29	Beatrice: 「H-Harder...!? Kuh... I won’t allow...!」	s18a	0179
PV01_1201_A	2	30	Bohgan: 「But, didn’t you say that I could enjoy myself with your boobs as  much as I wanted?」	s18a	0180
PV01_1201_A	2	31	Beatrice: 「Kuhihi!? Damn you... You horny man...!」	s18a	0181
PV01_1201_A	2	32	Bohgan: 「I will take that as a yes.」	s18a	0182
PV01_1201_A	2	33	I drove my fingers into her soft boobs and dug them into her from  over her brasserie.	s18a	0183
PV01_1201_A	2	34	Beatrice: 「Guhuuu...!?」	s18a	0184
PV01_1201_A	2	35	The Empress shut her eyes tightly and bit down on her lips.	s18a	0185
PV01_1201_A	2	36	She wasn’t in pain.	s18a	0186
PV01_1201_A	2	37	Even though she was no ordinary woman, her ripe body had been  remodelled──	s18a	0187
PV01_1201_A	2	38	Beatrice: 「Kuhiii!? Uhiii... Uhu, Uhuuun?」	s18a	0188
PV01_1201_A	2	39	Her brasserie started giving off scraping sounds as I strongly  pushed my fingers into her, as if it was crying out.	s18a	0189
PV01_1201_A	2	40	Beatrice began swaying her body back and forth while trying to  endure that stimulation, which was so rough that it would have  been extremely painful under normal circumstances.	s18a	0190
PV01_1201_A	3	1	However, the Empress was feeling it, as if she was being lovingly  caressed by her lover.	s18a	0191
PV01_1201_A	3	2	Bohgan: 「Are you still not feeling good?」	s18a	0192
PV01_1201_A	3	3	Beatrice: 「W-What a stupid question... Uuuuh, I already told you! How  many more times do you wish to hear it...? Or do you simply  want to humiliate me?」	s18a	0193
PV01_1201_A	3	4	Bohgan: 「No. That isn’t my intention at all.」	s18a	0194
PV01_1201_A	3	5	Beatrice: 「If you do humiliate me... Ahhhh, I will break these arms of  yours...!」	s18a	0195
PV01_1201_A	3	6	Her body was trembling uncontrollably due to the pleasure, as she  threatened me with those disdainful words.	s18a	0196
PV01_1201_A	3	7	On top of that, the sweat oozing out of her massive boobs increased  and those large beads of sweat trickled down into the deep chasm of  her cleavage.	s18a	0197
PV01_1201_A	3	8	It was clear to see that she was taking on a frustrated attitude  simply because she didn’t want to accept the fact that she was  experiencing pleasure from this act.	s18a	0198
PV01_1201_A	3	9	Bohgan: 「Excuse me, I shouldn’t have expected the Commodore to feel it so  much. Only a whore could feel it because of this.」	s18a	0199
PV01_1201_A	3	10	Beatrice: 「Whaaa!? A-A whore!?」	s18a	0200
PV01_1201_A	3	11	Beatrice threw a murderous gaze towards me after unconsciously  raising a scream, as if she had lost all her composure.	s18a	0201
PV01_1201_A	3	12	Bohgan: (Kukuku... Did you think that I accused you of being a whore?)	s18a	0202
PV01_1201_A	3	13	It was proof of the fact that she was feeling it due to the movement  of my hands.	s18a	0203
PV01_1201_A	3	14	Bohgan: 「Is something wrong?」	s18a	0204
PV01_1201_A	3	15	Beatrice: 「N-No... Such words though... Ugh... Don’t use them with me...」	s18a	0205
PV01_1201_A	3	16	Her voice was trembling so much that her words simply petered out.	s18a	0206
PV01_1201_A	3	17	The Empress was lusting to be engulfed in more pleasure like a  bitch-in-heat, however, she had become upset at being unable to  hide her intentions.	s18a	0207
PV01_1201_A	3	18	Bohgan: (However, there is still a lot more to come, Beatrice. I am going to  torment you to my heart’s desire, starting now.)	s18a	0208
PV01_1201_A	3	19	Bohgan: 「Since the Commodore isn’t feeling it, does that mean that my  arousal isn’t being transmitted onto you? I can’t allow that...  Now, if you will excuse me!」	s18a	0209
PV01_1201_A	3	20	Beatrice: 「Uuuuh!? Are you going to do it even more!? Uaaah, Stop! Are you  taking my brassiere off without my consent... Kuuuh!?」	s18a	0210
PV01_1201_A	3	21	I stripped her brasserie off.	s18a	0211
PV01_1201_A	3	22	Beatrice: 「Ahaaa...!?」	s18a	0212
PV01_1201_A	3	23	The Empress exposed her breasts to me while conscious.	s18a	0213
PV01_1201_A	3	24	They shook heavily after bursting out of the confines of her  brasserie, due to their elasticity.	s18a	0214
PV01_1201_A	3	25	Bohgan: 「Ooooh! The Commodore’s boobs are just as wonderful as I  remember!」	s18a	0215
PV01_1201_A	3	26	Beatrice: 「Kuh... Hiii!? A-Are you... satisfied yet...?」	s18a	0216
PV01_1201_A	3	27	Bohgan: 「No way! I will never again get an opportunity to gaze at the  voluptuous boobs of the female Commodore, whose mere name strikes  fear into everyone’s hearts. Please, let me observe them for a  while longer.」	s18a	0217
PV01_1201_A	3	28	Bohgan: 「They seem to be quite soft but at the same time they are so  firm that they jiggle quite nicely, giving them a firm and youthful  look.」	s18a	0218
PV01_1201_A	3	29	Bohgan: 「Furthermore, they aren’t sagging down even a bit. It is hard to  believe that the Commodore is a mother.」	s18a	0219
PV01_1201_A	3	30	Beatrice: 「You bastard... Are you trying to compliment me? Your cocky mouth...  is going to be the end of you.」	s18a	0220
PV01_1201_A	3	31	Beatrice tried to intimidate me.	s18a	0221
PV01_1201_A	3	32	However, it just came off as farcical due to the way her boobs,  which had completely dyed in a lewd pink colour, were swaying  heavily.	s18a	0222
PV01_1201_A	3	33	On top of that, her voice was tinged with heat and even more beads  of sweat had risen up on her exposed skin, giving her the look of a  mere bitch-in-heat.	s18a	0223
PV01_1201_A	3	34	Bohgan: 「Forgive my impoliteness. However, what I just said wasn’t meant  as an insult. After all, any man is bound to get mesmerized by your  beautiful face and body.」	s18a	0224
PV01_1201_A	3	35	Beatrice: 「Nhaaa, Nnngh... C-Cut it out. Is this the manner in which... one  speaks to a married woman?」	s18a	0225
PV01_1201_A	3	36	Bohgan: 「But you were the one who offered up your body for me, a man who  isn’t even your husband.」	s18a	0226
PV01_1201_A	3	37	Beatrice: 「Kuuuh!? T-That was a mistake! You are so stubborn! Will you use  your mouth appropriately from now on!?」	s18a	0227
PV01_1201_A	3	38	Bohgan: 「And what about now? You are once again exposing your alluring  skin to a man who isn’t your husband, aren’t you?」	s18a	0228
PV01_1201_A	3	39	Beatrice: 「Nguuuh...!?」	s18a	0229
PV01_1201_A	3	40	Bohgan: 「The Commodore’s boobs have become so taut and even the nipples  have pushed out of the areolae and are supremely erect... All this  in front of man who isn’t your beloved husband.」	s18a	0230
PV01_1201_A	4	1	Beatrice: 「... You better watch it. If you continue this, I will terminate  our business deal.」	s18a	0231
PV01_1201_A	4	2	Her words weren’t simply meant as a threat to our deal, but also  as a serious warning of her murderous intent.	s18a	0232
PV01_1201_A	4	3	However, the fact that she had become so serious all of a sudden  was proof that she had been well and truly cornered.	s18a	0233
PV01_1201_A	4	4	This situation, in which I was able to dominate the Supreme  Commander of the Kushan Armed Forces was getting me extremely  aroused.	s18a	0234
PV01_1201_A	4	5	Bohgan: 「Excuse me. I have no intention of letting our business deal  collapse.」	s18a	0235
PV01_1201_A	4	6	Bohgan: 「However, there is no way I can suppress my arousal! I will enjoy  myself as much as is possible without letting it collapse!」	s18a	0236
PV01_1201_A	4	7	I reached out my hands to the lewdly thrust out boobs of the Empress  and──	s18a	0237
PV01_1201_A	4	8	Bohgan: 「Chyubaaa! Chyuchyuuuuuuu!」	s18a	0238
PV01_1201_A	4	9	I sucked one of the Empress’s supremely erect nipple into my mouth,  which was jutting out of her areolae and bit down on it.	s18a	0239
PV01_1201_A	4	10	Beatrice: 「Nhaaa!!? Uhaaa!? Uguh, Kuh! Uuuuh!?」	s18a	0240
PV01_1201_A	4	11	Beatrice let out a frustrated voice.	s18a	0241
PV01_1201_A	4	12	She somehow managed to clench her teeth in order to suppress it,  despite her trembling jaw.	s18a	0242
PV01_1201_A	4	13	However, due to the pleasant feelings, her muffled moans still  continued to leak out of her clenched teeth regardless and her  body trembled intermittently between them.	s18a	0243
PV01_1201_A	4	14	Beatrice: 「D-Doing such a thing here!? Fuh... Uguh, The animal... that is  a man, Kufuuuh... No matter how long passes, you will always be  juvenile...」	s18a	0244
PV01_1201_A	4	15	Bohgan: 「Juvenile, huh? Well, that is fine I guess. As long as I can  continue sucking on your boobs like this.」	s18a	0245
PV01_1201_A	4	16	Bohgan: (I am going to drive you insane, while you are still conscious of  your true self, by humiliating you like this!)	s18a	0246
PV01_1201_A	4	17	Bohgan: 「Chyujuuu! Jyujujujuuu!」	s18a	0247
PV01_1201_A	4	18	Beatrice: 「Kuaaah!? Uh!? Uuuuh! Don’t suck...!」	s18a	0248
PV01_1201_A	4	19	Beatrice’s remodelling had progressed well.	s18a	0249
PV01_1201_A	4	20	Even though a man other than her husband was sucking on her boobs,  she had become unable to escape from that hellish pleasure.	s18a	0250
PV01_1201_A	4	21	However, she earned my grudging respect since she was managing to  endure that pleasure, which would have driven an average woman to  an explosive orgasm by now.	s18a	0251
PV01_1201_A	4	22	Bohgan: (This is exactly why it is worth making you fall!)	s18a	0252
PV01_1201_A	4	23	Beatrice: 「Uhiii!? Guh, Haaa...! Kuh... Such hard sucking... Do you crave  your mommy’s boobs despite being at such an age...!?」	s18a	0253
PV01_1201_A	4	24	Bohgan: 「Any man would become like this when faced with voluptuous boobs  such as these. Also, since my cock has become supremely erect, I  would argue that these boobs of yours are a bit too erotic to be  like my Mommy’s.」	s18a	0254
PV01_1201_A	4	25	Beatrice: 「Gufuuuh...!? S-Sex isn’t allowed...!」	s18a	0255
PV01_1201_A	4	26	Bohgan: 「I know that very well. However, these boobs of yours are mine for  now! Berobero, Jyuccchhhyuuuuu!」	s18a	0256
PV01_1201_A	4	27	Beatrice: 「Nnnnngh!!? Sucking, with your tongue...!? Fuguuunnn!?」	s18a	0257
PV01_1201_A	4	28	I wagged my tongue over her scrumptious nipple, which was standing  erect inside my mouth, and plastered it with my saliva before sucking  it all up again.	s18a	0258
PV01_1201_A	4	29	The Empress ground her teeth hard and tried to conceal her lewd  feelings desperately.	s18a	0259
PV01_1201_A	4	30	However, her body was trembling tremendously because of the sexual  pleasure that she was being assaulted with, and not just her face,  but even the skin of her body flushed in humiliation.	s18a	0260
PV01_1201_A	4	31	Bohgan: 「This is amazing. The Commodore’s nipples are so delicious!」	s18a	0261
PV01_1201_A	4	32	While continuing the act of lewdly licking and slurping on her  nipple all over, I sank my hand into her other boob and started  rubbing her as yet free nipple with my fingers.	s18a	0262
PV01_1201_A	4	33	Beatrice: 「Shuddup... Kufuaaah!!? Uhaaa...!? Kuuuuh!? How long... are you  going to continue dish...!?」	s18a	0263
PV01_1201_A	4	34	Bohgan: 「I am not done yet. It is a once in a life opportunity for me to  suck on the nipples of an enchantress like you. More... I want to  do it even more!」	s18a	0264
PV01_1201_A	4	35	I grabbed a tight hold on both of her boobs and yanked them towards  each other.	s18a	0265
PV01_1201_A	4	36	Beatrice: 「W-What are you...? Stop──」	s18a	0266
PV01_1201_A	4	37	Bohgan: 「How about both of them together!? Chyubabababaaa!!」	s18a	0267
PV01_1201_A	4	38	I brought her boobs together as if I was crushing her cleavage and  sucked in both of her nipples at the same time.	s18a	0268
PV01_1201_A	4	39	Beatrice: 「Ahuuu!!? Kah, Haaa!? Haaaaaaa!!?」	s18a	0269
PV01_1201_A	4	40	And finally, the Empress let out her sweet voice.	s18a	0270
PV01_1201_A	5	1	Her eyes became transfixed on my lips, as I sucked on her nipples,  and she became unable to avert her gaze as she continued to stare  at me.	s18a	0271
PV01_1201_A	5	2	Bohgan: 「These nipples seem to be stretching even more, even though they  are already so erect! Jyuzuzuuuuu!!」	s18a	0272
PV01_1201_A	5	3	Beatrice: 「Kuaaahahaaa!!? T-They are really stretchiiing, Uhaaa!? Don’t...  do both of them togetheeer...!」	s18a	0273
PV01_1201_A	5	4	Bohgan: 「I can’t stop myself sucking on the Commodore’s nipples, which  have become erect entirely like cocks! Chyuuu～paaah!」	s18a	0274
PV01_1201_A	5	5	Beatrice: 「Uuuunhaaa!!?」	s18a	0275
PV01_1201_A	5	6	I sucked on her fleshy tips, which had become completely wet with  my slimy drool, by letting them slip in and out of my mouth, as if  I was suckling on her boobs.	s18a	0276
PV01_1201_A	5	7	Because of that, the Empress not only started crying out in a lovely  voice but also began squirming her body lewdly in front of me.	s18a	0277
PV01_1201_A	5	8	Bohgan: (Kukukuku! Even your husband will never be able to forgive you for  having such an obscene body, entirely like a whore’s from rundown  districts!)	s18a	0278
PV01_1201_A	5	9	Beatrice: 「Gaaah, Haaa! Uaaah!? A-Are you happy now!? Enough already...!」	s18a	0279
PV01_1201_A	5	10	It looked like her body had been driven into a corner and, while  wondering if she had reached her own limit, she said that in a  trembling voice.	s18a	0280
PV01_1201_A	5	11	She also clasped her fist tightly, in order to make her body endure  it in one way or another.	s18a	0281
PV01_1201_A	5	12	Bohgan: 「A while longer! Just a while longer with these delicious nipples  of yours! Jyujyuuu!」	s18a	0282
PV01_1201_A	5	13	Beatrice: 「Fuaaah!!? Right there again...!?」	s18a	0283
PV01_1201_A	5	14	Bohgan: 「Ooooh, Your nipples taste sweet! Right, you are a mother after all.  You raised your little girl with these. It looks like your maternal  instincts have been awakened and, as a result, the ingredients of  your mother’s milk are oozing out.」	s18a	0284
PV01_1201_A	5	15	Beatrice: 「R-Ridiculous...!? Fuaaah!? Kuh, Uuuun, This is... so good! Don’t  suck that hard... Nhaaa!?」	s18a	0285
PV01_1201_A	5	16	Bohgan: 「I can’t let go of these nipples. The more I do this, the more  delicious they become! Jyupupuuu! Jyubababaaa!」	s18a	0286
PV01_1201_A	5	17	Beatrice: 「Kuhiii!? Ugh, Ahahaaa!!?」	s18a	0287
PV01_1201_A	5	18	The Commodore female body stiffened up and began to convulse  uncontrollably.	s18a	0288
PV01_1201_A	5	19	And just like that, she became unable to endure the tremendous  pleasure which had been welling up inside her.	s18a	0289
PV01_1201_A	5	20	Bohgan: (You seem to be diligently trying to endure this, however, this is  as far as you go. Now while you are still conscious, I am going to  force you to cum shamelessly in front of me!)	s18a	0290
PV01_1201_A	5	21	Beatrice: 「Hah, Ughiii!? Uaaah! H-Hey! E-End it already...! The terms of our  business deal... have now been fulfilled!」	s18a	0291
PV01_1201_A	5	22	Bohgan: 「Jyuuu～paaa! Even though I really don’t want to part with these  sensual beauties, I will since you are proposing it, but... after  doing one last thing.」	s18a	0292
PV01_1201_A	5	23	Beatrice: 「G-Good...! Fuuuh, Fuuuh... Well then... let them go...」	s18a	0293
PV01_1201_A	5	24	Bohgan: 「Yes. Just one last thing!」	s18a	0294
PV01_1201_A	5	25	Bohgan: 「Kuuuh!」	s18a	0295
PV01_1201_A	5	26	I pierced my front teeth hard into her erect and stretched out  nipples.	s18a	0296
PV01_1201_A	5	27	Beatrice: 「Nnn～～～～～～～～～～gh!!!!!???」	s18a	0297
PV01_1201_A	5	28	Beatrice’s voice got stuck in her throat.	s18a	0298
PV01_1201_A	5	29	And immediately, her legs began to wobble uncontrollably.	s18a	0299
PV01_1201_A	5	30	The surprise assault amidst my caressing had led her all the way  to an orgasm.	s18a	0300
PV01_1201_A	5	31	Beatrice: 「Kihiii... You bastaaard... D-Didn’d y-you shay dat you were  ending id...!?」	s18a	0301
PV01_1201_A	5	32	Bohgan: 「Yes, but only after this last thing, Koririri!!」	s18a	0302
PV01_1201_A	5	33	Beatrice: 「Fuhuuu!!? Nnnnnnh!!? Kuuu──────────uh!!?」	s18a	0303
PV01_1201_A	5	34	I bit down so hard on her stiff nipples, that both my upper and  lower front teeth started aching.	s18a	0304
PV01_1201_A	5	35	As a result of which the Empress’s teeth began chattering, which  she had been grinding to stop her voice from leaking out.	s18a	0305
PV01_1201_A	5	36	Tears appeared in the corners of her eyes and she began drooling  lewdly from the edges of her lips.	s18a	0306
PV01_1201_A	5	37	Bohgan: (Your orgasm is clear to see, you bloody woman! What a feeling  to indulge in this orgasmic face of yours while you are still  conscious!)	s18a	0307
PV01_1201_A	5	38	Beatrice: 「Kuhuuunnn!!? D-D-Don’d b-bite... Uhiii, Sh-Shtop id...!」	s18a	0308
PV01_1201_A	5	39	Bohgan: 「Huh? What was that?」	s18a	0309
PV01_1201_A	5	40	I looked up at the aroused Empress and asked her, while gnawing on  her luscious and erect nipples, causing my upper and lower teeth to  grind.	s18a	0310
PV01_1201_A	6	1	Beatrice: 「Ughuuuuuuunnnnn!!!!!??? Don’d talk... Gufuh, while biting!  Uhuuun!!?」	s18a	0311
PV01_1201_A	6	2	The female Commodore was showing off her nipple-orgasm, in  accordance with the tremendous pleasure that she was being  assaulted with.	s18a	0312
PV01_1201_A	6	3	The Empress’s face was no longer visible. In its place was the  face of a bitch-in-heat, who had thrown herself at the mercy of  her orgasm and cocked her eyes to the centre.	s18a	0313
PV01_1201_A	6	4	Beatrice: 「Kuwaaah!? Uh, Ngh, Nnnnh... Are you happy...!? Uuuun!? Led me  go already...!」	s18a	0314
PV01_1201_A	6	5	Bohgan: 「... Fuuuh, Looks like I have no choice.」	s18a	0315
PV01_1201_A	6	6	I complied to her request this time.	s18a	0316
PV01_1201_A	6	7	And released both her boobs and her nipples from my grasp.	s18a	0317
PV01_1201_A	6	8	Beatrice: 「Uhuuu, Kaaah!!? Hah, Hah, Hah...! Auuuh, Kufuuuh...!」	s18a	0318
PV01_1201_A	6	9	Beatrice’s excited nipples were throbbing even more than before,  causing her to let out long and ragged breaths.	s18a	0319
PV01_1201_A	6	10	She left her loose mouth open and her eyes unfocused, as she stared  off into the distance.	s18a	0320
PV01_1201_A	6	11	The Empress was still submerged in the afterglow of her unbearable  orgasm.	s18a	0321
PV01_1201_A	6	12	Beatrice: 「Wid dish... Aaah, our bushinessh deal... ish now in effect...!」	s18a	0322
PV01_1201_A	6	13	Bohgan: 「... Business deal? Ah, that is correct. I completely forgot about  that, while looking at you completely engulfed in pleasure.」	s18a	0323
PV01_1201_A	6	14	Beatrice: 「Uheee...!? W-Who would ged engulfed in pleashure, Ukuh...  Daaah!?」	s18a	0324
PV01_1201_A	6	15	Bohgan: 「I guess not, however your nipples are harder now than they were  before we started and look entirely like hard erect cocks, due to  manner in which they are twitching.」	s18a	0325
PV01_1201_A	6	16	Beatrice: 「Daaah!? Sh-Shut up...! Ah, Haaa... That is all your fault...!  Ahaaa... Your bite-marks are still there...!?」	s18a	0326
PV01_1201_A	6	17	Just as she said, my bite-marks had been imprinted on her nipples.  However, instead of loathing the sight of that, she merely gazed  at her own nipples ecstatically.	s18a	0327
PV01_1201_A	6	18	Looking at her body twitch intermittently, it seemed like she was in  the midst of the afterglow of her orgasm.	s18a	0328
PV01_1201_A	6	19	Bohgan: 「Could it be that you are indulging in the orgasm you experienced  just now?」	s18a	0329
PV01_1201_A	6	20	Beatrice: 「O-O-Orgasm!? N-No way! Guh, I, absolutely..., Uguuuh, didn’t hit  it!」	s18a	0330
PV01_1201_A	6	21	She desperately protested against my allegations immediately.	s18a	0331
PV01_1201_A	6	22	She was still being dictated by the pleasure which is why she  didn’t realize it, however, the fact that she was so desperate  in her attempt to hide it from me was proof enough that she had  indeed orgasmed.	s18a	0332
PV01_1201_A	6	23	I was extremely amused at the way the as yet conscious Empress was  being toyed with by the pleasure.	s18a	0333
PV01_1201_A	6	24	Bohgan: 「Well, that’s good. After all, a woman who relishes being caressed  by a man, who she doesn’t even love, and orgasms is nothing but a  whore.」	s18a	0334
PV01_1201_A	6	25	Beatrice: 「Kuuuh!!? Guuuh! Uh, Fuuuh, Fuuuh... Is that so...? Then, don’t  ask... needless questions.」	s18a	0335
PV01_1201_A	6	26	She glared at me.	s18a	0336
PV01_1201_A	6	27	However, those eyes of hers were still dyed in pleasure.	s18a	0337
PV01_1201_A	6	28	Beatrice: 「I am going to leave... now.」	s18a	0338
PV01_1201_A	6	29	She was trying to endure the pleasure while tidying up her attire,  in order to prevent me from noticing her trembling legs.	s18a	0339
PV01_1201_A	6	30	After which, she immediately took her leave.	s18a	0340
PV01_1201_A	6	31	Bohgan: 「Your Excellency.」	s18a	0341
PV01_1201_A	6	32	Beatrice: 「W-What...?」	s18a	0342
PV01_1201_A	6	33	Bohgan: 「Watch your step.」	s18a	0343
PV01_1201_A	6	34	Beatrice: 「I knooow...!」	s18a	0344
PV01_1201_A	6	35	Beatrice’s face was still flushed, as she staggered out on her  wobbly legs.	s18a	0345
PV01_1201_A	6	36	Bohgan: 「Your Excellency.」	s18a	0346
PV01_1201_A	6	37	Beatrice: 「W-What is it now!?」	s18a	0347
PV01_1201_A	6	38	Bohgan: 「You have forgotten your mantle.」	s18a	0348
PV01_1201_A	6	39	Beatrice: 「Kuh!」	s18a	0349
PV01_1201_A	6	40	Beatrice snatched her mantle that I was holding out to her, and  took off immediately in order to hide herself.	s18a	0350
PV01_1201_A	7	1	Bohgan: 「Kukuku! Having a physical relationship with both the mother and  the daughter is quite enjoyable. I never thought that watching the  dishevelled figures of both these women, while they are conscious  of themselves, would be this enjoyable!」	s18a	0351
PV01_1201_A	7	2	I had forced Kila to behave similarly during the time of our  breakfast.	s18a	0352
PV01_1201_A	7	3	Bohgan: 「There is a lot more of this to come, you bloody women!」	s18a	0353
PV01_1201_A	7	4	I stifled by laughter, while rubbing my right arm.	s18a	0354
PV01_1201_A	7	5	SALTAR: S019A
PV01_1201_A	7	6	SALTAR: S019A
