PV01_2601_A	1	1	The mother and daughter had been made to orgasm until they had gone  insane and their pride had been ripped to shreds so terribly that  they had become literal pig-sluts, as they continued feel it with  their uncouth bodies.	s29a	0642
PV01_2601_A	1	2	Beatrice: 「Urgh, Uhuuu... Uuuuh... Ahuuu... Ahiii...!? Fuhihiii!」	s29a	0643
PV01_2601_A	1	3	Kila: 「Haaa, Heh... Heh... Eguuuh... Ah... Nhiii!? Nheheee...」	s29a	0644
PV01_2601_A	1	4	Both the mother and the daughter, who had been placed beside each  other in front of the line, turned their melted gazes on me.	s29a	0645
PV01_2601_A	1	5	Their uncouth figures were being held from behind by brawny soldiers,  who had spread their legs wide open.	s29a	0646
PV01_2601_A	1	6	Their cunts, which had been thrust into mercilessly, had been left  gaping wide open and their pussy-meat was convulsing uncontrollably,  as they continued to indulge in those feelings.	s29a	0647
PV01_2601_A	1	7	Their wombs had been filled up with such a large amount of semen,  that it was still spurting out of their cervixes with sputtering  sounds.	s29a	0648
PV01_2601_A	1	8	Kila: 「Kuhiii!? Uhaaa... Aaah... Ahuhuuu...」	s29a	0649
PV01_2601_A	1	9	Copious amounts of frothy semen was gushing out of their slackened  assholes as well.	s29a	0650
PV01_2601_A	1	10	The semen, which was streaming out of both their meat-holes, had  accumulated on the floor――	s29a	0651
PV01_2601_A	1	11	Jyorororooo, Jyororororororororooo!	s29a	0652
PV01_2601_A	1	12	A large amount of urine had blended into that pool on the floor, as  they continued to leak their urine out uncontrollably.	s29a	0653
PV01_2601_A	1	13	Beatrice: 「Nguuuh... Uhuuu... Kuuuh...」	s29a	0654
PV01_2601_A	1	14	Beatrice glared at me with her melted face, as drool dribbled out of  her mouth and mucous ran down her nostrils.	s29a	0655
PV01_2601_A	1	15	Bohgan: 「Ohooo! Are you still able to make such a face? You are truly the  Empress, Beatrice.」	s29a	0656
PV01_2601_A	1	16	Even though she had been raped throughout the night, she still had  some pride as the Empress left on her face.	s29a	0657
PV01_2601_A	1	17	However, the aroused and tense bodies, that both the women were  exposing in front of me――	s29a	0658
PV01_2601_A	1	18	Were no different to those of pig-sluts.	s29a	0659
PV01_2601_A	1	19	Their sweat-drenched bodies were trembling uncontrollably and their  nipples were standing erect to their very limits, as if they were  still orgasming intermittently.	s29a	0660
PV01_2601_A	1	20	Kila: 「Hehe!? Aaah... Hahiii... Hyaaa... Hih!? Hiii... Moddeeer... I am...  going to kill dish guy... for certain...」	s29a	0661
PV01_2601_A	1	21	Beatrice: 「Kila... Do you think... dat your modder... will led you handle  her bushinessh...? Fuhiii... I won’d be able to ged my peasche...  unlessh I am the one who killsh him...」	s29a	0662
PV01_2601_A	1	22	Bohgan: 「Kukuku... How can you still say such things? You are sore losers  who don’t even know when to give up. You can no longer even hope to  touch me without my permission.」	s29a	0663
PV01_2601_A	1	23	Bohgan: 「You know that from your own actions already, don’t you?」	s29a	0664
PV01_2601_A	1	24	They could no longer move their bodies with their own will.	s29a	0665
PV01_2601_A	1	25	They had been made to learn that fact, while being raped throughout  the night.	s29a	0666
PV01_2601_A	1	26	Bohgan: 「How many times did you cum while being raped throughout the night?  Hmmm? How many times did you orgasm?」	s29a	0667
PV01_2601_A	1	27	Numerical counters had been scrawled on the semen-smeared bodies of  both the women.	s29a	0668
PV01_2601_A	1	28	The figure of 91 had been etched onto Beatrice’s plump thighs――	s29a	0669
PV01_2601_A	1	29	And the figure of 87 had been etched onto Kila’s pretty face and  thighs.	s29a	0670
PV01_2601_A	1	30	Bohgan: 「So... You were made to cum these many times, huh? Did you enjoy  yourself thoroughly?」	s29a	0671
PV01_2601_A	1	31	All the men looked down at the faces of the two women, who had gone  completely flaccid, and sneered at them.	s29a	0672
PV01_2601_A	1	32	Kila: 「Uhuuu... Hah, Hah... Are... Are you done... enjoying yourselves  already...? You are all really pathetic men, aren’t you...?」	s29a	0673
PV01_2601_A	1	33	Beatrice: 「Uhuuun... Nfuh... That’s right... You are all just trash, who  could do nothing but ejaculate prematurely... I-I was really bored  throughout...」	s29a	0674
PV01_2601_A	1	34	They hadn’t submitted yet.	s29a	0675
PV01_2601_A	1	35	Both, the mother and her daughter, put their breathing in order and  said that pretentiously, in order to show that to me.	s29a	0676
PV01_2601_A	1	36	Bohgan: 「Hahaha! The Empress and the Grim Reaper, who had engulfed the  universe with their terror, do possess shocking tenacity, don’t  they?」	s29a	0677
PV01_2601_A	1	37	I burst into laughter and praised both the women.	s29a	0678
PV01_2601_A	1	38	However, this was as far as I was willing to toy with them.	s29a	0679
PV01_2601_A	1	39	I reverted back to my real face and looked down at the mother and  her daughter coldly.	s29a	0680
PV01_2601_A	1	40	Bohgan: 「I did want to enjoy you a lot more. However, this is the end.」	s29a	0681
PV01_2601_A	2	1	Bohgan: 「Beatrice Kushan, Kila Kushan. As I mentioned before, I will be  erasing your personalities now.」	s29a	0682
PV01_2601_A	2	2	Both the women stiffened their bodies on hearing my declaration.	s29a	0683
PV01_2601_A	2	3	Kila: 「Hngh... Kuuuh...! Mother...!」	s29a	0684
PV01_2601_A	2	4	Beatrice: 「Ngh, Hah, Haaa... Don’t get flustered... Kila...」	s29a	0685
PV01_2601_A	2	5	It was clear to see that the face of the mother, who was consoling  her own daughter, had also become pale.	s29a	0686
PV01_2601_A	2	6	Bohgan: 「Begin.」	s29a	0687
PV01_2601_A	2	7	I sent a signal to my subordinates, who began preparing the apparatus  to erase their personalities.	s29a	0688
PV01_2601_A	2	8	There was no doubt that the mother and her daughter were looking for  an opportunity while waiting for a mistake, in order to attempt an  escape from their inevitable fate.	s29a	0689
PV01_2601_A	2	9	However, the fact was that there was nothing they could do about it  anymore.	s29a	0690
PV01_2601_A	2	10	Two men stretched their arms towards them and pierced the nape of  their necks with syringes.	s29a	0691
PV01_2601_A	2	11	Kila: 「Guuuh...!!」	s29a	0692
PV01_2601_A	2	12	Beatrice: 「Nguguh...!!」	s29a	0693
PV01_2601_A	2	13	The urine, which had been trickling out of their crotches noisily,  came to a halt.	s29a	0694
PV01_2601_A	2	14	They weren’t going to greet death, while spouting out their urine  uncouthly.	s29a	0695
PV01_2601_A	2	15	Both the women locked their gazes with mine and glared at me, as if  to show off their proud and noble spirits.	s29a	0696
PV01_2601_A	2	16	Beatrice: 「Is this... Haaa... the drug that will erase our personalities...?  Kuh... Guuuh...」	s29a	0697
PV01_2601_A	2	17	The syringes contained a crimson-coloured fluorescent drug, which  was glimmering ominously.	s29a	0698
PV01_2601_A	2	18	Bohgan: 「That’s right. It is a solution of special nano-machines, which  will dissolve the chips embedded in your brains once injected and  erase your personalities in the process.」	s29a	0699
PV01_2601_A	2	19	Beatrice: 「I see...」	s29a	0700
PV01_2601_A	2	20	Beatrice gave a small nod before closing her mouth, and steeled  herself for the inevitable.	s29a	0701
PV01_2601_A	2	21	Bohgan: 「Kuku... Well, I will ask you once again. Do you want to beg for  your lives one last time?」	s29a	0702
PV01_2601_A	2	22	Kila: 「Uh, Fuuuh... How ridiculous! Who would beg for their lives to a  man like you!?」	s29a	0703
PV01_2601_A	2	23	Kila raised a voice filled with her rage.	s29a	0704
PV01_2601_A	2	24	As for Beatrice, she wasn’t about to even respond to my ridiculous  question and didn’t show any reaction.	s29a	0705
PV01_2601_A	2	25	Bohgan: 「There is no reason to get angry. I asked, just in case. I was being  completely serious.」	s29a	0706
PV01_2601_A	2	26	Kila: 「...! If you want to kill us, then kill us right away!」	s29a	0707
PV01_2601_A	2	27	Bohgan: 「Kukuku... You are really impatient to die, aren’t you? I guess  the mother-daughter pair have enjoyed themselves to their heart’s  desires. I feel a bit sorry that we will be parting company.」	s29a	0708
PV01_2601_A	2	28	Kila: 「How worthless...! You have a wicked hobby of shaming leaders, who  have resigned to their deaths.」	s29a	0709
PV01_2601_A	2	29	Bohgan: 「Hohooo... I see. Well, I am sure you meant what you just said,  Lieutenant Kila. Well then, shall we begin?」	s29a	0710
PV01_2601_A	2	30	Kila: 「... Ugh!」	s29a	0711
PV01_2601_A	2	31	Beatrice: 「... ... ... ...」	s29a	0712
PV01_2601_A	2	32	Kila leaked out a small moan, however, she didn’t display the fact  that she was flustered.	s29a	0713
PV01_2601_A	2	33	Beatrice closed her eyelids silently as well.	s29a	0714
PV01_2601_A	2	34	Bohgan: 「Oh yes! Wait a moment.」	s29a	0715
PV01_2601_A	2	35	I stopped my subordinates―― just as they were about to inject the  drug into the nape of their necks.	s29a	0716
PV01_2601_A	2	36	Kila: 「... Is there still something left?」	s29a	0717
PV01_2601_A	2	37	Kila glared at me in frustration.	s29a	0718
PV01_2601_A	2	38	Bohgan: 「Excuse me. I almost forgot something. Both of you have a message  that needs to be delivered.」	s29a	0719
PV01_2601_A	2	39	Kila: 「... A message?」	s29a	0720
PV01_2601_A	2	40	Bohgan: 「That’s right. Kukuku... That was really close, I almost forgot.  Hey! Bring that thing here.」	s29a	0721
PV01_2601_A	3	1	One of my subordinates passed me the video-monitor, which had been  placed in the corner of the room.	s29a	0722
PV01_2601_A	3	2	Bohgan: 「I will erase your personalities after you are done watching it.」	s29a	0723
PV01_2601_A	3	3	I stuck out the video-monitor in front of both the women――	s29a	0724
PV01_2601_A	3	4	Kila: 「Ah...!?」	s29a	0725
PV01_2601_A	3	5	Beatrice: 「Ahuhuuu!!!!!」	s29a	0726
PV01_2601_A	3	6	The mother and her daughter let out bitter groans from their mouths,  the moment they say the image of the person on the monitor.	s29a	0727
PV01_2601_A	3	7	The expression on their faces changed, from one of resignation to  the fate of their inevitable deaths to one of shock, and they began  to tremble outright.	s29a	0728
PV01_2601_A	3	8	Bohgan: 「Don’t you want to know why the Armoured Cavalry Unit didn’t come  to the aid of their ex-Commanders?」	s29a	0729
PV01_2601_A	3	9	I asked both the women while stifling my laughter, however, it looked  like my voice hadn’t even reached their ears.	s29a	0730
PV01_2601_A	3	10	What was being projected on the screen of the monitor was the grim  face of a man, Lucius Romanoff.	s29a	0731
PV01_2601_A	3	11	Beatrice’s husband and Kila’s father.	s29a	0732
PV01_2601_A	3	12	Beatrice: 「Darling...!」	s29a	0733
PV01_2601_A	3	13	Kila: 「Father!」	s29a	0734
PV01_2601_A	3	14	Lucius Romanoff didn’t respond to the two women, who had called out  to him.	s29a	0735
PV01_2601_A	3	15	Even though he had a bitter grimace on his face, he began to speak  in an indifferent tone.	s29a	0736
PV01_2601_A	3	16	Lucius: 「Firstly, let me apologize to you. I made a deal with Donny Bohgan,  for the sake of the revival of our ruined home-nation.」	s29a	0737
PV01_2601_A	3	17	Beatrice: 「A deal... with this man...!?」	s29a	0738
PV01_2601_A	3	18	Beatrice opened her eyes wide and looked at me.	s29a	0739
PV01_2601_A	3	19	Kila: 「W-Why...!? Why would you deal with this low-life, Father...!?」	s29a	0740
PV01_2601_A	3	20	Bohgan: 「Kukuku... Just shut up and listen. You will understand the reason  for it soon enough.」	s29a	0741
PV01_2601_A	3	21	The deal that Lucius was referring to was that――	s29a	0742
PV01_2601_A	3	22	He would have to order all the Kushan Armed Forces to withdraw and,  in exchange, I would keep his real identity a secret.	s29a	0743
PV01_2601_A	3	23	He would have to abandon the mother, Beatrice, and her daughter,  Kila, to my custody, as hostages as well.	s29a	0744
PV01_2601_A	3	24	And in exchange for that, I was to help Lucius Romanoff build a  foundation of power within the Neo-Terras, using my influence.	s29a	0745
PV01_2601_A	3	25	This was the gist of the entirety of our deal.	s29a	0746
PV01_2601_A	3	26	Bohgan: 「Beatrice, you dear husband, and Kila, you beloved father, has  abandoned both of you.」	s29a	0747
PV01_2601_A	3	27	Beatrice: 「That is... Darling... Why...!? What about our dream...!?」	s29a	0748
PV01_2601_A	3	28	Kila: 「Father! Fatheeer!」	s29a	0749
PV01_2601_A	3	29	Why had Lucius abandoned them?	s29a	0750
PV01_2601_A	3	30	Not knowing the reason for that, both the women began to tremble even  more furiously.	s29a	0751
PV01_2601_A	3	31	Bohgan: (Kukuku... You will know soon enough why you have been abandoned.  Lucius will explain it himself.)	s29a	0752
PV01_2601_A	3	32	Lucius: 「It isn’t something I wanted bring up at this moment... However,  it is you who betrayed me first.」	s29a	0753
PV01_2601_A	3	33	Beatrice: 「What do you mean...?」	s29a	0754
PV01_2601_A	3	34	Kila: 「We never betrayed you, Father!」	s29a	0755
PV01_2601_A	3	35	Both the women raised voices of confusion on not having understood  the reason yet.	s29a	0756
PV01_2601_A	3	36	Lucius made an extremely grim face in order to crush the protests of  both the women, almost as if he had anticipated such a response from  them.	s29a	0757
PV01_2601_A	3	37	Lucius: 「I have seen plenty of both of you indulging wildly in sex-orgies  with soldiers. Isn’t it your long-cherished fetish to become slaves  to men?」	s29a	0758
PV01_2601_A	3	38	The cold words of their beloved man pierced through the hearts of the  mother and her daughter.	s29a	0759
PV01_2601_A	3	39	Beatrice: 「T-That iiis...」	s29a	0760
PV01_2601_A	3	40	Kila: 「Father... Uhuuu...」	s29a	0761
PV01_2601_A	4	1	Their faces distorted in despair and tears began to flow down their  cheeks.	s29a	0762
PV01_2601_A	4	2	However, their tears didn’t affect Lucius’s heart whatsoever.	s29a	0763
PV01_2601_A	4	3	Lucius: 「Finally... and let me be very clear about this. Your mere existence,  as lewd whores, is a disgrace to my home-nation.」	s29a	0764
PV01_2601_A	4	4	Lucius: 「If your behaviour ever comes to light, it would crush the unity of  the proud people of my home-nation.」	s29a	0765
PV01_2601_A	4	5	Lucius: 「I requested my friend here, Mr. Bohgan, to make sure that none of  it ever takes centre stage, no matter the cost. Please, don’t let  me down any more than you already have.」	s29a	0766
PV01_2601_A	4	6	Lucius bluntly declared to the mother and her daughter that he was  breaking all ties with them, with a cold, emotionless face, before  cutting the video-call.	s29a	0767
PV01_2601_A	4	7	Beatrice: 「Darling...! Please! Darling! Please, listen to meee!」	s29a	0768
PV01_2601_A	4	8	Kila: 「That’s not true! Fatheeer! All of that... was because of this  man’s scheming!」	s29a	0769
PV01_2601_A	4	9	At the very end, Lucius had shown them a face, as if he was looking  at trash.	s29a	0770
PV01_2601_A	4	10	The man, that they truly loved, had dismissed them entirely and had  considered them to be nothing more than disgusting whores.	s29a	0771
PV01_2601_A	4	11	Beatrice and Kila raised heart-breaking shrieks of despair on  realizing that fact.	s29a	0772
PV01_2601_A	4	12	They yelled at the monitor desperately, however, the monitor was no  longer showing anything.	s29a	0773
PV01_2601_A	4	13	Bohgan: 「Well, now that the message has been delivered, shall we wind this  up? After all, Lucius has entrusted me, personally, to deal with both  of you.」	s29a	0774
PV01_2601_A	4	14	Beatrice: 「Uhaaaaaaa! Waaait! Please, wait!」	s29a	0775
PV01_2601_A	4	15	Kila: 「P-Pleaseee! Uh! Uhaaa! Please, waaait!」	s29a	0776
PV01_2601_A	4	16	Beatrice and Kila raised pleading screams, while shedding tears.	s29a	0777
PV01_2601_A	4	17	They had been held in contempt by their beloved man, who was under a  misunderstanding, and were about to greet their own deaths.	s29a	0778
PV01_2601_A	4	18	They felt fear of dying such a needless death.	s29a	0779
PV01_2601_A	4	19	Both the women immediately developed a strong attachment to their  lives, in order to clear that misunderstanding.	s29a	0780
PV01_2601_A	4	20	The stubbornness of the Empress and the Grim Reaper had snapped and  been crushed. And then, they began to bawl loudly.	s29a	0781
PV01_2601_A	4	21	Bohgan: 「Hahaha!! Your uncouth orgasmic gape-faces drenched in tears!!  These will be your faces, as you die!!」	s29a	0782
PV01_2601_A	4	22	Beatrice: 「I will do anything! I will do anything at all! I beg you! I beg  yooou!」	s29a	0783
PV01_2601_A	4	23	Kila: 「I will become a pig-slut whore! I will offer you my pussy every  day! Please, pleeease!」	s29a	0784
PV01_2601_A	4	24	Beatrice: 「Me too... Don’t erase me... Please, don’t erase meee!」	s29a	0785
PV01_2601_A	4	25	Bohgan: 「Well... I guess I can keep one of you as a pig-slut whore, can’t  I?」	s29a	0786
PV01_2601_A	4	26	Kila: 「P-Pick me! My mother’s pussy is baggy! I will serve you with my  pussy!」	s29a	0787
PV01_2601_A	4	27	Beatrice: 「Shut up, Kila! Do you want your mother to be erased!?」	s29a	0788
PV01_2601_A	4	28	Kila: 「Of course, Mother! Your baggy pussy isn’t suited for a pig-slut  whore, Mother!」	s29a	0789
PV01_2601_A	4	29	Beatrice: 「You bastaaaaard!」	s29a	0790
PV01_2601_A	4	30	Kila: 「No one enjoys the pussy of an old hag!」	s29a	0791
PV01_2601_A	4	31	Beatrice: 「You little girl! Do you wish to die!?」	s29a	0792
PV01_2601_A	4	32	Kila, who had always respected her own mother, was abusing her now,  in order to cling to life during the moment of her death.	s29a	0793
PV01_2601_A	4	33	She wanted to merely save herself.	s29a	0794
PV01_2601_A	4	34	The strong bond between the mother and her daughter was severed, and  they continued hurling profanities at each other.	s29a	0795
PV01_2601_A	4	35	Beatrice: 「What is a little girl like you even capable of!?」	s29a	0796
PV01_2601_A	4	36	Kila: 「You can’t make even one man cum with your baggy pussy, you old  hag!」	s29a	0797
PV01_2601_A	4	37	The mother and her daughter continued to abuse each other, while  shedding tears.	s29a	0798
PV01_2601_A	4	38	And then, they looked at me and started begging me to spare their  lives, with tears running down their cheeks.	s29a	0799
PV01_2601_A	4	39	I had been really looking forward to seeing such uncouth figures of  theirs.	s29a	0800
PV01_2601_A	4	40	Bohgan: 「Hahaha! How pitiful! It would have been better had you been erased  while getting along with each other, rather than showing your uncouth  figures to me.」	s29a	0801
PV01_2601_A	5	1	Kila: 「D-Dat ish...!」	s29a	0802
PV01_2601_A	5	2	Beatrice: 「P-Please, wait! Erase Kila! I-I will do anything for you! My pussy,  my ass-pussy, everything of mine is yours!」	s29a	0803
PV01_2601_A	5	3	Kila: 「Please, erase the old hag! Please, erase the arrogant old hag!」	s29a	0804
PV01_2601_A	5	4	Bohgan: 「Shut up! Your filthy and stinking pussies are completely useless  to me. Well, this is farewell.」	s29a	0805
PV01_2601_A	5	5	Beatrice: 「Nooooo! Nooooo! Stop iiiiit!」	s29a	0806
PV01_2601_A	5	6	Kila: 「Help meee! Pleashe, help meeeee!」	s29a	0807
PV01_2601_A	5	7	Bohgan: 「Do it!」	s29a	0808
PV01_2601_A	5	8	The drug was injected into them, on my signal.	s29a	0809
PV01_2601_A	5	9	Kila: 「Gaaah...!? Help meee! Help meeeee!」	s29a	0810
PV01_2601_A	5	10	Beatrice: 「S-Stooop... Ohooo...!」	s29a	0811
PV01_2601_A	5	11	Beatrice and Kila peeled the whites of their eyes, while continuing  to scream.	s29a	0812
PV01_2601_A	5	12	Their pleading voices dropped off slowly――	s29a	0813
PV01_2601_A	5	13	And their saliva drooled out of their partially open lips.	s29a	0814
PV01_2601_A	5	14	Bohgan: 「It was fun, Beatrice, Kila.」	s29a	0815
PV01_2601_A	5	15	My parting words didn’t even reach the two women.	s29a	0816
PV01_2601_A	5	16	A few seconds after the drug had been injected into them――	s29a	0817
PV01_2601_A	5	17	All expressions disappeared from the faces of the Empress and the  Grim Reaper.	s29a	0818
PV01_2601_A	5	18	Bohgan: 「This is war. It was your misfortune that you ended up as my enemy.  Kukuku! Hahahahahahahaha!」	s29a	0819
PV01_2601_A	5	19	I laughed victoriously and hurled insults at both the women, however,  they would never be able to respond to me again.	s29a	0820
PV01_2601_A	5	20	―――― Six days until our arrival in Libra。	s29a	0821
PV01_2601_A	5	21	The battleship continued its advance through the Sand Sea, as per  schedule.	s29a	0822
PV01_2601_A	5	22	SALTAR: S030A
PV01_2601_A	5	23	SALTAR: S030B
PV01_2601_A	5	24	SALTAR: S030C
