PV01_1801_A	1	1	Kila: 「Kuh... Ugh... Ahuuu...」	s20b	0283
PV01_1801_A	1	2	Kila leaked out a small voice, as she held a video-monitor in her  right hand and rested her left hand on the floor while sticking  her ass out.	s20b	0284
PV01_1801_A	1	3	The image reflecting of the video-monitor was of a man with the same  dark-brown coloured skin as Kila――	s20b	0285
PV01_1801_A	1	4	It was Lucius Romanoff.	s20b	0286
PV01_1801_A	1	5	Kila: 「Father...」	s20b	0287
PV01_1801_A	1	6	Lucius: 「Hello, Kila. You got in touch much sooner than what we had planned.  Have you reached Libra City already?」	s20b	0288
PV01_1801_A	1	7	I heard him speak in his soft-spoken voice, as he addressed his  daughter lovingly.	s20b	0289
PV01_1801_A	1	8	Kila: 「N-No... We are still inside the ship... Father...」	s20b	0290
PV01_1801_A	1	9	Her skirt had been rolled up and her naked ass was pointed directly  at me.	s20b	0291
PV01_1801_A	1	10	Even though she was throwing apprehensive glances at me as I stood  behind her, she feigned calmness and continued to talk to her beloved  father.	s20b	0292
PV01_1801_A	1	11	I slapped my dick on Kila’s ass lightly, in order to fan her shame  even more.	s20b	0293
PV01_1801_A	1	12	Kila: 「Hyaha!? Kuh, Hah, Ungh!」	s20b	0294
PV01_1801_A	1	13	Kila was unable to bear the humiliation of being slapped on her ass  and raised a voice.	s20b	0295
PV01_1801_A	1	14	Lucius: 「Kila? What is the matter?」	s20b	0296
PV01_1801_A	1	15	A suspicious look came on Lucius’ face on seeing Kila raise her  voice abruptly.	s20b	0297
PV01_1801_A	1	16	Kila: 「N-No... I-It is nothing, Nh... It is just that... the ship is  swaying a little...」	s20b	0298
PV01_1801_A	1	17	Lucius: 「Is that so? Anyway, I want to see you two as soon as possible.」	s20b	0299
PV01_1801_A	1	18	Kila sent sharp glances in my direction whenever her father took a  pause while talking.	s20b	0300
PV01_1801_A	1	19	Kila: 「Ngh... Kuuuh... Father will notice you, Aaah... Stop doing weird  things...」	s20b	0301
PV01_1801_A	1	20	Bohgan: 「Kuku... I haven’t really done anything yet though, have I?」	s20b	0302
PV01_1801_A	1	21	I slapped my dick on her ass again, as I said that.	s20b	0303
PV01_1801_A	1	22	Kila: 「Kuh... Hiii... Fuaaah... Kuuuh...」	s20b	0304
PV01_1801_A	1	23	Kila’s boobs, which had spilled out of her attire, swayed back and  forth heavily, every time she twisted her body.	s20b	0305
PV01_1801_A	1	24	Bohgan: 「Lieutenant Kila, you will end up in trouble if you forget that you  are in the middle of your Public Relations Mission right now. Don’t  get too ecstatic while talking to your father.」	s20b	0306
PV01_1801_A	1	25	Kila: 「Hah... Haaa, Ngh... Nhuuu... Kuuuh...」	s20b	0307
PV01_1801_A	1	26	Kila looked back at me with an expression of frustration on her  face――	s20b	0308
PV01_1801_A	1	27	Lucius: 「What I meant to say was that when you come here, I have a present  in store for you, Kila.」	s20b	0309
PV01_1801_A	1	28	Kila: 「Fuhaaa... Aha, What is it, Father...? This present that you speak  of...」	s20b	0310
PV01_1801_A	1	29	She showed a gentle face to her father, which I had never seen her  show anyone else.	s20b	0311
PV01_1801_A	1	30	Bohgan: (Hmph! Isn’t such a face unbecoming of a woman who calls herself  the Grim Reaper?)	s20b	0312
PV01_1801_A	1	31	She loved and respected her father from the bottom of her heart.	s20b	0313
PV01_1801_A	1	32	A dark yet cold emotion welled up within my heart, the moment I  recognized the feelings behind the expression on Kila’s face.	s20b	0314
PV01_1801_A	1	33	Bohgan: (Now, I am going to make you think of my cock more than your father,  Kila.)	s20b	0315
PV01_1801_A	1	34	Lucius: 「Hahaha... It is surprise, you will just have to look forward to it,  Kila.」	s20b	0316
PV01_1801_A	1	35	Kila: 「Nh... Aha... I am extremely excited, Father... Can you give me a  small hint?」	s20b	0317
PV01_1801_A	1	36	Lucius: 「Let us see. A hint, huh...?」	s20b	0318
PV01_1801_A	1	37	I thrust my dick forward and pressed it against Kila’s lewd slit,  as she was tried to converse with her father――	s20b	0319
PV01_1801_A	1	38	And, buried my meat-pole inside her slowly.	s20b	0320
PV01_1801_A	1	39	Kila: 「Kuhi... Hiii!? Hngh, Hih... Nhaaa!」	s20b	0321
PV01_1801_A	1	40	I suddenly penetrated Kila and an intense stimulation rose up from  her cunt, causing her to raise her voice reflexively.	s20b	0322
PV01_1801_A	2	1	However, as soon as she caught sight of her father’s face in front  of her eyes――	s20b	0323
PV01_1801_A	2	2	Kila: 「Kuh... Ugh... Uh... Ngh... Nhuuu...」	s20b	0324
PV01_1801_A	2	3	She suppressed her ecstatic voice and somehow managed to bring it  under her control.	s20b	0325
PV01_1801_A	2	4	Bohgan: 「Ohooo... You are just as I expected, Lieutenant Kila.」	s20b	0326
PV01_1801_A	2	5	Kila: 「Aha, Hah... Kuh... Please take it out, Captain... I-I am doing  this right now... F-Father may notice us...」	s20b	0327
PV01_1801_A	2	6	Bohgan: 「Hmph! And what about your pussy, which is tightly clamping down on  me, Lieutenant?」	s20b	0328
PV01_1801_A	2	7	Her pussy-meat had started squeezing my meat-pole all over, the  moment I buried it inside her.	s20b	0329
PV01_1801_A	2	8	Bohgan: 「And your nipples as well... They are standing erect like cocks,  aren’t they?」	s20b	0330
PV01_1801_A	2	9	The nipples at the tips of her heavily swaying boobs had poked out  and become erect like a pair of dicks.	s20b	0331
PV01_1801_A	2	10	Kila: 「T-That is... Hah!? Aha, Nh... Nguh... Kuh... Kufuuuh!」	s20b	0332
PV01_1801_A	2	11	Lucius: 「A hint for your present, huh...? You are really smart, Kila. If it  is too simple of a hint, you will figure it out immediately.」	s20b	0333
PV01_1801_A	2	12	He hadn’t even realized that his own daughter was being penetrated  by my dick from the back――	s20b	0334
PV01_1801_A	2	13	He was cheerfully thinking of a hint to give her for his stupid  present.	s20b	0335
PV01_1801_A	2	14	Bohgan: 「Your father is an imbecile.」	s20b	0336
PV01_1801_A	2	15	Kila: 「Kuh... Uuuuh! I won’t allow you... to insult my father...!」	s20b	0337
PV01_1801_A	2	16	Bohgan: 「Kuku... If he can’t even realize that his own daughter is having  sex, what else can I call him but an imbecile?」	s20b	0338
PV01_1801_A	2	17	While saying so, I shoved my meat-pole even deeper inside her causing  her pussy-meat to react even more strongly.	s20b	0339
PV01_1801_A	2	18	Kila: 「Hah, Haaa, Kuuuh... Aaah! S-Stop... No more...」	s20b	0340
PV01_1801_A	2	19	Kila was unable to bear it and tried to cut the video-call, as I  pumped my dick in and out of her.	s20b	0341
PV01_1801_A	2	20	Bohgan: 「Uh-oh. Cutting the call would amount to a breach of the terms  of our deal. Do you really want my subordinates to spread that  information over our military intelligence network?」	s20b	0342
PV01_1801_A	2	21	I leaned forward and whispered that into her ears, while rubbing and  massaging the meat on her bubble-butt.	s20b	0343
PV01_1801_A	2	22	Kila: 「Kuh... You despicable...! Fuaaah, Fuh, Nhuuu...」	s20b	0344
PV01_1801_A	2	23	Bohgan: 「That was our deal, wasn’t it? If you want this to end, you better  make me cum quickly!」	s20b	0345
PV01_1801_A	2	24	Kila: 「Nfuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuh!!」	s20b	0346
PV01_1801_A	2	25	Whap! Whap! Whap! Whap!	s20b	0347
PV01_1801_A	2	26	I spanked her taut dark-brown ass and began pumping my meat-pole in  and out of her even more furiously.	s20b	0348
PV01_1801_A	2	27	I gouged into the meat-folds of her pussy, while ramming my dick  against her womb over and over again.	s20b	0349
PV01_1801_A	2	28	Kila: 「Hah!? Hngh! Guh... Kuuuh... P-Please stop it... F-Father is going  to hear the sound... Uhuuu!」	s20b	0350
PV01_1801_A	2	29	Bohgan: 「Kuku... Didn’t your father just say that you are really smart,  Kila? In that case, use that smartness in order to deceive him!」	s20b	0351
PV01_1801_A	2	30	Lucius: 「Kila...? I can hear some sounds. What is going on?」	s20b	0352
PV01_1801_A	2	31	Just as Kila had feared, the dry slapping sounds of her ass being  spanked were heard by Lucius.	s20b	0353
PV01_1801_A	2	32	Kila: 「S-Sounds... huh? Ngh, Nkuuuh... I-I don’t know what it is that  you are hearing... C-Could it be some sort of noise?」	s20b	0354
PV01_1801_A	2	33	Bohgan: (It is a big deal for this woman to deceive her beloved father...  I look forward to see how she goes about deceiving him.)	s20b	0355
PV01_1801_A	2	34	I grabbed a hold of Kila’s waist and began to pound her so furiously  that her upper body shook with each thrust.	s20b	0356
PV01_1801_A	2	35	Kila: 「Kufuuuh! Ngh... Nnnnnnh! Guguh, Guh, Nfuuuh... Nnnnnnnh!」	s20b	0357
PV01_1801_A	2	36	Kila’s upper body was shaking so furiously that even Lucius saw  it.	s20b	0358
PV01_1801_A	2	37	Lucius: 「Kila...? W-What is the matter? Is something wrong!?」	s20b	0359
PV01_1801_A	2	38	Lucius raised an alarmed voice, on seeing Kila’s upper body suddenly  start shaking.	s20b	0360
PV01_1801_A	2	39	Kila: 「W-We entered a storm... just now... w-which is why, the ship is  shaking... Hah! Hah! Nfuuuh...!」	s20b	0361
PV01_1801_A	2	40	Lucius: 「Is that so...? Are you alright? Both, Beatrice and you, are my  priceless diamonds, you know?」	s20b	0362
PV01_1801_A	3	1	Kila: 「I-I am fine... Such a storm... Hih!? Hyuuuh! Is something I have  gotten accustomed to... There is no need to worry, Father.」	s20b	0363
PV01_1801_A	3	2	Lucius: 「Is that so? Even so, I think it would be better if we don’t have  too long a chat. Let us just cut our call for now.」	s20b	0364
PV01_1801_A	3	3	Bohgan: 「Continue the call... Even if he cuts it, it will still amount to  a breach of the terms our deal.」	s20b	0365
PV01_1801_A	3	4	I threatened Kila and ordered her to continue the call.	s20b	0366
PV01_1801_A	3	5	Kila: 「W-Waaait... Father... I-It is quite alright... because I am really  fine... Ahaaa...」	s20b	0367
PV01_1801_A	3	6	Bohgan: (Take this! I am putting on my last spurt now!)	s20b	0368
PV01_1801_A	3	7	Kila: 「Ofuuuh!? Nkuuuuuuuuh!!」	s20b	0369
PV01_1801_A	3	8	I continued to rape her from the back, as she lied to her father.	s20b	0370
PV01_1801_A	3	9	Kila’s cunt became extremely sensitive due to indulging in such an  immoral act.	s20b	0371
PV01_1801_A	3	10	Kila: 「Kuh, Ugh, Guh, Unnnhuuu!!」	s20b	0372
PV01_1801_A	3	11	Bohgan: 「Can you hear it, Lieutenant Kila? The melody of your pussy?」	s20b	0373
PV01_1801_A	3	12	Guchyuuu... Nchyuuu, Nchyuuu! Kuchuchyuuu!	s20b	0374
PV01_1801_A	3	13	Her honey-juices dribbled out of her pussy and soaked her inner  thighs, as the sounds of her pussy-meat churning echoed around the  room.	s20b	0375
PV01_1801_A	3	14	Kila: 「Ahaaa... Nkuh... Hah, Hah, Ngh... Nghuuuuu...」	s20b	0376
PV01_1801_A	3	15	Kila’s face flushed the moment those obscene squelching sounds  reached her ears.	s20b	0377
PV01_1801_A	3	16	However, as Kila’s body had become supremely aroused, her areolae  swelled up along with her erect nipples, which had begun to throb.	s20b	0378
PV01_1801_A	3	17	Lucius: 「Kila, do you really want to continue chatting at such a time? It  is enough for me to see that you are safe.」	s20b	0379
PV01_1801_A	3	18	Kila: 「Hah, Nfuuuh, Ahuuu... I-I... Hah, still want to talk to you...」	s20b	0380
PV01_1801_A	3	19	She was left with no choice but to yield to my demand, in order to  protect her father.	s20b	0381
PV01_1801_A	3	20	Kila continued to talk to her father, despite trembling with the fear  of being noticed by her father while having sex.	s20b	0382
PV01_1801_A	3	21	Bohgan: (Well, well. How long will you be able to endure this!?)	s20b	0383
PV01_1801_A	3	22	Kila was on the verge of breaking completely and I neared my orgasm  on noticing her like that.	s20b	0384
PV01_1801_A	3	23	I began to graze her meat-walls by ramming into the depths of her  pussy, having put on a last spurt.	s20b	0385
PV01_1801_A	3	24	Kila: 「Kuh... Ungh... Kuuuh, Fuh, Fuh... Aaah!? Ngh, Aaaaah!」	s20b	0386
PV01_1801_A	3	25	Tears welled up in Kila’s eyes, as if she was begging me on being  driven into a corner.	s20b	0387
PV01_1801_A	3	26	I gave Kila a sneering grin on noticing her pleading eyes, as if she  was wishing for me to stop and――	s20b	0388
PV01_1801_A	3	27	I thrust my rigid dick all the way into her deepest part.	s20b	0389
PV01_1801_A	3	28	Kila: 「Kuhiii...!? Ugh, Guh... Fuuuh... Uh... Kufuuuh!」	s20b	0390
PV01_1801_A	3	29	Lucius: 「Kila? You are sweating profusely... What is the matter? Wouldn’t  it be better if we cut the call for now?」	s20b	0391
PV01_1801_A	3	30	Kila: 「P-Please wait... It is alright... I-I am fine...」	s20b	0392
PV01_1801_A	3	31	Bohgan: 「Let us do this, Lieutenant Kila!!!!」	s20b	0393
PV01_1801_A	3	32	My glans throbbed with the desire to stain Kila’s womb as soon as  possible.	s20b	0394
PV01_1801_A	3	33	Kila: 「W-Wait... Haaa!? Agh... T-That... Now... now... Aaaah!」	s20b	0395
PV01_1801_A	3	34	It would be a finishing blow for her, if I ejaculated now.	s20b	0396
PV01_1801_A	3	35	Kila sensed that herself, however, she was in no position to do  anything about it.	s20b	0397
PV01_1801_A	3	36	Kila: 「Kuh!? Uh... Kuhuuu! Nnnnnnnnnnnnh!」	s20b	0398
PV01_1801_A	3	37	Bohgan: 「Take it! And cuuum!」	s20b	0399
PV01_1801_A	3	38	Kila: 「Kughiii!?」	s20b	0400
PV01_1801_A	3	39	Kila’s face slackened and ended up collapsing.	s20b	0401
PV01_1801_A	3	40	Kila: 「Uguguh... Stop it!」	s20b	0402
PV01_1801_A	4	1	Kila shifted the video-monitor to the side as she didn’t want to  show him her orgasmic gape-face, now that she was on the verge of  her orgasm.	s20b	0403
PV01_1801_A	4	2	Bohgan: (Such a half-measure will never work!!)	s20b	0404
PV01_1801_A	4	3	Doryuryuryuuu! Dobyuryuuuuu!	s20b	0405
PV01_1801_A	4	4	I buried my rigid dick inside her all the way up to its base and  ended up crushing her womb.	s20b	0406
PV01_1801_A	4	5	Kila: 「Unghuuuuuhuuuuuhuuuuu!!」	s20b	0407
PV01_1801_A	4	6	And just like that, I spewed out my semen inside her, filling her  pussy up in the blink of an eye.	s20b	0408
PV01_1801_A	4	7	Pussshaaaaaaaaaaaaa!	s20b	0409
PV01_1801_A	4	8	Kila: 「Cummiiiiiiiiiiiiing!!!」	s20b	0410
PV01_1801_A	4	9	Kila spouted out a tide, while raising her orgasmic voice that echoed  all around the room.	s20b	0411
PV01_1801_A	4	10	Kila: 「Aaaargh!! Cumming! Cumming! Cumming!!!」	s20b	0412
PV01_1801_A	4	11	Kila: 「Nod my whooooomb!!! Cumming!! Don’d make my whomb gulp your  shemen-miiirk!」	s20b	0413
PV01_1801_A	4	12	She was having an intensely supreme orgasm, now that her endurance  had reached its limit.	s20b	0414
PV01_1801_A	4	13	Bohgan: 「Kuhaha, Don’t hold back, Kila! Is it good!? Your beloved father  can hear your orgasmic voice!」	s20b	0415
PV01_1801_A	4	14	Kila: 「Cummiiiiinnnnng! Cummiiiiiiiiiinnnnnng!」	s20b	0416
PV01_1801_A	4	15	Bohgan: 「Hmmm...?」	s20b	0417
PV01_1801_A	4	16	Lucius didn’t have a look of astonishment on his face, despite the  fact that she was screaming out in her orgasmic voice.	s20b	0418
PV01_1801_A	4	17	Even though she had shifted the video-monitor away to avoid showing  him her orgasmic gape-face―― Her voice should have been heard by  him.	s20b	0419
PV01_1801_A	4	18	Bohgan: 「I see. You sly pig-slut! You surely can’t claim that “The call  is still on” anymore, since you turned the sound off even if did  keep the video-call on. Kukuku...」	s20b	0420
PV01_1801_A	4	19	Kila had used her quick wit and came up with that solution in order  to escape the worst-case scenario, just as she reached her orgasm.	s20b	0421
PV01_1801_A	4	20	Kila: 「Oho♪ Oho♪ Ohooo! Id ish coming... Id ish coming ouuud! M-My  whomb... ish being gouged into by your shemen-miiirk!」	s20b	0422
PV01_1801_A	4	21	She raised her uncouth orgasmic voice and exposed her orgasmic  gape-face, however, both her voice and her face wasn’t noticed by  her father.	s20b	0423
PV01_1801_A	4	22	Bohgan: 「You are just as I expected, Lieutenant Kila. I will let you have  your victory for the day. However, you must turn on the sound and  resume your chat with your father right now.」	s20b	0424
PV01_1801_A	4	23	I began extracting my dick out of her, after having finished filling  her flesh-pot up to the brim with my semen.	s20b	0425
PV01_1801_A	4	24	Kila: 「Ahah, Hah... Kuh... Kufuuuh... Ahah, Hah, Nhuuu...」	s20b	0426
PV01_1801_A	4	25	Kila turned on the sound of the video-call again, even as massive  amounts of my semen poured of her gaping cunt like a waterfall.	s20b	0427
PV01_1801_A	4	26	Lucius: 「Kila, what was that abrupt interruption? I was surprised that your  face wasn’t visible all of a sudden as well.」	s20b	0428
PV01_1801_A	4	27	Kila: 「Fuaaah... Hiii, Kufuuuh... T-The ship was swaying greatly...  w-which is why... Ah... Ahuuu...」	s20b	0429
PV01_1801_A	4	28	Jyororororooo, Jyorororororororooo!	s20b	0430
PV01_1801_A	4	29	She was indulging in the afterglow of her orgasm with her body while  blowing a tide, when suddenly her urine poured out.	s20b	0431
PV01_1801_A	4	30	Kila: 「Hiii... Ahaaa... Hiii... Hah, Haaa... Aaaah...」	s20b	0432
PV01_1801_A	4	31	Lucius: 「I can hear some sounds again. It sounds like a water leakage... Is  the ship alright?」	s20b	0433
PV01_1801_A	4	32	Her father could hear the sound of her urine leaking out.	s20b	0434
PV01_1801_A	4	33	Her body reacted to that humiliation and――	s20b	0435
PV01_1801_A	4	34	Kila: 「Fuhi... Hih... Hiii... Aaah, Ahaaa... I-It is... alright...  Guh...」	s20b	0436
PV01_1801_A	4	35	Her face slackened lewdly, as she looked at her father’s face in  front of her.	s20b	0437
PV01_1801_A	4	36	Bohgan: (Hmph. It looks she will orgasm instantly if I shove my cock inside  her now.)	s20b	0438
PV01_1801_A	4	37	Shall I show Lucius the orgasmic gape-face of his daughter?	s20b	0439
PV01_1801_A	4	38	Such a dark and intense passionate urge flared up inside me.	s20b	0440
PV01_1801_A	4	39	Bohgan: (No... It is still too soon... Kuku, I will be patient with you for  now, Kila.)	s20b	0441
PV01_1801_A	4	40	A puddle formed on the floor due to the semen overflowing out of her  mixed with the golden-coloured water that she was spouting out, and  the floor got completely soaked.	s20b	0442
PV01_1801_A	5	1	Kila: 「The transmission seems to be poor... Ngh... Nnnnh, as a result of  the storm... Hah, Fuh, Aaaah...」	s20b	0443
PV01_1801_A	5	2	Lucius: 「Is that so...? You need not worry even though it is such a terrible  storm.」	s20b	0444
PV01_1801_A	5	3	Kila: 「N-No... However... t-the storm seems to have dissipated for now...  Haaa, Hah, It is... alright...」	s20b	0445
PV01_1801_A	5	4	Lucius: 「Mhm. Anyway, you don’t need to push yourself repeatedly like  this. You are my precious and only daughter, aren’t you? Well,  I should get going now... I love you, Kila.」	s20b	0446
PV01_1801_A	5	5	Kila: 「Ahah... Kuh... Ahaaa... F-Father... I-I... love you too...」	s20b	0447
PV01_1801_A	5	6	Kila responded to him in a voice, which was tinged with the pleasure  on being made to orgasm by me.	s20b	0448
PV01_1801_A	5	7	Bohgan: (Kuku... I will make you tell him that you love my cock very soon,  Kila.)	s20b	0449
PV01_1801_A	5	8	I was going to steadily destroy the love and respect that Kila held  for her father with my dick.	s20b	0450
PV01_1801_A	5	9	I swore that within my heart, as I saw the image of Lucius disappear  off the video-monitor.	s20b	0451
PV01_1801_A	5	10	Meanwhile, as the daughter was orgasming while conversing with her  father.	s20b	0452
PV01_1801_A	5	11	Her mother――	s20b	0453
