S002A	1	1	The Space Era had been brilliant.	s02a	0000
S002A	1	2	Two major technologies, the terra-forming plant and the plasma-engine,  had been developed at the dawn of this era.	s02a	0001
S002A	1	3	Following the first terra-forming project of Mars in the year  2123 A.D., numerous other planets and satellites had become  terrestrial, and various space colonies had been established.	s02a	0002
S002A	1	4	Humanity spread throughout the Solar System in the blink of an eye,  with the super powerful plasma-engine at the core of its advance.	s02a	0003
S002A	1	5	However, even though technology had advanced and the places where  life thrived had changed, it had made little difference to the nature  of humanity.	s02a	0004
S002A	1	6	It became common practice for the people in space, who were the elite  of this new era, to drive the impoverished people to Earth.	s02a	0005
S002A	1	7	The Earth State took control of these colonies and gradually became  stronger.	s02a	0006
S002A	1	8	Martian city-states, star-colony systems and other space colonies,  which rebelled against this faction, established the Federation of  the Space Alliance which was based on Jupiter’satellite, Titan.	s02a	0007
S002A	1	9	They jointly established the first space army of the human race and  succeeded in acquiring a powerful voice within the space society.	s02a	0008
S002A	1	10	Each star-colony broke ties with the Earth State, one after another,  under the pretext of a peaceful solution, and became independent.	s02a	0009
S002A	1	11	The isolation of the nations on Earth deepened, and the four  super-powers therein became concerned about the transfer of the  political centre of the Space Era and the potential birth of a  huge nation, which could rule the entire Solar System.	s02a	0010
S002A	1	12	These four super-powers ― The European-Russian Federation, the  American-Pacific Federation, The Great Asian Commonwealth and the  Large People’s Republic of China ― proclaimed a great alliance of  the Earth State after many years of conflict.	s02a	0011
S002A	1	13	Any nations which opposed the infringement of the four super-powers,  who were named the Alliance, upon their sovereignty were attacked  with thermo-nuclear weapons by these four powers.	s02a	0012
S002A	1	14	It was known as the August War of Blood, the worst massacre in human  history.	s02a	0013
S002A	1	15	All opposing powers were wiped off the face of the Earth, and the  National Union of Earth was established.	s02a	0014
S002A	1	16	And soon, in the year 2210 A.D.,	s02a	0015
S002A	1	17	It was approved via an electronic vote that the satellite, Titan,  would be the head of the association conducting the negotiations  between the Federation of the Space Alliance and the National Union  of Earth.	s02a	0016
S002A	1	18	The Universal Federal Government was established in a way that the  Federation of the Space Alliance and the National Union of Earth  would be allied to become the first unified regime of humanity.	s02a	0017
S002A	1	19	It was the beginning of space history.	s02a	0018
S002A	1	20	However, the promise of peace that the people expected in this  new era had transformed to that of sheer disappointment, within  ten years.	s02a	0019
S002A	1	21	Neo-Terras made it their top priority for the return of humanity  to Earth and the protection of their Earthly interests.	s02a	0020
S002A	1	22	While the New-Solars aimed to break away from the vested interests  of the National Union of Earth.	s02a	0021
S002A	1	23	The embers of this fiery universal conflict continued to smoulder.	s02a	0022
S002A	1	24	The people in the Universal Federal Government became divided into  two factions, the military faction and the civilian faction, and  instigated a fierce tug-of-war, which was akin to a civil war.	s02a	0023
S002A	1	25	In these circumstances, the ex-Commander of the Space Federal Army,  Donny Bohgan,	s02a	0024
S002A	1	26	Assumed the Dukedom of the fortress nation of Cordelia of Uranus,  which was also the standard bearer for the neutral forces, and  established a third power, Die Erde, starting a new space calendar  in the process.	s02a	0025
S002A	1	27	Bohgan, the founder and the first chairman of Die Erde, ended up  embroiling New-Solars’ and Neo-Terras’ star-colonies and space  colonies into the rebellion, after they had risen up to revolt  against the Universal Federal Government.	s02a	0026
S002A	1	28	Neo-Terras and New-Solars, in this moment of crisis, ended up joining  hands in a secret truce.	s02a	0027
S002A	1	29	With the reputation of the Universal Federal Government in tatters,  they marched on Cordelia, the stronghold of Die Erde, with an Allied  Fleet comprised of both factions.	s02a	0028
S002A	1	30	Space Era Year 45, New Space Era Year 1. The war broke out in the  tertiary atmosphere of Cordelia.	s02a	0029
S002A	1	31	Everyone in the Solar System was confident of victory for the Allied  Fleet, however the result was unexpected.	s02a	0030
S002A	1	32	Donny Bohgan drove the Allied Fleet to the brink of annihilation by  directing the Die Erde Armed Forces himself.	s02a	0031
S002A	1	33	It was an overwhelming victory.	s02a	0032
S002A	1	34	The Allied Fleet suffered historic losses and it was estimated that  it would take them ten years to just rebuild their forces.	s02a	0033
S002A	1	35	Following that war, the influence of Neo-Terras and New-Solars  rapidly deteriorated, and soon thereafter, the Empress, Beatrice  Kushan, began her rebellion under the pretext of development and  started heavily rewriting the Martian power-map.	s02a	0034
S002A	1	36	Now, the Solar System was about to enter a new phase.	s02a	0035
S002A	1	37	Now――	s02a	0036
S002A	1	38	Earth Year 2256 A.D., Space Era Year 46, New Space Era Year 2...	s02a	0037
S002A	1	39	On October 28.	s02a	0038
S002A	1	40	Within the Martian Sand Sea.	s02a	0039
S002A	2	1	A battleship was navigating the vast desert.	s02a	0040
S002A	2	2	The name of this battleship was the Tristan.	s02a	0041
S002A	2	3	It was a high-speed battleship of the Libra Armed Forces.	s02a	0042
S002A	2	4	These battleships had been obsolete antiques until recently, before  the drastic changes in the Martian environment and in particular the  occurrence of the Sand Sea.	s02a	0043
S002A	2	5	The desert battleships used Deuterium as fuel and Plasma, generated  by nuclear fusion within the engine-core, as an energy source in  order to rotate the screws and generate driving force.	s02a	0044
S002A	2	6	This seemingly primitive system of propulsion was designed to  overcome the Sand Sea.	s02a	0045
S002A	2	7	This desert’s sand which was of a special nature, with properties  of water, was called Minimal Sand, and its compatibility with every  other precision equipment was abysmal.	s02a	0046
S002A	2	8	Minimal Sand would enter any gaps like water and clog the machinery  like sand.	s02a	0047
S002A	2	9	If mobile weapons weren’t designed with the Sand Sea specifications,  they would soon clog up with the sand and become dysfunctional.	s02a	0048
S002A	2	10	The superiority of these sand-based weapons would, undoubtedly,  greatly affect the outcome of wars on Mars.	s02a	0049
S002A	2	11	It could be said that in these circumstances the wars on Mars were  akin to the First World War, when command on the seas had made a big  impact on the outcome of the war.	s02a	0050
S002A	2	12	The Tristan, blowing up a spray of the Minimal Sand, was about to  reach Perseus City, the stronghold of the Kushan Armed Forces.	s02a	0051
S002A	2	13	Adamo: 「Gentlemen! The great duty that you have been bestowed with finally  enters the second stage!」	s02a	0052
S002A	2	14	I declared loudly.	s02a	0053
S002A	2	15	My name was Celio Adamo.	s02a	0054
S002A	2	16	I was the Colonel of the Libra Armed Forces, and the Captain of  the Tristan.	s02a	0055
S002A	2	17	Right now, I was in the Tristan’s operations room.	s02a	0056
S002A	2	18	All my senior officers were gathered in front of me.	s02a	0057
S002A	2	19	The faces of my men were glaring, like wild beasts on the verge of  assaulting women.	s02a	0058
S002A	2	20	Seeing that look on their faces put me in a good spirit.	s02a	0059
S002A	2	21	I addressed each and every one of my men to make my point clear.	s02a	0060
S002A	2	22	Adamo: 「Since the beginning, we, of Libra, have declared our eternal  neutrality to this dispute, even as the fierce ground battle in  the quagmire has continued unabated.」	s02a	0061
S002A	2	23	Adamo: 「The Martian capital, with its talented personnel, is now an  economic powerhouse that no power can ignore any longer.」	s02a	0062
S002A	2	24	Adamo: 「And now, to ensure that Libra can fulfil its heavy responsibility  to the interspace community satisfactorily,」	s02a	0063
S002A	2	25	Adamo: 「We have our best personnel to bridge the peace talks on Mars  between the all-conquering Kushan Armed Forces and the forces of  the Neo-Terras!」	s02a	0064
S002A	2	26	My Men: 「Yes Sir!!」	s02a	0065
S002A	2	27	Adamo: 「At last, we, the messengers of peace, will invite “The Empress”  and her daughter, “The Grim Reaper of the Sands”, on-board the  Tristan!」	s02a	0066
S002A	2	28	My Men: 「Yes Sir!!」	s02a	0067
S002A	2	29	Adamo: 「Let us all welcome them appropriately!」	s02a	0068
S002A	2	30	The officers whistled at my words and stood upright and ready.	s02a	0069
S002A	2	31	Everyone was thinking about the same thing.	s02a	0070
S002A	2	32	To rape the pig-sluts who didn’t know their place, and dominate,  and abuse and ravage them thoroughly.	s02a	0071
S002A	2	33	As always.	s02a	0072
S002A	2	34	No. In the most severe way possible, taking into account all our  past grudges against them.	s02a	0073
S002A	2	35	Adamo: 「Gentlemen! It seems to me that the Empress has been caught! In  the trap of Celio Adamo? No,」	s02a	0074
S002A	2	36	Bohgan: 「In the trap of Donny Bohgan!!」	s02a	0075
S002A	2	37	I thrust my right fist up.	s02a	0076
S002A	2	38	My Men: 「Captain! We have been looking forward to this! Revenge on the  pig-sluts!!」	s02a	0077
S002A	2	39	Their raucous cheers rose to a cacophony and shook the Tristan.	s02a	0078
S002A	2	40	Bohgan: 「Kukuku」	s02a	0079
S002A	3	1	Yes, it was me.	s02a	0080
S002A	3	2	It was Donny Bohgan.	s02a	0081
S002A	3	3	I was the highest authority in Die Erde, however, now I was going  by the name of Celio Adamo, a soldier of one of the city-states of  Mars.	s02a	0082
S002A	3	4	Of course, it was all a ploy for the sake of crushing those women.	s02a	0083
S002A	3	5	Bohgan: 「Gentlemen!!」	s02a	0084
S002A	3	6	I commanded my excited men.	s02a	0085
S002A	3	7	Bohgan: 「The fact that Mahoi died was something I had considered to be a  possibility!」	s02a	0086
S002A	3	8	Bohgan: 「Being a combat operative, he was bound to “do something” in the  den of the tigress!」	s02a	0087
S002A	3	9	My Men: 「Yes Sir!!」	s02a	0088
S002A	3	10	It was only the other day, that Mahoi’s severed head had been  delivered to Moller’s residence.	s02a	0089
S002A	3	11	My only expectation had been for him to do his duty like a quiet  dog, but he was a foolish man.	s02a	0090
S002A	3	12	No, those pig-sluts would have killed him regardless.	s02a	0091
S002A	3	13	Because, they didn’t like dogs.	s02a	0092
S002A	3	14	Bohgan: 「After the war situation escalates in our favour, I believe the old  leadership of the Neo-Terras, who have desired to gain a foothold on  Mars for years, will cooperate with us, even if Beatrice and Kila  Kushan end up dead.」	s02a	0093
S002A	3	15	Bohgan: 「Beatrice and Kila have already been made to believe that the fake  peace negotiations are genuine.」	s02a	0094
S002A	3	16	My Men: 「Yes Sir!!」	s02a	0095
S002A	3	17	Bohgan: 「Because, our word has already spread among the Neo-Terras!!!」	s02a	0096
S002A	3	18	Bohgan: 「Beatrice has surely obtained reports from her spies in the  Neo-Terras by now, as she seems to have been investigating us  carefully, and she will be of the belief that we are genuine!」	s02a	0097
S002A	3	19	Bohgan: 「No one, including those old men who have been playing their big  game behind our backs while using our cooperation, knows the truth  about us!!!」	s02a	0098
S002A	3	20	My Men: 「Yes Sir!!」	s02a	0099
S002A	3	21	Bohgan: 「Of course, we have no intention of fulfilling the hopes of those  old men!!!」	s02a	0100
S002A	3	22	Bohgan: 「I am not going to kill Beatrice and Kila!」	s02a	0101
S002A	3	23	Bohgan: 「We will make them our pawns and let them live their lives as pigs,  or let them die of shame and humiliation as pigs!!」	s02a	0102
S002A	3	24	My Men: 「Yes Sir!!」	s02a	0103
S002A	3	25	Bohgan: 「Gentlemen, be rest assured!!」	s02a	0104
S002A	3	26	Bohgan: 「I have spent several years investing in the governing body of the  Libra Armed Forces, who live by the peace-at-any-price attitude, and  now we will put that investment to good use!」	s02a	0105
S002A	3	27	Bohgan: 「In other words, all of us hold the responsibility of executing  this strategy of mine!」	s02a	0106
S002A	3	28	My Men: 「Yes Sir!!」	s02a	0107
S002A	3	29	Bohgan: 「We are to creep in as the Libra Armed Forces, a third party with  goodwill, on those bloody women!!! Those bloody women have killed  tens of thousands of our people on Mars!!!」	s02a	0108
S002A	3	30	Bohgan: 「Indeed, Beatrice Kushan and Kila Kushan are to be put up on the  Brainwashing <Memory Implant> devices!」	s02a	0109
S002A	3	31	Bohgan: 「I will destroy the spirits of those arrogant women!!! They will  be transformed completely into sluts!!! And serve us as pig-sluts  at our beck and call!!!」	s02a	0110
S002A	3	32	My Men: 「Yes Sir!!!!」	s02a	0111
S002A	3	33	My Men: 「Bohgan!! Bohgan!! Bohgan!! Bohgan!!」	s02a	0112
S002A	3	34	The excited men stomped the ground in unison.	s02a	0113
S002A	3	35	Some of them were already sporting bulging crotches.	s02a	0114
S002A	3	36	They were totally reliable.	s02a	0115
S002A	3	37	They weren’t mere dogs.	s02a	0116
S002A	3	38	They were wolves.	s02a	0117
S002A	3	39	Bohgan: 「Calm down!」	s02a	0118
S002A	3	40	I quickly waved my hand.	s02a	0119
S002A	4	1	My faithful wolf pack fell silent instantly.	s02a	0120
S002A	4	2	Bohgan: 「Major Hans!!!」	s02a	0121
S002A	4	3	Hans: 「Yes!」	s02a	0122
S002A	4	4	Major Hans straightened his heel and took one step forward.	s02a	0123
S002A	4	5	Bohgan: 「Report the results.」	s02a	0124
S002A	4	6	Hans: 「The Brainwashing <Memory Implant> devices installed on the Tristan  are perfectly concealed.」	s02a	0125
S002A	4	7	Hans: 「Radio waves coming from the engine-core will disturb any sensors  and make them impossible to track.」	s02a	0125
S002A	4	8	The man, who I had selected as my Lieutenant recently, saluted with  a calm gesture.	s02a	0126
S002A	4	9	Originally, the Director of the 『Brainwashing Laboratory』, he  had been evaluated and found to have a good balance of diversity  of skills and intelligence, and was appointed as my Lieutenant.	s02a	0127
S002A	4	10	He was a good man and the self-styled 『Widow Eater』. He would  train women after killing their husbands, and would expose them  to the knowledge that he was the one responsible for the murder  of their husbands just before the moment of their fall.	s02a	0128
S002A	4	11	Bohgan: 「Captain Ingeborg!!!」	s02a	0129
S002A	4	12	Ingeborg: 「Brainwashing <Memory Implant> devices are primed and fully  operational for use!」	s02a	0130
S002A	4	13	He was the highest authority when it came to the practice of the  brainwashing and remodelling process, and had compiled his genius  for the sake of the Brainwashing <Memory Implant> devices.	s02a	0131
S002A	4	14	He had a slight figure but was a sharp individual who had established  a reputation, especially with respect to the army’s operation skills,  and was trusted by my staff officers for his judgement as well.	s02a	0132
S002A	4	15	He was a person whose hobby was to collect books. He idolized the  writers of the twentieth century who particularly liked violence  by rape, such as Marquis de Sade, and owned a number of his rare  paper-books.	s02a	0133
S002A	4	16	Bohgan: 「Lieutenant Olov!!!」	s02a	0134
S002A	4	17	Olov: 「N-New type of aphrodisiac has been p-perfected, C-Captain!!!」	s02a	0135
S002A	4	18	Olov: 「I will welcome the pig-sluts by thoroughly perverting them with  our cutting edge remodelling technology! Uhihi!」	s02a	0136
S002A	4	19	The mad-scientist with a Ph. D. degree in chemistry and who had  specialized in the research on aphrodisiacs, gave a vulgar smile.	s02a	0137
S002A	4	20	It could be said that he was the one genius who was born every  100 years, however, his field of interest was sexual abuse.	s02a	0138
S002A	4	21	He had a manic habit of cutting and collecting limbs and he had  also kept a few girls at his home, having fashioned them into  living sex-toys.	s02a	0139
S002A	4	22	Bohgan: 「Army-Surgeon Captain Magnus!!!」	s02a	0140
S002A	4	23	Magnus: 「Preparation of the “Convenient Personality” is complete.」	s02a	0141
S002A	4	24	Magnus: 「Mars will be yours to command in approximately two weeks, just  about the time when we transfer those two women to Libra City, my  Lord.」	s02a	0142
S002A	4	25	The aging man was a specialist on brain operations, and manipulated  memory functions.	s02a	0143
S002A	4	26	He had totally devoted himself to the development of perverted new  personalities (Perverted memory transformation), and worked hard  every day with that goal in mind. He was a really capable doctor.	s02a	0144
S002A	4	27	I had heard that he had two long-held dreams, to create a brain that  had the same function as a pussy, and a pussy that thought like a  brain.	s02a	0145
S002A	4	28	Major Hans, Captain Ingeborg, Lieutenant Olov, and Army-Surgeon  Captain Magnus.	s02a	0146
S002A	4	29	They were Bohgan’s confidants.	s02a	0147
S002A	4	30	Bohgan: 「Excellent, I look forward to your success. Hail for the glory of  Die Erde!!!」	s02a	0148
S002A	4	31	My Men: 「Hail!!!」	s02a	0149
S002A	4	32	It sounded like the burning chorus of lust.	s02a	0150
S002A	4	33	I retired to the Captain’s quarters, after having given my  subordinates the last of the instructions.	s02a	0151
S002A	4	34	I poured red Martian wine into my glass and raised my glass up to  the Martian sky, as a dust storm danced along it.	s02a	0152
S002A	4	35	Bohgan: 「Cordelia is on the verge of withering away due to these bloody  women rampaging violently all over Mars, but... I am close now.」	s02a	0153
S002A	4	36	Bohgan: 「As fate would have it, I have to overcome this problem again.」	s02a	0154
S002A	4	37	Bohgan: 「My most terrible enemies, Beatrice Kushan and Kila Kushan...  You will be made to wallow in my revenge, I swear it!」	s02a	0155
S002A	4	38	My right arm, with which I was holding the glass, creaked  slightly.	s02a	0156
S002A	4	39	It was giving off the jarring sound of a machine.	s02a	0157
S002A	4	40	My right arm was a prosthetic arm.	s02a	0158
S002A	5	1	Phantom limb pain.	s02a	0159
S002A	5	2	The spot where my arm had been severed by those women, was stinging  in pain.	s02a	0160
