S004A	1	1	6 hours ago.	s04a	0000
S004A	1	2	April 9―― 01:15	s04a	0001
S004A	1	3	280 kilometres north-west from the encounter point of the Die Erde  fleet and the Kushan fleet―――	s04a	0002
S004A	1	4	The shadowy silhouettes of mobile units appeared in the jet black  Sand Sea.	s04a	0003
S004A	1	5	It was the Augusta battalion comprised of 80 battle-mounts, launched  from the Die Erde fleet.	s04a	0004
S004A	1	6	They had set up 16 V-shaped formations comprised of 5 battle-mounts  each with its wings projecting forward, the so-called Crane wing  formation, and were advancing.	s04a	0005
S004A	1	7	They were moving through the Sand Sea as it slid underneath them,  and looked like giants who had placed their torsos on the base of  a tripod.	s04a	0006
S004A	1	8	A periscope was surveying all this from deep within the sand.	s04a	0007
S004A	1	9	――――	s04a	0008
S004A	1	10	Bouroux: 「Miss, the enemy’s task force has been discovered on the course as  expected. This is perfect.」	s04a	0009
S004A	1	11	An old man, who had the looks reminiscent of a hero from the medieval  times, said so cheerfully.	s04a	0010
S004A	1	12	Colonel Armand Bouroux.	s04a	0011
S004A	1	13	He was the Captain of the Kushan Armed Forces’s new weapon, the  Sand Sea type super high-speed submarine, Race.	s04a	0012
S004A	1	14	He was the most experienced officer of the Kushan Armed Forces.	s04a	0013
S004A	1	15	He had been personally appointed by Beatrice to be the guardian of  her daughter, Kila, similar to other older people of his ilk.	s04a	0014
S004A	1	16	Kila: 「Perhaps, the enemy had knowledge about the dispatch of our cavalry  unit, however... Fufufu... the speed of our advance has definitely  not been measured♪」	s04a	0015
S004A	1	17	Kila Kushan replied to him, as he stood on the bridge-deck.	s04a	0016
S004A	1	18	She was in the cockpit of the new Sand Sea armoured-mount, Excelsior,  which was docked to the high-speed submarine Race.	s04a	0017
S004A	1	19	Regardless of that, a radiant smile was etched onto her face.	s04a	0018
S004A	1	20	A smile―― which was very sharp.	s04a	0019
S004A	1	21	Bouroux: 「It was good that this Sand Sea type ultra-high-speed submarine,  <Race>, was ready in time for the war against the Die Erde Army,  Miss.」	s04a	0020
S004A	1	22	Kila: 「It is still too early to rejoice. I don’t think Mother will want  to lose to the enemy’s fleet, even though it is twice as large as  ours.」	s04a	0021
S004A	1	23	Bouroux: 「I know that very well! We will destroy the enemy’s new modelled  force quickly, before rushing in with a pointed ambush of our own  on the enemy’s fleet.」	s04a	0022
S004A	1	24	Kila: 「Yes, Armand. Timing is key♪」	s04a	0023
S004A	1	25	Bouroux was addressing Kila as “Miss” and Kila replied back, by  referring to him by his first name “Armand”.	s04a	0024
S004A	1	26	Although, Kila was the daughter of the Commodore Beatrice, who was  the Supreme Commander, it wasn’t in accordance to the protocols  within an organization like the army.	s04a	0025
S004A	1	27	Far from blaming Kila for calling him by his first name, Bouroux  looked at her with proud eyes, having developed an intimate bond  with her.	s04a	0026
S004A	1	28	There was a reason why it was said that, 『The fate of the Kushan  Armed Forces rests on the shoulders of the Lady and the Lass』.	s04a	0027
S004A	1	29	And so, the old man was advising the young girl directly, with a  face which showed that he was neither taking such things to heart,  nor paying mind to her trivial silliness.	s04a	0028
S004A	1	30	Bouroux: 「The ability of the enemy hasn’t yet been measured, Miss. Don’t  be negligent.」	s04a	0029
S004A	1	31	Kila: 「They won’t be able to demonstrate their abilities until we engage  them.」	s04a	0030
S004A	1	32	Kila said so, before nimbly pushing in the departure sequence.	s04a	0031
S004A	1	33	Bouroux: 「May the warrior’s fortune be with you.」	s04a	0032
S004A	1	34	Kila: 「Heavy armour Excelsior, deploying!」	s04a	0033
S004A	1	35	――――	s04a	0034
S004A	1	36	Zooooooosh!!!	s04a	0035
S004A	1	37	The sandy surface cracked heavily.	s04a	0036
S004A	1	38	And it burst out from the sand all of a sudden, blowing up sand  similar to a water-fountain.	s04a	0037
S004A	1	39	A distinctive silhouette with both shoulders spread wide, emerged  in the night sky.	s04a	0038
S004A	1	40	Kila was driving the Excelsior.	s04a	0039
S004A	2	1	Kila: 「Pain!!!」	s04a	0040
S004A	2	2	Her eyes sparkled.	s04a	0041
S004A	2	3	She moved her hand skilfully, which was holding the control stick.	s04a	0042
S004A	2	4	Her targets were locked on.	s04a	0043
S004A	2	5	8 small anti-ship jet-missiles,	s04a	0044
S004A	2	6	All were fired!	s04a	0045
S004A	2	7	――――	s04a	0046
S004A	2	8	Booooooooom!!	s04a	0047
S004A	2	9	Eight explosions spread out over the jet black Sand Sea.	s04a	0048
S004A	2	10	All were perfect strikes.	s04a	0049
S004A	2	11	All the targeted mounts of the Augusta battalion turned into scraps  of iron, in an instant.	s04a	0050
S004A	2	12	They had been caught off guard and the weakness of their armour was,  now, exposed.	s04a	0051
S004A	2	13	Kila: 「It is a new model! Looks like their armour is made of paper.」	s04a	0052
S004A	2	14	Kila smiled fearlessly, and stepped hard on the foot pedal.	s04a	0053
S004A	2	15	The thrusters of the Excelsior fired off with a roar.	s04a	0054
S004A	2	16	She plunged right into the core of the Augusta battalion without  hesitation, even though it still had 72 battle-mounts left.	s04a	0055
S004A	2	17	Augusta Soldiers: 「How did the enemy get here!?」	s04a	0056
S004A	2	18	Augusta Soldiers: 「I-It is massive!!」	s04a	0057
S004A	2	19	Augusta Soldiers: 「What the hell is that!? Does the enemy have a new model!!!?」	s04a	0058
S004A	2	20	Kila: 「Such dull reactions!!」	s04a	0059
S004A	2	21	Augusta Soldiers: 「This is 30 kilometres north of the calculated sand zone, isn’t  it!? Is this new model capable of travelling so fast...? Tch!!」	s04a	0060
S004A	2	22	Kila: 「Have made you slow!!」	s04a	0061
S004A	2	23	Augusta Soldiers: 「Uwaaaaaaaaah!!」	s04a	0062
S004A	2	24	The fact that 8 battle-mounts had suddenly been shot down in an  ambush, caused the soldiers of the Augusta battalion to fall into  an extreme panic.	s04a	0063
S004A	2	25	They couldn’t deal with this unexpected turn of events, and two  more mounts were shot down, followed by one more.	s04a	0064
S004A	2	26	Mecklinger: 「The opponent may be massive, but it is only one armoured-mount!  Even though it is a new model, the Augusta’s firepower has been  specially designed to deal with the Sand Sea armoured-mounts!」	s04a	0065
S004A	2	27	Augusta Soldiers: 「Y-Yes!!」	s04a	0066
S004A	2	28	Mecklinger: 「Besiege it securely, and bring it down!!」	s04a	0067
S004A	2	29	Augusta Soldiers: 「Roger that!!!」	s04a	0068
S004A	2	30	Mecklinger was truly a veteran war hero.	s04a	0069
S004A	2	31	He attempted to lead his floundering charges by inspiring them,  without being distracted at the unexpected ambush.	s04a	0070
S004A	2	32	It seemed like the calm demeanour of the Brigadier-General was  working, as the soldiers of the Augusta battalion regained their  poise and dispatched a number of their troops towards Kila, and  she was trapped within their siege.	s04a	0071
S004A	2	33	Kila: 「Their commander isn’t a fool.」	s04a	0072
S004A	2	34	Even though she had destroyed more than ten of their battle-mounts,  the enemy was still a massive group.	s04a	0073
S004A	2	35	However, despite being surrounded by them, Kila wasn’t even remotely  shaken.	s04a	0074
S004A	2	36	Mecklinger: 「I will draw the attention of the enemy! Deploy the bombs and blow  a hole in the flank of that massive thing!」	s04a	0075
S004A	2	37	Mecklinger plunged himself towards the enemy, just as the siege  enclosure shut completely.	s04a	0076
S004A	2	38	Kila: 「Hah! Did you think I would be deceived by such a manoeuvre!?」	s04a	0077
S004A	2	39	Wisely, Kila didn’t commit to battle with the onrushing machine.	s04a	0078
S004A	2	40	On the contrary, she moved organically around the enemy in order to  confuse the surrounding troops, as he tried to move in a coordinated  pattern while acting as a decoy.	s04a	0079
S004A	3	1	Considering that she was outnumbered, she moved skilfully, sliding  in and out of the line of sight of the surrounding enemy units so  that if they did attack her, they would end up slaughtering each  other.	s04a	0080
S004A	3	2	The Excelsior’s big frame was being driven brilliantly, even though  it was twice the size of the Augusta.	s04a	0081
S004A	3	3	Its splendidly flowing movement looked like a brilliant dance being  performed by a giant on the sandy stage.	s04a	0082
S004A	3	4	Obviously, the soldiers of the Augusta were unable to take any  actions and started to panic yet again.	s04a	0083
S004A	3	5	Augusta Soldiers: 「W-What is this thing!? What a monster!!」	s04a	0084
S004A	3	6	Mecklinger: 「Don’t shoot!! You will end up shooting each other!!!」	s04a	0085
S004A	3	7	By the time Mecklinger realized his soldiers’ intentions, it was  already too late.	s04a	0086
S004A	3	8	The Excelsior danced nimbly, one step at a time, around the Augusta,  as a diaspora of explosions engulfed their surroundings.	s04a	0087
S004A	3	9	Mecklinger: 「This movement... The famed practice of the Grim Reaper, huh?」	s04a	0088
S004A	3	10	Mecklinger: 『This new model! Is it being operated by the ace of the Kushan  Armed Forces, Kila Kushan!?』	s04a	0089
S004A	3	11	Mecklinger turned on the communications-line and called out to his  opponent.	s04a	0090
S004A	3	12	It looked like blood had rushed into the head of the ace-pilot,  on having come up against a formidable opponent.	s04a	0091
S004A	3	13	Kila: 『So, are you their Commander? Name yourself.』	s04a	0092
S004A	3	14	Kila gave him a similarly pointed response,	s04a	0093
S004A	3	15	As they continued their fierce battle with each other.	s04a	0094
S004A	3	16	Mecklinger: 『Mecklinger, Brigadier-General Emmerich Mecklinger.』	s04a	0095
S004A	3	17	Kila: 『Fufufu... Cordelia’s wolf on the Martian surface?』	s04a	0096
S004A	3	18	Mecklinger: 『It is an honour to meet the Grim Reaper of the Sand Sea. Ladies  first is my creed. I will banish you to the netherworld of the sand  very soon.』	s04a	0097
S004A	3	19	Kila: 『Ladies first？ Don’t make me laugh, you perverted homo-sexual  bastard.』	s04a	0098
S004A	3	20	Mecklinger: 『Still... it is extremely uncultured for a woman to enter the  battlefield, Miss. I will banish you, along with your mother.』	s04a	0099
S004A	3	21	Kila: 『Keep on prattling!』	s04a	0100
S004A	3	22	They didn’t retreat from each other.	s04a	0101
S004A	3	23	Both put their lives on the line and continued to shoot, while  abusing each other.	s04a	0102
S004A	3	24	After tens of seconds, their bout was complete.	s04a	0103
S004A	3	25	Mecklinger: 『Of course, blood is likely to rise to your head immediately,  especially since you are a woman.』	s04a	0104
S004A	3	26	Mecklinger confirmed that his subordinates had positioned themselves  on the flanks,	s04a	0105
S004A	3	27	And on his next attack, he feinted quickly and raced to her backside,  putting considerable distance between them.	s04a	0106
S004A	3	28	Kila: 『Brisk!』	s04a	0107
S004A	3	29	Kila opened up her thrusters fully.	s04a	0108
S004A	3	30	She went into overdrive and chased after the fleeing Mecklinger.	s04a	0109
S004A	3	31	The black battle-mount raced like a meteor over the Sand Sea.	s04a	0110
S004A	3	32	Mecklinger: 『Now!!!』	s04a	0111
S004A	3	33	Mecklinger’s men were waiting for that straight-line movement.	s04a	0112
S004A	3	34	The firepower of dozens of battle-mounts of the Augusta battalion  converged.	s04a	0113
S004A	3	35	The Excelsior was enveloped in a tremendous explosion, due to the  attack that was done from all sides.	s04a	0114
S004A	3	36	Mecklinger: 『Farewell, Miss!』	s04a	0115
S004A	3	37	Cordelia’s wolf said brazenly.	s04a	0116
S004A	3	38	However―――	s04a	0117
S004A	3	39	As the smoke of the explosion slowly cleared,	s04a	0118
S004A	3	40	The still-intact frame of the Excelsior appeared.	s04a	0119
S004A	4	1	Kila: 『Un-for-tu-nate.』	s04a	0120
S004A	4	2	Mecklinger: 『R-Ridiculous!? Even the main-cannon firepower of the Augusta’s  battle-mounts couldn’t get through that!?』	s04a	0121
S004A	4	3	Unable to hide it, a look of astonishment spread over Mecklinger’s  face, even though he was someone who bore great pride in possessing  an orderly appearance.	s04a	0122
S004A	4	4	Kila: 『Kukuku... Did you really think you had caught me in your trap?』	s04a	0123
S004A	4	5	A distortion occurred in the air around the Excelsior, and little  sparks of lightning ran across it.	s04a	0124
S004A	4	6	An invisible field was enveloping the battle-mount.	s04a	0125
S004A	4	7	Mecklinger: 『A sh-shield weapon!? How!!?』	s04a	0126
S004A	4	8	Kila: 『The shield is down to 20%. Surprisingly, your firepower is  equivalent in its potency to the Sand Sea armoured-mounts of  “The Dreadnought”.』	s04a	0127
S004A	4	9	Even though she was extremely surprised, Kila was grinning with  a fearless smile etched across her face.	s04a	0128
S004A	4	10	Mecklinger: 『Kuuuh!!!!?』	s04a	0129
S004A	4	11	Mecklinger clenched his teeth.	s04a	0130
S004A	4	12	Kila: 『Cordelia’s wolf, do you really think you have the time to  hesitate?』	s04a	0131
S004A	4	13	Mecklinger: 『Fuh... Well, you seem to be quite proud of that shield,  however――』	s04a	0132
S004A	4	14	Mecklinger was trying to regain his composure.	s04a	0133
S004A	4	15	However, his words were interrupted midway.	s04a	0134
S004A	4	16	Beeeeeep!!	s04a	0135
S004A	4	17	Mecklinger: 『What!?』	s04a	0136
S004A	4	18	Warning beeps reflected across the control-panel of Mecklinger’s  battle-mount.	s04a	0137
S004A	4	19	No, not just his. Most of his battalion’s mounts were beeping.	s04a	0138
S004A	4	20	It was a lock-on warning.	s04a	0139
S004A	4	21	Augusta Soldiers: 『There are numerous metal reactions in the sand!?』	s04a	0140
S004A	4	22	Augusta Soldiers: 『M-Missiles!!!!』	s04a	0141
S004A	4	23	Mecklinger: 『All units, use evasive manoeuvres at once!!!』	s04a	0142
S004A	4	24	Mecklinger screamed at his subordinates, while also acting on his  own in order to avoid the incoming missiles.	s04a	0143
S004A	4	25	A group of missiles burst out from the sand.	s04a	0144
S004A	4	26	They were a tremendous number.	s04a	0145
S004A	4	27	Mecklinger: (Were there other submarines in the sand, besides hers!?)	s04a	0146
S004A	4	28	However, not only did the missiles approach.	s04a	0147
S004A	4	29	The sandy surface itself blew up, as if a volcano had erupted.	s04a	0148
S004A	4	30	The armoured-mounts of “The Dreadnought”, along with the intact  Sand Sea Armoured Cavalry Unit of the Kushan fleet, all came forth  together.	s04a	0149
S004A	4	31	A total of 30 battle-mounts.	s04a	0150
S004A	4	32	The missile-attack had been a decoy as well.	s04a	0151
S004A	4	33	Just as the formation of the Augusta battalion collapsed to avoid  them,	s04a	0152
S004A	4	34	As if having been waiting for it in the dark depths of the sand, the  troops of the Dreadnought surfaced and brought forth their ambush.	s04a	0153
S004A	4	35	Mecklinger: 『Their Armoured Cavalry Unit is all over us!? How is this  possible!!!!?』	s04a	0154
S004A	4	36	A flash of explosions lit up in a sequence.	s04a	0155
S004A	4	37	Mecklinger: 『Was their pace more than what we had measured!!?』	s04a	0156
S004A	4	38	The good-looking man’s mask of composure had completely collapsed  by now.	s04a	0157
S004A	4	39	The reason why the Die Erde faction was able to continue the  excellent advance of its irresistible forces in outer space――	s04a	0158
S004A	4	40	Was because of the tactical deployment of the Chinook assault-esque  transport-ships, as a means to compensate for cruising long  distances at high speeds, which was one of the major weaknesses  of the armoured-knights,	s04a	0159
S004A	5	1	In the Sand Sea of Mars, Mecklinger had underestimated the  possibility that the enemy could have methods to realize a  similar means of transport.	s04a	0160
S004A	5	2	It had left him knocking on the doors of the netherworld.	s04a	0161
S004A	5	3	Kila: 『Farewell, Brigadier-General.』	s04a	0162
S004A	5	4	He heard the voice of the Grim Reaper of the Sand Sea over the  death throes of his subordinates.	s04a	0163
S004A	5	5	Her cold voice was well-suited for both her personas.	s04a	0164
S004A	5	6	Mecklinger: 『!!!!!!!!』	s04a	0165
S004A	5	7	At that very moment,	s04a	0166
S004A	5	8	Kila’s single sniping strike blew up the body of Mecklinger’s  battle-mount into numerous pieces.	s04a	0167
S004A	5	9	Although, Mecklinger had successfully managed to avoid the  missile-attack, as well as the ambush of The Dreadnought,	s04a	0168
S004A	5	10	Kila was never going to miss this critical opportunity.	s04a	0169
S004A	5	11	And then――――	s04a	0170
S004A	5	12	10 battle-mounts had been caught in the decoy missile-attack,	s04a	0171
S004A	5	13	More than 28 battle-mounts were demolished or shot down in the  subsequent fierce assault of the Dreadnought.	s04a	0172
S004A	5	14	In a few hours, the Augusta battalion lost its General with more than  half of its forces, and was completely thrown out of the battle.	s04a	0173
S004A	5	15	Now, all they had to do was wait and hunt down the remainder.	s04a	0174
S004A	5	16	SALTAR: S005A
