S015A	1	1	... ... ... ...	s15a	0000
S015A	1	2	I invited Beatrice and Kila for breakfast, after having concluded  the two farces that I had performed early in the morning.	s15a	0001
S015A	1	3	Beatrice: 「... ... ... ...」	s15a	0002
S015A	1	4	Kila: 「... ... ... ... ... ...」	s15a	0003
S015A	1	5	Yesterday, both of them had gobbled food up like pigs on a pig farm,  however, they didn’t seem to be eating even a bit of it today.	s15a	0004
S015A	1	6	They seemed to be really uncomfortable, as they merely sipped on  some orange juice and munched on a bit of bread.	s15a	0005
S015A	1	7	It seemed like their clitorises were grazing against their panties  even now, and both of them continued to adjust their sitting postures  constantly, while squirming their bodies restlessly.	s15a	0006
S015A	1	8	It was amusing looking at them trying to endure the pleasure and  the mother and daughter, who usually had an intimate relationship,  were uncharacteristically silent and had barely even looked at each  other.	s15a	0007
S015A	1	9	Bohgan: 「What would you two like to have this morning?」	s15a	0008
S015A	1	10	Kila: 「Huh?」	s15a	0009
S015A	1	11	Beatrice: 「Have what!?」	s15a	0010
S015A	1	12	When I spoke out, both of them got startled and raised their faces  together.	s15a	0011
S015A	1	13	Bohgan: 「No, I mean I don’t feel like eating much right now.」	s15a	0012
S015A	1	14	Beatrice: 「N-No... I think I drank a bit too much yesterday...」	s15a	0013
S015A	1	15	Kila: 「Ahuuu... Me too... I have a bit of a hangover...」	s15a	0014
S015A	1	16	Beatrice: 「Kila, you as well? It seems the mother and her daughter are quite  alike, especially when it comes to this thing, huh...? Hehe...」	s15a	0015
S015A	1	17	Kila: 「Yes. That is true, isn’t it...? Hehehe...」	s15a	0016
S015A	1	18	The mother-daughter pair laughed awkwardly.	s15a	0017
S015A	1	19	However, they were purposely avoiding looking at each other.	s15a	0018
S015A	1	20	They were afraid of looking into each other’s eyes.	s15a	0019
S015A	1	21	Moreover, each of them couldn’t care less about the other’s  strained behaviour, as they desperately tried to suppress the  constant throbbing of their clitorises.	s15a	0020
S015A	1	22	Bohgan: 「Yesterday, I drank too much as well. I can’t even remember how  many times I had to use the toilet last night.」	s15a	0021
S015A	1	23	Beatrice: 「... ... ... ...!」	s15a	0022
S015A	1	24	Kila: 「... ... ...!」	s15a	0023
S015A	1	25	Both their bodies shuddered.	s15a	0024
S015A	1	26	Bohgan: 「Ah, No... Apologies for my impoliteness. It isn’t a topic that I  should be going on about when having a meal.」	s15a	0025
S015A	1	27	Beatrice: 「Ah... Yes... That’s right.」	s15a	0026
S015A	1	28	Kila: 「Please refrain yourself...」	s15a	0027
S015A	1	29	Both of them hung their heads down in embarrassment and started  biting their lips.	s15a	0028
S015A	1	30	Bohgan: (Kukukuku... These reactions.)	s15a	0029
S015A	1	31	They knew that they had urinated as well.	s15a	0030
S015A	1	32	And while doing so, they had revelled in the luscious pleasure from  that act.	s15a	0031
S015A	1	33	However, had they noticed that the pleasure that was born every time  they walked wasn’t simply because of their clit-rings?	s15a	0032
S015A	1	34	Both these women had been undermined by a kind of “poison”, which  had been injected into the entirety of their skeletal framework,  causing their entire bodies to be eroticized.	s15a	0033
S015A	1	35	And since they didn’t know about it, it was bound to be extremely  bewildering.	s15a	0034
S015A	1	36	That was exactly what I had aimed for.	s15a	0035
S015A	1	37	To have unknown pleasure gush out of their own bodies, like steam.	s15a	0036
S015A	1	38	Just imagining both of them suffering that hellish carnal pleasure  had caused my crotch to seethe with the heat of lust.	s15a	0037
S015A	1	39	Bohgan: (Even so...)	s15a	0038
S015A	1	40	This mother-daughter witch-duo had become jittery due to the events  of the morning and I couldn’t help but be amused by their awkward  appearances.	s15a	0039
S015A	2	1	Bohgan: (I am certain that you two had never even imagined that you would be  waking up in bed with me.)	s15a	0040
S015A	2	2	Both the women had, seemingly, submitted their bodies to me under  the influence of alcohol and allowed me to install clit-rings onto  them.	s15a	0041
S015A	2	3	Both of them didn’t want those series of shameful acts to be known  by the other.	s15a	0042
S015A	2	4	Having been the one to have orchestrated this situation, I felt  like mocking both the women as I watched them try their best  to not arouse even a bit of suspicion in the other.	s15a	0043
S015A	2	5	Bohgan: 「By the way, I want to talk about something that happened  yesterday to the both of you――」	s15a	0044
S015A	2	6	Beatrice: 「W-What!?」	s15a	0045
S015A	2	7	Kila: 「What is it?」	s15a	0046
S015A	2	8	Both the women got startled and raised their heads.	s15a	0047
S015A	2	9	Their faces became stiff as they thought, 『Surely not that?』, and  they became oblivious to presence of the other.	s15a	0048
S015A	2	10	I let out a chuckle and said with a grin,	s15a	0049
S015A	2	11	Bohgan: 「There is still a lot of the wine left with which I treated both of  you last night. How about it? Can both of you give me your esteemed  company tonight as well?」	s15a	0050
S015A	2	12	Beatrice: 「I will pass on it!!」	s15a	0051
S015A	2	13	Kila: 「I am going to pass!」	s15a	0052
S015A	2	14	Both of them raised their voices in unison and rebuffed my offer.	s15a	0053
S015A	2	15	Even though they had an intimate relationship, they still wanted to  keep that a secret from each other.	s15a	0054
S015A	2	16	Bohgan: 「Is that so? That is unfortunate... I had hoped that we would be  able to have a good time again.」	s15a	0055
S015A	2	17	Beatrice: 「... ... ... ...」	s15a	0056
S015A	2	18	Kila: 「... ... ... ... ... ...」	s15a	0057
S015A	2	19	When I said that with a suggestive smile, both the women fell silent  in embarrassment.	s15a	0058
S015A	2	20	Beatrice: 「I think I drank too much yesterday, which is why I will excuse  myself today.」	s15a	0059
S015A	2	21	Beatrice said that before getting off her seat and left the  military-lounge, without saying a word to her own daughter.	s15a	0060
S015A	2	22	Despite the fact that she was being tormented by her clitoris now,  the manner in which she walked out seemed normal, just as I had  expected of the Empress.	s15a	0061
S015A	2	23	Kila: 「I will excuse myself. Thank you for the meal.」	s15a	0062
S015A	2	24	Kila got up as well and turned her back to me.	s15a	0063
S015A	2	25	Bohgan: 「You need to be more natural. Otherwise, your mother is going to  get suspicious.」	s15a	0064
S015A	2	26	Kila: 「I know.」	s15a	0065
S015A	2	27	Kila said so without looking back, stretched her back and walked out,  however, she was much slower compared to her mother.	s15a	0066
S015A	2	28	After being left alone, I began to eat my big portion of food in  order to build up my reserves of energy for the day.	s15a	0067
S015A	2	29	Bohgan: 「Well, that was a good performance.」	s15a	0068
S015A	2	30	I had successfully managed to establish secrets with both the  women.	s15a	0069
S015A	2	31	Since both of them had a sharp perception, they were bound to  notice the awkwardness of the other,	s15a	0070
S015A	2	32	Which is why they were being forced to act calmly, since they  couldn’t afford the other to notice it.	s15a	0071
S015A	2	33	Bohgan: 「Well then, what should I do now...?」	s15a	0072
S015A	2	34	I began thinking about it while in the Captain’s quarters.	s15a	0073
S015A	2	35	Due to today’s preparations, there was no risk for me of being  suddenly killed by having my brains blown out.	s15a	0074
S015A	2	36	However, I didn’t believe that both of them had completely  submitted to me yet.	s15a	0075
S015A	2	37	If both of them had planned to kidnap the old man as per my  expectations, then it was crucial for them to let this ship  be under my command.	s15a	0076
S015A	2	38	However, this was the Empress and the Grim Reaper that I was  dealing with.	s15a	0077
S015A	2	39	If their bodies were undermined too much by pleasure, it was very  likely that they might try to force the situation.	s15a	0078
S015A	2	40	How would they reveal themselves?	s15a	0079
S015A	3	1	And what measures could I undertake to counter them?	s15a	0080
S015A	3	2	SELECCIONAR 1: S015B
S015A	3	3	SELECCIONAR 2: S015C
