S018A	1	1	Voyage: Day 4――	s18a	0000
S018A	1	2	Beatrice: 「... ... ... ... ... ...」	s18a	0001
S018A	1	3	Kila: 「... ... ... ... ... ...」	s18a	0002
S018A	1	4	I was having breakfast with the two “conscious” women this  morning.	s18a	0003
S018A	1	5	Although both of them were eating their meals slowly, they seemed  to be pretty normal.	s18a	0004
S018A	1	6	They had come over to the military-lounge to eat by themselves, and  there didn’t seem to be any complications.	s18a	0005
S018A	1	7	Fuuuh... I felt relief in my heart.	s18a	0006
S018A	1	8	After all, I had performed the dream-memory infiltration on both  of them yesterday, which involved the risk of the subjects becoming  invalid.	s18a	0007
S018A	1	9	Either way, it would have been amusing even if they had become  invalid.	s18a	0008
S018A	1	10	However, I would have had to alter my plans greatly, if that had  indeed transpired.	s18a	0009
S018A	1	11	Beatrice: 「... Fuuuh...」	s18a	0010
S018A	1	12	Kila: 「... Uhuuu...」	s18a	0011
S018A	1	13	Neither Beatrice nor Kila knew that they had been interrogated  within their dreams, or that their bodies had been remodelled  while they were being brainwashed at the same time.	s18a	0012
S018A	1	14	However, they could feel the change in their bodies today.	s18a	0013
S018A	1	15	Not only were they not proceeding with their meals, but they were  also unconsciously letting out sighs, tinged with carnal desires.	s18a	0014
S018A	1	16	Knowing this mother-daughter pair, they had no doubt tried to  determine the cause of their abnormal feelings, by means of  blood-tests.	s18a	0015
S018A	1	17	However, they could never even imagine that their very bones and  their urethras had been obscenely remodelled.	s18a	0016
S018A	1	18	And, it was nearly impossible to examine anyway.	s18a	0017
S018A	1	19	Beatrice: 「... Hnghnnn...」	s18a	0018
S018A	1	20	Kila: 「... Fuuuuh...」	s18a	0019
S018A	1	21	Every time the mother and her daughter leaned forward to have their  meal, they were being assaulted by a throbbing sensation causing them  to flush all over and hold their breaths.	s18a	0020
S018A	1	22	As a sharp shiver ran through their bodies, they both became so  uncomfortable that they stopped bothering to even acknowledge my  presence.	s18a	0021
S018A	1	23	Bohgan: (Looks like the clit-rings are working their magic... Kukuku...)	s18a	0022
S018A	1	24	It seemed like the clit-rings, which was a secret between me and  each of them, was undermining their strong and noble spirits.	s18a	0023
S018A	1	25	Beatrice: 「Captain...」	s18a	0024
S018A	1	26	Bohgan: 「What is the matter, Commodore? It seems like you haven’t eaten  much at all.」	s18a	0025
S018A	1	27	Beatrice: 「I haven’t been feeling well since this morning.」	s18a	0026
S018A	1	28	Bohgan: 「Say no more. I will make arrangements with my medical staff  immediately to──」	s18a	0027
S018A	1	29	Beatrice: 「That won’t be necessary...」	s18a	0028
S018A	1	30	Bohgan: 「Is that so? Well, as you wish, Commodore.」	s18a	0029
S018A	1	31	Beatrice: 「Even so... We would prefer to have our meals in our room.」	s18a	0030
S018A	1	32	Bohgan: 「Both of you? In that case, I will have my subordinates deliver it  to your room.」	s18a	0031
S018A	1	33	Kila: 「No need... Just let our juniors deliver it to us.」	s18a	0032
S018A	1	34	They were planning to examine the food in the hopes of finding the  cause of their bodies’ abnormalities.	s18a	0033
S018A	1	35	The food was completely normal, obviously, and there was nothing to  gain out of it.	s18a	0034
S018A	1	36	However, the fruits of the brainwashing and remodelling process  were showing such strong effects that they couldn’t help but be  suspicious of just about everything.	s18a	0035
S018A	1	37	I felt elated while thinking about how my outright devious schemes  were undermining the bodies of both these bloody women, with them  having no clue about it whatsoever.	s18a	0036
S018A	1	38	So much so, that I was almost about to burst out in laughter.	s18a	0037
S018A	1	39	Kila: 「Captain... Can you help us procure some drugs from the  infirmary?」	s18a	0038
S018A	1	40	Bohgan: 「I understand. I will let the Doctor know about it.」	s18a	0039
S018A	2	1	Both of them were about to leave the lounge, having spoken what was  on their mind.	s18a	0040
S018A	2	2	Bohgan: 「Commodore, please wait a moment.」	s18a	0041
S018A	2	3	Beatrice: 「... What is it?」	s18a	0042
S018A	2	4	Bohgan: 「I have to talk to you about something. It is concerning that  thing.」	s18a	0043
S018A	2	5	I said that and quickly ran my eyes over the part of her attire  covering her crotch.	s18a	0044
S018A	2	6	Beatrice: 「... ... ... ...!」	s18a	0045
S018A	2	7	Beatrice noticed my eyes and gasped out in shock.	s18a	0046
S018A	2	8	She realized immediately what it was that I wanted to talk to her  about.	s18a	0047
S018A	2	9	It was about the “specially made” ring that had been shamefully  installed onto her sensitive place.	s18a	0048
S018A	2	10	Kila: 「... Mother?」	s18a	0049
S018A	2	11	Beatrice: 「... I am sorry, but please go on ahead.」	s18a	0050
S018A	2	12	Kila: 「Yes...」	s18a	0051
S018A	2	13	Kila left us after looking at the expression on her mother’s face  with a puzzled look.	s18a	0052
S018A	2	14	Bohgan: 「Now, to the Captain’s quarters.」	s18a	0053
S018A	2	15	Beatrice: 「... ... ... ...」	s18a	0054
S018A	2	16	Beatrice was glaring at me but obeyed by orders regardless and  followed me.	s18a	0055
S018A	2	17	Beatrice: 「What the hell were you thinking!?」	s18a	0056
S018A	2	18	No sooner had we reached the Captain’s quarters than she started  barking at me furiously.	s18a	0057
S018A	2	19	The outspoken manner in which she was behaving now was completely  different to the way she had been acting in front of her daughter.	s18a	0058
S018A	2	20	Bohgan: 「You have become really moody all of a sudden.」	s18a	0059
S018A	2	21	Beatrice: 「Shut up.」	s18a	0060
S018A	2	22	Bohgan: 「It is really cold considering it is towards a man who you indulged  with in the pleasures of the flesh, Commodore... No, Beatrice.」	s18a	0061
S018A	2	23	Beatrice: 「You bastard!」	s18a	0062
S018A	2	24	She seized my collar with an expression on her face like that of  a lioness, which would have been enough to make an average person  cower in fear.	s18a	0063
S018A	2	25	Beatrice: 「Don’t misunderstand me, Captain.」	s18a	0064
S018A	2	26	Bohgan: 「Misunderstand you? And why is that?」	s18a	0065
S018A	2	27	Beatrice: 「What happened that night was a mistake. It will never happen  between you and me ever again.」	s18a	0066
S018A	2	28	She pulled my face close to hers forcefully and glared at me with  overbearing eyes, as if trying to crush my spirit.	s18a	0067
S018A	2	29	Beatrice: 「A cruel fate will be in store for you, if you dare to bring me  anymore trouble.」	s18a	0068
S018A	2	30	The Empress was surprisingly back to her impertinent best, despite  having been despondent for the entirety of yesterday as if she had  been resurrected.	s18a	0069
S018A	2	31	Bohgan: (Kukuku, To think this woman is still like this... It is just as I  had expected.)	s18a	0070
S018A	2	32	If not for this woman, I wouldn’t have lost my subordinates or my  right arm in that fateful naval war, which had also damaged my pride  considerably.	s18a	0071
S018A	2	33	Bohgan: 「So, are you fine with the way things are? Without my cooperation,  that “accessory” will be a part of you for your entire life.」	s18a	0072
S018A	2	34	Beatrice: 「Fuh... Are you threatening me? Don’t forget that there are many  ways for me to make you obey me, one of them being “allowing you  to live”.」	s18a	0073
S018A	2	35	Bohgan: 「Fuuuh... I understand. Well then, since you mean business, let us  make a deal.」	s18a	0074
S018A	2	36	Beatrice: 「... A deal?」	s18a	0075
S018A	2	37	Beatrice rebuffed my offer, as if she had caught a whiff of danger  emanating from me.	s18a	0076
S018A	2	38	Bohgan: 「How about just for the duration of your time on this ship? You  would really love to say “I compel you to obey my orders” while  we are here, won’t you?」	s18a	0077
S018A	2	39	Beatrice: 「... ... ... ...」	s18a	0078
S018A	2	40	She narrowed her eyes and glared at me fixedly, as if trying to see  through me.	s18a	0079
S018A	3	1	Bohgan: 「Being with you that night was unforgettable for me. Especially  that beautiful and flexible body of yours. And... I promise to  personally cooperate in the removal of your clit-ring.」	s18a	0080
S018A	3	2	Beatrice: 「Fuh. To think a haughty Libran soldier would even consider making  a business deal with me, as if we were on equal terms.」	s18a	0081
S018A	3	3	Beatrice stuck out her chest proudly.	s18a	0082
S018A	3	4	They were hidden at the moment, however, the nipples on her boobs  would always be supremely erect from now.	s18a	0083
S018A	3	5	Bohgan: 「I beg your pardon.」	s18a	0084
S018A	3	6	Beatrice: 「So, what are you hoping for?」	s18a	0085
S018A	3	7	Bohgan: 「Obviously, to be with you──」	s18a	0086
S018A	3	8	Beatrice: 「There will be NO sex.」	s18a	0087
S018A	3	9	She gave a pointed response, having anticipated what I was about to  propose.	s18a	0088
S018A	3	10	Bohgan: 「Is it because of your sense of duty towards your daughter and  your husband?」	s18a	0089
S018A	3	11	Beatrice: 「────!」	s18a	0090
S018A	3	12	A bloodlust raced through Beatrice.	s18a	0091
S018A	3	13	Even though she was simply glaring at me, it almost felt as if I was  suffocating while being strangled.	s18a	0092
S018A	3	14	Bohgan: 「No, I meant...! It was a slip of tongue, please forgive me.  Roger that, no sex it is then. In that case, there is only one  other thing that we can do.」	s18a	0093
S018A	3	15	It was a proposal that the Empress would never accept under  normal circumstances.	s18a	0094
S018A	3	16	However, the Empress’s body was now being undermined by the  clit-ring, the torment of which had made her heart malleable.	s18a	0095
S018A	3	17	Beatrice: 「Kuh... What a sneak.」	s18a	0096
S018A	3	18	Beatrice gave me a sharp look, which was filled with her  humiliation.	s18a	0097
S018A	3	19	Bohgan: 「Are you okay with that?」	s18a	0098
S018A	3	20	Beatrice: 「If this annoying ring doesn’t come off, I will kill you in the  cruellest way possible in this universe.」	s18a	0099
S018A	3	21	Bohgan: 「I do want a long life as well. Please, be rest assured.」	s18a	0100
S018A	3	22	This woman would probably have already killed me right here, if she  had possessed the means to remove the ring herself.	s18a	0101
S018A	3	23	As easily as one crushes an insect.	s18a	0102
S018A	3	24	However, that was all ifs and buts.	s18a	0103
S018A	3	25	In any case, this terrifying woman was going to be my puppet by the  time we reached Libra.	s18a	0104
S018A	3	26	She was worth the risk.	s18a	0105
S018A	3	27	After all, Beatrice Kushan was going to be a woman only until that  point.	s18a	0106
S018A	3	28	After all, this woman──	s18a	0107
S018A	3	29	Was a woman that I could enjoy the most when she was still  “conscious”.	s18a	0108
S018A	3	30	Beatrice: 「So, what are you planning to do?」	s18a	0109
S018A	3	31	Bohgan: 「Well then...」	s18a	0110
