S025B	1	1	Subordinates: 「Thank you very much.」	s25b	0000
S025B	1	2	The perverted scientists, Hans, Ingeborg, Olov, and Magnus, were  all seemingly relieved with the results of the brainwashing and  remodelling process, which was now on the verge of completion.	s25b	0001
S025B	1	3	However, I noticed a slight flash of anxiety go over their faces.	s25b	0002
S025B	1	4	Bohgan: 「Gentlemen, what is the matter?」	s25b	0003
S025B	1	5	I asked my colleagues the reason for their anxiety, after having  sensed it.	s25b	0004
S025B	1	6	Hans opened his mouth of behalf of the entire staff.	s25b	0005
S025B	1	7	Hans: 「Even now the navigation-system is still under lockdown, Captain.  I couldn’t lift it.」	s25b	0006
S025B	1	8	Hans: 「In case we are attacked tomorrow, all our efforts will amount to  nothing. Even though the brainwashing degree is at 90% presently,  what is incomplete is incomplete nonetheless.」	s25b	0007
S025B	1	9	Bohgan: 「Are you implying that I am not prepared for it?」	s25b	0008
S025B	1	10	Hans didn’t respond to that.	s25b	0009
S025B	1	11	Hans: 「Let me report the results from our investigation in the infirmary  of the communication records, Captain.」	s25b	0010
S025B	1	12	Bohgan: 「Very well.」	s25b	0011
S025B	1	13	Hans: 「Captain, as you guessed rightly, the Empress and the Grim Reaper  ordered a raid by relaying assault-points on our planned route from  the infirmary.」	s25b	0012
S025B	1	14	Hans: 「It will occur at 15:00 exactly, right before their brainwashing  process is to be completed.」	s25b	0013
S025B	1	15	Bohgan: 「Well, well...」	s25b	0014
S025B	1	16	The Goddess of Destiny was, undoubtedly, a woman who despised me  thoroughly.	s25b	0015
S025B	1	17	Hans: 「We can’t alter our plan at this stage. However, we could get  them to unlock the navigation-system, by using the dream-memory  infiltration device.」	s25b	0016
S025B	1	18	Hans: 「I suggest we kill these pigs, after we alter our route.」	s25b	0017
S025B	1	19	Bohgan: 「The dream-memory infiltration device, huh? You know what it means  to use it on them again, don’t you?」	s25b	0018
S025B	1	20	Hans: 「The probability of them becoming invalid will rise up to 50%, as  it will be their second dream-memory infiltration. What do you say,  Captain?」	s25b	0019
S025B	1	21	Hans truly considered it to be the appropriate course of action.	s25b	0020
S025B	1	22	However, I shook my head.	s25b	0021
S025B	1	23	Bohgan: 「That can’t be allowed to happen. In case that does happen, the  old man of the Neo-Terras will be only one who will be pleased.」	s25b	0022
S025B	1	24	Bohgan: 「Even if the Kushan Armed Forces are defeated, we don’t possess a  powerful enough force to clean up this mess.」	s25b	0023
S025B	1	25	Bohgan: 「Mars will descend into further chaos, and that will only benefit  the powerful Neo-Terras and New-Solars.」	s25b	0024
S025B	1	26	Hans: 「Nevertheless, Captain...」	s25b	0025
S025B	1	27	I raised my hand to shut Hans’s mouth.	s25b	0026
S025B	1	28	Bohgan: 「Complete the brainwashing of these pigs, so that we can take over  the Kushan Armed Forces and gain control of Mars.」	s25b	0027
S025B	1	29	Bohgan: 「We have to gain control of their infantry, in order to emerge  victorious against the powerful Neo-Terras and New-Solars.」	s25b	0028
S025B	1	30	Hans: 「Well then, shall I imprison them?」	s25b	0029
S025B	1	31	I shook my head again.	s25b	0030
S025B	1	32	Bohgan: 「Be completely indifferent unless something out of the ordinary  happens. It will be my perfect victory, if I can understand what  these intelligent pigs are up to.」	s25b	0031
S025B	1	33	Bohgan: 「I know that you all are feeling anxious. However, I have faith in  the brainwashing and remodelling process, that you all have overseen  so far.」	s25b	0032
S025B	1	34	Bohgan: 「I have absolute trust in you all, so much so, that I am entrusting  all our lives in your hands. This is my request. For the sake of our  perfect victory!」	s25b	0033
S025B	1	35	Subordinates: 「Y-Yes Sir!!」	s25b	0034
S025B	1	36	My men steeled themselves as well, after hearing my words.	s25b	0035
S025B	1	37	And, that was that.	s25b	0036
S025B	1	38	Victory or death?	s25b	0037
S025B	1	39	The Goddess of Destiny could go to hell.	s25b	0038
S025B	1	40	If there was such a goddess, I would rape her.	s25b	0039
S025B	2	1	If she was a witch, I would impregnate her.	s25b	0040
S025B	2	2	This was how it had always been for me... This was the way of Donny  Bohgan.	s25b	0041
S025B	2	3	To believe in myself and push forward.	s25b	0042
S025B	2	4	―――― Eight days until our arrival in Libra.	s25b	0043
S025B	2	5	SALTAR: S026A
S025B	2	6	SALTAR: S026A
