S031A	1	1	On November 10.	s31a	0000
S031A	1	2	Twelve days after our departure from Perseus City.	s31a	0001
S031A	1	3	The battleship, Tristan, arrived safely in Libra.	s31a	0002
S031A	1	4	I was waiting for a man at the Libra space-station, along with the  Kushan mother and daughter.	s31a	0003
S031A	1	5	General William Ahle Moller of the Neo-Terras.	s31a	0004
S031A	1	6	I had planned to capture him, after having lured him in by using  both these women as bait.	s31a	0005
S031A	1	7	I had already notified the senile yet lustful old man that the  brainwashing process on them had been completed.	s31a	0006
S031A	1	8	I had placed both my arms behind my back as I was pretending to be  their prisoner, which was all just a sham.	s31a	0007
S031A	1	9	However, I wanted to make it seem like they were the ones who had  called Moller, after capturing me.	s31a	0008
S031A	1	10	It was all a scheme to help the old man, and Beatrice’s husband,  Lucius Romanoff―― The new face of hope.	s31a	0009
S031A	1	11	With that, I would be able to increase the debt of gratitude that  Lucius Romanoff owed me.	s31a	0010
S031A	1	12	Beatrice: 「... ... ... ... ... ...」	s31a	0011
S031A	1	13	Kila: 「... ... ... ... ... ... ... ...」	s31a	0012
S031A	1	14	Both, Beatrice and Kila, were standing beside me in complete  obedience.	s31a	0013
S031A	1	15	Both of them looked to be back to her original selves, as the Empress  and the Grim Reaper, now that they had been administered with drugs  in order to block their nerves from carrying pleasure signals.	s31a	0014
S031A	1	16	However, even though their entire bodies weren’t being tormented  by pleasure anymore, their personalities were still the ones which  I had created for them.	s31a	0015
S031A	1	17	Now that I had the most powerful witch of Mars on my side, there was  no reason why I couldn’t capture the lecherous old geezer.	s31a	0016
S031A	1	18	There was a sullen look on the faces of both the women.	s31a	0017
S031A	1	19	Bohgan: 「What is with your faces?」	s31a	0018
S031A	1	20	Beatrice: 「Can’t you tell without the need to say it out loud?」	s31a	0019
S031A	1	21	Kila: 「I don’t want to speak to you as well.」	s31a	0020
S031A	1	22	They replied while sulking, entirely like spoilt children conversing  with their parent.	s31a	0021
S031A	1	23	Bohgan: 「Oh dear... Are you so annoyed because Lucius Romanoff is going to  take credit for this?」	s31a	0022
S031A	1	24	Both the women snapped back at me, as if they were taken aback with  what I had just said.	s31a	0023
S031A	1	25	Beatrice: 「Obviously. I want to work for you, however, not so that that man  can take credit for it!!」	s31a	0024
S031A	1	26	Kila: 「That’s right!! That guy will be back to his lecherous ways with  me as soon as possible!」	s31a	0025
S031A	1	27	Beatrice: 「That is a possibility, isn’t it? That does sound like something  that scum would do.」	s31a	0026
S031A	1	28	Kila: 「Mother, can you please be the one to partner up with that guy?」	s31a	0027
S031A	1	29	Beatrice: 「Stop kidding me!! I would rather die than have sex with such a  man. If he ever tries to do that, I am just going to kill him!!」	s31a	0028
S031A	1	30	Kila: 「I am going to kill him as well!!」	s31a	0029
S031A	1	31	As both the women bared their murderous intent for the man, I spoke  up,	s31a	0030
S031A	1	32	Bohgan: 「Wait just a moment. I will end up in a bother if he does die now.  I have planned to impersonate Lucius Romanoff, and make use of that  for my sake.」	s31a	0031
S031A	1	33	Bohgan: 「It will “extend” my reach over the universe. I can understand  your feelings well, however, I need you to control them for a while  longer.」	s31a	0032
S031A	1	34	Kila: 「I can... understand that, however...」	s31a	0033
S031A	1	35	Beatrice: 「That’s right. I understand that, however, I can’t control my  feelings.」	s31a	0034
S031A	1	36	Even though both the women nodded at my words, I could clearly see  their dark emotions swirling around them.	s31a	0035
S031A	1	37	Beatrice: 「Bohgan... Now that I know the joy of being loved by you, just the  thought of being touched by that man is enough to my make hair stand  on end. I can’t control my murderous intent, to be honest.」	s31a	0036
S031A	1	38	Kila: 「Me too, Master Bohgan. I will definitely end up killing him, if he  comes in front of me now.」	s31a	0037
S031A	1	39	Bohgan: （Oh dear... Did I maybe plant a bit too much of hatred for him in  them?）	s31a	0038
S031A	1	40	Even though I had done it to them myself, the hatred that these women  were harbouring for him was truly terrible.	s31a	0039
S031A	2	1	The moment I had mentioned Lucius Romanoff’s name in front of them,  they had become unable to hold themselves back from exposing their  true intentions.	s31a	0040
S031A	2	2	Bohgan: 「I understand. I will arrange this in such a way that you girls  don’t have to encounter that man.」	s31a	0041
S031A	2	3	Beatrice: 「Really!? Thank you!!」	s31a	0042
S031A	2	4	Kila: 「Thank you very much, Master Bohgan!!」	s31a	0043
S031A	2	5	Both of them hugged me with joy-filled faces,	s31a	0044
S031A	2	6	And were about to kiss me on both my left and right cheeks.	s31a	0045
S031A	2	7	Bohgan: 「Wait just a moment! The enemy might suspect you if you are seen  behaving like this. Act a bit more like the Empress and the Grim  Reaper!」	s31a	0046
S031A	2	8	Beatrice: 「Ah! That’s right, isn’t it? Sorry.」	s31a	0047
S031A	2	9	Kila: 「Forgive me, Master Bohgan.」	s31a	0048
S031A	2	10	Both of them responded bashfully, before reverting their faces back  to suit their original personalities.	s31a	0049
S031A	2	11	However, I noticed from the corners of my eyes that they were still  sneering a bit.	s31a	0050
S031A	2	12	Bohgan: 「He will be arriving here soon. The old man’s escort consists  of 12 specially trained soldiers. I don’t think they will pose  any threat to you, however, don’t lose your focus.」	s31a	0051
S031A	2	13	Beatrice: 「Of course.」	s31a	0052
S031A	2	14	Kila: 「No man can stand up to my knife.」	s31a	0053
S031A	2	15	Both the women said resolutely, however immediately after that, they  began to talk to each other in a bizarre manner.	s31a	0054
S031A	2	16	Kila: 「Well, Mother?」	s31a	0055
S031A	2	17	Beatrice: 「What?」	s31a	0056
S031A	2	18	Kila: 「How about we compete to see how many of them we can kill?」	s31a	0057
S031A	2	19	Beatrice: 「Very well. That should make it clear which woman is more useful  for Bohgan.」	s31a	0058
S031A	2	20	Kila: 「Right? And there are 12 specially trained soldiers... So, how about  we get one of Master Bohgan’s ejaculation for each one?」	s31a	0059
S031A	2	21	Beatrice: 「Hooo... That’s a good idea. In other words, I will be able to  monopolize Bohgan, if I kill them all.」	s31a	0060
S031A	2	22	Kila: 「Oh dear. I don’t intend to give you even one, Mother.」	s31a	0061
S031A	2	23	Bohgan: 「Are you girls just going to ignore my wishes?」	s31a	0062
S031A	2	24	Beatrice: 「Ah...」	s31a	0063
S031A	2	25	Kila: 「N-No... I didn’t mean it like that...」	s31a	0064
S031A	2	26	The bizarre spark in both the women was snuffed out, the moment I  interrupted them.	s31a	0065
S031A	2	27	Bohgan: 「Oh, very well. If that is what motivates you, then compete with  each other to see who is better among you.」	s31a	0066
S031A	2	28	Kila: 「Thank you very much!!」	s31a	0067
S031A	2	29	Beatrice: 「Leave it to me. I will exterminate them all in no time!!」	s31a	0068
S031A	2	30	I felt sympathy for the 12 men, who were going to be killed like  insects.	s31a	0069
S031A	2	31	Just then, I noticed Moller’s car approaching us.	s31a	0070
S031A	2	32	Beatrice: 「He is here.」	s31a	0071
S031A	2	33	Kila: 「Ufufu」	s31a	0072
S031A	2	34	The faces of both the women were shining brilliantly.	s31a	0073
S031A	2	35	That’s it. That’s the way.	s31a	0074
S031A	2	36	Work for me.	s31a	0075
S031A	2	37	Like pigs.	s31a	0076
S031A	2	38	Bohgan: 「Well then, it is show-time!!!」	s31a	0077
S031A	2	39	Devious scheming, raping women, and fighting.	s31a	0078
S031A	2	40	My ambitions would continue to grow.	s31a	0079
S031A	3	1	Until the day I would extend my reach over the entire universe.	s31a	0080
S031A	3	2	SALTAR: END2
S031A	3	3	SALTAR: ＧＯＯＤエンド１
