KS017B	1	1	Asagi: 「Eh---♪ Ahhhhhh!!!」	s17ts	0000
KS017B	1	2	I cried out like mad, while I shivered violently.	s17ts	0001
KS017B	1	3	I accepted the pleasure, as well as the shame.	s17ts	0002
KS017B	1	4	My body, that had been degraded through corruption by pleasure into that of an ordinary woman, was inspected.	s17ts	0003
KS017B	1	5	Asagi: （It's impossible!）	s17ts	0004
KS017B	1	6	Even the eyeball tentacle looking at my miserable orgasm face didn't raise my resistance anymore.	s17ts	0005
KS017B	1	7	What kind of woman could endure such demonic torture?	s17ts	0006
KS017B	1	8	Asagi: 「Hyiii, unbearable!! Iguiguiguigu☆」	s17ts	0007
KS017B	1	9	Being stared at by the eyeball, my body was unable to move and sunk back exhausted.	s17ts	0008
KS017B	1	10	It was not my fault.	s17ts	0009
KS017B	1	11	I was a woman before a Taimanin.	s17ts	0010
KS017B	1	12	No matter how virtuous I was, I couldn't do anything but miserably shake my hips in front of this tentacle.	s17ts	0011
KS017B	1	13	Becoming a prisoner to orgasms, I could only beg for mercy.	s17ts	0012
KS017B	1	14	My mind was completely invaded by the sweet pain of the demonic darkness that had entered me.	s17ts	0013
KS017B	1	15	SALTAR: 合流０２へ
KS017B	1	16	SALTAR: KS017D
