AS018A	1	1	The battleship Jerkel.	as18a	0000
AS018A	1	2	The secret lab.	as18a	0001
AS018A	1	3	Brainwashing was being performed on Alicia and Maya again today.	as18a	0002
AS018A	1	4	Brainwashing for the sake of turning them into complete bitch slaves.	as18a	0003
AS018A	1	5	The 6 p.m. bell would ring very soon.	as18a	0004
AS018A	1	6	Alicia and Maya had tried to return to sanity today.	as18a	0005
AS018A	1	7	Even so, the brainwashing work in the lab was proceeding at a quick pace.	as18a	0006
AS018A	1	8	The pair's slutty voices could be heard without pause.	as18a	0007
AS018A	1	9	The brainwashing had been constant.	as18a	0008
AS018A	1	10	Bogan: 「Hmph, they've started making pretty pig bitch slave-like cries, haven't they?」	as18a	0009
AS018A	1	11	While listening to the slutty voices that were given off as they kept cumming endlessly, I decided to get a report from my trusty subordi- nates.	as18a	0010
AS018A	1	12	Alicia: 「Uiguuuuuuhh! Gugih?! Higih... iih... ihiiiiiiiiiiiiii!!!!!!」	as18a	0011
AS018A	1	13	Like yesterday, Alicia's limbs had been snugly fit into the equipment, and her cries of pleasure echoed in my ears.	as18a	0012
AS018A	1	14	Bogan: 「Ho. Compared to yesterday, kuku, her nipples have gotten pretty nice, haven't they?」	as18a	0013
AS018A	1	15	Her nipples had grown a lot, to the point where I could even tell from a look.	as18a	0014
AS018A	1	16	Their length had grown even further than yesterday, and they were jiggling around as they were being pulled on.	as18a	0015
AS018A	1	17	It felt like she had grown super-long nipples from her breasts.	as18a	0016
AS018A	1	18	Long needles connected to electrical cords were cruelly sticking into her shapely breasts, and kept sending an electric current into them constantly.	as18a	0017
AS018A	1	19	Alicia: 「Niuuuu! Nfuu! Nheh! Hebubububu! Heuh... uih... iiaaaaaah!!」	as18a	0018
AS018A	1	20	As the current flowed in, muffled screams, which were tinged with ecstasy, rushed out from her mouth, to which a mask-like device had been affixed.	as18a	0019
AS018A	1	21	It appeared that Alicia, whose body had transformed into that of a whore, was even able to turn the stimulation of the electric current into pleasure.	as18a	0020
AS018A	1	22	Alicia: 「Haguuuuu, nbuohh, ohigii, eiiguuuuuuuuu!!」	as18a	0021
AS018A	1	23	Bogan: 「Kukuku, seems she's cumming while baring the whites of her eyes, huh? Nice look.」	as18a	0022
AS018A	1	24	Hans: 「Yes! The orgasm count has reached 87 today.」	as18a	0023
AS018A	1	25	The number 87 appeared on the device which indicated the number of times she had reached orgasm.	as18a	0024
AS018A	1	26	Bogan: 「How was it yesterday? Did you make them cum 1000 times?」	as18a	0025
AS018A	1	27	Olov: 「Uhii! They just barely orgasmed 1000 times. At the end, they were cumming constantly, though, and even peeing themselves.」	as18a	0026
AS018A	1	28	Perhaps because he had remembered yesterday's brainwashing, Olov shivered as he answered me.	as18a	0027
AS018A	1	29	Bogan: 「So, today you're making them drink semen for hydration, huh......?」	as18a	0028
AS018A	1	30	Transparent tubes stretched from the masks that had been fitted to their mouths, and were connected to glass tanks.	as18a	0029
AS018A	1	31	They were filled to the brim with a huge amount of semen.	as18a	0030
AS018A	1	32	Semen was constantly flowing through the tubes, and into Alicia and Maya's mouths.	as18a	0031
AS018A	1	33	Alicia: 「Gaboh... gobu... gobu! Fugugugu! Egu! Ueh! Eoohh! Oh... hiiiii!!」	as18a	0032
AS018A	1	34	Alicia and Maya continued raising screams in the brief pauses between noisily gulping down the semen.	as18a	0033
AS018A	1	35	Maya: 「Fugubububu...... hegu... heguuu... ngu! Gu, gokyuu! Gokyuu! Ngyuuuuu...」	as18a	0034
AS018A	1	36	As she swallowed the semen, which was flowing in an endless stream, Maya's swollen clitoris was being pulled on.	as18a	0035
AS018A	1	37	Like Alicia's nipples, Maya's clitoris had also become even bigger and longer than yesterday.	as18a	0036
AS018A	1	38	Electrical cords were connected to the vibrators that had been crammed into her vagina and anus, and made an electric current flow into the two holes as they were dug into.	as18a	0037
AS018A	1	39	Not to be outdone by Alicia, Maya was shedding tears as she orgasmed from the stimulation of the electricity that went through her flesh walls, which had been dug into and become tender.	as18a	0038
AS018A	1	40	Maya: 「Hobububu! Hobuuu... eh... ebuuu?! Ehiii! Iiaah! Aiaaaaah!!!」	as18a	0039
AS018A	2	1	Indecent voices of pleasure came out from their mouths, which had slagged me off as a lowlife just days before.	as18a	0040
AS018A	2	2	Now, I was once again succeeding at turning shitty, conceited women into sows.	as18a	0041
AS018A	2	3	Bogan: 「Well, shall I have you report on your progress?」	as18a	0042
AS018A	2	4	My mood improved due to the fact that everything was proceeding favourably, and I decided to get another report from my subordinates.	as18a	0043
AS018A	2	5	Hans: 「The brainwashing progress is at 75％. If we have another two days, I think we will be able to erase their old personalities.」	as18a	0044
AS018A	2	6	Bogan: 「Two days, huh? Kukuku, these ladies held out surprisingly well, didn't they?」	as18a	0045
AS018A	2	7	I had assumed that Alicia, who was called the Onihime, would be tough, but――	as18a	0046
AS018A	2	8	I hadn't expected that Maya, who I had thought of as a young noblewoman of gentle birth, would resist on par with her.	as18a	0047
AS018A	2	9	However, no matter how much they tried to struggle, the result would be the same. They would both just become pig bitches.	as18a	0048
AS018A	2	10	Hans: 「They were pretty tough subjects, but once they've gone this far...」	as18a	0049
AS018A	2	11	Bogan: 「Don't let your guard down! No good will come of showing these shit women any weakness.」	as18a	0050
AS018A	2	12	I focused my mind as I warned not just my subordinates, but also myself.	as18a	0051
AS018A	2	13	Hans: 「Aye, sir!」	as18a	0052
AS018A	2	14	Ingeborg took a step forward and swapped places with Hans, who had saluted.	as18a	0053
AS018A	2	15	Ingeborg: 「Presently, instead of the Fellatio Doll procedure, we are conducting newly-developed remodelling.」	as18a	0054
AS018A	2	16	The Fellatio Doll procedure would remodel everywhere from the tongue to the throat, and give them pleasure that was equivalent to having their vagina violated just from performing fellatio――	as18a	0055
AS018A	2	17	In other words, it was a procedure that would make their throats similar to vaginas.	as18a	0056
AS018A	2	18	That extremely inhumane procedure had been banned under Space Federation law thanks to Rieri, who was the root cause of a storm of criticism that it treated women as nothing but objects.	as18a	0057
AS018A	2	19	As for this new sexual remodelling procedure, which served as a replacement for the Fellatio Doll procedure――	as18a	0058
AS018A	2	20	Bogan: 「Hmm. What are the effects of that remodelling? I trust they're better than the Fellatio Doll procedure.」	as18a	0059
AS018A	2	21	Ingeborg: 「Together with the lung genitalization remodelling, I think we can arrange for “spontaneous feelings of sexual excitement”. This kind of aphrodisiac will seem suspicious, since the effects manifest continuously, and are quite unnatural.」	as18a	0060
AS018A	2	22	Bogan: 「Don't get too abstract. Could you explain it in a little more detail?」	as18a	0061
AS018A	2	23	Ingeborg: 「Well, then, the explanation should come from Olov......」	as18a	0062
AS018A	2	24	Bogan: 「Olov, if you please.」	as18a	0063
AS018A	2	25	Olov: 「Uhii!」	as18a	0064
AS018A	2	26	Having been called, Olov took a step forward, and began the explanation in place of Ingeborg.	as18a	0065
AS018A	2	27	Olov: 「For the procedure this time, we have primarily remodelled the gustatory nerves. That means they will feel supreme joy from the act of sucking cock.」	as18a	0066
AS018A	2	28	Bogan: 「Hmm......」	as18a	0067
AS018A	2	29	Olov: 「When the gustatory nerves sense semen or Cowper's fluid, an abnormal level of endorphins will be secreted inside the brain.」	as18a	0068
AS018A	2	30	Bogan: 「So that means, you're doing that to fix the taste of semen in their memories?」	as18a	0069
AS018A	2	31	Alicia: 「Nguh?! Guh! Hegugugu... eh... ebuuu! Buryuu...... nbiiih! Eh! Eaaah!」	as18a	0070
AS018A	2	32	Maya: 「Hegih?! Hegu... nguuu! Juru! Uuh... Obubububu! Heoh! Heooohh!!」	as18a	0071
AS018A	2	33	Semen continued gushing in from the tanks.	as18a	0072
AS018A	2	34	The pair were gulping it down as they shed tears, raised voices of delight and orgasmed.	as18a	0073
AS018A	2	35	Olov: 「Uhii! As I'd expect from the Captain. You're quick to understand. Right now, we're just confirming the results of the procedure.」	as18a	0074
AS018A	2	36	Bogan: 「No wonder they're drinking semen like it's delicious. Kukuku. So, if the procedure is a success, then once they start sucking a cock, they'll become unable to hold back, yes?」	as18a	0075
AS018A	2	37	Olov: 「Indeed. Kuhihi, they'll start wanting to suck cock all the time! The more they suck and suck, the more their bodies will ache, the more pleasure will arise, and the more unbearable it will become.」	as18a	0076
AS018A	2	38	Olov: 「This means that they will become addicted, and turn into fellatio junkies. As long as there's a cock, they'll start to want to suck on it, no matter where they are or whose it is.」	as18a	0077
AS018A	2	39	Bogan: 「Kuhahahahaha! You mean, The Alicia and Maya will become cock-loving women, and start wanting to suck cock all day long?!」	as18a	0078
AS018A	2	40	Olov: 「That's right! Moreover, if they happen to taste something like semen, they'll be greatly aroused! This will mark their completion as perverts who can climax from drinking cum.」	as18a	0079
AS018A	3	1	Bogan: 「I see. You mean, their completion as perverted bitch slaves. Kukuku, isn't that a wonderful procedure?」	as18a	0080
AS018A	3	2	Olov: 「I have named this one the 『Semen Doll Procedure』.」	as18a	0081
AS018A	3	3	Bogan: 「It's a shame we can't announce this, isn't it......? Kukuku!」	as18a	0082
AS018A	3	4	Alicia: 「Uah! Iih... efuuu! Heh, hehii?! Nnaaaah! Gupuh! Gyupupupuuu!」	as18a	0083
AS018A	3	5	I made a derisive smile as I gazed upon the pair, who continued to orgasm without knowing that they had been uncouthly remodelled.	as18a	0085
AS018A	3	6	They both kept raising voices of pleasure, as if they were sobbing with joy from having undergone the Semen Doll procedure.	as18a	0086
AS018A	3	7	SALTAR: AS018B
AS018A	3	8	SALTAR: AS018C
