PV01_3301_A	1	1	Alicia: 「Maya!!」	as26a	0036
PV01_3301_A	1	2	There, surrounded by naked men, was the figure of Maya Cordelia.	as26a	0037
PV01_3301_A	1	3	Maya: 「Honnn! Nfuuu!! Fuboh, ooohhh!!」	as26a	0038
PV01_3301_A	1	4	Maya was being violated in her formal regalia, with every single hole being plugged up by burly men.	as26a	0039
PV01_3301_A	1	5	The crotch area of her tights had been torn, and meat poles were being thrust inside both her vagina and anus at the same time.	as26a	0040
PV01_3301_A	1	6	Not only that, but she was even holding another man's genitals in her hand, and a glans was sticking into the flesh inside her mouth, making her cheek bulge out.	as26a	0041
PV01_3301_A	1	7	Man: 「Hora, suck it more firmly! Tighten your lips and stroke my dick!」	as26a	0042
PV01_3301_A	1	8	Maya: 「Fubuh! Zubu! Guboh! Gupu, gupu, gubupu!!」	as26a	0043
PV01_3301_A	1	9	Man: 「Don't forget me, either! 'Cause afterwards, I'm gonna shoot my semen straight into your womb!!」	as26a	0044
PV01_3301_A	1	10	Man: 「You like having your tits rubbed while your ass pussy is being raped, don't you? Maya-chan is a serious anal fucker, after all!!」	as26a	0045
PV01_3301_A	1	11	Maya: 「Funnnh!! Fuoh, oohhh!! Ass pussy, tits, I like iit! Ah'm an, anal fuckah!! Uhooohhh!!」	as26a	0046
PV01_3301_A	1	12	While admitting that she was an anal fucker, she pushed her buttocks back against one of the men of her own accord.	as26a	0047
PV01_3301_A	1	13	Man: 「Heheh, I'm getting a little jealous! Eat up my cock, too, with your nympho cunt! 'Cause I'm gonna make sure to creampie you and make you have a womb orgasm!!」	as26a	0048
PV01_3301_A	1	14	Maya: 「Ah'm eadin uuup, haunh, hyaaaaaa!! A cock with mah nympho cunnt! Wanna womb orgashmmmm!!」	as26a	0049
PV01_3301_A	1	15	She was lowering her hips rhythmically, voluntarily putting her body weight on the cock of the man she straddled.	as26a	0050
PV01_3301_A	1	16	Man: 「I'm letting out lots of precum, aren't I? It's nice and delicious, right, Maya-sama?!」	as26a	0051
PV01_3301_A	1	17	Maya: 「Ahh, pre-semen from a dick! Chuzuzuuuuu! Jururu, gububu! Goboohh! Gubuh?! Funh, fugunnn?!!」	as26a	0052
PV01_3301_A	1	18	She voluntarily moved her face towards the penis that had been held out in front of her eyes, stuffed her cheeks with it, then sucked up the Cowper's fluid and trembled with pleasure.	as26a	0053
PV01_3301_A	1	19	Man: 「Maya Hime-sama, your hand has stopped! Yeah, grip it firmly, ohh! Jerk it like that!」	as26a	0054
PV01_3301_A	1	20	Maya: 「Yehhsh, ah'm grippin iid! Aaah! Hohhhhhht!! Jerking hand ish meltiiiing!!」	as26a	0055
PV01_3301_A	1	21	Even though Maya was being tormented by all of the men, her nipples and her flesh bud, which had reached an improbable size for a human, were erect, and she was satisfying herself without any reluctance.	as26a	0056
PV01_3301_A	1	22	So much so that she voluntarily pressed her hips against the man she straddled, thrust her ass out backwards, and chased after the other meat poles with her lips and hand.	as26a	0057
PV01_3301_A	1	23	Even though she was surrounded by men she didn't know, and being exposed to eyes that were gleaming as they awaited their turn.	as26a	0058
PV01_3301_A	1	24	Maya: 「Nfuhyaaah, cock's good, lots of cocks, so habbyyy, aaannh, morre, please gib me mooore!!」	as26a	0059
PV01_3301_A	1	25	Not the slightest trace of having once been the Princess of this nation, or dignity as the country's Grand Duchess, could be sensed from her appearance as she deliriously indulged in pleasure.	as26a	0060
PV01_3301_A	1	26	All that was there was the figure of a completely degraded sow.	as26a	0061
PV01_3301_A	1	27	Alicia: 「Ahh...... Maya......!」	as26a	0062
PV01_3301_A	1	28	Seeing Maya being violated in front of her eyes, Alicia reflexively raised her voice.	as26a	0063
PV01_3301_A	1	29	She was supposed to represent the hopes and dreams of Alicia, who had brought her up with loving care, and Alicia had probably received a considerable shock from the fact that she had ended up turning into a hopeless slut.	as26a	0064
PV01_3301_A	1	30	Bogan: 「Had you not attempted something silly like trying to kill me, I wouldn't have to make Maya do such a thing.」	as26a	0065
PV01_3301_A	1	31	Alicia: 「You bastaaaarrrd!!」	as26a	0066
PV01_3301_A	1	32	Alicia scowled at me, with eyes that were filled with burning rage and murderous intent, but she was unable to do anything to hurt me.	as26a	0067
PV01_3301_A	1	33	Maya: 「Haaah?! Hime Nee-hyamaa? You god back, huh? Heaaaaahh!!」	as26a	0068
PV01_3301_A	1	34	Man: 「Don't look away, pig bitch!! Oraaa!!」	as26a	0069
PV01_3301_A	1	35	The men crowded around Maya and flung their hips toward her flesh holes.	as26a	0070
PV01_3301_A	1	36	Maya: 「Hahiiiiiinnh!!」	as26a	0071
PV01_3301_A	1	37	Alicia: 「Maya!!!」	as26a	0072
PV01_3301_A	1	38	Bogan: 「Don't move! Watch from there.」	as26a	0073
PV01_3301_A	1	39	I, who held absolute power over Alicia, barked as she tried to charge forward, and the Onihime had no choice but to stop her legs immediately.	as26a	0074
PV01_3301_A	1	40	Bogan: 「Burn this firmly into your eyes! The sight of Maya meeting such a pitiful fate because of you. Fuhahahaha!!」	as26a	0075
PV01_3301_A	2	1	Alicia: 「Kuu!! Shiiiiit!!」	as26a	0076
PV01_3301_A	2	2	After sneering for a while at Alicia, who bit her lip almost hard enough to tear it apart, I sent an instruction to the crew members.	as26a	0077
PV01_3301_A	2	3	Man: 「From here on out, we'll do it without holding back! I'll massage Maya-chan's tits as I scrub the inside of her bowels!!」	as26a	0078
PV01_3301_A	2	4	Man: 「I'll tease her womb!! I'm gonna pound the entrance to your womb, so have a womb orgasm!!」	as26a	0079
PV01_3301_A	2	5	Maya: 「Yehhhhsh, please massage my tits as you meg the inshide of mah belly shloppy! I'll, have a womb orgashmm, I'm gonna cum a lod from mah woomb!!」	as26a	0080
PV01_3301_A	2	6	Bashubashubashubashu!!!! Juchujuchubajunn!!!	as26a	0081
PV01_3301_A	2	7	Maya: 「Uhyaaaaaaaah?!! Theh'ah so, harrrrd, uhyooooohhhhh!!」	as26a	0082
PV01_3301_A	2	8	As instructed, they thrust their hips, and pumped in and out of the fleshy depths of Maya's vagina and anus.	as26a	0083
PV01_3301_A	2	9	Truly without restraint, they gave in to their carnal desires and thrust with the force of surging waves, almost hard enough to wreck Maya's genitals and excretion orifice.	as26a	0084
PV01_3301_A	2	10	Maya: 「Hoaaah! Bein rubbed!! The walls of my cunt and asshooole, bein rubbed!! Kyufuuuuuuu!!!」	as26a	0085
PV01_3301_A	2	11	It seemed that she had been forced to lightly cum, due to the extremely violent rhythm of the two-hole assault.	as26a	0086
PV01_3301_A	2	12	Maya: 「Ueaaah...... eah, hehyah...... ah, hyaaa...... ehehieaheaheehh......」	as26a	0087
PV01_3301_A	2	13	Maya made her body twitch and pointed a look of ecstasy at them, sluttishly opening her mouth halfway and slobbering.	as26a	0088
PV01_3301_A	2	14	Man: 「Uhyou! Please watch, Alicia-sama! Maya Hime-sama is having her cunt and anus fucked! Look!!!」	as26a	0089
PV01_3301_A	2	15	Man: 「This girl is a truly great anal fucker!! She's taking my cock in as far as it goes and wrapping her flesh around it!」	as26a	0090
PV01_3301_A	2	16	Man: 「Nympho pussy is the best!! Her womb is kissing the tip of my dick!! And it's squeezing with all its strength!」	as26a	0091
PV01_3301_A	2	17	As if showing off to Alicia, who was like a big sister to Maya, the men violated the “little sister” while looking like they owned the place.	as26a	0092
PV01_3301_A	2	18	Maya: 「Nhoohh! Oooohhhh!! Oh, aaaah, Hime Nee-shamaaaaa!!」	as26a	0093
PV01_3301_A	2	19	Alicia: 「M, Maya......! I'm sorry......」	as26a	0094
PV01_3301_A	2	20	Maya: 「Why issh, Hime Neheh-shamaa! Hmmmm! Ah, apologishinnng?! Ah'm habbyy! Hohh, feehs goooooh!!」	as26a	0095
PV01_3301_A	2	21	Alicia: 「Ugguh...... Sorry......」	as26a	0096
PV01_3301_A	2	22	Maya was being mercilessly raped in front of Alicia, who hung her head as she apologized.	as26a	0097
PV01_3301_A	2	23	The men swung their hips so hard that the flesh of their groins slapped against hers noisily.	as26a	0098
PV01_3301_A	2	24	Bojubojubyujubibih!!! Bashubashubashubashu!!!!	as26a	0099
PV01_3301_A	2	25	Maya: 「Nnohh! Oooh!! Ohooh!! Hoaah!! Hie Nee-hamaaa!!」	as26a	0100
PV01_3301_A	2	26	The Grand Duchess of this country was howling like an animal and satisfying herself while calling out that name, without even caring about her slutty appearance being seen by Alicia, who she respected and adored.	as26a	0101
PV01_3301_A	2	27	Man: 「You're getting off from being watched by Hime Nee-sama, aren't you?!!」	as26a	0102
PV01_3301_A	2	28	Man: 「Maya-chan is a perverted pig woman, who gets off from being watched as she's cumming hard!!」	as26a	0103
PV01_3301_A	2	29	Maya: 「Ahh, Ahiiiieee'm! A perverded womaaaannn! Who geds off, fwom, fwomm! From bein washed bah Hie Neh-shamaaa!」	as26a	0104
PV01_3301_A	2	30	Even appearing delighted to disparage herself, Maya screamed the words of a pig bitch as she sluttishly stuck her tongue out and panted.	as26a	0105
PV01_3301_A	2	31	Man: 「Maya-sama, give me fellatio service! Rub my cock against the inner lining of your mouth! Until it becomes sticky with your filthy drool, okay?!」	as26a	0106
PV01_3301_A	2	32	Maya: 「Ohh! Mm, kuh, ferrashioooo!! Yeeessh, Ah'll ferrate, habumuu!」	as26a	0107
PV01_3301_A	2	33	Despite being subjected to the hard thrusting of the meat poles in both her vagina and shithole, she voluntarily brought another filthy cock deep into her mouth again, as she was told.	as26a	0108
PV01_3301_A	2	34	Maya: 「Gubububu! Guboh, jubohh! Haaah, rubbing, penish inshide my mouuth! Lahk thissh? Zuboh, gujubu! Guboboboh!」	as26a	0109
PV01_3301_A	2	35	The penis was thrust into the lining of her mouth, to the point where the shape of the glans bulged out on her cheek, and she rubbed it while grinding it into her own flesh.	as26a	0110
PV01_3301_A	2	36	She smeared the saliva that had been secreted because of that onto the meat pole, and firmly clamped her lips around it as she stroked it.	as26a	0111
PV01_3301_A	2	37	Maya: 「Fuguguu? Juruuuuu! Nguh?!! Mhmhmmh!! Gubugubuuuuuuunnh!!」	as26a	0112
PV01_3301_A	2	38	Appearing to have sensed the taste of the man's filthy precum with her tongue, the Grand Duchess of Cordelia raised a moan that was intoxicated with pleasure, without pulling out the cock that she held in her mouth.	as26a	0113
PV01_3301_A	2	39	Man: 「Oho! You lightly came again, huh?! How is it? Does it feel good to suck cock, Maya-sama?」	as26a	0114
PV01_3301_A	2	40	Maya: 「Ih feelsh gooh...... Gububu! Buchuu, making my mouth pussyy, memorishe the shape oh yoh peniss, incredibllllle! Gujuuuuuu!」	as26a	0115
PV01_3301_A	3	1	Man: 「Heheheh! That's right, firmly memorize my penis with your mouth pussy! If you do, I'll let out a lot more precum!」	as26a	0116
PV01_3301_A	3	2	Maya: 「Haaah, Ah wan Cowper'sh fluiid! Gujubububu! Bubu! Guboboh, buboboboh!」	as26a	0117
PV01_3301_A	3	3	She eagerly brought in the hugely swollen glans, and rubbed it against the flesh on the inside of her mouth, which was probably slimy with drool, without even caring that her cheek was bulging out.	as26a	0118
PV01_3301_A	3	4	Maya: 「Aaaah, Cowper's fluid ish shpurtin ouuuut!! Juzuzu! Zuzozozo! Cumming fwom the taaste, fueeeeeh!! Jujujuu! Gufuuuuunn!!」	as26a	0119
PV01_3301_A	3	5	Despite rolling her eyeballs upward and exposing a disgraceful expression, Maya, who was incessantly attacked by extremely strong pleasure, never tried to spit out the cock.	as26a	0120
PV01_3301_A	3	6	With a cumming face that was improper for a Grand Duchess, she moved her head frantically, making loud, sticky noises resound.	as26a	0121
PV01_3301_A	3	7	Man: 「What an erotic face, even though you're the representative of this country! To cum from pre... Maya-sama is a semen junkie, isn't she?」	as26a	0122
PV01_3301_A	3	8	Maya: 「Ahiee, gububuuu! L, lub shemenn! Juzuzuzu! This taste feelsh gooh, cummiiiinnnng!!」	as26a	0123
PV01_3301_A	3	9	While still giving fellatio, she unabashedly climaxed with an orgasm face.	as26a	0124
PV01_3301_A	3	10	It seemed that she was quite pleased with the Semen Doll remodelling.	as26a	0125
PV01_3301_A	3	11	Man: 「Good, good, now beg! 'Cause I'm gonna let you drink real semen!」	as26a	0126
PV01_3301_A	3	12	Maya: 「Haaah, aah! Please let this shemen doll pig womaaannn! Drink yoh cock juuuiche!」	as26a	0127
PV01_3301_A	3	13	Man: 「More! While holding it in your mouth, Maya-sama!」	as26a	0128
PV01_3301_A	3	14	Maya: 「Habumuh! Please gib me cock juiche, juru heeh! Gyububu! Gupohh, cock juuice! Zujuu! Cock juice! Spurt it into mah mouth pussheeeeh!」	as26a	0129
PV01_3301_A	3	15	Having lost her old, rebellious personality and become obedient, Maya continued her fellatio service while breathing out embarrassing pleading words like she had gone insane.	as26a	0130
PV01_3301_A	3	16	Man: 「Good! I'm going to let it out soon, Maya-sama!」	as26a	0131
PV01_3301_A	3	17	Man: 「I'm gonna let it out too, so please stroke it, Maya Hime-sama!」	as26a	0132
PV01_3301_A	3	18	Maya: 「Yessssh, pleashe gibbit to mee! Semen, semen...... Shemefububuu! Gujuu! Jururuu! Aaah, semehhhnnn!! Gyuboh! Guboboh!」	as26a	0133
PV01_3301_A	3	19	Having been remodelled, and completely awoken as a semen doll, the pig woman was a natural semen junkie who cried out repeatedly and begged for cum.	as26a	0134
PV01_3301_A	3	20	Man: 「Uuu! I'm gonna bukkake you! I'm going to dirty Maya Hime-sama, the Grand Duchess!!」	as26a	0135
PV01_3301_A	3	21	Man: 「It's coming out!! Drink my semen!!」	as26a	0136
PV01_3301_A	3	22	Maya: 「Gujuboh! Gubobo! Gubu gubu gubu!! Zubooh! Gyubobobooh!!」	as26a	0137
PV01_3301_A	3	23	Man: 「Take this, Grand Duchess!!!」	as26a	0138
PV01_3301_A	3	24	The men who were making her give a handjob and perform oral sex thrust their hips out towards Maya.	as26a	0139
PV01_3301_A	3	25	Byuruuuu! Byuuuuuuuuuu!!! Dobyubububububu!! Dobudobudobuu!!!	as26a	0140
PV01_3301_A	3	26	Maya: 「Guuunnnnhnhnhnhnhh?!!!」	as26a	0141
PV01_3301_A	3	27	As dirty juices were splashing onto her, Maya bucked and moaned, as if she had been thrown into disarray by the fact that a large amount of actual semen, rather than precum, was flowing into her mouth.	as26a	0142
PV01_3301_A	3	28	Man: 「Hahahaha!! My semen is splattering onto Maya Hime-sama!! I'm dirtying my idol, Maya Hime-sama!!」	as26a	0143
PV01_3301_A	3	29	Man: 「Maya-sama, don't just cum, drink it properly! Without spilling a drop!!」	as26a	0144
PV01_3301_A	3	30	Maya: 「Fugunnnnnhh!!! Nfuh, ngugu, zujuuuuu!! Zuzozozo!! Ngungunguuuuu!!!」	as26a	0145
PV01_3301_A	3	31	The semen doll, who made her body shiver, noisily sucked on the glans, even as she climaxed from the taste of cum.	as26a	0146
PV01_3301_A	3	32	She seemed to be moving her tongue as she held the meat pole inside, and was savouring the dirty juices that had built up in her mouth as if she were chewing them or something.	as26a	0147
PV01_3301_A	3	33	Man: 「Right, right! Maya-sama really is a semen junkie pig bitch! After you fully memorize the taste of my semen with your tongue, swallow it!」	as26a	0148
PV01_3301_A	3	34	Maya: 「Rububu, nbuu! Ngungungu! Fuguguuuuu!! Nnuu, gogyuu! Gokyu! Obuuunnnh!! Gokun!」	as26a	0149
PV01_3301_A	3	35	Maya was noisily gulping down the man's smelly juices. She appeared to have fully savoured the dirty-white lumps as she skillfully smacked her tongue against her membranes, teeth, and the cock that she held in her mouth.	as26a	0150
PV01_3301_A	3	36	Every time her throat wriggled up and down, her body twitched and climaxed over and over again.	as26a	0151
PV01_3301_A	3	37	She swallowed and slurped as she reacted to the climaxes with a pleasured-looking orgasm face.	as26a	0152
PV01_3301_A	3	38	Man: 「Suck it up until the last drop, and gulp it down!」	as26a	0153
PV01_3301_A	3	39	Maya: 「Yehhsh! Chuhuu! Chuuuuuu! Gufuunnnnnh!! Ngugu, goku! Gokun! Ufuuuuuuu!!」	as26a	0154
PV01_3301_A	3	40	Man: 「She's orgasming from drinking semen! What a perverted slut! I'm gonna creampie this pig woman's anus, too!!」	as26a	0155
PV01_3301_A	4	1	Man: 「Gulp this down with your womb as well! I'm gonna shoot it straight in, and fill up your womb and pussy!!」	as26a	0156
PV01_3301_A	4	2	The men who had been thrusting their cocks into Maya's flesh holes constantly, even while she was in the middle of drinking cum, suddenly put on a spurt.	as26a	0157
PV01_3301_A	4	3	Maya: 「Fuhyaaaaaa!! Semen's comiiin! Cweampiiie! Ohhh, please shoot shemennn! Into my cunt an anuusss!!」	as26a	0158
PV01_3301_A	4	4	Man: 「I'm gonna shoot it in! Oraa!!!」	as26a	0159
PV01_3301_A	4	5	Maya: 「Ahii☆」	as26a	0160
PV01_3301_A	4	6	Dobubuu!! Byubobobooooohhhh!!! Doboboh, byububyububyububyububyubuu!!!	as26a	0161
PV01_3301_A	4	7	Without pausing after the bukkake and the ejaculation inside her mouth, semen, which seethed with carnal desire, was discharged into her vagina and asshole as well.	as26a	0162
PV01_3301_A	4	8	Maya: 「Id caaame?! Aaaaaaaaahh!!! Semen spurtin ouut, hiiiiiiiiihh!!!」	as26a	0163
PV01_3301_A	4	9	Having received the cum, which poured into her with the force of surging waves, Maya threw her head far back while twitching her flesh holes, which held cocks deep inside them.	as26a	0164
PV01_3301_A	4	10	She trembled like she had gone mad as she climaxed from the creampies, which had continued in quick succession while she was in the middle of cumming over and over.	as26a	0165
PV01_3301_A	4	11	Man: 「This anus is amazing! It's wringing out my semen!! Heh heh, I'll rub your tits, too, so try to squeeze out more!!」	as26a	0166
PV01_3301_A	4	12	Man: 「This is quite a good one as well!! She's stroking my cock with her cunt, and sucking on the glans with her cervix!!」	as26a	0167
PV01_3301_A	4	13	Maya: 「Drinkin shemenn!! Fuooooohh!! Whiile drinkin, I'mmmmm! Gyummmmiiiiinnnng!!!」	as26a	0168
PV01_3301_A	4	14	While indulging in the seed of men she didn't even know, the Grand Duchess of Cordelia twitched all the way down to the tips of her toes, and had a massive climax.	as26a	0169
PV01_3301_A	4	15	Man: 「Hora, hora, Maya-sama! If you're going to drink semen, you need to cum while sucking on my cock, too!!」	as26a	0170
PV01_3301_A	4	16	Maya: 「Hoooh, hyoooh! Suckin coock! Ugyu, while cumming...... Chuuu! Chuchuu! Ngi?! Fugyuuunnnnhh!!」	as26a	0171
PV01_3301_A	4	17	She clung to the meat pole in front of her eyes, which dripped with the remnants of its ejaculation, and nosily sucked out the remaining juices.	as26a	0172
PV01_3301_A	4	18	And then, tasting the cum that she had sucked out, Maya appeared to be assailed by a strong orgasm as she rolled her eyes back and exposed a pathetic ahegao.	as26a	0174
PV01_3301_A	4	19	Man: 「Heh heh! She's drinking from three places at once! What a pig bitch!」	as26a	0175
PV01_3301_A	4	20	Man: 「She's having a strong orgasm from this! You call this perverted pig woman a Grand Duchess?!!」	as26a	0176
PV01_3301_A	4	21	Maya: 「Uhoh, oohh! Ahiee, am, a perverded pih womaaaaan! Nod a Grand Duchess, uhyuuuuuu!!」	as26a	0177
PV01_3301_A	4	22	Even though she was being ridiculed and abused, Maya just got off, bending back and forth like she was arching her entire body.	as26a	0178
PV01_3301_A	4	23	The Grand Duchess of Cordelia had been completely corrupted. All that was there was the figure of a sow who had been degraded into a sexual gratification tool for the men.	as26a	0179
PV01_3301_A	4	24	While showering that figure with scorn and jeers, the men pulled their penises out from their respective flesh holes.	as26a	0180
PV01_3301_A	4	25	Maya: 「Ooooohhhh?!!! Puhhll, pullin ouuuh!! Hyaiiiiiiiiihh!!!」	as26a	0181
PV01_3301_A	4	26	Man: 「Guhyahyahyahya!! Maya-chan even orgasms just from pulling out!!」	as26a	0182
PV01_3301_A	4	27	Man: 「She's still making her ass twitch and begging for it!! She could be good enough to work in a brothel!!」	as26a	0183
PV01_3301_A	4	28	Maya: 「Haooohh! Oohhh, hooh, ohhu...... uah, hauuuuh......」	as26a	0184
PV01_3301_A	4	29	Released from the feeling of pressure, Maya ended up being tormented by the urge to defecate, and she climaxed again.	as26a	0185
PV01_3301_A	4	30	Perhaps because the huge waves of pleasure had finally gone away, she was drained of strength, as if she had grown exhausted.	as26a	0186
PV01_3301_A	4	31	Maya: 「Hehyah...... hyah...... hyafu...... eheaheaheeeeaah～～～」	as26a	0187
PV01_3301_A	4	32	Semen noisily gurgled back out from her vagina and anus, which had been spread out by the men's genitals until now.	as26a	0188
PV01_3301_A	4	33	Alicia: 「Kuu......! Maya......」	as26a	0189
PV01_3301_A	4	34	Alicia was unable to look directly at the unbelievably disgraceful appearance of the Grand Duchess of Cordelia, who had embodied her hopes and dreams.	as26a	0190
PV01_3301_A	4	35	Man: 「Are you satisfied with this? Do you want more semen?」	as26a	0191
PV01_3301_A	4	36	Maya: 「Ohaah...... oaah, Ahiee, I want...... Fuuu! Moah semenn......! Please give me gooey shemeeennnn!」	as26a	0192
PV01_3301_A	4	37	Alicia: 「Maya!! Enough already, stop it!! Guuu......!!」	as26a	0193
PV01_3301_A	4	38	It looked like she wanted to rush forward right now, but that was too bad. She was grinding her teeth on the spot, unable to move.	as26a	0194
PV01_3301_A	4	39	Bogan: 「I'll say this one more time, Alicia. Maya went through this because of you!」	as26a	0195
PV01_3301_A	4	40	Alicia: 「Shhhiiiit! P, please make it stop......!」	as26a	0196
PV01_3301_A	5	1	Alicia, who couldn't hate me more than she already did, begged me, in a hoarse voice that shook with anger.	as26a	0197
PV01_3301_A	5	2	Bogan: 「Kukuku. I had intended to send Maya to a dangerous brothel or something after this, but──」	as26a	0198
PV01_3301_A	5	3	Alicia: 「Brothel?! You bastard!!」	as26a	0199
PV01_3301_A	5	4	She glared at me, with almost enough force to throw herself at me.	as26a	0200
PV01_3301_A	5	5	Bogan: 「Well, I'm not an oni. If you demonstrate a repentant attitude, I'll hold off on sending her to the brothel.」	as26a	0201
PV01_3301_A	5	6	Alicia: 「What would you have me do?! If you give me an order, this will end, right?!」	as26a	0202
PV01_3301_A	5	7	Bogan: 「Fuhahahaha!! If that were the case, this would be no fun as a game. It would become pointless to have retained your personality.」	as26a	0203
PV01_3301_A	5	8	Alicia: 「Ukkuh......!」	as26a	0204
PV01_3301_A	5	9	I raised the edges of my lips, and Alicia bit down on her own lip and glared at me.	as26a	0205
PV01_3301_A	5	10	Bogan: 「This will be amusing because you're going to act of your own volition. Olov!」	as26a	0206
PV01_3301_A	5	11	Olov: 「Yes!」	as26a	0207
PV01_3301_A	5	12	I handed Alicia a syringe filled with liquid medicine, which I had gotten Olov to prepare.	as26a	0208
PV01_3301_A	5	13	Alicia looked quizzically between me and the object in her hand.	as26a	0209
PV01_3301_A	5	14	Bogan: 「Kukuku. That's a pregnancy stimulant.」	as26a	0210
PV01_3301_A	5	15	Alicia: 「What?!!」	as26a	0211
PV01_3301_A	5	16	The liquid medicine inside the syringe was a pregnancy-promoting agent infused with nanomachine technology, known as 『Critical Baby』, which was famous as a wonder drug for fertility treatment.	as26a	0212
PV01_3301_A	5	17	Merely 10 minutes after injecting it, the effects would become apparent, and the ovi would be made forcibly ready by the nanomachines.	as26a	0213
PV01_3301_A	5	18	Then, the nanomachines would provide support so that it would be easy to get pregnant, and they would be 100％ fertilized.	as26a	0214
PV01_3301_A	5	19	Furthermore, to allow her to make sure of the pregnancy, it also had the effect of making the woman intuitively sense the moment of fertili- zation. It was an outstanding drug.	as26a	0215
PV01_3301_A	5	20	Alicia: 「No way, with this......!」	as26a	0216
PV01_3301_A	5	21	Bogan: 「That's right. Inject yourself with that, and have sex with me.」	as26a	0217
PV01_3301_A	5	22	Alicia, who knew what a dangerous drug it was for her, made the palm of her hand, which the syringe had been placed on, tremble.	as26a	0218
PV01_3301_A	5	23	Bogan: 「Today, your lover is at work, and won't come home until morning, right? You can fully enjoy yourself!」	as26a	0219
PV01_3301_A	5	24	Alicia: 「Kuuu......! If I refuse that......」	as26a	0220
PV01_3301_A	5	25	Bogan: 「If you refuse, I'll just send Maya off to an especially dangerous place, even among brothels.」	as26a	0221
PV01_3301_A	5	26	Alicia: 「Such cowardly......!! You bastard, I'll definitely kill you!!!」	as26a	0222
PV01_3301_A	5	27	While making her angry roar echo throughout the room, Alicia thrust the needle of the syringe into herself, and pumped the liquid medicine into her body.	as26a	0223
PV01_3301_A	5	28	And then, she pulled out the syringe, snapped it in half, and threw it away as forcefully as she could, as if putting all of her hatred into it.	as26a	0224
PV01_3301_A	5	29	Bogan: 「Kukuku, that's good.」	as26a	0225
PV01_3301_A	5	30	Alicia: 「Haah, what do you intend to do, by making me pregnant with your child?!」	as26a	0226
PV01_3301_A	5	31	Bogan: 「Once you become the mother of my child, you won't think about trying to kill me as much, will you?」	as26a	0227
PV01_3301_A	5	32	Alicia: 「Hmm! Are you seriously thinking something like that?」	as26a	0228
PV01_3301_A	5	33	Bogan: 「Partly. Besides that, I acknowledge that your true strength is the greatest in the universe. Become my woman, Alicia.」	as26a	0229
PV01_3301_A	5	34	Alicia: 「Fufu, this joke is going too far! Who would have your──」	as26a	0230
PV01_3301_A	5	35	Before Alicia got to finish saying that all the way to the end, I had flung off my clothes and pointed my already-hard meat pole towards her.	as26a	0231
PV01_3301_A	5	36	Bogan: 「Now, Alicia, give my cock some paizuri service.」	as26a	0232
PV01_3301_A	5	37	Alicia: 「Wh, what the?! Don't point that dirty thing at me! Who would give you something like, p, paizuri?!」	as26a	0233
PV01_3301_A	5	38	Bogan: 「Hora, look, Alicia. So much precum is coming out of my cock. It's flooding out because I want you.」	as26a	0234
PV01_3301_A	5	39	Alicia: 「D, don't kid around......!」	as26a	0235
PV01_3301_A	5	40	Despite saying so, Alicia's gaze did not move away from my cock.	as26a	0236
PV01_3301_A	6	1	It seemed that her horny body, which had undergone remodelling, had sniffed out the scent of my precum, and was reacting to it.	as26a	0237
PV01_3301_A	6	2	Alicia: 「Ah, uu...... nguh......」	as26a	0238
PV01_3301_A	6	3	Seeming thirsty, she was constantly moving her mouth and trying to gulp down her saliva.	as26a	0239
PV01_3301_A	6	4	She was probably being tormented by intense thirst.	as26a	0240
PV01_3301_A	6	5	To speak figuratively, as far as Alicia was concerned, my precum was like an oasis that she had finally found after walking through the desert for days.	as26a	0241
PV01_3301_A	6	6	Bogan: 「No need to hold back, Alicia! You should sate that thirst with my cock.」	as26a	0242
PV01_3301_A	6	7	Alicia: 「D, don't kid a, round......」	as26a	0243
PV01_3301_A	6	8	There was no longer any force in those words the second time.	as26a	0244
PV01_3301_A	6	9	Seeing my cock, she would be experiencing an ache so strong that she couldn't help herself.	as26a	0245
PV01_3301_A	6	10	It seemed that all this woman's anger and hatred had turned into carnal desire, which was erupting inside her to the point where she couldn't bear it.	as26a	0246
PV01_3301_A	6	11	Bogan: 「You can't tell me you're trying to hold back that much.」	as26a	0247
PV01_3301_A	6	12	Alicia: 「Wh, wha......?!」	as26a	0248
PV01_3301_A	6	13	I approached Alicia, and spoke softly into her ear.	as26a	0249
PV01_3301_A	6	14	And then, I slowly took off her cloak, tore open her chest area, and exposed both of her sensuous breasts.	as26a	0250
PV01_3301_A	6	15	Alicia: 「Y, you bastard! I never said I'd...... d, do it......」	as26a	0251
PV01_3301_A	6	16	Bogan: 「Now, begin, Alicia.」	as26a	0252
PV01_3301_A	6	17	I said, as I laid down on the bed.	as26a	0253
PV01_3301_A	6	18	Alicia: 「Haaah～......! Ku......!」	as26a	0254
PV01_3301_A	6	19	She gazed at my meat pole, which rose towards the ceiling, and made a needy-looking face. However, she realized that, and grimaced in a panic.	as26a	0255
PV01_3301_A	6	20	Alicia, who was now completely unable to hide the fact that she was horny, made a show of looking back at Maya in a stiff, exaggerated motion, and then scowled at me.	as26a	0256
PV01_3301_A	6	21	Alicia: 「If, if I do it with my chest, that's enough, right......?」	as26a	0257
PV01_3301_A	6	22	Bogan: 「Fu kukuku!」	as26a	0258
PV01_3301_A	6	23	SALTAR: AS026A_01MPG
PV01_3301_A	6	24	SALTAR: AS026A_EV
