S001A_01EV	1	1	Natsuko: 「！！！」	s03a	0348
S001A_01EV	1	2	That something entered my field of vision having opened my eyes just a little. For a moment I watched that, then I seemed to raise a spontaneous shriek.	s03a	0349
S001A_01EV	1	3	Mizuki: 「Haa, haaa, mother........mother's tits.........」	s03a	0350
S001A_01EV	1	4	Natsuko: （Wh, what is this.........Mizukii, what are you doing!!）	s03a	0351
S001A_01EV	1	5	With my sleepiness being blown off in an instant, with half open eyes, I saw...my son's penis.	s03a	0352
S001A_01EV	1	6	Natsuko: （Aah, like this.......doing things as far as like this.......）	s03a	0353
S001A_01EV	1	7	My son's penis was pushed into the cleavage between my breasts. The tip of which was nudging my lips.	s03a	0354
S001A_01EV	1	8	Mizuki: 「Aah, nn, my cock is inbetween my mother's soft.......tits, nnn, it feels so wonderful」	s03a	0355
S001A_01EV	1	9	Natsuko: （Stop, stop this instant, Mizukii, like this, it's no good doing things like this）	s03a	0356
S001A_01EV	1	10	I cried out frantically in my mind, but my body wouldn't move so that it became paralyzed and I couldn't utter a single word I thought.	s03a	0357
S001A_01EV	1	11	Mizuki: 「Nn, fuuu, fuuu, nnuuuuu」	s03a	0358
S001A_01EV	1	12	With spitting out a short breath, Mizuki began moving his waist slowly.	s03a	0359
S001A_01EV	1	13	Natsuko: （Aah, aah, he's moving......fuuu, Mizuki's penis is moving inbetween my breasts）	s03a	0360
S001A_01EV	1	14	The activity of his pounding blood vessels was handed down to my chest directly. That hard, hot sensation  was something I remembered about my husband's penis.	s03a	0361
S001A_01EV	1	15	Natsuko: （Aah, why am I thinking about stupid things..... if, if you don't stop this instant）	s03a	0362
S001A_01EV	1	16	Rubbing your penis against your mother's breasts is absolutely wrong. If you don't stop this instant Mizuki.....	s03a	0363
S001A_01EV	1	17	In spite of thinking about that many times over, my voice and body too, did not react. Binding me, I was too horrified to call out.	s03a	0364
S001A_01EV	1	18	If he is noticed by me doing things like this, If Mizuki knows........maybe I'll make Mizuki embarrassed to the point of never recovering.	s03a	0365
S001A_01EV	1	19	With seeming to consider that, and while also  thinking about if I made him not stop,  I hesitated to say anything.	s03a	0366
S001A_01EV	1	20	Mizuki: 「Haa, fuuu, nn, it feels good, mother, it feels so amazing」	s03a	0367
S001A_01EV	1	21	In the interval that I was puzzled, Mizuki moved his hips slowly, rubbing his penis against me.	s03a	0368
S001A_01EV	1	22	Natsuko: 「Nn, fuuu, haaaa」	s03a	0369
S001A_01EV	1	23	Mizuki: 「Mother? Nn, mother, are you awake?」	s03a	0370
S001A_01EV	1	24	With me raising an unintentional voice, Mizuki gazed  firmly into my face. Mizuki's face grew vague in the  gloomy room.	s03a	0371
S001A_01EV	1	25	Natsuko: （I can't watch.......to his mother, I can't watch with my eyes like this......）	s03a	0372
S001A_01EV	1	26	I closed my eyes in a rush so that I wasn't exposed by Mizuki and a forced breathing as if I were sleeping.	s03a	0373
S001A_01EV	1	27	Mizuki: 「That's good........nn, fuuu, If I were exposed doing things like this......we wouldn't  be able to live together again, would we, mother」	s03a	0374
S001A_01EV	1	28	Huddling closer to my breasts, Mizuki applied pressure with his penis for himself.	s03a	0375
S001A_01EV	1	29	Natsuko: （Aah, I can feel.............I can feel Mizuki's  penis moving）	s03a	0376
S001A_01EV	1	30	Mizuki's eyes looked hard at me....... He shouldn't be looking at his mother like that. Mizuki had the eyes of a male animal.	s03a	0377
S001A_01EV	1	31	Natsuko: （Like this...Do I have no choice but to continue pretending being asleep now? Supposing if he knows I'm awake...）	s03a	0378
S001A_01EV	1	32	Then, his relations to his mother would be broken...... And, Mizuki, would no longer be around me.....	s03a	0379
S001A_01EV	1	33	Natsuko: （No.......that absolutely cannot happen..........now, nn, fuu, now........as it is........）	s03a	0380
S001A_01EV	1	34	I was scared to lose Mizuki. Because, from losing my  husband, regarding me, it was about Mizuki's life itself.  My heart seemed to tear even thinking about losing Mizuki.	s03a	0381
S001A_01EV	1	35	Mizuki: 「Haa, nnn, fuuu, how does it feel there mother? Nn, why are they getting so hard for?」	s03a	0382
S001A_01EV	1	36	Natsuko: 「Fuuu, nn, nnn, nfuuuuu」	s03a	0383
S001A_01EV	1	37	Mizuki's fingers pinched the protuberances that existed at the tips of my breasts.	s03a	0384
S001A_01EV	1	38	Natsuko: （Hiaaah!? Aah, aah, that sort of place, kuuu, don't touch）	s03a	0385
S001A_01EV	1	39	My whole body trembled with the stimulation of my nipples, a voiced seemed to want to rush out. With frantically plugging my voice that welled up in my throat,	s03a	0386
S001A_01EV	1	40	Mizuki: 「Haa, aah, mother's nipples are getting hard........ Nn, nnn, mother is also feeling it, isn't she」	s03a	0387
S001A_01EV	2	1	So as to savor the sensation of my stiff nipples, Mizuki continued to shift his fingers.	s03a	0388
S001A_01EV	2	2	Natsuko: （Aah, like that........nn, fuuu, that's dirty, don't move them...... fuuu, kuu, nnnuuu）	s03a	0389
S001A_01EV	2	3	With the activity of my son's fingers, as soon as my nipples tingled like that, sensations were returning that I had completely forgotten from long ago.	s03a	0390
S001A_01EV	2	4	Mizuki: 「Haa, nn, mother, motherrrr」	s03a	0391
S001A_01EV	2	5	Natsuko: 「Nn, fuuu, fuu, nnuuuuu」	s03a	0392
S001A_01EV	2	6	His penis moved throughout the inside of my breasts. The tip pushed against my lips continuously.	s03a	0393
S001A_01EV	2	7	Natsuko: （Stop it.......aah, stop it Mizuki.......... nnn, don't push your penis........）	s03a	0394
S001A_01EV	2	8	From the end of Mizuki's swollen penis, a syrupy liquid was overflowing. Mizuki daubed my lips with that.	s03a	0395
S001A_01EV	2	9	Natsuko: 「Fuu, fuu, nnn, nn, kufuuu..........」	s03a	0396
S001A_01EV	2	10	It was the cute penis that I had entered together with in  the bath since he was a child, wasn't it. Moral courage,  like a man's symbol...pressing onto my...his mother's face.	s03a	0397
S001A_01EV	2	11	Natsuko: （Aah, I can't let him do things like this........ nn, nnn, in spite of what he's doing......I, I..........）	s03a	0398
S001A_01EV	2	12	A sweet aching began to shroud my body little by little.	s03a	0399
S001A_01EV	2	13	Mizuki: 「Haa, haa, uuu, fuu, nnuuuuu」	s03a	0400
S001A_01EV	2	14	Mizuki swung his waist, feeling him  huddle closer to my breasts.	s03a	0401
S001A_01EV	2	15	Natsuko: 「Fuuu, nn, nfuuuu, nuuuu」	s03a	0402
S001A_01EV	2	16	Lured to that Mizuki letting out breathing at the good feelings, I too revealed a sweet breath.	s03a	0403
S001A_01EV	2	17	Natsuko: （Aah, aah, no........it's no good thinking weird  things......being Mizuki's partner.......... what am I thinking）	s03a	0404
S001A_01EV	2	18	With feeling the budding of emotions deep inside in the role of a woman who had forgotten them, I frantically tried to suppress that.	s03a	0405
S001A_01EV	2	19	Natsuko: （Things like feeling this way with my son's penis........ I'm not that sort of mother.........aah, nnnnuu）	s03a	0406
S001A_01EV	2	20	Although I cried that out many times over in my mind, the sweet pleasant feelings, little by little, drenched my entire body so that it ached and became sweaty.	s03a	0407
S001A_01EV	2	21	Mizuki: 「Haa, nnn, motherr, I wonder if mother is also feeling it too? Her nipples, are getting so hard......」	s03a	0408
S001A_01EV	2	22	While revealing a voice so as though he were talking to me, Mizuki pinched my nipples harder.	s03a	0409
S001A_01EV	2	23	Natsuko: 「Fuuu, nn, nfuuuuu」	s03a	0410
S001A_01EV	2	24	With the sharp stimulus of my nipples becoming sensitive, my voice endured in earnest of seeming to want to rush out.	s03a	0411
S001A_01EV	2	25	Natsuko: （Stopp, Mizuki, aaah, don't touch them again...... please, I'm begging you）	s03a	0412
S001A_01EV	2	26	The stimulation of my nipples made my womanhood wake up. Things like making me recall my own feminine instincts with my son.......	s03a	0413
S001A_01EV	2	27	Natsuko: （Nooo, noooo!! It's absolutely no good like this!!）	s03a	0414
S001A_01EV	2	28	Crying out the words of denial in my mind many, many times over, Mizuki did not give in and stop his caressing of me.	s03a	0415
S001A_01EV	2	29	Natsuko: （Haa, haa, like this...nn, I really... of course, I should've warned Mizuki...）	s03a	0416
S001A_01EV	2	30	Even if I humiliated Mizuki by doing it, I wonder if it would've been better to stop his wrong actions and not allow him to do this?	s03a	0417
S001A_01EV	2	31	With seeming to consider it once more, I peeked open my eyes and gazed at Mizuki's face suspended in the darkness.	s03a	0418
S001A_01EV	2	32	Mizuki: 「Haa, aaah, mother, since you're my mother, things like marrying again, I absolutely won't let you」	s03a	0419
S001A_01EV	2	33	Finding his eyes filled with ecstasy, he revealed a voice while swinging his waist.	s03a	0420
S001A_01EV	2	34	Natsuko: （Hafuuu, aah, it's about marrying again....... Nnnn, that hurt Mizuki, didn't it.........）	s03a	0421
S001A_01EV	2	35	Mizuki really thought I was marrying again. Was it the shock of that that made Mizuki do these things?	s03a	0422
S001A_01EV	2	36	Natsuko: （Supposing that is so.......That, this is.......my fault?）	s03a	0423
S001A_01EV	2	37	If that's right, I have to be careful with Mizuki here, I must not hurt Mizuki any further than I already have.	s03a	0424
S001A_01EV	2	38	Natsuko: （A bit longer.......nn, aah, maybe I'll give Mizuki his satisfaction for a bit longer if that's the case........）	s03a	0425
S001A_01EV	2	39	Before as well, I would let him touch my body when I was in bed. That time too, he had returned to his room eventually......	s03a	0426
S001A_01EV	2	40	Natsuko: （Yes.........nn, fuuu, aaah, He'll return to his room before long.......）	s03a	0427
S001A_01EV	3	1	After Mizuki returns to his room satisfied, that will be the end of it.	s03a	0428
S001A_01EV	3	2	Natsuko: （Fuu, nnu, and then..........haa, nuu, tomorrow morning... I'll have a proper talk with him.......I should expect also that Mizuki would understand）	s03a	0429
S001A_01EV	3	3	With having just a little more patience, everything will  be fine again........after it's finished and I haven't hurt him...I should be able to tolerate it for my dear Mizuki.	s03a	0430
S001A_01EV	3	4	Each time he rubbed his penis against my breasts, I had to fight frantically to keep my reason from  cutting off, with seeming to derive me of a conclusion,	s03a	0431
S001A_01EV	3	5	Natsuko: （A little more.......since it's just a little more......）	s03a	0432
S001A_01EV	3	6	While muttering in my mind many times, I left my body to Mizuki's mercy.	s03a	0433
S001A_01EV	3	7	Mizuki: 「Mother, aah, from, seeing my penis.......nnu, too much sensation, liquid is coming out」	s03a	0434
S001A_01EV	3	8	Natsuko: （Aah, naa, d, don't press it on...... fuu, fuaaah, nfuuuuu）	s03a	0435
S001A_01EV	3	9	Mizuki pressed and rubbed onto my face the tip that was oozing out pre-cum.	s03a	0436
S001A_01EV	3	10	Natsuko: （It's big.......aah, and hard.........fuaah, ahfuuu, it's hotness sort of burns me）	s03a	0437
S001A_01EV	3	11	While his penis drew closer, in my nose a man's...... the full odor of a male.	s03a	0438
S001A_01EV	3	12	Natsuko: 「Fuu, fuu, nn, kufuuunn」	s03a	0439
S001A_01EV	3	13	So as to react to that male odor, I felt the insides of my stomach become hot so that it flared up, seething,	s03a	0440
S001A_01EV	3	14	Natsuko: （Aah, s, such.........I, I, hiaah, aaah, things like this...........nuuuuu）	s03a	0441
S001A_01EV	3	15	My womb ached, and I felt a hot fluids overflowing from that place.	s03a	0442
S001A_01EV	3	16	Natsuko: （My feelings........I, feel the pressing of my son's  penis......despite being his mother,  I'm feeling this..........）	s03a	0443
S001A_01EV	3	17	My nectar was overflowing, wetting and crawling along my inner thighs, making a stain on the sheets. My nectar kept overflowing, not ending to that extent.	s03a	0444
S001A_01EV	3	18	Natsuko: 「Kuuu, fuu, nn, nnuuu.........」	s03a	0445
S001A_01EV	3	19	It no good to let Mizuki become aware of that......as his mother, there was absolutely no way I could let him know. As to the reason I'm feeling this way with my son's penis...	s03a	0446
S001A_01EV	3	20	Natsuko: （Please.......because I'm begging.........nnu, stop........）	s03a	0447
S001A_01EV	3	21	On the verge of losing reason, I was showing reactions in the role of a woman, shouting inside my mind so as to complain to my body. But.........	s03a	0448
S001A_01EV	3	22	Mizuki: 「Kuu, fuuu, haa, haaa, motherr, my mother also wants to feel it, she wants to feeling my cock」	s03a	0449
S001A_01EV	3	23	With listening to his seemingly painful voice with Mizuki's penis, my heart beat triumphantly, gathering speed as my body grew hotter.	s03a	0450
S001A_01EV	3	24	Natsuko: （Haa, haa, I hear it Mizuki........ nnn, I hear it throbbing）	s03a	0451
S001A_01EV	3	25	Overlooking his penis inserted between my breasts, perhaps my intensely beating heart could be felt by Mizuki. Supposing that's the case.........	s03a	0452
S001A_01EV	3	26	Natsuko: （I'll be noticed by Mizuki........ Kuu, Mizuki will know I'm feeling like this）	s03a	0453
S001A_01EV	3	27	It's absolutely wrong for him to know. It was to the degree that when I seemed to think about it, my womb ached,  excited by that fall from virtue, and I became even wetter.	s03a	0454
S001A_01EV	3	28	Natsuko: （Haa, haaaa, aaah, w, why is it like this.......... Naah, aaah, things like feeling this way with my son's penis, I, I!!）	s03a	0455
S001A_01EV	3	29	A long time ago......with coincidentally losing my husband, I had shut in the raptures of being a woman, now,  because of my son, it was trying to untie that seal.	s03a	0456
S001A_01EV	3	30	Natsuko: （Hurry.......hurry up and finish Mizuki, your mother, your mother is feeling strange, finish quickly）	s03a	0457
S001A_01EV	3	31	Even though now my body showed womanly reactions, the reason I did have left was in the role of a mother.  But.....	s03a	0458
S001A_01EV	3	32	Natsuko: （As it is...fuuu, ahfuu, as it is, if this continues...）	s03a	0459
S001A_01EV	3	33	My remaining reason as a mother would also go out, perhaps it would become so that I'd seek only gratification as a woman.	s03a	0460
S001A_01EV	3	34	Natsuko: （Things like reaching my womanhood....... before my son........ it's wrong, it's absolutely wrong!!）	s03a	0461
S001A_01EV	3	35	I was really going mad......with that sort of dread  covering my body, a cold sweat rose to the surface of my skin making me sweaty with pleasure so that it ached.	s03a	0462
S001A_01EV	3	36	Mizuki: 「Kuu, fuuu, aah, mother, nnn, soon I, won't be able to endure it」	s03a	0463
S001A_01EV	3	37	While pinching my nipples, Mizuki hastened the movement of his hips.	s03a	0464
S001A_01EV	3	38	Natsuko: 「Nn, fuuu, nbuu, nfuuuuuu」	s03a	0465
S001A_01EV	3	39	It was as if I was paying no notice to what was happening as Mizuki pushed onto my face the tip of his  penis intensely.	s03a	0466
S001A_01EV	3	40	Natsuko: （Not able to endure it...by no means, Mizuki  now...s, surely it's a lie...that sort of...）	s03a	0467
S001A_01EV	4	1	His penis pressing on my face I clearly realized was convulsing.	s03a	0468
S001A_01EV	4	2	Natsuko: （Coming.........from Mizuki's penis........ Aah, semen is coming?）	s03a	0469
S001A_01EV	4	3	Mizuki was ejaculating to me. For a second I called to mind that scene.	s03a	0470
S001A_01EV	4	4	Natsuko: （Aah, aaah, aaaaaah!!）	s03a	0471
S001A_01EV	4	5	Intense pleasant feelings ran throughout my entire body, as my body reminiscingly shook. My overflowing  nectar increased and my womb got hot so that it burned.	s03a	0472
S001A_01EV	4	6	Natsuko: （W, why, is my body hot, hii, hiaah, a, a lie, I'm imagining my son ejaculating, I!!）	s03a	0473
S001A_01EV	4	7	My head became numb, in my mind, only the image of Mizuki ejaculating was suspended. And my body continued to react sensitively to that wild idea.	s03a	0474
S001A_01EV	4	8	Mizuki: 「It's coming, mother, since it's coming!!」	s03a	0475
S001A_01EV	4	9	Natsuko: （Fuaah, aah, Mizuki's sperm is coming, aah, aaah, his sperm, kufuuu, fuuuuu!!）	s03a	0476
S001A_01EV	4	10	With my excitement rising, my whole body stiffened at the sweet pleasure, trembling bit by bit.	s03a	0477
S001A_01EV	4	11	Natsuko: （Aaah, fuu, l, lie, n, noo, although it's wrong, I, I, more, moreee!!）	s03a	0478
S001A_01EV	4	12	Mizuki: 「Motherrrr!! Cumming!!」	s03a	0479
S001A_01EV	4	13	Natsuko: （Uaaaaah!! Coming, kuu, uuu, I, I tooooooo!! Aaaaaaaaaaah!!）	s03a	0480
S001A_01EV	4	14	While fighting frantically to not let the shouts in my mind be let out, I took Mizuki's semen.	s03a	0481
S001A_01EV	4	15	Natsuko: 「Haa, nn, nfuuu, kufuuuuu」	s03a	0482
S001A_01EV	4	16	Mizuki's semen rained down furiously so that it struck my whole face.	s03a	0483
S001A_01EV	4	17	Natsuko: （Ama.........amazing.......aah, aah, so intense like this, fuaah, I can feel how hot it is）	s03a	0484
S001A_01EV	4	18	Together with Mizuki's ejaculation, large waves  of orgasms assailed my body. Although I stifled  frantically my voice of delight...........	s03a	0485
S001A_01EV	4	19	Natsuko: 「Fuuu, kuuu, nuu, nfuuu, fuaaaaah」	s03a	0486
S001A_01EV	4	20	I wasn't able to completely contain my sweet, gasping voice.	s03a	0487
S001A_01EV	4	21	And then..........	s03a	0488
S001A_01EV	4	22	Natsuko: （Haa, fuaah, aaaaah, it's going in my........ nnuu, Mizuki's semen is going in my..........）	s03a	0489
S001A_01EV	4	23	The semen he threw out in a large quantity, was falling down and dangling towards the inside of my partly open lips.	s03a	0490
S001A_01EV	4	24	Natsuko: （Mizuki's sperm..........chuuu, churuu, chupuu, Mizuki's sperm is inside my mouth.........）	s03a	0491
S001A_01EV	4	25	With taking and entwining my tongue around the sperm reminiscingly, I swallowed it on instinct.	s03a	0492
S001A_01EV	4	26	Natsuko: （Aah, Mizuki's flavor.........this is the taste of Mizuki's  sperm, isn't it.........kuuu, aaaaah）	s03a	0493
S001A_01EV	4	27	Mizuki's sperm made its way to my stomach on its way from my throat. While in a trance at that taste, once again a large wave of pleasure advanced upon me.	s03a	0494
S001A_01EV	4	28	Natsuko: 「Nn, kuu, fuaaah, aah, ahfuuu, fuaaaaaah」	s03a	0495
S001A_01EV	4	29	Simply because I wanted to fill my womb with that hot, young sperm, my body ached and still more of my nectar overflowed.	s03a	0496
S001A_01EV	4	30	Natsuko: （I, haa, nnuu, came......... I orgasmed again swallowing Mizuki's sperm......... Aah, nuuuuu）	s03a	0497
S001A_01EV	4	31	While my son reached it, I savored an orgasm, I got it again when I swallowed my son's sperm.	s03a	0498
S001A_01EV	4	32	Natsuko: （Haa, haa, things, things like this..........）	s03a	0499
S001A_01EV	4	33	My head was in disorder at the pleasure in the role of a woman I had forgotten long ago, I looked up at Mizuki's face continuing to still ejaculate.	s03a	0500
S001A_01EV	4	34	Mizuki: 「Haa, haa, haaa, on mother, I came so much on mother's face.........kuu, nnuuuu」	s03a	0501
S001A_01EV	4	35	Whether or not I was excited a second time about dirtying me, the semen on my face was furiously scattered around.	s03a	0502
S001A_01EV	4	36	Natsuko: （Hafuu, fuaaah, aah, things like a mother orgasming at being dirtied by her son's sperm......）	s03a	0503
S001A_01EV	4	37	With attracting the waves of pleasure from Mizuki, intense unpleasant feelings budded concerning myself orgasming.	s03a	0504
S001A_01EV	4	38	Mizuki: 「Nn, kuu, haa, haaa............ mother, now, I'd better you clean you up」	s03a	0505
S001A_01EV	4	39	With Mizuki finally finishing ejaculating and separating me to get tissues, I gently brushed my face sticky with his semen.	s03a	0506
S001A_01EV	4	40	My hair and face and then my dirtied breasts had been cleaned up by Mizuki. In detail, Mizuki's movements were tender caresses, but that made my body burn again....	s03a	0507
S001A_01EV	5	1	Natsuko: （With this it's over.......nn, fuuu, it won't happen again）	s03a	0508
S001A_01EV	5	2	For the sake of preserving myself as a mother, I repeated those words inside my mind over and over.	s03a	0509
S001A_01EV	5	3	Mizuki: 「Fuu, nn, with this I'm done. Mother, good night........」	s03a	0510
S001A_01EV	5	4	Mizuki, having wiped off the semen so that I was clean, left the room from giving me a kiss on the cheek after hesitating a little.	s03a	0511
