S003A	1	1	Aiko: 「Mr. Matsumura, you're drinking again, aren't you」	s03a	0000
S003A	1	2	Matsumura: 「Ah, no, that」	s03a	0001
S003A	1	3	Aiko: 「Do not play dumb with me. Because I talked to your wife. Besides, the cost of your liver is not worth it」	s03a	0002
S003A	1	4	Matsumura: 「Haa……」	s03a	0003
S003A	1	5	Aiko: 「Haa, don't give me that. If you don't stop  drinking, don't you know what will happen?」	s03a	0004
S003A	1	6	Matsumura: 「I, I'm sorry……」	s03a	0005
S003A	1	7	Aiko: 「As for Mr. Matsumura being sorry, I'm already tired of hearing it. Got it? Next time you don't listen to my advice, if you drink.........」	s03a	0006
S003A	1	8	Matsumura: 「I, I understand. Ok, since I will stop  drinking already」	s03a	0007
S003A	1	9	Aiko: 「Ok, since I'm giving you some medicine........ So, next time, please come in two weeks」	s03a	0008
S003A	1	10	Matsumura: 「Ok, thank you very much」	s03a	0009
S003A	1	11	Aiko: 「Take care」	s03a	0010
S003A	1	12	Dr. Aiko, while filling out clinical records, Mr. Matsumura left the examining room.	s03a	0011
S003A	1	13	Aiko: 「Fuuu, you have to really wonder if alcohol is more important to him than living, huh?」	s03a	0012
S003A	1	14	Katsuragi Clinic being the only hospital in town, the one sole doctor, Aiko Katsuragi, breathed a sigh.	s03a	0013
S003A	1	15	Aiko: 「Ok, please hand this over to the receptionist」	s03a	0014
S003A	1	16	Natsuko: 「Ok」	s03a	0015
S003A	1	17	From Dr. Aiko looking over the clinical records she had finished writing, I held them to the receptionist and instantly returned.	s03a	0016
S003A	1	18	Aiko: 「I wonder, was that the last patient after Mr. Matsumura?」	s03a	0017
S003A	1	19	Natsuko: 「Yes. Mr. Matsumura was the last」	s03a	0018
S003A	1	20	Aiko: 「Nnnn, well then, we made it through the morning」	s03a	0019
S003A	1	21	Dr. Aiko, giving a stretch, spat out a big sigh.	s03a	0020
S003A	1	22	Natsuko: 「That's enough for now.........」	s03a	0021
S003A	1	23	Aiko: 「Oh? But, for sure Mrs. Natsuko must be tired?」	s03a	0022
S003A	1	24	With Dr. Aiko's face watching my face, she looked doubtful.	s03a	0023
S003A	1	25	Natsuko: 「Is, is that so? But, I'm not tired at all........」	s03a	0024
S003A	1	26	Although I swung my head in a rush, I felt startled inside.	s03a	0025
S003A	1	27	Aiko: 「Take it easy now. Because Mrs. Natsuko is the only registered nurse at Katsuragi Clinic.」	s03a	0026
S003A	1	28	Natsuko: 「That's so.........but, Dr. Aiko is also the only doctor, isn't she」	s03a	0027
S003A	1	29	Aiko: 「I'm fine. Because it's not things like  getting tired at all」	s03a	0028
S003A	1	30	Dr. Aiko shrugged her shoulders, acting silly. That's  to say it's different when she shows it to patients, with a  "playing dumb" expression, I feel she's always affectionate.	s03a	0029
S003A	1	31	Aiko: 「But, really........your complexion is kind of poor, are you unwell?」	s03a	0030
S003A	1	32	Dr. Aiko, having returned to her doctor's face from her silly face, stared at me once again.	s03a	0031
S003A	1	33	Natsuko: 「Ah, I'm really okay. That........it's a little lack of sleep.......」	s03a	0032
S003A	1	34	Aiko: 「Lack of sleep? I wonder,  is something bothering you?」	s03a	0033
S003A	1	35	Natsuko: 「My troubles......wel, well.........」	s03a	0034
S003A	1	36	What to do.........with Dr. Aiko, I wondered whether or not to speak my mind of my smoldering troubles inside my chest........	s03a	0035
S003A	1	37	Aiko: 「Mrs. Natsuko?」	s03a	0036
S003A	1	38	Dr. Aiko stared at my hesitant face.	s03a	0037
S003A	1	39	Natsuko: 「Ah, no, it's nothing.........since I'm all right」	s03a	0038
S003A	1	40	As I thought, I couldn't talk about it to this person. With seeming to think about that, I showed a swing of  my head to Dr. Aiko.	s03a	0039
S003A	2	1	Aiko: 「Ok. But, if something is really bothering you, please say something, ok」	s03a	0040
S003A	2	2	I guess she didn't feel like pushing it out of me. Seeing me shake my head, Dr. Aiko closed the conversation with a little nod.	s03a	0041
S003A	2	3	Aiko: 「Well then, shall we get some lunch soon?」	s03a	0042
S003A	2	4	Natsuko: 「Why not........I'm a little hungry」	s03a	0043
S003A	2	5	Aiko: 「If you have an appetite, that's all right. I'm also famished」	s03a	0044
S003A	2	6	With saying it with a smile, Dr. Aiko left the examining room.	s03a	0045
S003A	2	7	Walking through a corridor fastening her residence with the doctor's office, Dr. Aiko entered her living room.	s03a	0046
S003A	2	8	Toshio: 「Ooh, I was going to call you just now. It's exactly noon, isn't it」	s03a	0047
S003A	2	9	Dr. Aiko's husband, Toshio Katsuragi, was in the living room, his face unraveled when he saw us.	s03a	0048
S003A	2	10	Aiko: 「You said noon.......what are you doing here. Aren't you suppose to be at school?」	s03a	0049
S003A	2	11	Dr. Aiko watched teacher Toshio with a face of not knowing why her husband was home.	s03a	0050
S003A	2	12	Toshio: 「What, now is a lunch break, isn't it. Besides, I don't have an afternoon class」	s03a	0051
S003A	2	13	Aiko: 「Fuuu, you snuck out again, didn't you」	s03a	0052
S003A	2	14	Toshio: 「Hahaa, that's ok, isn't it Look, are you going to have lunch?」	s03a	0053
S003A	2	15	Aiko: 「Fuu, although it doesn't matter even if it's take out food」	s03a	0054
S003A	2	16	Toshio: 「Mrs. Natsuko too, please, by all means have a seat. Since I'll treat you to some soba I made on my previous break」	s03a	0055
S003A	2	17	Natsuko: 「Dr. Toshio made it himself?」	s03a	0056
S003A	2	18	Regarding his employment as a teacher, he was referred to as a doctor in the same way as Dr. Aiko was whether or not he was actually one.	s03a	0057
S003A	2	19	Toshio: 「Oh yes. If I do say so myself, I'm fairly skillful at it」	s03a	0058
S003A	2	20	Aiko: 「Truly, your hobbies are the only thing you care about... You're impossible」	s03a	0059
S003A	2	21	Natsuko: 「Oh, that's good, isn't it. I think having things like many hobbies is fantastic」	s03a	0060
S003A	2	22	Toshio: 「Hahahaa, Mrs. Natsuko understands well. Natsuko wants to follow in my footsteps too, doesn't she」	s03a	0061
S003A	2	23	Aiko: 「Hobbies are fine, but you should be a bit more  considerate of the people around you..... Fuuu, maa, what am I saying, it's hopeless, isn't it」	s03a	0062
S003A	2	24	Dr. Aiko began a complaint, but shook her head a little, giving up.	s03a	0063
S003A	2	25	Toshio: 「Look, look, all you're doing is complaining..... Now, let's eat. Because I'm really starved」	s03a	0064
S003A	2	26	Dr. Toshio brought the soba and served it up in a heap.	s03a	0065
S003A	2	27	Natsuko: 「There's.....so much, isn't there.....」	s03a	0066
S003A	2	28	Toshio: 「Hahaa, I wonder a little too much? If there's too much, it's ok if we eat on it even tonight. Ok, now, by all means, please eat」	s03a	0067
S003A	2	29	Natsuko: 「T, then, cheers.....」	s03a	0068
S003A	2	30	Though, I wonder is this too much? While seeming to think my innermost thoughts, I took a portion of soba with my chopsticks, urged on by my hunger.	s03a	0069
S003A	2	31	Aiko: 「Fuuu, surely, I too think you made too much」	s03a	0070
S003A	2	32	Toshio: 「What? You can't eat any more?」	s03a	0071
S003A	2	33	Seeing Dr. Aiko putting down her chopsticks, Dr. Toshio looked a little displeased.	s03a	0072
S003A	2	34	Aiko: 「I said I can't eat any more.....I've had enough」	s03a	0073
S003A	2	35	Toshio: 「Is that so.....maa, I also couldn't make our  children eat it. No good having leftovers.  That aside, how was the taste?」	s03a	0074
S003A	2	36	Aiko: 「The taste? I think it's better than soba bought in the market, but......」	s03a	0075
S003A	2	37	Toshio: 「Don't you think it isn't like that? It should be much more appetizing than the soba on the market」	s03a	0076
S003A	2	38	Dr. Toshio's face became dim on account of it being unthinkable.	s03a	0077
S003A	2	39	Aiko: 「Isn't that what I also said..... As for me, it's better than soba on the market」	s03a	0078
S003A	2	40	Toshio: 「Fuuu, you're always like that...... One way or another you complain about everything I do」	s03a	0079
S003A	3	1	Aiko: 「What? How did you get that I was complaining?」	s03a	0080
S003A	3	2	With Dr. Toshio's words that he softly muttered, Dr. Aiko stiffened up her mouth.	s03a	0081
S003A	3	3	Natsuko: 「Uh, umm......the soba, I thought it was delicious」	s03a	0082
S003A	3	4	With speaking in a rush so as to smooth the couple's relationship,	s03a	0083
S003A	3	5	Aiko: 「It's ok, Mrs. Natsuko. This doesn't concern you. It isn't delicious when you don't say it isn't delicious. Since it's useless making this person grasp that」	s03a	0083
S003A	3	6	Natsuko: 「Ah, no, I really......」	s03a	0084
S003A	3	7	Toshio: 「I'm returning to school......since it's already time」	s03a	0085
S003A	3	8	With Dr. Toshio standing up rudely, having ruined his mood completely, he left the living room.	s03a	0086
S003A	3	9	Aiko: 「Fuuuu, leaving without finishing again..... and also not cleaning up......」	s03a	0087
S003A	3	10	Dr. Aiko breathed a sigh seeing the tableware with leftover soba on the table.	s03a	0088
S003A	3	11	Natsuko: 「In spite of going through that trouble of making soba for Dr. Aiko......」	s03a	0089
S003A	3	12	Aiko: 「Aah, it's ok, it's ok. Because doing things for me is an excuse. That man only wants to do things for himself」	s03a	0090
S003A	3	13	Natsuko: 「Ha, haa……」	s03a	0091
S003A	3	14	Aiko: 「Truly, at such a time, Mrs. Natsuko is enviable」	s03a	0092
S003A	3	15	Natsuko: 「I'm.........enviable?」	s03a	0093
S003A	3	16	Aiko: 「Yes.......I too, like Mrs. Natsuko, want to enjoy being alone」	s03a	0094
S003A	3	17	Natsuko: 「I, I.......although one might say I'm alone, there's also Mizuki.......」	s03a	0095
S003A	3	18	Aiko: 「Oh, with your children also, surely you're able to see others?」	s03a	0096
S003A	3	19	Natsuko: 「Ha? See others?」	s03a	0097
S003A	3	20	Aiko: 「Yes......oh, is there any chance that..... your lack of sleep is because you're not able to  sleep all night long enduring that, I wonder?」	s03a	0098
S003A	3	21	With thinking about floating an impish facial  expression, Dr. Aiko gazed at me curiously.	s03a	0099
S003A	3	22	Natsuko: 「"That".......is it "that"?」	s03a	0100
S003A	3	23	Aiko: 「Yes.....oh, was I on the mark? It's enviable, is it not. Things like me, already my husband has neglected me for how many years?」	s03a	0101
S003A	3	24	Natsuko: 「Ah, n, no, that isn't it. My lack of sleep isn't because of things like that.......because I also lost my husband....I'm not seeing anyone......」	s03a	0102
S003A	3	25	Aiko: 「Eh? Really? You said you lost your husband, no less than 10 years ago now, right?」	s03a	0103
S003A	3	26	Natsuko: 「Y, yes, that's right, but.....but, my children's things and housework.....besides, because I have to work, finding the time........」	s03a	0104
S003A	3	27	Talking about the matter of my dead husband, was no longer something hurt me. Because, together  with time, my grief had, little by little, faded away.......	s03a	0105
S003A	3	28	Even so, I did feel a little pain deep inside, but.....	s03a	0106
S003A	3	29	Aiko: 「It's wasteful, isn't it. If that's the case Mrs. Natsuko, I think I'd be gathering men up and throwing them away, but.......」	s03a	0107
S003A	3	30	Natsuko: 「I, I couldn't do things like that. Things like a mother of a family like me.......」	s03a	0108
S003A	3	31	Aiko: 「Oh, if Mrs. Natsuko is a mother of a family, then I'm a grandmother of a family, aren't I」	s03a	0109
S003A	3	32	Natsuko: 「Ah, n, no, I didn't mean it like that........」	s03a	0110
S003A	3	33	Aiko: 「Is that so......because I'm a crony grandmother, is why my husband also doesn't give me any, isn't it」	s03a	0111
S003A	3	34	Natsuko: 「Uh, umm, that.........I........」	s03a	0112
S003A	3	35	Dr. Aiko let her shoulders sag. I couldn't find any words to that response. Although it wasn't my plan to say it like that....	s03a	0113
S003A	3	36	Aiko: 「.......fuu, fufuu, fufufufufuuu」	s03a	0114
S003A	3	37	Dr. Aiko's shoulders, bit by bit, began to tremble, her face hidden, and as I thought about what she said, she let out a laughter, not able to withstand it anymore.	s03a	0115
S003A	3	38	Natsuko: 「Dr. Aiko.......pl, please don't make fun!」	s03a	0116
S003A	3	39	The moment I heard her laughter, I understood that she was making a joke on my behalf. With my loud, spontaneous voice,	s03a	0117
S003A	3	40	Aiko: 「Fufufuu, forgive me, won't you...... But, you really aren't seeing anyone?」	s03a	0118
S003A	4	1	Natsuko: 「Th, this conversation is already over」	s03a	0119
S003A	4	2	Aiko: 「It's wasteful, don't you think. Wondering what all the men are doing, huh」	s03a	0120
S003A	4	3	Natsuko: 「Th, that, I, I have to return home soon. It's wrong if I don't get started on dinner」	s03a	0121
S003A	4	4	Aiko: 「Yes........well then, I also have to clean up and I wonder about sorting the clinical records」	s03a	0122
S003A	4	5	Natsuko: 「Aah, since I'll clean up」	s03a	0123
S003A	4	6	Aiko: 「I'm fine, I'm fine. Because cleaning up after a husband is the wife's duty. Mrs. Natsuko, leave me to my house chores」	s03a	0124
S003A	4	7	Dr. Aiko swung her head lightly, beginning to clean up the leftover soba.	s03a	0125
S003A	4	8	Natsuko: 「W, well then, I'll return home at once,  see you later」	s03a	0126
S003A	4	9	Aiko: 「Yes, well, see you」	s03a	0127
S003A	4	10	From saying my farewells to Dr. Aiko, I left Katsuragi Clinic towards home.	s03a	0128
S003A	4	11	With returning home straight from Katsuragi Clinic, I breathed once to let go of my feelings.	s03a	0129
S003A	4	12	From now, I had to remain firm doing housework in the role of a mother with children with no longer being a registered nurse.	s03a	0130
S003A	4	13	With seeming to persuade myself of that, I opened the door and entered my house.	s03a	0131
S003A	4	14	Natsuko: 「Well then........」	s03a	0132
S003A	4	15	With getting through with preparing dinner, I took one short breath.	s03a	0133
S003A	4	16	From the afternoon medical examinations finishing, and with Mizuki instantly returning home, it would be no good if didn't have any dinner prepared, huh.	s03a	0134
S003A	4	17	Natsuko: 「Next is, laundry, isn't it......」	s03a	0135
S003A	4	18	From inside the laundry basket in the corner of the room, I fetched the clothes to be washed.	s03a	0136
S003A	4	19	Natsuko: 「Aah!? W, what........?」	s03a	0137
S003A	4	20	With a sensation running along my finger, I let out a surprised voice.	s03a	0138
S003A	4	21	Natsuko: 「Th, this..........」	s03a	0139
S003A	4	22	Hanging in the air from the fluid on my finger, was a grassy-smelling odor.	s03a	0140
S003A	4	23	Natsuko: 「What is this on my underwear..........?」	s03a	0141
S003A	4	24	This morning, this was the underwear I had changed out of before going to work.	s03a	0142
S003A	4	25	Natsuko: 「Aaah！？」	s03a	0143
S003A	4	26	In the instant I comprehended what that was, my body went rigid.	s03a	0144
S003A	4	27	Natsuko: 「S, such........on his mother's underwear...... se........m.......en..........」	s03a	0145
S003A	4	28	Mizuki's sperm had been purposely disgorged onto my underwear. Since I had gone out, Mizuki had gotten it wet by masturbating using that........	s03a	0146
S003A	4	29	Natsuko: 「W, why would he do such a thing.......」	s03a	0147
S003A	4	30	With putting my hand on the panties Mizuki had dirtied, I recalled a flashback of events that had happened this year.	s03a	0148
S003A	4	31	Until last year, there hadn't been anything unusual with Mizuki. But, this year......	s03a	0149
S003A	4	32	First, although he had watched me intermittently  casually changing clothes, that, nowadays, he peeked  at me when I took baths, and now.....	s03a	0150
S003A	4	33	Natsuko: 「As far as something like this........」	s03a	0151
S003A	4	34	He had come to doing his mischief on my underwear. Furthermore....in the underwear I had worn until morning...	s03a	0152
S003A	4	35	Natsuko: 「On his mother's underwear, things like this......」	s03a	0153
S003A	4	36	I understood the matter of a boy going through puberty taking an interest in women. But, towards his own mother....why did he bear such carnal desires?	s03a	0154
S003A	4	37	Natsuko: 「Now...is it ok to just let it go? What would you...」	s03a	0155
S003A	4	38	If only my husband were here at a time like this... Maybe he could tell me what to in this situation. But...my husband isn't here.	s03a	0156
S003A	4	39	Natsuko: 「What to do........what can I do.......」	s03a	0157
S003A	4	40	With spontaneously grasping tightly the dirtied underwear, I touched the semen with my finger again.	s03a	0158
S003A	5	1	Natsuko: 「Aah……」	s03a	0159
S003A	5	2	With parting my hand unintentionally, and with the pitter-patter of my heartbeat,  I dropped the panties to the floor.	s03a	0160
S003A	5	3	Natsuko: 「As I thought.....this is wrong, isn't it...... as is, if I leave it like this......」	s03a	0161
S003A	5	4	Although I think it's an impossible subject, Mizuki is taking an interest in women, but if he's watching me as the target of sex, I absolutely cannot let that happen	s03a	0162
S003A	5	5	Natsuko: 「But……」	s03a	0163
S003A	5	6	If I talked about it right to Mizuki's face, I would surely hurt his feelings.	s03a	0164
S003A	5	7	Natsuko: 「Aah, I don't know......I don't know what is the right  thing to do....... you, you」	s03a	0165
S003A	5	8	With almost begging the help of my dead husband, I didn't know the best course of action.	s03a	0166
S003A	5	9	Natsuko: 「Dr. Aiko.......should I ask Dr. Aiko?」	s03a	0167
S003A	5	10	This morning, I recalled Dr. Aiko's words of about discussing my troubles.	s03a	0168
S003A	5	11	Mamoru Katsuragi was Mizuki's friend, and he was Dr. Aiko's son......	s03a	0169
S003A	5	12	Natsuko: 「Yes......if it's Dr. Aiko, surely.......」	s03a	0170
S003A	5	13	Even though she has more experience  raising children, because it's Dr. Aiko,  maybe she can give me some good advice.	s03a	0171
S003A	5	14	Natsuko: 「It's not something to get embarrassed about..... it's for the sake of Mizuki.......」	s03a	0172
S003A	5	15	Mizuki cannot go down this wrong path without his father here, if I'm level-headed.........	s03a	0173
S003A	5	16	Natsuko: 「I'll consult with Dr. Aiko........」	s03a	0174
S003A	5	17	With muttering a little so as to express my decision and determination, I picked up my panties that had fallen to the floor.	s03a	0175
S003A	5	18	Because afternoon examinations had begun, the most busy time had gradually passed. After this, it was expected there were no patients....	s03a	0176
S003A	5	19	Aiko: 「Fuuuu, I wonder if today's finally ending with this」	s03a	0177
S003A	5	20	A patient was leaving the examining room, leaving just me and her. Dr. Aiko put out a big stretch.	s03a	0178
S003A	5	21	Natsuko: 「Seems that way, huh.......」	s03a	0179
S003A	5	22	Now, I had no choice but to talk. Because, after the  medical examinations had finished, Mizuki would come home without dinner prepared.	s03a	0180
S003A	5	23	Aiko: 「What's wrong? Although, you sort of don't look so well again?」	s03a	0181
S003A	5	24	Natsuko: 「Uh, umm, Dr. Aiko.......」	s03a	0182
S003A	5	25	With my appeal, Dr. Aiko turned her eyes directly at me.	s03a	0184
S003A	5	26	Natsuko: 「……」	s03a	0185
S003A	5	27	What to do. What would be the best way of saying it? Naturally, I wondered if it would be better to settle it between just me and Mizuki.	s03a	0186
S003A	5	28	With hesitating once again, for a short while I sunk into silence.	s03a	0187
S003A	5	29	Aiko: 「What's the matter? By any chance, I wonder is it about your lack of sleep?」	s03a	0188
S003A	5	30	Natsuko: 「Y, yes. Umm, as a matter of fact......」	s03a	0189
S003A	5	31	As I thought, I was losing control of the situation. Since I wasn't able to come up with a solution myself, I have no choice. With seeming to tell myself this,	s03a	0190
S003A	5	32	Natsuko: 「It's about Mizuki......that.......I wanted to ask  Dr. Aiko.......」	s03a	0191
S003A	5	33	Aiko: 「Mizuki-kun? Ahh!? Did something happen to your son at home?」	s03a	0192
S003A	5	34	Natsuko: 「N, no, it's related to Mamoru-kun. Mizuki, that.....」	s03a	0193
S003A	5	35	Aiko: 「Mrs. Natsuko, calm down a little. Take a deep breath.」	s03a	0194
S003A	5	36	Dr. Aiko spoke softly in order to calm my feelings. With hearing that voice of Dr. Aiko's, little by little I settled down.	s03a	0195
S003A	5	37	Natsuko: 「From the beginning of this year........Mizuki has been peeking at me bathing and changing clothes」	s03a	0196
S003A	5	38	I had said it. I had spoken the embarrassing conduct of my son. My face became hot so that it burned with embarrassment.	s03a	0197
S003A	5	39	Aiko: 「Mizuki-kun is it.........and? Is he only just peeking at you when you bathe and change clothes?」	s03a	0198
S003A	5	40	Natsuko: 「N, no, there's something else.......at night...... sometimes when I'm sleeping......he touches  my body.....」	s03a	0199
S003A	6	1	Aiko: 「He touches your body.......I wonder, does he caress you?」	s03a	0200
S003A	6	2	Dr. Aiko made a sound in her throat, gazing at me with indistinct, muddy eyes.	s03a	0201
S003A	6	3	Natsuko: 「C caress me, it's, it's not like that at all. That........I feel him gently brushing me...... it's just touching」	s03a	0202
S003A	6	4	Aiko: 「I see......but, does Mrs. Natsuko, with touching, also get strange feelings?」	s03a	0203
S003A	6	5	Dr. Aiko leaned forward like she was a little excited by it.	s03a	0204
S003A	6	6	Natsuko: 「W, what are you saying.......Mizuki is my son. That sort of thing with a son......」	s03a	0205
S003A	6	7	Aiko: 「Of, of course, huh. I'm sorry........my questions were a little weird」	s03a	0206
S003A	6	8	With raising up her partly leaned forward body, Dr. Aiko coughed a little.	s03a	0207
S003A	6	9	Natsuko: 「Umm, and I.......don't know what the best thing to do is........」	s03a	0208
S003A	6	10	Aiko: 「I see......but, I think you shouldn't care about things like that」	s03a	0209
S003A	6	11	Natsuko: 「A, are you sure? But, as far as on my underwear.... that, although if it's a practical joke.......」	s03a	0210
S003A	6	12	Aiko: 「A practical joke......Did he masturbate using Mrs. Natsuko's underwear?」	s03a	0211
S003A	6	13	Natsuko: 「Ah, y, yes.......that on my underwear....... that was on it」	s03a	0212
S003A	6	14	Aiko: 「"That".......sperm?」	s03a	0213
S003A	6	15	Natsuko: 「Y, yes........」	s03a	0214
S003A	6	16	Aiko: 「I see.........Mizuki-kun's sperm.........」	s03a	0215
S003A	6	17	Like she were imagining Mizuki masturbating, Dr. Aiko stared into empty space.	s03a	0216
S003A	6	18	Natsuko: 「Dr. Aiko........really, is Mizuki surely all right as  he is? That child, since his father is gone...... that.....」	s03a	0217
S003A	6	19	Aiko: 「It's all right.......maa, because he's that sort of  age......his age can't be helped holding an interest in women」	s03a	0218
S003A	6	20	Natsuko: 「But, in his own mother......doing things like that with a mother partner, Mizuki is......」	s03a	0219
S003A	6	21	Aiko: 「You're making a fuss, it's fine, don't think about it. He's just showing his interest in the opposite sex closest to him. Although.......」	s03a	0220
S003A	6	22	Natsuko: 「Although, what?」	s03a	0221
S003A	6	23	Aiko: 「Gradually, maybe you had better let him be more independent, huh」	s03a	0222
S003A	6	24	Natsuko: 「Independent?」	s03a	0223
S003A	6	25	Aiko: 「Yes. It's not just Mizuki-kun, If Mrs. Natsuko also doesn't not let go from Mizuki-kun」	s03a	0224
S003A	6	26	Natsuko: 「Me also letting go........umm, well, surely it's ok not to advise him of his mischief then?」	s03a	0225
S003A	6	27	Aiko: 「It's ok, it's ok. Leave him alone, eventually Mizuki will be able to find someone he likes and then he'll shift his interest to them. Now, it's just temporary」	s03a	0226
S003A	6	28	Natsuko: 「Haa.........is that so.......」	s03a	0227
S003A	6	29	With Dr. Aiko's words putting out an easy reply, on one hand I felt relieved, feeling  just a little desolate.	s03a	0228
S003A	6	30	Aiko: 「Yes......as for speeding it up, you have to make him point his interest to the opposite sex  other than Mrs. Natsuko, don't you think」	s03a	0229
S003A	6	31	Natsuko: 「You mean, get him a girlfriend?」	s03a	0230
S003A	6	32	Aiko: 「It doesn't have to be a girlfriend. As long as he likes someone, because it's good if he has them on his mind」	s03a	0231
S003A	6	33	Natsuko: 「Haa........but, things like telling him to like girls  other than me, it's strange, isn't it」	s03a	0232
S003A	6	34	Aiko: 「Aaah, although if I were a bit younger, I would  give Mizuki-kun a companion」	s03a	0233
S003A	6	35	Natsuko: 「Eh?」	s03a	0234
S003A	6	36	While smiling all of a sudden, the meaning of  Dr. Aiko's words she departed did not catch on for a moment.	s03a	0235
S003A	6	37	Natsuko: 「A companion......Dr. Aiko?」	s03a	0236
S003A	6	38	Aiko: 「Yes.......If it were to permitted by Mrs. Natsuko, I, with Mizuki-kun......」	s03a	0237
S003A	6	39	Even if it were certainly a joke, while her eyes were wet and filled to the brim with a sensuality, Dr. Aiko looked hard at me.	s03a	0238
S003A	6	40	Natsuko: 「Uh, umm, a companion......... N, no, Dr. Aiko like that, nothing but a joke......」	s03a	0239
S003A	7	1	Aiko: 「Oh? Really, what reason do I have to joke? Naturally, if Mizuki-kun were to say he was able to be interested in me, but.......」	s03a	0240
S003A	7	2	Natsuko: 「Th, that sort of........things like that, I........」	s03a	0241
S003A	7	3	Aiko: 「Fufufuu, but, maa, because the reality those sorts of things are impossible, this conversation isn't really necessary, is it」	s03a	0242
S003A	7	4	With shrugging her shoulders a little, Dr. Aiko muttered seeming a little disappointed.	s03a	0243
S003A	7	5	Aiko: 「Mrs. Natsuko too, pay those things no mind for the remainder, huh. If you worry about only Mizuki's things, Mizuki-kun also might become aware of Mrs. Natsuko」	s03a	0244
S003A	7	6	Natsuko: 「Understood. As Dr. Aiko says, I'll give it no more serious thought for the remainder」	s03a	0245
S003A	7	7	Aiko: 「Yes, and that.......you won't let him go, huh.  I wonder why you don't find an extra hand,  even if it's a new boyfriend?」	s03a	0246
S003A	7	8	Natsuko: 「W, why this conversation again」	s03a	0247
S003A	7	9	Aiko: 「Among patients as well, Mrs. Natsuko feels uneasy around those sorts of people」	s03a	0248
S003A	7	10	Natsuko: 「S, since this conversation is already over. Aah, are there any more patients coming?」	s03a	0249
S003A	7	11	Aiko: 「Fufuu, I sort of deceived you a little, didn't I」	s03a	0250
S003A	7	12	Natsuko: 「Ah, umm, since I'm summoning the patients」	s03a	0251
S003A	7	13	Although the conversation had strayed to somewhat strange territory, it was a good idea to consult with  Dr. Aiko.	s03a	0252
S003A	7	14	While my feelings lightened up just a little, I opened the door of the examining room.	s03a	0253
S003A	7	15	Today with leaving behind Katsuragi Clinic having  finished work, I was making my way home.	s03a	0254
S003A	7	16	Natsuko: 「Oh? Maki-chan, hello」	s03a	0255
S003A	7	17	With coming upon Dr. Aiko's daughter, Maki Katsuragi walking ahead of me, I greeted her while waving a little.	s03a	0256
S003A	7	18	Maki: 「Hello, Mrs. Natsuko. I appreciate your work」	s03a	0257
S003A	7	19	Maki-chan lowered her head in a polite bow.	s03a	0258
S003A	7	20	Natsuko: 「Maki-chan, are you just going out I wonder?」	s03a	0259
S003A	7	21	Maki: 「After this, I'm going to my brother-in-law's place」	s03a	0260
S003A	7	22	Natsuko: 「Oh, I see.........fufuu, but you're not trying to be  a hindrance to the newly-weds and possibly making your Onee-chan mad, are you?」	s03a	0261
S003A	7	23	Dr. Aiko's eldest daughter was Maki-chan's older sister, and her newly wed name was now Shiori Nakamura. With teasing Maki-chan a little,	s03a	0262
S003A	7	24	Maki: 「Onee-chan, is sort of a little busy........ She said she'd be late today too」	s03a	0263
S003A	7	25	Natsuko: 「Aahh, I see.......it must be hard being a teacher, huh」	s03a	0264
S003A	7	26	Maki: 「So, I'm substituting for Onee-chan and helping my brother-in-law」	s03a	0265
S003A	7	27	Natsuko: 「Fufuu, Teacher Shiori is also no match for Maki-chan, is she」	s03a	0266
S003A	7	28	Maki: 「Fufuu, you think so? Although, wouldn't my Onee-chan do the same for me........ Aah, if I don't get going soon」	s03a	0267
S003A	7	29	Natsuko: 「Aah, I'm sorry. I'm keeping you, aren't I. Well then, take care, huh」	s03a	0268
S003A	7	30	Maki: 「Yes, goodbye」	s03a	0269
S003A	7	31	With bowing her head politely once more, Maki-chan lightly walked away.	s03a	0270
S003A	7	32	Natsuko: 「……」	s03a	0271
S003A	7	33	For a short while, from seeing Maki-chan go off into the distance, I too left for home.	s03a	0272
S003A	7	34	Natsuko: 「I'm home」	s03a	0273
S003A	7	35	With opening the door and entering the house,	s03a	0274
S003A	7	36	Mamoru: 「Ah, pardon me」	s03a	0275
S003A	7	37	Haruhide: 「Pardon us, mam」	s03a	0276
S003A	7	38	With Dr. Aiko's son, Mamoru-kun, Mizuki's classmate, Haruhide Yukimi  had come to play.	s03a	0277
S003A	7	39	Natsuko: 「Welcome. You look like you're having fun, huh. What are you talking about I wonder?」	s03a	0278
S003A	7	40	I had overheard as I was entering the house, while recalling the three people's laughter, I asked them about it,	s03a	0279
S003A	8	1	Mamoru: 「Ah, yeah. Maa, this and that.....」	s03a	0280
S003A	8	2	Haruhide, with Mamoru, exchanged glances, hesitating and mumbling on their words.	s03a	0281
S003A	8	3	Natsuko: 「I wonder is it something you can't tell to an adult?」	s03a	0282
S003A	8	4	Mizuki: 「It had nothing to do with mother」	s03a	0283
S003A	8	5	Natsuko: 「Oh, I see.........but, even so, it doesn't matter,  does it」	s03a	0284
S003A	8	6	Mizuki: 「Are you guys going to go already? Hurry up and go」	s03a	0285
S003A	8	7	Natsuko: 「Oh, don't talk to them like that, Mizuki. Since both of them may have a soft drink now」	s03a	0286
S003A	8	8	Mamoru: 「Ah, mam. Since we really should be going soon...... H, Haruhide?」	s03a	0287
S003A	8	9	Haruhide: 「Y, yeah. Mam, your pardon」	s03a	0288
S003A	8	10	Urged on by Mizuki's words, the two hurriedly left the living room.	s03a	0289
S003A	8	11	Natsuko: 「Mou, Mizuki. Using that sort of tone.......」	s03a	0290
S003A	8	12	Mizuki: 「But, the fact is they had to really leave. Other than that, I'm starved」	s03a	0291
S003A	8	13	Natsuko: 「Yeah, yeah, since I'm making it now......... Look, go to your room and study until then」	s03a	0292
S003A	8	14	Mizuki: 「If it's study, I already finished with Mamoru」	s03a	0293
S003A	8	15	Mizuki stared at me seeming serious about what he said.	s03a	0294
S003A	8	16	Natsuko: 「W, what? If you're going to watch me like that, surely you can come make dinner」	s03a	0295
S003A	8	17	Why am I becoming aware of Mizuki. Because it doesn't mean he has interest in me. While calming my fast-beating heart, I advised Mizuki.	s03a	0296
S003A	8	18	Mizuki: 「I guess it's nothing. Since it's ok, don't worry about me, hurry up and make dinner」	s03a	0297
S003A	8	19	Natsuko: 「……Mou, it's because he's a weird child」	s03a	0298
S003A	8	20	From having a strange hunch, I warned him once again not to watch me, while taking with my body Mizuki's reluctant glance, I began making dinner.	s03a	0299
S003A	8	21	With finishing dinner, cleaning up, and returning to the living room, Mizuki, while laying down, watched television.	s03a	0300
S003A	8	22	Natsuko: 「Mizuki, have you washed and taken a bath?」	s03a	0301
S003A	8	23	Mizuki: 「Nn? I haven't washed. Mother'll wash me. While you're at it, run some hot water.  Then, I'll get in the bath.」	s03a	0302
S003A	8	24	Natsuko: 「You know, Mizuki. Turn to me for just a minute」	s03a	0303
S003A	8	25	Mizuki: 「What? But I'm trying to watch TV now」	s03a	0304
S003A	8	26	Natsuko: 「As for cleaning in the bath, surely Mizuki can do his share of the work? Why does your mother  have to wash you?」	s03a	0305
S003A	8	27	Mizuki: 「Because I'm tired today...... Besides, mother has always washed me, hasn't she」	s03a	0306
S003A	8	28	Natsuko: 「Ok, listen, Mizuki. You can't rely on your mother forever. Does that not mean that your mother has to care for Mizuki indefinitely?」	s03a	0307
S003A	8	29	I turned the words Dr. Aiko had said about a parent letting go of their children around in my head.	s03a	0308
S003A	8	30	Mizuki: 「What are you talking about?」	s03a	0309
S003A	8	31	Whether or not Mizuki was also feeling my determination and how I was different than normal, he returned a gaze with eyes that seemed a little uneasy.	s03a	0310
S003A	8	32	Natsuko: 「It means that now...since even Mizuki cannot be a child forever, it's not good if your not  able to do things for yourself」	s03a	0311
S003A	8	33	Mizuki: 「What isn't it ok since mother is here........or else, you're not saying things like mother isn't going to be here, are you?」	s03a	0312
S003A	8	34	Natsuko: 「Th, that is.......although the reason isn't that I'm not going to be here........」	s03a	0313
S003A	8	35	Mizuki: 「If so, surely there's no problem?」	s03a	0314
S003A	8	36	Mizuki wouldn't be able to be independent as he  understood it now. Here, even if I have to take an attitude so as to refuse him a little.....	s03a	0315
S003A	8	37	Natsuko: 「Although it's not that I won't be here, but, if mother gets married again, what then? I can't look after just Mizuki, can I?」	s03a	0316
S003A	8	38	Mizuki: 「……」	s03a	0317
S003A	8	39	Something came to mind at once with me speaking of a second marriage as Mizuki stiffened his face, flabbergasted.	s03a	0318
S003A	8	40	Natsuko: 「A, among the patients..... since there's a person that says he likes things  about your mother」	s03a	0319
S003A	9	1	As I spoke of things I did not really mean, I faltered inside my mind.	s03a	0320
S003A	9	2	Mizuki: 「Mother.......married again?」	s03a	0321
S003A	9	3	Mizuki asked the question with a trembling voice.	s03a	0322
S003A	9	4	Natsuko: 「A second marriage.......I think so」	s03a	0323
S003A	9	5	Mizuki: 「Thud!!」	s03a	0324
S003A	9	6	Together with a short, sharp voice,  Mizuki struck the table violently.	s03a	0324
S003A	9	7	Natsuko: 「Ah, Mi, Mizukii」	s03a	0325
S003A	9	8	With thinking about why he glared at me so strongly in silence, Mizuki broke off into run towards his room.	s03a	0326
S003A	9	9	Natsuko: 「Mizuki, wait, wait this instant! I'm still not finished talking」	s03a	0327
S003A	9	10	Although I called for him to halt, Mizuki did not stop and confined himself to his room on the second floor.	s03a	0328
S003A	9	11	Natsuko: 「……」	s03a	0329
S003A	9	12	I stood in the living room, overcome  with surprise.	s03a	0330
S003A	9	13	Would it have been better if I hadn't lied about  getting married again.....although, inside, the regret rose to my head, there was nothing I could do about it now.	s03a	0331
S003A	9	14	Since Mizuki will calm down, tomorrow, it seems I can speak about it more precisely again. If that's the case, I should expect Mizuki to understand too......	s03a	0332
S003A	9	15	Although I had seemed to tell myself not to, my heart and mind sunk into a deep depression, having nothing else to divert my worries.	s03a	0333
S003A	9	16	After all, it's no good worrying about what to do. I returned to my bedroom with feeling exhausted.	s03a	0334
S003A	9	17	Natsuko: 「Fuuuuu」	s03a	0335
S003A	9	18	I let out a big, spontaneous sigh.	s03a	0336
S003A	9	19	Natsuko: 「You......... Of course, it wasn't a good idea to lie, was it......」	s03a	0337
S003A	9	20	I talked to my husband's Buddhist mortuary tablet so as to seek his assistance. But, it gave me no reply.	s03a	0338
S003A	9	21	Natsuko: 「If you were here, I wouldn't have to worry like this by myself.......」	s03a	0339
S003A	9	22	Considering Mizuki's feelings, since I haven't married again, I wonder how it had gotten like this?	s03a	0340
S003A	9	23	Various thoughts in my exhausted head came to mind and vanished.	s03a	0341
S003A	9	24	Natsuko: 「Tomorrow.......I should be honest......」	s03a	0342
S003A	9	25	I expect he'll understand when we discuss it. Anyway, today I should get some rest. With raising my body sluggishly, I prepared for bed.	s03a	0343
