S016C	1	1	Kazuma: 「Teacher Yamasaki...with Izumi...with Miss Shinohara, what were you talking to her about?」	s16c	0000
S016C	1	2	While feeling uneasy,  I asked Suzuko Yamasaki a question.	s16c	0001
S016C	1	3	Suzuko: 「Fufuu...fufuu, hahahahahaa」	s16c	0002
S016C	1	4	Suzuko Yamasaki's laughter resounded suddenly within the room that had fallen silent. With feeling like she was scoffing at me in her voice, I grew irritated.	s16c	0003
S016C	1	5	Kazuma: 「What...is so funny?」	s16c	0004
S016C	1	6	Suzuko Yamasaki returned a stare, laughing at my low-pitched question.	s16c	0005
S016C	1	7	Suzuko: 「Fufufuu, forgive me... It was because that was a little  uncharacteristic of you」	s16c	0006
S016C	1	8	Kazuma: 「What...was?」	s16c	0007
S016C	1	9	Suzuko: 「The always composed president of the Gang Rape Club seeming to be interested in my talk with Miss Shinohara,  huh...fufuu, that impatient face of yours too...fufufuu」	s16c	0008
S016C	1	10	I began to feel increasingly unsettled at Suzuko's manner of floating composed laughs at me.	s16c	0009
S016C	1	11	Kazuma: （I guess I shouldn't take too much of this to heart...）	s16c	0010
S016C	1	12	I bit down and gritted my teeth spontaneously at my failure of exposing my one weakness that I had to guard against.	s16c	0011
S016C	1	13	Kazuma: 「Teacher Yamasaki...can you quit with the foolery」	s16c	0012
S016C	1	14	I couldn't allow Suzuko Yamasaki to discern my feelings for Izumi. While calming my feelings in order to mend the mistake I had made, I turned to Suzuko Yamaskai.	s16c	0013
S016C	1	15	Kazuma: 「Miss Shinohara and I have nothing...」	s16c	0014
S016C	1	16	Suzuko: 「Miss Shinohara, is it.  Don't you always call her Izumi? But even in front of me, why are you being evasive?」	s16c	0015
S016C	1	17	Kazuma: 「What...do you mean...Izumi and I are just childhood friends...」	s16c	0016
S016C	1	18	Suzuko: 「That so...fufuu, well then, for what reason are you being formal in front of me, I wonder? You seem to always call her Izumi, do you not?」	s16c	0017
S016C	1	19	Kazuma: 「That has nothing to do with Teacher Yamasaki...」	s16c	0018
S016C	1	20	Suzuko: 「Is that so, I wonder? Hey, Mr. President. Know what... I think...I've found your weakness, I've been observing you for a long time」	s16c	0019
S016C	1	21	A cold sweat broke out along my back at those words of Suzuko Yamasaki's.	s16c	0020
S016C	1	22	Suzuko: 「Fufuu, did you also not consider that I would do  things like observe you?」	s16c	0021
S016C	1	23	The moment I saw Suzuko Yamasaki float a composed laugh, I had realized that this woman had discerned my feelings for Izumi.	s16c	0022
S016C	1	24	Kazuma: 「……」	s16c	0023
S016C	1	25	Kajimura's vulgar face came to my mind, like I was having a flashback. It wasn't just Kajimura, but now Suzuko Yamasaki that knew about my feelings for Izumi...	s16c	0024
S016C	1	26	In any case, as for my childhood friends, how had they been perceived by Suzuko Yamasaki and Kajimura  from enrolling at this school...	s16c	0025
S016C	1	27	With not even I being aware of it, perhaps my eye contact with Izumi had differed from other people.	s16c	0026
S016C	1	28	Kazuma: （I was careless...from when I was noticed by Kajimura, if I had been more careful from that day on...）	s16c	0027
S016C	1	29	With Kajimura vanishing in my mind, I felt irritated at  myself and uneasy about resolving this problem.	s16c	0028
S016C	1	30	Suzuko: 「What's this, you seem to be awfully occupied with your thoughts, huh」	s16c	0029
S016C	1	31	Seeing me saying nothing else, Suzuko Yamasaki gave an unfeeling smile.	s16c	0030
S016C	1	32	Suzuko: 「Cooperate with me」	s16c	0031
S016C	1	33	With pointing a sharp look, like it pierced me, Suzuko Yamasaki muttered in a low voice.	s16c	0032
S016C	1	34	Kazuma: 「Again...what were you talking about...」	s16c	0033
S016C	1	35	Suzuko: 「Have the circumstances changed since then?」	s16c	0034
S016C	1	36	Kazuma: 「...nothing has changed」	s16c	0035
S016C	1	37	Suzuko Yamasaki wasn't definitively aware of Izumi. With saying that and turning around to leave,	s16c	0036
S016C	1	38	Suzuko: 「Think hard about it, huh. Because you rose to the top  to be able to protect the girl you have feelings for」	s16c	0037
S016C	1	39	With that single utterance, my body froze.	s16c	0038
S016C	1	40	Kazuma: （I guess she is aware...）	s16c	0039
S016C	2	1	With my faint hopes being crushed, I stared feebly at Suzuko Yamasaki.	s16c	0040
S016C	2	2	Suzuko: 「You want to protect...Miss Shinohara, don't you?」	s16c	0041
S016C	2	3	Staring at me, Suzuko Yamasaki asked me a question.	s16c	0042
S016C	2	4	Kazuma: 「……」	s16c	0043
S016C	2	5	Suzuko: 「When you became the president of the Gang Rape Club to reliably protect Miss Shinohara...you eliminated all possibilities of Miss Shinohara becoming maiden, huh」	s16c	0044
S016C	2	6	Staring at me in silence, Suzuko Yamasaki spun elegant words.	s16c	0045
S016C	2	7	Suzuko: 「However, you doing things like that selfishly, what do you think would happen if the Gang Rape Club  people found that out, I wonder?」	s16c	0046
S016C	2	8	With floating a derisive smile, Suzuko Yamasaki cut off her words temporarily.	s16c	0047
S016C	2	9	Suzuko: 「They would hold resentment towards you in particular... Fufuu, like when teacher Kajimura knew, huh」	s16c	0048
S016C	2	10	Kazuma: 「Kuu...」	s16c	0049
S016C	2	11	After the matter with Maki and Teacher Shiori, I had not seen Toshinobu's face in the Gang Rape Club. However, supposing...	s16c	0050
S016C	2	12	If Toshinobu found out about my feelings towards Izumi...	s16c	0051
S016C	2	13	A shiver ran up my spine as I thought about Toshinobu's vile face raping the elected maiden.	s16c	0052
S016C	2	14	Kazuma: 「Teacher's selfishness...for the sake of your own satisfaction...is going to drag Izumi into this?」	s16c	0053
S016C	2	15	Suzuko: 「Fufuu, who's selfish, I wonder? How about all the people you've trampled over so far as a result of their lusts?」	s16c	0054
S016C	2	16	Flames of anger burst into Suzuko Yamasaki's eyes.	s16c	0055
S016C	2	17	Kazuma: 「……」	s16c	0056
S016C	2	18	That sharp look collided with me as I felt explosive tension shrouding me and Suzuko Yamasaki.	s16c	0057
S016C	2	19	Suzuko: 「I will say it only once more...cooperate with me. If you do, nothing bad will happen」	s16c	0058
S016C	2	20	Kazuma: 「...just tell me what you have in mind... let me hear it」	s16c	0059
S016C	2	21	Putting emphasis in my interest in what Suzuko Yamasaki was considering, I asked her a question about it.	s16c	0060
S016C	2	22	Suzuko: 「There are people that work at a TV station that are friends of mine from my student days...」	s16c	0061
S016C	2	23	For the sake of breaking the ceremony, Suzuko Yamasaki was going to collect data on the ceremony by persuading those friends to cover it.	s16c	0062
S016C	2	24	And then, with putting pressure on stopping the ceremony on the important people of this town with that evidence...	s16c	0063
S016C	2	25	And if need be, putting pressure on the politicians as well, Suzuko Yamasaki revealed her plan to me.	s16c	0064
S016C	2	26	Suzuko: 「How about it? Even you, truly would like to escape the ceremony」	s16c	0065
S016C	2	27	Suzuko Yamasaki, having finished talking, gazed at me with a face of strong determination.	s16c	0066
S016C	2	28	Suzuko: 「As for the matter of wanting your cooperation, I want  to arrange the important people of this town to be  participating in the Gang Rape Club when it's covered」	s16c	0067
S016C	2	29	Kazuma: 「……」	s16c	0068
S016C	2	30	Suzuko: 「The people in power will fear it being taken away.  So, if you guard them against knowing about it,  the ceremony itself should fall at their own hands.」	s16c	0069
S016C	2	31	I realized the extent of Suzuko Yamasaki's  determination. If she had arranged all of this,  perhaps the plan would work.	s16c	0070
S016C	2	32	It seemed to be a sure thing that the people in power would seek to protect themselves from being exposed, thus destroying the ceremony.	s16c	0071
S016C	2	33	If that's the case, I guess it would be fine to cooperate with Suzuko Yamasaki?	s16c	0072
S016C	2	34	If I cooperated and the Gang Rape Club fell, I guess I had no worry about Izumi becoming maiden.	s16c	0073
S016C	2	35	However...	s16c	0074
S016C	2	36	Suzuko: 「What's so funny!?」	s16c	0075
S016C	2	37	Suzuko Yamasaki scowled sharply at a thin smile coming upon my face.	s16c	0076
S016C	2	38	Kazuma: 「No...nothing...」	s16c	0077
S016C	2	39	Suzuko: 「……」	s16c	0078
S016C	2	40	Suzuko was glaring at me like she was on high alert, but	s16c	0079
S016C	3	1	Kazuma: 「...understood then. I'll try to cooperate with the teacher. Because I do want to protect Izumi」	s16c	0080
S016C	3	2	Just as she heard my reply, a triumphant expression came upon her face.	s16c	0081
S016C	3	3	Now, with being threatened by Izumi's matter, I had no other choice but to play by Suzuko Yamasaki's rules.	s16c	0082
S016C	3	4	I had to protect Izumi by any means possible.	s16c	0083
S016C	3	5	No matter what it took...	s16c	0084
S016C	3	6	Suzuko: 「Ok. With this, that abominable ceremony will come to end. After this, this town will start anew」	s16c	0085
S016C	3	7	Suzuko Yamasaki, having reached an agreement with me, raised a high pitched voice like she was a little excited by the prospect.	s16c	0086
S016C	3	8	Kazuma: 「……」	s16c	0087
S016C	3	9	Suzuko: 「From now, we will be on the same team. Welcome aboard」	s16c	0088
S016C	3	10	Suzuko Yamasaki held out her hand to me as she said that.	s16c	0089
S016C	3	11	Kazuma: 「Yes...」	s16c	0090
S016C	3	12	With returning a handshake, I gave a light nod with a blank expression.	s16c	0091
S016C	3	13	From the day that I exchanged that handshake with Suzuko Yamasaki, several days had passed.	s16c	0092
S016C	3	14	From that day, my mind had awoken from the pleasure of being with Maki and Teacher Shiori. I had carried  on as usual as president of the Gang Rape Club.	s16c	0093
S016C	3	15	And then, with the day arriving when a new maiden was to be elected...	s16c	0094
S016C	3	16	For the purpose of raping the new maiden, the Gang Rape Club members had assembled, one after another.	s16c	0095
S016C	3	17	After the members had vanished into the former school building...	s16c	0096
S016C	3	18	Kazuma: 「Were you able to validate them?」	s16c	0097
S016C	3	19	I pointed my eyes to Suzuko Yamasaki emerging from a thicket.	s16c	0098
S016C	3	20	Suzuko: 「Yes, I have recorded everyone that has come on a list」	s16c	0099
S016C	3	21	Suzuko, having confirmed the participants from hiding in a thicket, nodded with a tense expression.	s16c	0100
S016C	3	22	Suzuko: 「But, it's surprising... You, listening so obediently to my instructions...」	s16c	0101
S016C	3	23	Kazuma: 「What can I say...Teacher Yamasaki induced me to obey her」	s16c	0102
S016C	3	24	While curling my lips and grinning at Suzuko,	s16c	0103
S016C	3	25	Suzuko: 「It's to that extent that you feel Miss Shinohara is important to you, isn't it...Fufuu, that child too will be happy. It seems she loves you very much」	s16c	0104
S016C	3	26	Suzuko too, finally smiled, like releasing her tension.	s16c	0105
S016C	3	27	Kazuma: 「There's no one else in the world...like Izumi」	s16c	0106
S016C	3	28	Suzuko: 「That every day worrying about someone so dear to you being dirtied will be over. And it's not just you, it concerns everyone else in this town, doesn't it」	s16c	0107
S016C	3	29	Kazuma: 「……」	s16c	0108
S016C	3	30	Suzuko: 「Ok, let's get going. It's almost time」	s16c	0109
S016C	3	31	Suzuko took a look at her watch as she said that and turned her heel and began walking. I too followed after her in silence.	s16c	0110
S016C	3	32	Suzuko: 「Very soon, very soon it will be over...」	s16c	0111
S016C	3	33	Destroying the detestable customs by her own hand. Whether or not she was getting excited about that, Suzuko muttered in an unusually high-pitched voice.	s16c	0112
S016C	3	34	Kazuma: 「……」	s16c	0113
S016C	3	35	About this time was when the town's most important people were expected to participate in the ceremony.	s16c	0114
S016C	3	36	As a result of catching the important people at the scene of the crime, it seems would destroy the Gang Rape Club in accordance with Suzuko's aim.	s16c	0115
S016C	3	37	But, I guess Suzuko didn't feel anything strange about this?	s16c	0116
S016C	3	38	There hadn't been a single person who had done something the likes of which she is doing now...	s16c	0117
S016C	3	39	Suzuko: 「They came!」	s16c	0118
S016C	3	40	With Suzuko's voice locating an approaching vehicle, I recovered my consciousness that had sunk into thought.	s16c	0119
S016C	4	1	My eyes fell upon a black van.	s16c	0120
S016C	4	2	Suzuko broke off into a run towards that van.	s16c	0121
S016C	4	3	Kazuma: 「……」	s16c	0122
S016C	4	4	While seeing her retreating figure, I too began stepping ahead slowly.	s16c	0123
S016C	4	5	Suzuko: 「I've been waiting. It's beginning soon.  Without delay...」	s16c	0124
S016C	4	6	With Suzuko, having rushed up to the van, pausing her words suddenly,	s16c	0125
S016C	4	7	Suzuko: 「...u!? This isn't...!? This vehicle is...」	s16c	0126
S016C	4	8	Gacha. As the door unlocked, it slid open.	s16c	0127
S016C	4	9	It seems she had sensed the danger on instinct. Suzuko took off running away from the van.	s16c	0128
S016C	4	10	However...	s16c	0129
S016C	4	11	Suzuko: 「Aaah!?」	s16c	0130
S016C	4	12	Dark chains spewed out from inside the van, catching onto and binding Suzuko's body.	s16c	0131
S016C	4	13	Surprise came onto Suzuko's face as she turned towards me.	s16c	0132
S016C	4	14	Kazuma: 「Teacher Yamasaki...you were not the only one who had tried to destroy the ceremony」	s16c	0133
S016C	4	15	I addressed Suzuko as she was slowly dragged inside the van like in slow motion.	s16c	0134
S016C	4	16	So, in the past too, with these ceremonies being destroyed, there had also been people who took  drastic actions similar to Suzuko.	s16c	0135
S016C	4	17	If you had gone back to those days and counted the amount, it perhaps would be no less than a thousand people.	s16c	0136
S016C	4	18	However, there was still one such ceremony left in existence that continued to feast on the maidens.	s16c	0137
S016C	4	19	Meaning...for the sake of safeguarding this ceremony, a dark organization had formed.	s16c	0138
S016C	4	20	Even with me being the president of the Gang Rape Club, that dark organization was an unknown element to the full picture.	s16c	0139
S016C	4	21	There were people who guarded against the people who were trying to destroy this ceremony.	s16c	0140
S016C	4	22	When something happens that, as president of the Gang  Rape Club, I cannot manage, with just speaking to the  Shinto Shrine, that organization takes care of it for me.	s16c	0141
S016C	4	23	Kazuma: （As had happened with Kajimura...and, now...）	s16c	0142
S016C	4	24	Suzuko: 「Noo, noooooo!!」	s16c	0143
S016C	4	25	Suzuko's expression changed from surprise to horror. The moment I heard her scream from her opened mouth,	s16c	0144
S016C	4	26	Dark chains wrapped around that mouth.	s16c	0145
S016C	4	27	Kazuma: 「...Teacher Yamasaki, you underestimated the profundity of the darkness of this town」	s16c	0146
S016C	4	28	With muttering like I was making a speech to Suzuko who was writhing about,	s16c	0147
S016C	4	29	Suzuko: 「……」	s16c	0148
S016C	4	30	The color of defeat lodged in Suzuko's eyes, and then spread throughout her face.	s16c	0149
S016C	4	31	Kazuma: 「……」	s16c	0150
S016C	4	32	Just a few days ago, Suzuko had stared at me brimming with self-confidence, but now, she had a frail, feminine expression, like the prey moving in for the kill.	s16c	0151
S016C	4	33	Kazuma: 「If you hadn't gotten involved...if you hadn't stuck your nose where it didn't belong, it wouldn't have to come to this, Teacher Yamasaki」	s16c	0152
S016C	4	34	Perhaps my voice already wasn't reaching Suzuko.	s16c	0153
S016C	4	35	Kazuma: 「……」	s16c	0154
S016C	4	36	Like being caught by a carnivorous animal, Suzuko was dragged inside the van.	s16c	0155
S016C	4	37	Suzuko: 「Uu, uu, uuuuuuu!!」	s16c	0156
S016C	4	38	Resisting to no purpose until the end, with Suzuko's body being swallowed up by the van,	s16c	0157
S016C	4	39	The van door shut.	s16c	0158
S016C	4	40	Kazuma: 「Good-bye, Teacher Yamasaki...」	s16c	0159
S016C	5	1	After this, I too didn't know what would happen to Suzuko.	s16c	0160
S016C	5	2	Like on queue with my words of farewell, the engine turned on and the van sped away.	s16c	0161
S016C	5	3	Kazuma: 「……」	s16c	0162
S016C	5	4	And then, passing by one another, a different van pulled up at the school.	s16c	0163
S016C	5	5	With the logo "Akitsushima TV" written on the side of the van entering my field of vision,	s16c	0164
S016C	5	6	Kazuma: 「Fuu...」	s16c	0165
S016C	5	7	A scornful laugh came upon my curled lips.	s16c	0166
S016C	5	8	Kazuma: 「I will absolutely protect...Izumi...」	s16c	0167
S016C	5	9	With that determination in my heart, I strode over to the men getting out of the van.	s16c	0168
S016C	5	10	The mist covering the town had lifted this morning as gentle morning sunshine illuminated this old town.	s16c	0169
S016C	5	11	Inside each person beginning a new day again...	s16c	0170
S016C	5	12	Inside a gloomy room, there were only  small noises resounding.	s16c	0171
S016C	5	13	Suzuko: 「Jyuu, jyuu, jyurururuu」	s16c	0172
