PV01_1901_A	1	1	Misleet: 「Ahguuu!!」	s30a	0040
PV01_1901_A	1	2	Misleet moaned as she was pushed down onto the floating seat used for interrogations.	s30a	0041
PV01_1901_A	1	3	She tried to escape, but her bound hands weren't giving her that option.	s30a	0042
PV01_1901_A	1	4	Misleet: 「U...kuu, y...ou」	s30a	0043
PV01_1901_A	1	5	I stripped Misleet's clothes and pushed my dick in between her exposed breasts.	s30a	0044
PV01_1901_A	1	6	Misleet: 「Kufuu...nn. Hot...」	s30a	0045
PV01_1901_A	1	7	Misleet's body jumped and bucked the moment the slippery sensation from precum and sweat grazed her breasts.	s30a	0046
PV01_1901_A	1	8	Misleet: 「Fuah...n, nnn. I can feel it beating... between my breasts. Huge cock, pounding... nn, nn」	s30a	0047
PV01_1901_A	1	9	It was as if she was waving her waist like  she was getting pleasure from just the pulsations.	s30a	0048
PV01_1901_A	1	10	Yuu: 「Kuku...what? Are you getting off already?」	s30a	0049
PV01_1901_A	1	11	Misleet: 「Th...that's not it. This is, hii...this is, the fault of this chest...these tits...ah, ahhh, my body is squirming...on its own...uuu」	s30a	0050
PV01_1901_A	1	12	If that were true, then I guess she would want to escape from it by contorting her body.	s30a	0051
PV01_1901_A	1	13	But Misleet's body now had first-rate pleasure flowing into it from merely writhing thanks to the increased sensory receptors all over her body.	s30a	0052
PV01_1901_A	1	14	Misleet: 「No...ahhh. Stop...it. Stop these good feelings, feeling like this...is crazy. I'm, going crazy. Fuah...ah」	s30a	0053
PV01_1901_A	1	15	Drool dangled out from the corners of her mouth as Misleet trembled at the pleasure continuing to  pump into her no matter how much she refused it.	s30a	0054
PV01_1901_A	1	16	Yuu: 「Ku...kukuu. You really turned that into a fine face, haven't you?」	s30a	0055
PV01_1901_A	1	17	Misleet: 「Kufuunn!」	s30a	0056
PV01_1901_A	1	18	Yuu: 「How is it? The feeling of a dick thrusting between and rubbing your too sensitive, huge tits it feels like it's thrusting into your pussy, right?」	s30a	0057
PV01_1901_A	1	19	Pushing my waist forward lightly as I said that, her breasts floating there already plastered with sweat clung to me.	s30a	0058
PV01_1901_A	1	20	Misleet: 「Hii...ahhh. Kuu...nn! Driving into me. Your huge dick driving forcefully into me... Ah, ahhh」	s30a	0059
PV01_1901_A	1	21	My own body temperature sunk down into the cleavage of her breasts that had become as sensitive as a normal clitoris all over.	s30a	0060
PV01_1901_A	1	22	Though afraid, Misleet was unable to look  away from the source of the fever twitching at the tip of her nose.	s30a	0061
PV01_1901_A	1	23	Misleet: 「I'm...having my breasts raped now...u, kuu, getting off...being raped...ah, ukuu」	s30a	0062
PV01_1901_A	1	24	A feeling of hopelessness burst out the moment she spoke that.	s30a	0063
PV01_1901_A	1	25	The pleasure spread like a disease through her  entire body before she could even imagine just how messed up she would soon be thanks to that.	s30a	0064
PV01_1901_A	1	26	Misleet: 「Stop...it, come on. This is absurd...」	s30a	0066
PV01_1901_A	1	27	Yuu: 「Yeah, it's going to be the end of you very soon...but, now!」	s30a	0067
PV01_1901_A	1	28	Misleet: 「Hii...ii!」	s30a	0068
PV01_1901_A	1	29	I began moving my waist slowly while a broad grin formed on my mouth.	s30a	0069
PV01_1901_A	1	30	Misleet: 「Kuhi...nn! Fuah...ahhh! Scrubbing,  scrubbing your cock into my pussy tits, don't rub against them...ahhh!」	s30a	0071
PV01_1901_A	1	31	Perspiration that seemed to coil around my dick seeped out endlessly as her breasts frothed  with pleasure from merely rubbing against them.	s30a	0072
PV01_1901_A	1	32	Yuu: 「Kah, kakahh! It really is slippery and tender like an ordinary pussy, isn't it」	s30a	0073
PV01_1901_A	1	33	Misleet: 「Hah...uukuu! Don't say things like that...」	s30a	0074
PV01_1901_A	1	34	Yuu: 「Titfucking isn't suppose to be this sensitive? I did give you a special drug, but this much?  You sure you didn't have the makings? Of a slave」	s30a	0075
PV01_1901_A	1	35	Misleet: 「Hikii...wh, who...who would be that...」	s30a	0076
PV01_1901_A	1	36	Yuu: 「Well, what is it then! This crazy sensitivity you have!」	s30a	0077
PV01_1901_A	1	37	Misleet: 「Higuuuu!!」	s30a	0078
PV01_1901_A	1	38	I pushed more and more into Misleet's breasts trying to resist me any way she could even if it was only through speech and conduct.	s30a	0079
PV01_1901_A	1	39	Misleet: 「Kuhii! Ahiiah! Ahhh! Don't push into them! So fully, don't push your fingers into them so fully! If you do that!」	s30a	0080
PV01_1901_A	1	40	Yuu: 「If I do that? If I do that, then what!? Tell me! Look! Look, look!, Look!!!」	s30a	0081
PV01_1901_A	2	1	I didn't stop driving the stimulus into her as I shouted out to her like that.	s30a	0082
PV01_1901_A	2	2	Misleet: 「Hiii! Eating into me! Hard fingers like dicks, finger dicks eating into me so much!」	s30a	0083
PV01_1901_A	2	3	Her breasts possessed a bounciness and suppleness that couldn't be compared to previously.	s30a	0084
PV01_1901_A	2	4	Misleet that had been changed into one big erogenous zone was going mad satisfying herself every time my fingers drove into her breasts.	s30a	0085
PV01_1901_A	2	5	Misleet: 「Fukiii! Cocks...so many cocks driving into me. All of my tits are being raped by cocks! I, I said this is absurd!」	s30a	0086
PV01_1901_A	2	6	Yuu: 「It's good like this, right? Having those retarded-looking swollen pussy tits raped like crazy by fingers, look!!!!」	s30a	0087
PV01_1901_A	2	7	Misleet: 「Kihii! Hiahh! Hiahhhh! Pussy tits, no! Don't rape my tits! Fuahh! Don't rape my  clit-sensitive tits!!」	s30a	0088
PV01_1901_A	2	8	But that joy didn't stop no matter how much she tried to refuse it verbally.	s30a	0089
PV01_1901_A	2	9	It was as if those gigantic breasts of hers were calling out for even more billowing pleasure every time my embedded fingers drove forward.	s30a	0090
PV01_1901_A	2	10	Misleet: 「Cumming! Cumming! While my pussy tits are raped by finger dicks and a cock, cum, cum, cum, cumming!!」	s30a	0091
PV01_1901_A	2	11	At last Misleet met a climax while making  her head tremble to the pleasure ceaselessly streaming into it.	s30a	0092
PV01_1901_A	2	12	But that wasn't the end of it.	s30a	0093
PV01_1901_A	2	13	There was no reason for it to be over now.	s30a	0094
PV01_1901_A	2	14	Misleet: 「I give up already! I came so much! Raping my  huge tits...I came so much with my huge pussy tits!  I'm cumming like crazy, so enough, enough, enough!!!」	s30a	0095
PV01_1901_A	2	15	Yuu: 「What, you think it's just you enjoying and satisfying themselves? Not yet! I'm still not done yet!!!」	s30a	0096
PV01_1901_A	2	16	Misleet: 「Hiahhhhhhhhhhhh!!!」	s30a	0097
PV01_1901_A	2	17	A deliciously muddy scream rose up the moment I pinched and lifted up her nipples that were as sensitive as a clit just after cumming.	s30a	0098
PV01_1901_A	2	18	Misleet: 「Those...those are my, ahhhh!!」	s30a	0099
PV01_1901_A	2	19	Yuu: 「How is it? Your already sensitive nipples. How is it when I pinch them there?」	s30a	0100
PV01_1901_A	2	20	I nuzzled her nipples against the palms of my pinched fingers while saying that.	s30a	0101
PV01_1901_A	2	21	Misleet: 「Fuahhh! Ahhhnn! Playing with my nipples... Stiffened nipples cumming to being pinched... fuahh! Don't make my erect nipples cum!!」	s30a	0102
PV01_1901_A	2	22	Misleet anguished away like she had gone mad with me just nuzzling her nipples lightly against my fingers.	s30a	0103
PV01_1901_A	2	23	Misleet: 「Feeling! Feeling in my nipples! Feeling the  ruggedness of your fingerprints, feeling cocks  on your fingerprints, cumming! I'm cumming again!!」	s30a	0104
PV01_1901_A	2	24	Yuu: 「That's good, cum as hard as you can! I'm going to make sure you keep cumming to that sensation after the fingerprints are left!」	s30a	0105
PV01_1901_A	2	25	Misleet: 「Fuuuu! Eating into them! Fingerprints are eating into my nipples! Eating into them, come on, it won't go back!!」	s30a	0106
PV01_1901_A	2	26	It was as if her breasts had a tremendous sensitivity like they had changed into two enormous clits.	s30a	0107
PV01_1901_A	2	27	Misleet: 「Hii...uuu...hiii! Hi, u, uu!」	s30a	0108
PV01_1901_A	2	28	Despite nothing really being done to her  with the weak stimulus sent to her nipples, her body flailed around like a fish out of water.	s30a	0109
PV01_1901_A	2	29	Misleet: 「Hiah...ah, tingling...u, from just... pinching my nipples, tingling...u...kuu...」	s30a	0110
PV01_1901_A	2	30	A tantrum of words ran out from her thoughts like they were immersed in washed-out feelings.	s30a	0111
PV01_1901_A	2	31	But the pleasure that was oozing out wasn't hiding them.	s30a	0112
PV01_1901_A	2	32	Yuu: 「You think the extremely good feelings are over huh? Huh, hey?」	s30a	0113
PV01_1901_A	2	33	Misleet: 「Hi, u...uu...kuhii...ii」	s30a	0114
PV01_1901_A	2	34	Yuu: 「But, are they? Hey!?」	s30a	0115
PV01_1901_A	2	35	I shook those breasts of hers to the left and right, still pinching her nipples while saying that.	s30a	0116
PV01_1901_A	2	36	Misleet: 「Hiahhhhhhh!」	s30a	0117
PV01_1901_A	2	37	A shriek of delight rose up just then.	s30a	0118
PV01_1901_A	2	38	Misleet: 「Breasts, breasts, shaking to the left and right, if you shake them, ah, ahhh, ahhhhh!!」	s30a	0119
PV01_1901_A	2	39	Misleet's body began waving to the left and right with the shaking tweaking her pinched nipples.	s30a	0120
PV01_1901_A	2	40	Misleet: 「Fuhiahh! Shaking...Shaking! Shaking my breasts around, ah, ahhh!!」	s30a	0121
PV01_1901_A	3	1	It was as if her extra-large breasts possessed enough mass of that of a separate individual.	s30a	0122
PV01_1901_A	3	2	Pleasure swarmed out from the bases of her breasts and nipples every time they shook.	s30a	0123
PV01_1901_A	3	3	Misleet: 「Fukuuu! I, hii, hiii! They'll tear if you do it that rough! My tits are tearing!」	s30a	0124
PV01_1901_A	3	4	Yuu: 「Yeah, maybe that's a good thing too! You hate it,  don't you!? Even just seeing these huge tits,  it'd be better without these crazy breasts, right?」	s30a	0125
PV01_1901_A	3	5	Misleet: 「Yes, but! Yes, but don't! Don't tear off my tits! Fuah, ahhh!!」	s30a	0126
PV01_1901_A	3	6	Her waist began bucking furiously with not only moving them to the left and right, but moving them up and down this time.	s30a	0127
PV01_1901_A	3	7	Misleet: 「Don't! My breasts, my huge, sensitive breasts, if you hold them, don't! Fuahhh! Don'tttttttttttttt!!」	s30a	0128
PV01_1901_A	3	8	Yuu: 「Ha, hahahah! Terrific! That Misleet "sama" going nuts satisfying herself having her breasts played with!」	s30a	0129
PV01_1901_A	3	9	Misleet: 「Ihiiyah! Ipiyahh! Saying things like that, don't, don't, don'ttttt!!!」	s30a	0130
PV01_1901_A	3	10	Misleet at this point was already gasping in a sort of cry, sensing pleasure even from my voice vibrating against her earlobes.	s30a	0131
PV01_1901_A	3	11	Yuu: 「Ku, kuu. It looks like the end of you will be superb! Well, shall I slowly indulge myself then!」	s30a	0132
PV01_1901_A	3	12	Misleet: 「Hi, pii!? What! What are you going to do! What else are you planning to do to me!!!?」	s30a	0133
PV01_1901_A	3	13	Yuu: 「Didn't I tell you, I said I'm going to savor in that body of yours before it breaks」	s30a	0134
PV01_1901_A	3	14	I began shaking her breasts again while smirking  at Misleet making her voice tremble at the  expectation of no less than that and dread.	s30a	0135
PV01_1901_A	3	15	Misleet: 「Hi...ku, th, this...is, ahhh!!!」	s30a	0136
PV01_1901_A	3	16	Not only was it to the left and right, but every which way.	s30a	0137
PV01_1901_A	3	17	Her waist began bucking at the same time as I  shook her breasts so that they slapped into  my hard dick pulsing from the bouncy sensations.	s30a	0138
PV01_1901_A	3	18	Misleet: 「Hiahh! Uu! Rubbing! Cock is rubbing and  scraping, at the base of my tits...ahhh!」	s30a	0139
PV01_1901_A	3	19	Which meant that the stimulus was obviously different than before.	s30a	0140
PV01_1901_A	3	20	Yuu: 「What would become of you...if I did it more and more, I wonder?」	s30a	0141
PV01_1901_A	3	21	Adding to that, I put strength into digging my fingernails into Misleet's nipples I was currently pinching.	s30a	0142
PV01_1901_A	3	22	Misleet: 「Fuuuu! My nipples too!? Doing it to my nipples too!!? Ukuu! Uhii! Ahahhhh! Plunging hard into my nipples as well!?」	s30a	0143
PV01_1901_A	3	23	Yuu: 「Yeah, I'm making you feel with every ounce of those massive breasts. Aren't you happy?」	s30a	0144
PV01_1901_A	3	24	Misleet: 「That...I don't, know! I don't know...but, hiuuu!!」	s30a	0145
PV01_1901_A	3	25	She tried to comprehend it, but she didn't care about it thanks to the pleasure shaving away at her body.	s30a	0146
PV01_1901_A	3	26	Misleet: 「Fuahhh! Every inch of my breasts are being raped! Slapping into my breasts!! Thrusting  cock, I...I'm, feeling like crazy!!!」	s30a	0147
PV01_1901_A	3	27	Speaking about that miserable figure of hers,  Misleet unconsciously and greedily indulged in still more of the pleasure.	s30a	0148
PV01_1901_A	3	28	Misleet: 「Kufuuu! Hiahh! Ahyuu! Penis...your penis  is rubbing, melting! The heat of your penis is melting into my huge breasts!」	s30a	0149
PV01_1901_A	3	29	It was clear that Misleet's body temperature was steadily rising every time she raised a lovely voice to the pleasure scorching her body.	s30a	0150
PV01_1901_A	3	30	And at the same time precum began rising up and overflowing from my dick from the sensation of that fever and sweat clinging to it.	s30a	0151
PV01_1901_A	3	31	Misleet: 「Kuhyunn!」	s30a	0152
PV01_1901_A	3	32	The brimmed over precum made noises as it brushed the tip of Misleet's nose.	s30a	0153
PV01_1901_A	3	33	Misleet: 「It's here...precum, precum, gushing juices are here... Fuah, that greasy man odor broth, flooding out into the cleavage of my breasts」	s30a	0154
PV01_1901_A	3	34	That voice took on an even sweeter enchantment the moment she lightly sniffed her nose and  smelled that bad smell.	s30a	0155
PV01_1901_A	3	35	Misleet: 「My nose, I'm feeling even with my nose. The odor of man juice, even the raw smell of a man is tugging at me」	s30a	0156
PV01_1901_A	3	36	Making her body quiver at that pleasure, she sprang her body up more and more trying to  acquire still more pleasure by rubbing my dick.	s30a	0157
PV01_1901_A	3	37	Misleet: 「Fuahhhh! Cock, cock, cock! Every inch of my  breasts...cock as far as my nose! I'm cumming  being smeared by cock...cumming! Cumming again!」	s30a	0158
PV01_1901_A	3	38	Yuu: 「Is that right... In that case, I'm going to hit you with even more of the finest quality of pleasure」	s30a	0159
PV01_1901_A	3	39	Misleet: 「U, kii!!」	s30a	0160
PV01_1901_A	3	40	I twisted and pinched Misleet's nipples raising  a lovely voice of pleasure that sounded like  she was going mad to the orgasm attacking her.	s30a	0161
PV01_1901_A	4	1	Misleet: 「Hikyuuuu! Overflow if you pinch them like that! My milk is going to spurt out!!!」	s30a	0162
PV01_1901_A	4	2	Yuu: 「Yeah, that's the idea. Try to make it shoot out like an ejaculation. Let me see you going mad cumming to a breast milk orgasm with my cock!」	s30a	0163
PV01_1901_A	4	3	I pulled on her twisted nipples more and more for the sake of spurring on that sensation of milk welling up in her breasts.	s30a	0164
PV01_1901_A	4	4	Misleet: 「Cominggg! My milk is coming out! My milk is going to spew out, ah, ahhhh!」	s30a	0165
PV01_1901_A	4	5	Yuu: 「That's it. Shoot it out! Hurry up and shoot it out!  Shoot it out like crazy!」	s30a	0166
PV01_1901_A	4	6	Misleet: 「Coming, coming, coming, coming! Breast milk coming out, breast milk orgasm, violent spewing  orgasm like a cock, spurting while cumminggg!!!」	s30a	0167
PV01_1901_A	4	7	Misleet: 「Hikyuuuuunnnnnnnnnnn!!」	s30a	0168
PV01_1901_A	4	8	In the next moment Misleet met a climax while breast milk shot out from her strongly pinched nipples that you could actually hear it.	s30a	0169
PV01_1901_A	4	9	Misleet: 「Coming out! Coming out! So much coming out!」	s30a	0170
PV01_1901_A	4	10	She called out in joy while leaping her body about together with the large amount of semen that had fired out at the same time.	s30a	0171
PV01_1901_A	4	11	Misleet: 「My milk is coming out! Shooting out with the cock milk! My milk is coming out like crazy, My head is going pure white!!!!」	s30a	0172
PV01_1901_A	4	12	Misleet: 「Fuah...fuah, fuahhhh! Pure white... Pure white...hii...fuah...I'm going pure white...to the semen and milk...」	s30a	0173
PV01_1901_A	4	13	Misleet made her gigantic breasts tremble like the tremors from my ejaculating cock were being handed down to her.	s30a	0174
PV01_1901_A	4	14	Breast milk continued to still endlessly  flow out like a water fountain from the tips of those breasts.	s30a	0175
PV01_1901_A	4	15	………………。	s30a	0176
PV01_1901_A	4	16	…………。	s30a	0177
PV01_1901_A	4	17	……。	s30a	0178
PV01_1901_A	4	18	Yuu: 「………」	s30a	0179
PV01_1901_A	4	19	Misleet: 「Hah, hah...ah...fuah...ah」	s30a	0180
PV01_1901_A	4	20	After a few minutes, I put on my space investigation clothes and gazed at my watch Misleet not being able to get up nearby.	s30a	0181
PV01_1901_A	4	21	There was still some semen and breast milk clinging to Misleet tumbled out on the floor, but I put her clothes on for the time being.	s30a	0182
PV01_1901_A	4	22	Yuu: 「It won't be long...」	s30a	0183
PV01_1901_A	4	23	And then the doorbell of the detention cell rang it seemed right after I had muttered that.	s30a	0184
PV01_1901_A	4	24	Yuu: 「...it's unlocked now, please come in」	s30a	0185
PV01_1901_A	4	25	The door opened at my response and several men in work clothes hurriedly entered the detention cell.	s30a	0186
PV01_1901_A	4	26	Yuu: 「Ahh, please make sure it's locked, huh. Just to be safe」	s30a	0187
PV01_1901_A	4	27	Staff Member: 「A, assistant...what in the world is this?」	s30a	0188
PV01_1901_A	4	28	Having assured that it was locked, one of the men that had entered the room grimaced slightly.	s30a	0189
PV01_1901_A	4	29	The smell of semen drifted about inside of the room.	s30a	0190
PV01_1901_A	4	30	But even that strong smell was painted out by a sweet, resin-like scent of breast milk.	s30a	0191
PV01_1901_A	4	31	And then, I guess it was natural that his expression became stiff when he saw Misleet fallen prostrate on the floor above all else.	s30a	0192
PV01_1901_A	4	32	Yuu: 「I gave her a little company before you all got  here. Her breast milk came out, but it's not toxic. Well, for most earthlings, but...here」	s30a	0193
PV01_1901_A	4	33	I handed out several pills while saying that.	s30a	0194
PV01_1901_A	4	34	Yuu: 「It's medicine to protect against infectious diseases, just to be safe. Please go ahead and swallow it since it takes effect immediately」	s30a	0195
PV01_1901_A	4	35	I took a step back after waiting for all of them to swallow what was in fact strong aphrodisiacs that had no after-effects.	s30a	0196
PV01_1901_A	4	36	Staff Member: 「Umm, assistant? Are you sure this is okay?」	s30a	0197
PV01_1901_A	4	37	Yuu: 「Yes, since this is what she wants... Hey?」	s30a	0198
PV01_1901_A	4	38	Misleet: 「Hah...hah...fueh?」	s30a	0199
PV01_1901_A	4	39	Yuu: 「It seems the bureau chief is completely  against it, but Misleet-san wants to feel  even better, right?」	s30a	0200
PV01_1901_A	4	40	Already the effects of the drug were materializing in the men as I grumbled out words I didn't expect any answer to.	s30a	0201
PV01_1901_A	5	1	Misleet: 「Ah...ahh...ahh. Penis...cock milk, so...much. This much, fueh...cock, ah...ahh...」	s30a	0202
PV01_1901_A	5	2	Yuu: 「Yes, that's right」	s30a	0203
PV01_1901_A	5	3	I nodded using "Yuu Saitou's" smiling face at Misleet looking this way someway or another.	s30a	0204
PV01_1901_A	5	4	Yuu: 「Since she seems to like it a bit rough, do whatever works...yeah, please do whatever works for you」	s30a	0205
PV01_1901_A	5	5	While sensing the men's nasal breathing quickly  accelerating behind me, I surrendered the way  to those desires on the edge of running wild.	s30a	0206
