S011B	1	1	Yuu: 「I guess I'm going to go through the trouble of  trying to help you...」	s11b	0000
S011B	1	2	Misleet: 「Kuu!?」	s11b	0001
S011B	1	3	Misleet's shoulders quivered at the look I was giving her as I desperately endured cracking a smile.	s11b	0002
S011B	1	4	Misleet: 「What are you going to do...?」	s11b	0003
S011B	1	5	Though she was clad in a bluffing persona, it seems she had remembered the "interrogation" of yesterday.	s11b	0004
S011B	1	6	It was only a little in the depths of her eyes, but I couldn't miss the tension that came into them in that moment.	s11b	0005
S011B	1	7	Yuu: 「What, all you have to do is cooperate」	s11b	0006
S011B	1	8	While saying that, I worked my way around Misleet's back.	s11b	0007
S011B	1	9	Misleet: 「Kuu...not again」	s11b	0008
S011B	1	10	Yuu: 「...don't move」	s11b	0009
S011B	1	11	I grumbled out a dark, unfamiliar voice for the first time since I had dealt with this woman as Misleet twisted around on reflex.	s11b	0010
S011B	1	12	Misleet: 「Uu」	s11b	0011
S011B	1	13	I guess she instinctively felt the intensely deep resentment that lurked in those words.	s11b	0012
S011B	1	14	I didn't miss the nervousness, though small, traveling through Misleet's body.	s11b	0013
S011B	1	15	Misleet: 「...」	s11b	0014
S011B	1	16	And then, in one swift movement, I stuck Misleet's arm with the silver needle.	s11b	0015
S011B	1	17	Misleet: 「Y...ou...u. Such things to me again...」	s11b	0016
S011B	1	18	Yuu: 「Again? Did I say anything? Perhaps you think that this is the same medicine you had yesterday?」	s11b	0017
S011B	1	19	While spilling out a chuckle at the intimidated Misleet...I injected it all into her at once and migrated back in front of her.	s11b	0018
S011B	1	20	Misleet: 「You classless monkey...」	s11b	0019
S011B	1	21	Yuu: 「Wonderful monkey. Let's try and set that matter straight now so that you'll be obedient to that monkey, huh」	s11b	0020
S011B	1	22	The medicine circulated all throughout her body at once as her blood flow picked up.	s11b	0021
S011B	1	23	It reached her brain in an instant and began eating into her normal thoughts and sense of reason.	s11b	0022
S011B	1	24	Misleet: 「U...ku...」	s11b	0023
S011B	1	25	The medicine that had been refined with science outside of Earth's took effect far quicker than anything made on Earth.	s11b	0024
S011B	1	26	Even if this planet's science understood the effectiveness of the medicine, then it still really wouldn't understand how it worked.	s11b	0025
S011B	1	27	I guess it was why the medicine in the state that it was now in was referred to as "refined".	s11b	0026
S011B	1	28	In other words, you could say that refined medicine was perfect; a sharpened knife.	s11b	0027
S011B	1	29	Misleet: 「U...kufuu...nn...nn」	s11b	0028
S011B	1	30	That sharpened medicine pierced into the brain  and exerted its effects in the most orderly manner  possible.	s11b	0029
S011B	1	31	Misleet: 「Wh...at...what is...this? What have you done to me?」	s11b	0030
S011B	1	32	Yuu: 「What's the matter?  Perhaps, ...you're getting drowsy?」	s11b	0031
S011B	1	33	Misleet: 「Wh...at...」	s11b	0032
S011B	1	34	Yuu: 「You'll bear with me since that is an initial side effect of that medicine」	s11b	0033
S011B	1	35	While smiling brightly, I peered into her face.	s11b	0034
S011B	1	36	Misleet: 「You...scumbag. What are you going to do  to me when I'm sleeping? Hah, do you even intend  on masturbating while watching me sleep?」	s11b	0035
S011B	1	37	Yuu: 「Never.....」	s11b	0036
S011B	1	38	She looked like she had somewhat heavy eyelids, but that was no problem to a woman with this kind of force of will.	s11b	0037
S011B	1	39	She was able to fight the medicine itself on force of will alone.	s11b	0038
S011B	1	40	But, there wasn't anything that you might call attractive about injecting sleeping medicine and the  like into this kind of woman.	s11b	0039
S011B	2	1	Yuu: 「By the way, Misleet?」	s11b	0040
S011B	2	2	Misleet: 「Wha...what? You fucking worm」	s11b	0041
S011B	2	3	Yuu: 「Misleet-san, are you a virgin?」	s11b	0042
S011B	2	4	Misleet: 「Whaa!?」	s11b	0043
S011B	2	5	For a moment, it seems she hadn't understood what I had said.	s11b	0044
S011B	2	6	Misleet: 「You bastard...what did you say...」	s11b	0045
S011B	2	7	I nodded to Misleet as she trembled slightly.	s11b	0046
S011B	2	8	Yuu: 「Listen closely. Are---you---a---virgin?」	s11b	0047
S011B	2	9	And then, I asked once more, putting special emphasis on those words.	s11b	0048
S011B	2	10	Misleet: 「Tha...that's no...kuuu!?」	s11b	0049
S011B	2	11	Immediately after, a change became visible.	s11b	0050
S011B	2	12	Misleet: 「Wha...what? I...what happened just...now?」	s11b	0051
S011B	2	13	Yuu: 「Look, hurry up and answer... Is the top leader of Dozuma, Misleet-san a virgin?」	s11b	0052
S011B	2	14	Misleet: 「That's...u...kuu!?」	s11b	0053
S011B	2	15	Yuu: 「Again」	s11b	0054
S011B	2	16	Misleet: 「Th, th, that's...n...not, true」	s11b	0055
S011B	2	17	She tried to bite and chew on her lips, but it was useless.	s11b	0056
S011B	2	18	Yuu: 「I couldn't hear you very well. Are you a virgin?」	s11b	0057
S011B	2	19	Misleet: 「I'm not」	s11b	0058
S011B	2	20	The words slipped out from her nicely shaped  lips that she was trying fruitlessly to chew on.	s11b	0059
S011B	2	21	Misleet: 「...whaa!?」	s11b	0060
S011B	2	22	Yuu: 「Haha, I see, I see, so Misleet-san isn't a virgin, huh?」	s11b	0061
S011B	2	23	Misleet: 「You...you bastard...what did you do...to me?」	s11b	0062
S011B	2	24	Yuu: 「Surely you know, don't you? It's a truth serum」	s11b	0063
S011B	2	25	I revealed the true nature of the syringe to Misleet who was trembling with anger and drowsiness caused by the medicine's effects.	s11b	0064
S011B	2	26	Misleet: 「Truth...serum...?」	s11b	0065
S011B	2	27	Yuu: 「Yes, not only that, but it was a very concentrated dose, no after effects either, very pricey...hahaa」	s11b	0066
S011B	2	28	Misleet: 「No way...you used such a thing, on me... to make me confess...?」	s11b	0067
S011B	2	29	Yuu: 「Not at all. It's so that my interrogation is fair as much as possible. There's no fun in finishing it immediately」	s11b	0068
S011B	2	30	I guess I was going to ravish her slowly and amply.	s11b	0069
S011B	2	31	Yuu: 「Well, shall we begin?」	s11b	0070
S011B	2	32	Misleet: 「Kuuu」	s11b	0071
S011B	2	33	While smiling at Misleet who had put herself on guard, I hoisted my hands to my belt buckle.	s11b	0072
