S012B	1	1	Yuu: 「...oh yes」	s12b	0000
S012B	1	2	I'm going to instill even more humiliation into that woman's body.	s12b	0001
S012B	1	3	I gave thought to just how miserable-looking that  bitch will be after this.	s12b	0002
S012B	1	4	A little preparation will be needed though.	s12b	0003
S012B	1	5	As I depicted in my mind the urgently needed things, my feet surged ahead without hesitation.	s12b	0004
S012B	1	6	………。	s12b	0005
S012B	1	7	……。	s12b	0006
S012B	1	8	…。	s12b	0007
S012B	1	9	After making sure there was no signs of anyone, I crept into the medical room.	s12b	0008
S012B	1	10	Yuu: 「Now then...」	s12b	0009
S012B	1	11	All kinds of various medicines made with techniques outside of Earth's were in front  of me on the shelves now.	s12b	0010
S012B	1	12	I slowly held aloft my identification to the facilities card reader and retrieved the contents from within.	s12b	0011
S012B	1	13	Yuu: 「Kuu!?」	s12b	0012
S012B	1	14	Immediately after, without any previous notice, the medical room door opened and I put away the bottle of medicine on reflex and readied myself.	s12b	0013
S012B	1	15	Fio: 「Watata...I can't believe this」	s12b	0014
S012B	1	16	It was Fio that seemed to have leaped inside.	s12b	0015
S012B	1	17	Fio: 「It's like this because the captain will say,  "do you have to keep relying on your assistant,  Fio Rahto-kun?" Hah...」	s12b	0016
S012B	1	18	Fio entering the room with a pitter patter as she imitated a voice that didn't really resemble him, still had not noticed me.	s12b	0017
S012B	1	19	Fio: 「Oh, oh? Yuu-san?」	s12b	0018
S012B	1	20	But, that didn't last long.	s12b	0019
S012B	1	21	Fio: 「Ah, uh, ummmm... B, by chance did you hear my impression of the captain, I wonder?」	s12b	0020
S012B	1	22	Yuu: 「...no. Apart from that, is something the matter,  bureau chief? Weren't you dispatched to the incident?」	s12b	0021
S012B	1	23	I asked in a dull tone, looking unpleasantly towards Fio who was blabbering like she had seen that.	s12b	0022
S012B	1	24	Fio: 「N, no. I was, but the stock of medical kits packed in the mobile vehicle got low...」	s12b	0023
S012B	1	25	Yuu: 「...is that right?」	s12b	0024
S012B	1	26	Fio was smiling awkwardly as I began slowly  clenching my fist in the hand she couldn't she.	s12b	0025
S012B	1	27	Fio: 「Oh? On that subject Yuu-san, is there something wrong with Misleet's interrogation?」	s12b	0026
S012B	1	28	She guessed at why I was here this time.	s12b	0027
S012B	1	29	Yuu: 「Yes, I was just a little ahead of you...」	s12b	0028
S012B	1	30	I had returned the medicine bottle I had taken right away, but whether or not it was from whatever the girl  was thinking seeing me at an open cabinet, she changed.	s12b	0029
S012B	1	31	Fio: 「Ah, by chance is it Misleet's nutrients?」	s12b	0030
S012B	1	32	Fio smiled immediately thereafter like she had remembered something.	s12b	0031
S012B	1	33	Fio: 「You sort of had to apply for it specifically last time, but if it's nutrients, then isn't it fine with just Yuu-san's approval?」	s12b	0032
S012B	1	34	Yuu: 「No, it's wrong if I don't include them in my reports just in case」	s12b	0033
S012B	1	35	Fio: 「Haha, Yuu-san is really honest, huh」	s12b	0034
S012B	1	36	Yuu: 「Haha...thanks」	s12b	0035
S012B	1	37	While responding to Fio's simple-minded talk, I played along and laughed too.	s12b	0036
S012B	1	38	Yuu: 「Here you are, bureau chief, a medical kit」	s12b	0037
S012B	1	39	And then, grasping onto it tightly, I ferried the nearby medical kit to Fio.	s12b	0038
S012B	1	40	Fio: 「Yeah, thank you! Well then」	s12b	0039
S012B	2	1	Fio left the medical room behind, leaving a vigorous voice like in her wake.	s12b	0040
S012B	2	2	Yuu: 「...I'm honest?」	s12b	0041
S012B	2	3	Well, more specifically, I guess you could say that "Yuu Saitou" was honest.	s12b	0042
S012B	2	4	Yuu: 「I lucked out...」	s12b	0043
S012B	2	5	That little girl was no longer here with me.	s12b	0044
S012B	2	6	That little girl, believing with certainty that "Yuu Saitou" was a good-natured person, didn't know that I had just narrowly escaped from a dire situation.	s12b	0045
S012B	2	7	While thinking about that, I reopened the medicine cabinet.	s12b	0046
S012B	2	8	………。	s12b	0047
S012B	2	9	……。	s12b	0048
S012B	2	10	…。	s12b	0049
S012B	2	11	Misleet: 「What? Aren't you considerably late coming today?」	s12b	0050
S012B	2	12	After taking the needed things from the medical room and leaving Fio, I had just entered the cell when Misleet greeted me.	s12b	0051
S012B	2	13	Misleet: 「I had thought for sure you had given up on my interrogation, but you have some surprising amount of guts, huh?」	s12b	0052
S012B	2	14	Yuu: 「Hahaa, despite what transpired yesterday, true to your title, the top leader of Dozuma still has some  pep, huh?」	s12b	0053
S012B	2	15	Misleet: 「Kuu」	s12b	0054
S012B	2	16	Speaking like that to test her nerves on purpose, Misleet's expression grew immediately stern.	s12b	0055
S012B	2	17	Misleet: 「Putting someone like me through such humiliation, don't believe you'll be able to die of old age like everyone else」	s12b	0056
S012B	2	18	Yuu: 「Haha, I don't know about that」	s12b	0057
S012B	2	19	Did this woman really think that she would play a part in that?	s12b	0058
S012B	2	20	But, without any relation to that, I was beginning today's "interrogation" from this moment on.	s12b	0059
S012B	2	21	Yuu: 「Hey, Misleet-san?」	s12b	0060
S012B	2	22	Misleet: 「...what?」	s12b	0061
S012B	2	23	Yuu: 「Shall we have a slight change of plans today?」	s12b	0062
S012B	2	24	Misleet added a vigilance to her shoulders at me addressing her.	s12b	0063
S012B	2	25	Yuu: 「Push?」	s12b	0064
S012B	2	26	Misleet: 「Eh? Wah!?」	s12b	0065
S012B	2	27	I pushed with all of my strength Misleet's shoulders rigid with vigilance.	s12b	0066
S012B	2	28	Misleet: 「Guu!?」	s12b	0067
S012B	2	29	I guess she never was thinking that I'd push her from the front all of a sudden.	s12b	0068
S012B	2	30	Misleet having her shoulders pushed so forcefully made her tumble over the glass chair she was sitting on.	s12b	0069
S012B	2	31	Yuu: 「You've gotten into a nice position, huh. Well, shall we really get started then?」	s12b	0070
S012B	2	32	And then, I reached out between Misleet's legs like that.	s12b	0071
