S027A	1	1	Fio: 「Yuu-san?」	s27a	0000
S027A	1	2	Yuu: 「Eh?」	s27a	0001
S027A	1	3	I reconstituted my mouth in hot haste upon suddenly hearing my name from behind.	s27a	0002
S027A	1	4	Yuu: 「Is something wrong. Bureau chief?」	s27a	0003
S027A	1	5	And then, of course Fio was standing there as I looked over my shoulder.	s27a	0004
S027A	1	6	Fio: 「Yeah, excuse me, I know you're busy. Could I have a minute?」	s27a	0005
S027A	1	7	Yuu: 「Yes, it's no problem at all」	s27a	0006
S027A	1	8	In any case, it seems it was the usual subject of talk.	s27a	0007
S027A	1	9	I nodded and approached the computer terminal that Fio was using.	s27a	0008
S027A	1	10	Yuu: 「Something up?」	s27a	0009
S027A	1	11	Fio: 「Yeah...  It's about Misleet's interrogation...」	s27a	0010
S027A	1	12	And then as expected, Fio wielded her authority and brought up the subject of Misleet's interrogation.	s27a	0011
S027A	1	13	Yuu: 「I'm sorry, am I handling it badly, I know I haven't made much progress...」	s27a	0012
S027A	1	14	Fio: 「Ah, no. It's not that I'm blaming Yuu-san in particular. It's just that other day got me a little worried...」	s27a	0013
S027A	1	15	Fio took on an unusually serious expression as she spoke.	s27a	0014
S027A	1	16	Yuu: 「………」	s27a	0015
S027A	1	17	Of course "that other day" meant this rookie detective witnessing Misleet's interrogation.	s27a	0016
S027A	1	18	Fio had given me the benefit of the doubt and  exempted her presence in the beginning, but...	s27a	0017
S027A	1	19	But now the fact she was exerting her influence one way or another meant...	s27a	0018
S027A	1	20	Fio: 「Isha...san」	s27a	0019
S027A	1	21	Yuu: 「!!」	s27a	0020
S027A	1	22	I shudder went up my spine at that name suddenly being heard.	s27a	0021
S027A	1	23	Fio: 「What? Is something wrong? Yuu-san?」	s27a	0022
S027A	1	24	Yuu: 「...n, no. What could be wrong? That name... Come to think of it, that name was in the  data in relation to Misleet, wasn't it?」	s27a	0023
S027A	1	25	Pretending to be calm as much as possible, I searched out the reason as to how or why the name had come up.	s27a	0024
S027A	1	26	Fio: 「Yeah」	s27a	0025
S027A	1	27	And then I felt more filled with zeal than ever with her nodding back at me.	s27a	0026
S027A	1	28	Fio: 「That is what Yuu-san has been throwing at Misleet-san lately, hasn't it?」	s27a	0027
S027A	1	29	Yuu: 「...yes」	s27a	0028
S027A	1	30	That was right after I had divulged my true colors to Misleet.	s27a	0029
S027A	1	31	That was when Fio had seen by my own mistake the act of me subduing Misleet trying to escape from the detention cell.	s27a	0030
S027A	1	32	Fortunately, I had deceived my way out of my little mishap with Misleet, but...	s27a	0031
S027A	1	33	Fio: 「I looked into Misleet's past when Yuu-san was interrogating her, she starting acting violently when you mentioned Isha-san, huh」	s27a	0032
S027A	1	34	Yuu: 「...yes」	s27a	0033
S027A	1	35	I felt myself grow rapidly cold while nodding at the little girl and her reasoning I was no match for.	s27a	0034
S027A	1	36	Fio: 「And then the last interrogation, I remembered Misleet's strange look when talking about Isha-san」	s27a	0035
S027A	1	37	Yuu: 「...is that right」	s27a	0036
S027A	1	38	Attaching lies to everything at the last moment after Misleet had been captured by Fio had lead up to this moment now...	s27a	0037
S027A	1	39	Yuu: （This girl...）	s27a	0038
S027A	1	40	My mind wandered beyond that thought.	s27a	0039
S027A	2	1	But, no further than that.	s27a	0040
S027A	2	2	Anyone could've seen that and drawn a line connecting Isha and Misleet being from the same faction of an organization.	s27a	0041
S027A	2	3	But who would be able to imagine drawing that line straight to me?	s27a	0042
S027A	2	4	I was certain that Fio's thoughts had  reached a dead end now.	s27a	0043
S027A	2	5	Yuu: 「You felt that there was something going on between Misleet and Isha?」	s27a	0044
S027A	2	6	At any rate, deciding that her thoughts were meaningless, I prompted Fio to speak.	s27a	0045
S027A	2	7	Fio: 「Y, yeah. I'm really just speculating from  here, but may I?」	s27a	0046
S027A	2	8	I nodded at Fio looking like she was choosing her words with care in some way.	s27a	0047
S027A	2	9	Fio: 「Several years ago...a bit before I became a detective. There was a record concerning Isha-san before Misleet-san became Dozuma's top leader」	s27a	0048
S027A	2	10	Yuu: 「Was that the space investigation's record?」	s27a	0049
S027A	2	11	As expected, a nod was given to my feedback.	s27a	0050
S027A	2	12	However.	s27a	0051
S027A	2	13	Fio: 「And because I was a little curious, I looked  into Isha-san in detail...since I thought Misleet-san had forced her into something...」	s27a	0052
S027A	2	14	Yuu: 「...forced?」	s27a	0053
S027A	2	15	I was caught a little off guard by those sudden words.	s27a	0054
S027A	2	16	Yuu: 「What do you mean by...forced? Misleet...to Isha?」	s27a	0055
S027A	2	17	Fio: 「Yeah」	s27a	0056
S027A	2	18	Fio nodded in agreement to my self-conscious words used as a substitute for conversational feedback.	s27a	0057
S027A	2	19	Fio: 「Yeah. It seems something obscure happened  concerning a big amount of funds and goods in the  organization just before Misleet-san was chosen...」	s27a	0058
S027A	2	20	Yuu: 「...ehh!?」	s27a	0059
S027A	2	21	My voice sounded slightly unstrung at Fio's words that sounded like she was reading them  right out from the investigation's record.	s27a	0060
S027A	2	22	Fio: 「? Is something wrong?」	s27a	0061
S027A	2	23	Yuu: 「Uh, umm...that flow of Dozuma's goods and  money, how was the investigation able to trace that?」	s27a	0062
S027A	2	24	I asked about the matter in surprise while restoring my "Yuu Saitou" persona in hot haste.	s27a	0063
S027A	2	25	The truth then was that we really weren't able to get a trace on that obscure flow of funds and goods, so naturally I was shocked at this news.	s27a	0064
S027A	2	26	Fio: 「Yeah. What with all the networks we have, and because of the traitor inside of Dozuma,  I'm unsure about credibility, but it's accessible」	s27a	0065
S027A	2	27	Yuu: 「………」	s27a	0066
S027A	2	28	In other words, they were willingly letting criminal information go for the sake of getting  at the "bigger fish" of the organization?	s27a	0067
S027A	2	29	Fio: 「So, at the end of where that obscure flow of  things ended up, Isha-san...」	s27a	0068
S027A	2	30	I guess they were trying to reel in the big  shot at the end of where the large amount of  funds and goods had ended up.	s27a	0069
S027A	2	31	Fio: 「But, Isha-san was purged as a traitor of the organization...it seems they weren't able to follow the flow of goods any further than her」	s27a	0070
S027A	2	32	Yuu: 「………」	s27a	0071
S027A	2	33	That seemed right.	s27a	0072
S027A	2	34	I was certain that Misleet and Hoffman conspired into tricking Isha into dealing with that obscure flow of funds.	s27a	0073
S027A	2	35	So, Isha was charged with embezzlement as a traitor of the organization.	s27a	0074
S027A	2	36	The worst means of tailoring Isha into being the villain.	s27a	0075
S027A	2	37	Fio: 「...Yuu-san? Is something wrong?」	s27a	0076
S027A	2	38	Yuu: 「...eh?」	s27a	0077
S027A	2	39	Fio: 「Yuu-san now, is making a really scary face...」	s27a	0078
S027A	2	40	I realized that my own face had become stiff  with suddenly hearing her uneasy voice.	s27a	0079
S027A	3	1	Yuu: 「S, sorry. I was just shocked that the investigation's search ability was as thorough as that...」	s27a	0080
S027A	3	2	I honestly wanted to say why that flow of funds couldn't have been stopped en route.	s27a	0081
S027A	3	3	While thinking that if they were willing to do that to a Dozuma big-shot, than the sky was the limit, I smiled and tried to hide my anger.	s27a	0082
S027A	3	4	Yuu: 「So, Isha betrayed the organization and embezzled the organization's money and goods...that about sums it up, doesn't it?」	s27a	0083
S027A	3	5	Fio: 「It seems that's the extent of the record. But, I'm worried that it was Misleet-san that purged Isha-san as a traitor of the organization...」	s27a	0084
S027A	3	6	Yuu: 「………」	s27a	0085
S027A	3	7	Compared to Fio that said that with a meek look, the color drained from my face at knowing much more than Fio did about the matter.	s27a	0086
S027A	3	8	Fio: 「Yuu-san was attacked in the interrogation  the other day...maybe Misleet-san forced Isha-san  into the matter and killed her...」	s27a	0087
S027A	3	9	This little girl didn't know.	s27a	0088
S027A	3	10	What that woman had done to Isha.	s27a	0089
S027A	3	11	She didn't know that she had met the worst kind of end.	s27a	0090
S027A	3	12	Fio: 「Maybe there was some reason Misleet-san killed Isha-san...」	s27a	0091
S027A	3	13	She knew nothing, but that didn't stop her from speculating.	s27a	0092
S027A	3	14	Fio: 「Maybe it was something to do with the selection to top leader where Misleet-san had to immediately purge Isha-san...」	s27a	0093
S027A	3	15	She surmised about "her" with mere assumption and conjecture.	s27a	0094
S027A	3	16	Yuu: 「...perhaps, what didn't Misleet have to do  with it?」	s27a	0095
S027A	3	17	Fio: 「...eh?」	s27a	0096
S027A	3	18	I realized my mouth had moved on its own accord.	s27a	0097
S027A	3	19	Yuu: 「Maybe Isha hadn't misappropriated the organization's money and goods...」	s27a	0098
S027A	3	20	I muttered.	s27a	0099
S027A	3	21	My mouth moved, letting my feelings that were more distinct than just anger go.	s27a	0100
S027A	3	22	Otherwise, the thought of "her" was much  too sad.	s27a	0101
S027A	3	23	Yuu: 「What if Misleet was involved with that embezzlement somehow or another?」	s27a	0102
S027A	3	24	It wasn't just that organization, but went as far as the space investigation that fixated her as Dozuma's traitor and that was too sad.	s27a	0103
S027A	3	25	Yuu: 「So, it's funny that there was an abnormal change in Misleet's reaction when Isha's name came up...」	s27a	0104
S027A	3	26	I declared as much as that unwittingly.	s27a	0105
S027A	3	27	Fio: 「………」	s27a	0106
S027A	3	28	And then Fio's eyes locked directly onto mine immediately thereafter.	s27a	0107
S027A	3	29	Yuu: 「...ah」	s27a	0108
S027A	3	30	I shut my mouth in hot haste seeing my own face reflected back in those persistently sincere eyes.	s27a	0109
S027A	3	31	Yuu: 「F, forgive me. I'm saying strange things at my own conjecture even though I haven't a clue about the investigation's search techniques...」	s27a	0110
S027A	3	32	In any case, it didn't change anything no matter what I said now.	s27a	0111
S027A	3	33	Even though I knew that, I couldn't just  stand there and say nothing and finished the  conversation by forcing a smile in hot haste.	s27a	0112
S027A	3	34	But, Fio's serious look was still turned towards me.	s27a	0113
S027A	3	35	I realized I had given in to my emotions and had said too much.	s27a	0114
S027A	3	36	Yuu: 「Ab, absolutely conjecture. Yeah, was it conjecture?」	s27a	0115
S027A	3	37	I didn't know at what point or how far the space investigation's search had ended.	s27a	0116
S027A	3	38	But I didn't expect the truth to be understood by anyone but the people on the inside where Misleet had feigned Isha's embezzlement and had her killed.	s27a	0117
S027A	3	39	Fio: 「Yeah...maybe」	s27a	0118
S027A	3	40	Yuu: 「Eh?」	s27a	0119
S027A	4	1	But Fio spilled out the words immediately following.	s27a	0120
S027A	4	2	Fio: 「Possibly...but, if there was a reason she killed Isha-san...then she must have regret about killing Isha-san...and that sort of reaction...」	s27a	0121
S027A	4	3	Assumption was added on top of assumption without anything to base it on.	s27a	0122
S027A	4	4	Yuu: 「Surely you can't expect that to be so」	s27a	0123
S027A	4	5	I interrupted those words.	s27a	0124
S027A	4	6	Fio: 「Eh? Yu, Yuu-san」	s27a	0125
S027A	4	7	Yuu: 「I don't think Misleet is a person like that」	s27a	0126
S027A	4	8	It's impossible that Misleet was regretful about killing Isha.	s27a	0127
S027A	4	9	Yuu: 「You don't think it's possible for the person that climbed up an organization on the backs of others to be forced to kill people?」	s27a	0128
S027A	4	10	Fio: 「Th, that sort of...」	s27a	0129
S027A	4	11	Fio shrunk away slightly at me suddenly taking a strong tone.	s27a	0130
S027A	4	12	Fio: 「Not caring at all about killing others...?」	s27a	0131
S027A	4	13	I nodded at Fio's voice as if that was difficult for her to say that.	s27a	0132
S027A	4	14	I was unable to believe that Misleet held any kind of sentiment for those that she killed.	s27a	0133
S027A	4	15	Yuu: 「...the people she killed didn't understand that either」	s27a	0134
S027A	4	16	Fio: 「No...way」	s27a	0135
S027A	4	17	Fio opened her mouth, not knowing the right  way to respond to my unusual talkativeness.	s27a	0136
S027A	4	18	Though it took a seconds, she began nodding towards me.	s27a	0137
S027A	4	19	Fio: 「If she committed a crime, then she should make up for it. It's reasonable she'd agree with that in her heart...I think」	s27a	0138
S027A	4	20	Yuu: 「………」	s27a	0139
S027A	4	21	Good god this girl...	s27a	0140
S027A	4	22	Does she really believe every person has "good intentions"?	s27a	0141
S027A	4	23	Does she just not get it or what?	s27a	0142
S027A	4	24	Whatever it was, I didn't have the time to make this little dreamer girl understand that now.	s27a	0143
S027A	4	25	Yuu: 「... I've got to get back to the interrogation, excuse me」	s27a	0144
S027A	4	26	Fio: 「Ah...」	s27a	0145
S027A	4	27	Fio stood stock still not saying anything back to me as I quickly turned and took my leave.	s27a	0146
S027A	4	28	………………。	s27a	0147
S027A	4	29	…………。	s27a	0148
S027A	4	30	……。	s27a	0149
S027A	4	31	Yuu: 「...goddamn, a waste of time」	s27a	0150
S027A	4	32	Those irritated words had left my mouth a  few minutes after I had left the tactics room.	s27a	0151
S027A	4	33	What the hell does that rookie space detective know?	s27a	0152
S027A	4	34	What does she know?	s27a	0153
S027A	4	35	Yuu: 「Shit...」	s27a	0154
S027A	4	36	I cursed once more.	s27a	0155
S027A	4	37	Yuu: 「Kuu!?」	s27a	0156
S027A	4	38	I collided into someone right as I rounded a corner in the hallway.	s27a	0157
S027A	4	39	The other person seemed just as surprised as I did as the papers they were holding went flying onto the floor.	s27a	0158
S027A	4	40	Yuu: 「S, sorry. That was stupid of me」	s27a	0159
S027A	5	1	Staff Woman: 「N, no. It was my fault...」	s27a	0160
S027A	5	2	I locked eyes with the staff member I had bumped into as I went to pick up the papers on reflex.	s27a	0161
S027A	5	3	Staff Woman: 「...ah」	s27a	0162
S027A	5	4	Yuu: 「?」	s27a	0163
S027A	5	5	Immediately after, the staff member that had recognized my face had cracked a voice.	s27a	0164
S027A	5	6	Staff Woman: 「F, forgive me assistant Yuu Saitou. I'll pick them up myself」	s27a	0165
S027A	5	7	And then she more hastily rustled up the scattered papers while calling out my name.	s27a	0166
S027A	5	8	Yuu: 「H, hey, you are?」	s27a	0167
S027A	5	9	Staff Woman: 「Well then, if you'll excuse me」	s27a	0168
S027A	5	10	Bowing, the woman staff member took  off running down the hallway carrying a mess of papers in her hands like that.	s27a	0169
S027A	5	11	Yuu: 「...what was that about?」	s27a	0170
S027A	5	12	Why was that medical room staff member in such a hurry?	s27a	0171
S027A	5	13	Yuu: 「...probably nothing. I'm in a hurry too」	s27a	0172
S027A	5	14	Shaking it off and not giving it any more thought than that, I rushed off to Misleet's  detention cell.	s27a	0173
S027A	5	15	………………。	s27a	0174
S027A	5	16	…………。	s27a	0175
S027A	5	17	……。	s27a	0176
S027A	5	18	SALTAR: S28A
S027A	5	19	SALTAR: S028A
