PV01_1901_A	1	1	Rikurou: "Huh... ah?"	s35a	1037
PV01_1901_A	1	2	At first, Rikurou couldn't comprehend what his eyes were  showing him.	s35a	1038
PV01_1901_A	1	3	Annerose: "Hyah... hgghii... ahiiiiiiih!!"	s35a	1039
PV01_1901_A	1	4	But there was no need to comprehend.	s35a	1040
PV01_1901_A	1	5	Because the entire scene unfolding before him was simple reality.	s35a	1041
PV01_1901_A	1	6	Annerose: "Ihii... yess! Ih's so gooood! My love, your dick, your  anal dick... ih's sooo goooooood!!!"	s35a	1042
PV01_1901_A	1	7	What occupied the cell was a female animal copulating  with a monster he'd never seen before.	s35a	1043
PV01_1901_A	1	8	Its swollen belly jiggled with delight in all directions.	s35a	1044
PV01_1901_A	1	9	And from the look of it at least, it seemed to be occupied  by something more than just liquid.	s35a	1045
PV01_1901_A	1	10	Annerose: "My asspussy feels amaziing! Ih's so goohood! Your giant  cock ish turning me inside out up to my mouth an' ih's so  gooooood!!"	s35a	1046
PV01_1901_A	1	11	Rikurou: "A-Annero... se...?"	s35a	1047
PV01_1901_A	1	12	He recognized that face.	s35a	1048
PV01_1901_A	1	13	But Annerose was madly writhing in pleasure and twisting  it with a look of rapture that Rikurou had never seen  before.	s35a	1049
PV01_1901_A	1	14	Annerose: "Yess!! I love having sex wi'hyouu! I like you, I love you,  I adore youuu! There's no'hingbehher than making looove!!!"	s35a	1050
PV01_1901_A	1	15	Rikurou: "Annerose...!"	s35a	1051
PV01_1901_A	1	16	He called that name in his bewilderment, but Annerose did  not respond.	s35a	1052
PV01_1901_A	1	17	No, she was utterly absorbed in breeding with the monster  that was violating her asshole.	s35a	1053
PV01_1901_A	1	18	She would never look his way again.	s35a	1054
PV01_1901_A	1	19	Annerose: "I lig'ih, I love'ih, I love'shex, I love making babies  wih'youuuuu!"	s35a	1055
PV01_1901_A	1	20	And more than likely, if not for certain, she herself  didn't want to leave this place.	s35a	1056
PV01_1901_A	1	21	It was a love that transcended species.	s35a	1057
PV01_1901_A	1	22	Rikurou: "What... the... What the hell is this!!!?"	s35a	1058
PV01_1901_A	1	23	Mayfeng: "That's right! Didn't I tell you? This pig is married to  that monster behind her♪ Don't they make the perfect  couple?"	s35a	1059
PV01_1901_A	1	24	Mayfeng spoke as if recalling something that had slipped  her mind as Rikurou screamed from this scene that surpassed  despair and comprehension.	s35a	1060
PV01_1901_A	1	25	In truth, she'd been looking forward to this moment.	s35a	1061
PV01_1901_A	1	26	Mayfeng: "They really are a perfect match... She kicked and screamed  for the first three months, but ever since it's been just  like this... hmhm."	s35a	1062
PV01_1901_A	1	27	Rikurou: "I-It can't be..."	s35a	1063
PV01_1901_A	1	28	Mayfeng: "She doesn't even remember her own name anymore... Well,  not that two animals in wedded bliss down here need one,  I suppose."	s35a	1064
PV01_1901_A	1	29	Mayfeng made a big shrug of her shoulders behind Rikurou,  who was audibly grinding his teeth.	s35a	1065
PV01_1901_A	1	30	But she then took her hand and gripped the back of his head  from behind.	s35a	1066
PV01_1901_A	1	31	Mayfeng: "Take a good, long look. It's not often you see many  married couples this happy, now do you?"	s35a	1067
PV01_1901_A	1	32	After having everything stripped away from her, all  Annerose wanted now was to live in peace.	s35a	1068
PV01_1901_A	1	33	Annerose: "I'm sho happy... I'h so happy I could'diee... I'h happy  enough to die, my loooove!"	s35a	1069
PV01_1901_A	1	34	Violent sexual hunger and the lust for conquest.	s35a	1070
PV01_1901_A	1	35	Unconditional love to receive it.	s35a	1071
PV01_1901_A	1	36	She had finally won it.	s35a	1072
PV01_1901_A	1	37	Annerose: "I wan'your cooock... ooh... cummiiinnngg!! I'm cumming my  looove! I'h cumming from my ass on your gigapeniiis!!"	s35a	1073
PV01_1901_A	1	38	Annerose: "Hakkhhhhnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnn!!"	s35a	1074
PV01_1901_A	1	39	Then came the supreme moment for the millionth time.	s35a	1075
PV01_1901_A	1	40	Annerose: "Tha's iiih, your gigapenis in my asspussy's cumming!  Th'bubbling sperm's... going from my stomach to my throat  to my mouth... up to my noooseee!!"	s35a	1076
PV01_1901_A	2	1	Her mad joy seemed to say there was no greater happiness than this.	s35a	1077
PV01_1901_A	2	2	No, that's exactly what it was to her now.	s35a	1078
PV01_1901_A	2	3	She didn't need anything else.	s35a	1079
PV01_1901_A	2	4	Annerose: "I love you! I love you so mushh! All I wan'is to fuck  and have sex wih'you forever an' ever an' ever!"	s35a	1080
PV01_1901_A	2	5	Rikurou: "Ah... aahh... aaahhh, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhh!"	s35a	1081
PV01_1901_A	2	6	That sent Rikurou hurtling into the bowels of despair.	s35a	1082
PV01_1901_A	2	7	"She" wasn't here anymore.	s35a	1083
PV01_1901_A	2	8	There was only something that looked like "her."	s35a	1084
PV01_1901_A	2	9	Mayfeng: "Oh, that's right. I did say I'd set her free, but  shouldn't you clear it with her husband, first?"	s35a	1085
PV01_1901_A	2	10	Mayfeng's voice stroked Rikurou's ears, speechless from  despair, his efforts these last six months having amounted to nothing.	s35a	1086
PV01_1901_A	2	11	Mayfeng: "He gets angry if you try and separate them, and hasn't  let her work for the last three months♪ Ahahahaha!"	s35a	1087
PV01_1901_A	2	12	She couldn't play along anymore and burst out laughing.	s35a	1088
PV01_1901_A	2	13	Rikurou: "... An...... ne...... rose......"	s35a	1089
PV01_1901_A	2	14	He managed to choke out that name one last time.	s35a	1090
PV01_1901_A	2	15	Annerose: "Ih's so goood! Yehesss! Moree! Please fill my insides,  knock my stomach up wih'your cuuuuuuuum!"	s35a	1091
PV01_1901_A	2	16	It was immediately drowned out by Annerose's howls of  pleasure, and disappeared.	s35a	1092
PV01_1901_A	2	17	SALTAR: END
