S016A [CM]\	1	1	The sun was sinking beneath the horizon by the time we  mounted our pursuit.	s16a	0000
S016A [CM]\	1	2	The time of long shadows in the interstice between day and  night.	s16a	0001
S016A [CM]\	1	3	The rapidly fading light makes tracking the assassins even  harder.	s16a	0002
S016A [CM]\	1	4	Mayfeng must have launched her assault with this exact  time of day in mind.	s16a	0003
S016A [CM]\	1	5	Annerose and I race along the rooftops to hunt down Miki's kidnappers.	s16a	0004
S016A [CM]\	1	6	But things aren't going so easily.	s16a	0005
S016A [CM]\	1	7	All too eager to die assassins keep slowing us down one  after another.	s16a	0006
S016A [CM]\	1	8	Annerose: "Haah!"	s16a	0007
S016A [CM]\	1	9	Annerose cuts them down without hesitation.	s16a	0008
S016A [CM]\	1	10	Annerose: "Seriously, they're all over the place... Tch, they split  up again!?"	s16a	0009
S016A [CM]\	1	11	They must have anticipated our pursuit because they break  into several groups to throw us off.	s16a	0010
S016A [CM]\	1	12	We'll lose them in a flash if we only focus on the ones  we can see.	s16a	0011
S016A [CM]\	1	13	Annerose: "□〇■・△〇◇＋・□■◇〇......, □〇■・△〇◇＋・□■◇〇......... This way!"	s16a	0012
S016A [CM]\	1	14	Annerose occasionally checks the way by chanting a spell  and sniffs the air, slowly but surely leading us closer to  Miki.	s16a	0013
S016A [CM]\	1	15	The endless stream of assassins hindering us is proof of  that.	s16a	0014
S016A [CM]\	1	16	Rikurou: "Kh..."	s16a	0015
S016A [CM]\	1	17	Annerose flies through the evening dusk, springing like a cat from rooftop to rooftop as she takes down assassins without missing a beat.	s16a	0016
S016A [CM]\	1	18	It takes everything I've got just to keep up with her.	s16a	0017
S016A [CM]\	1	19	There's no catching up if I fall behind now.	s16a	0018
S016A [CM]\	1	20	I grit my teeth and follow after her.	s16a	0019
S016A [CM]\	1	21	Assassins: "Sha!" "Sha!"	s16a	0020
S016A [CM]\	1	22	More assassins emerge from the shadows of the rooftop.	s16a	0021
S016A [CM]\	1	23	Two of them.	s16a	0022
S016A [CM]\	1	24	Annerose: "Out of my way!"	s16a	0023
S016A [CM]\	1	25	Annerose doesn't slow down for a second before the ambush  from either side and instantly sends their heads flying.	s16a	0024
S016A [CM]\	1	26	However... the real trap laid elsewhere.	s16a	0025
S016A [CM]\	1	27	For the very moment Annerose had finished them off--	s16a	0026
S016A [CM]\	1	28	The roof under our feet gave way and a swarm of rope darts  came attacking from below.	s16a	0027
S016A [CM]\	1	29	Annerose: "Tch...!"	s16a	0028
S016A [CM]\	1	30	Annerose tries to leap away.	s16a	0029
S016A [CM]\	1	31	But we're on bad footing.	s16a	0030
S016A [CM]\	1	32	Even though she deflected nearly all of them with her blade,  one had snaked up from behind and wound itself around her  leg.	s16a	0031
S016A [CM]\	1	33	Rikurou: "Annerose!!"	s16a	0032
S016A [CM]\	1	34	Annerose: "No--!"	s16a	0033
S016A [CM]\	1	35	She tried to cut herself free with Kongo Yasha.	s16a	0034
S016A [CM]\	1	36	But...	s16a	0035
S016A [CM]\	1	37	Craaaaaash!!	s16a	0036
S016A [CM]\	1	38	Annerose: "Kuh...!!!"	s16a	0037
S016A [CM]\	1	39	The entire rooftop itself let alone where she stood collapsed in an explosion.	s16a	0038
S016A [CM]\	1	40	Rikurou: "Woah!"	s16a	0039
S016A [CM]\	2	1	The floor suddenly crumbles beneath me as well.	s16a	0040
S016A [CM]\	2	2	There's nothing I can do but fall with Annerose.	s16a	0041
S016A [CM]\	2	3	Rikurou: "Aaaaaaaahhhh!!"	s16a	0042
S016A [CM]\	2	4	Rikurou: "Guhaahh!!"	s16a	0043
S016A [CM]\	2	5	With pieces of the roof clattering around me, I slam into  the hard floor.	s16a	0044
S016A [CM]\	2	6	I couldn't brace for the impact and landed square on my  back.	s16a	0045
S016A [CM]\	2	7	Awful cracking sounds come from my spine as my body  bounces to a stop on the ground.	s16a	0046
S016A [CM]\	2	8	Rikurou: "Ngh, ghh... shit......"	s16a	0047
S016A [CM]\	2	9	Lying paralyzed on my back, I can see what's left of the  destroyed ceiling.	s16a	0048
S016A [CM]\	2	10	I'm wincing from the pain so I can't exactly tell, but it  looks like I fell at least 20 or 30 meters.	s16a	0049
S016A [CM]\	2	11	Rikurou: "Gh... guhagh..."	s16a	0050
S016A [CM]\	2	12	It feels like a bomb went off in my guts.	s16a	0051
S016A [CM]\	2	13	I spit up globs of blood, staining my mouth red.	s16a	0052
S016A [CM]\	2	14	For a normal person this would spell certain death.	s16a	0053
S016A [CM]\	2	15	But in my case, I'll heal up if I stay still.	s16a	0054
S016A [CM]\	2	16	More importantly...	s16a	0055
S016A [CM]\	2	17	Rikurou: "A...... Annerose......"	s16a	0056
S016A [CM]\	2	18	Were this any other time I wouldn't be worried about  her.	s16a	0057
S016A [CM]\	2	19	She'd use a spell or something and be fine, humming a  tune all the while.	s16a	0058
S016A [CM]\	2	20	But I know Mayfeng's rope dart had her tangled up back there.	s16a	0059
S016A [CM]\	2	21	Rikurou: "Anne... rose... are you... okay...?"	s16a	0060
S016A [CM]\	2	22	I twist my body, groaning from the pain wracking every  inch of me to try and see if she's safe.	s16a	0061
S016A [CM]\	2	23	What met my eyes, however--	s16a	0062
S016A [CM]\	2	24	Rikurou: "............!!"	s16a	0063
S016A [CM]\	2	25	Was a sight beyond my wildest imaginings.	s16a	0064
S016A [CM]\	2	26	Annerose is tied up.	s16a	0065
S016A [CM]\	2	27	Narrow ropes are wrapped round and round her body, tightly  restraining her.	s16a	0066
S016A [CM]\	2	28	They're Mayfeng's rope darts.	s16a	0067
S016A [CM]\	2	29	Several of them have their tips buried deep in the floor,  leaving Annerose unable to move.	s16a	0068
S016A [CM]\	2	30	The ground beneath her glows with a strange light as she's  forced to stand frozen in place.	s16a	0069
S016A [CM]\	2	31	Mayfeng: "I finally did it...!!!!"	s16a	0070
S016A [CM]\	2	32	Mayfeng wears a triumphant smile at having captured  Annerose.	s16a	0071
S016A [CM]\	2	33	And what's more, six assassins have her surrounded as  well.	s16a	0072
S016A [CM]\	2	34	One of them's carrying an unconscious Miki.	s16a	0073
S016A [CM]\	2	35	Rikurou: (Damn it...)	s16a	0074
S016A [CM]\	2	36	I need to help her ASAP but my body's not ready yet.	s16a	0075
S016A [CM]\	2	37	My broken spine and ruined organs have only just started  regenerating.	s16a	0076
S016A [CM]\	2	38	Rikurou: (Heal... hurry up and heal!!)	s16a	0077
S016A [CM]\	2	39	Mayfeng: "Hmhmhm, you look absolutely wonderful, Steel Witch  Annerose."	s16a	0078
S016A [CM]\	2	40	Annerose: "Then what do you say we trade spots?"	s16a	0079
S016A [CM]\	3	1	Mayfeng: "Thanks but I think I'll pass. I love tying up naughty  little kittens, but being tied up myself isn't really my  thing."	s16a	0080
S016A [CM]\	3	2	Annerose: "Of course not. Using these masks for your dirty work  and pulling cheap tricks are much better suited for a  filthy Mudsnake, after all."	s16a	0081
S016A [CM]\	3	3	I don't know if she's got a plan or if she's just being  gutsy, but Annerose intentionally tries to provoke  Mayfeng.	s16a	0082
S016A [CM]\	3	4	Mayfeng: "Hmhm... idiot. You think I'm going to fall for that?  Staying cool comes first. Yes... perfectly cool♪"	s16a	0083
S016A [CM]\	3	5	Mayfeng licks Annerose up and down with her eyes.	s16a	0084
S016A [CM]\	3	6	They're gleaming with sadistic lust.	s16a	0085
S016A [CM]\	3	7	Annerose: "Staying cool? That's a laugh. Calling someone a little  kitten when YOU'RE the little kitten all turned on. Decide  snakes weren't your thing anymore?"	s16a	0086
S016A [CM]\	3	8	Annerose keeps her eyes locked on Mayfeng and rails her  again.	s16a	0087
S016A [CM]\	3	9	Mayfeng: "Oh, I'm still a snake. And I've got the fangs to prove  it."	s16a	0088
S016A [CM]\	3	10	Mayfeng says with supreme fulfillment, drawing two long,  sharp needles from her cleavage.	s16a	0089
S016A [CM]\	3	11	Mayfeng: "And what do you suppose these are?"	s16a	0090
S016A [CM]\	3	12	Annerose: "Can't say I care."	s16a	0091
S016A [CM]\	3	13	Mayfeng: "Oh, you will soon... mm."	s16a	0092
S016A [CM]\	3	14	Mayfeng dramatically kisses the needles.	s16a	0093
S016A [CM]\	3	15	Mayfeng: "To tell you the truth, I'd love to pop those impudent  little eyes of yours..."	s16a	0094
S016A [CM]\	3	16	She makes slow, easy circles with the needles right in  front of Annerose's eyes to scare her.	s16a	0095
S016A [CM]\	3	17	Annerose: "Go for it."	s16a	0096
S016A [CM]\	3	18	Annerose's expression doesn't change a bit as she stares  Mayfeng down.	s16a	0097
S016A [CM]\	3	19	It's not from lack of fear, it's her tremendous mental  fortitude.	s16a	0098
S016A [CM]\	3	20	Mayfeng: "I would, but one's fall is best seen with one's own eyes,  don't you think?"	s16a	0099
S016A [CM]\	3	21	Mayfeng says mockingly, drawing a line with the points of  the needles from Annerose's eyes down to her chest.	s16a	0100
S016A [CM]\	3	22	Then, stops them right in front of her nipples.	s16a	0101
S016A [CM]\	3	23	Annerose: "You make me sick."	s16a	0102
S016A [CM]\	3	24	Mayfeng: "Don't worry, you'll be begging me to stick them in of  your own accord before long."	s16a	0103
S016A [CM]\	3	25	Annerose: "Oh, really? I think I'd like to see that."	s16a	0104
S016A [CM]\	3	26	Mayfeng: "Just hold on tight. Here we go...... poke!"	s16a	0105
S016A [CM]\	3	27	Mayfeng pierces Annerose's nipples with the poison  needles.	s16a	0106
S016A [CM]\	3	28	Annerose: "Kh...!!!"	s16a	0107
S016A [CM]\	3	29	It's no surprise she jumps from anxiousness.	s16a	0108
S016A [CM]\	3	30	Mayfeng: "They're not even close to going in yet."	s16a	0109
S016A [CM]\	3	31	With light pressure from Mayfeng, the needles slowly sink  deeper in.	s16a	0110
S016A [CM]\	3	32	Annerose: "...............!"	s16a	0111
S016A [CM]\	3	33	Not even Annerose can keep from quietly groaning at  whatever pain was assaulting her.	s16a	0112
S016A [CM]\	3	34	Mayfeng: "My needles stimulate the nerves directly. Isn't the pain  incredible?"	s16a	0113
S016A [CM]\	3	35	Annerose: "It's nothing to brag about... just one or two of these  little things..."	s16a	0114
S016A [CM]\	3	36	Mayfeng: "That's what I thought. So this is what we'll do next."	s16a	0115
S016A [CM]\	3	37	Mayfeng flicks the needle piercing her nipple and pinches  the end of it between her fingers.	s16a	0116
S016A [CM]\	3	38	Annerose: "Kuh......! Ngh... ah, wh-what're you...!?"	s16a	0117
S016A [CM]\	3	39	Annerose had gone pale.	s16a	0118
S016A [CM]\	3	40	A white substance from Mayfeng's fingers was travelling  down the needle and into Annerose's breast.	s16a	0119
S016A [CM]\	4	1	Mayfeng: "Here we go～～♪ Injection～♪ Poison injectio～nnn♪  Kiss our rough and tumble Witch goodbye～♪"	s16a	0120
S016A [CM]\	4	2	Annerose: "Ah... ngh... y-you think this will... kh..."	s16a	0121
S016A [CM]\	4	3	Her cheeks flush, and a light sweat breaks out on her skin.	s16a	0122
S016A [CM]\	4	4	She begins to tremble with small jerks.	s16a	0123
S016A [CM]\	4	5	Clearly, something other than pain was eating away at  Annerose's body.	s16a	0124
S016A [CM]\	4	6	Mayfeng: "Do you want to know my power?"	s16a	0125
S016A [CM]\	4	7	Annerose: "T-Tattoos... you thought a Witch like me wouldn't know?"	s16a	0126
S016A [CM]\	4	8	Mayfeng: "That's right, the source of power from the Witches I've  killed is the tattoo on my back. It lets a human like me  use the powers of a Witch."	s16a	0127
S016A [CM]\	4	9	Annerose: "Always... relying on someone else to get the job done,  huh...? What a joke..."	s16a	0128
S016A [CM]\	4	10	Mayfeng: "Say what you want. With the tattoo, I can create poison.  Poison to kill, poison to drive insane... whatever I like.  That's why they call me White Snake."	s16a	0129
S016A [CM]\	4	11	Mayfeng triumphantly explains with all the arrogance  particular to those whose victory has been assured.	s16a	0130
S016A [CM]\	4	12	Mayfeng: "What I just injected you with is an aphrodisiac poison  among poisons♪ It scrambles your pleasure sensors and  puts you in a state of forced arousal.  You're going to want cock so badly you won't be able  to stand it♪"	s16a	0131
S016A [CM]\	4	13	Annerose: "Insane as usual, I see... I'll never fall for your...  kh..."	s16a	0132
S016A [CM]\	4	14	Annerose grits her teeth and fights Mayfeng's aphrovenom.	s16a	0133
S016A [CM]\	4	15	Mayfeng: "Ahaha, that's a Witch for you. Any normal person would be  done for in under a second. But fight too hard and you'll  end up a vegetable as your brain burns out your nerves♪"	s16a	0134
S016A [CM]\	4	16	Mayfeng: "Come on, it's me watching so squeal for it like a good  little pig. Okay? Say, 'Plea～se give me cock.'"	s16a	0135
S016A [CM]\	4	17	Annerose: "Kh... you'll regret not killing me when you had the  chance."	s16a	0136
S016A [CM]\	4	18	Mayfeng: "Ah～～～hahaha! Good, very good! I love cliche lines like  that. Don't stop now, let me hear some more."	s16a	0137
S016A [CM]\	4	19	Annerose: "Kh...... this poison......"	s16a	0138
S016A [CM]\	4	20	Mayfeng: "Oh my, look at you trying so hard. Fine then. I haven't  got all day so gentlemen... give the girl a hand♪"	s16a	0139
S016A [CM]\	4	21	Assassin: "Heheheh..."	s16a	0140
S016A [CM]\	4	22	The luridly chuckling assassins close in on Annerose like  they'd been waiting for the word.	s16a	0141
S016A [CM]\	4	23	Rikurou: "Hold iiiiiiiiit!!!"	s16a	0142
S016A [CM]\	4	24	I get up with a bloody scream.	s16a	0143
S016A [CM]\	4	25	My body's still not fully healed yet.	s16a	0144
S016A [CM]\	4	26	It's only my spine that's finally reconnected. My insides  are still a complete mess.	s16a	0145
S016A [CM]\	4	27	I'm almost ready to pass out just standing here.	s16a	0146
S016A [CM]\	4	28	But I don't care.	s16a	0147
S016A [CM]\	4	29	Annerose is about to be defiled right in front of me.	s16a	0148
S016A [CM]\	4	30	I'm not going to let that happen.	s16a	0149
S016A [CM]\	4	31	Rikurou: (She's my woman!)	s16a	0150
S016A [CM]\	4	32	I can't say it out loud, but that sole, blazing emotion is  what drives me forward.	s16a	0151
S016A [CM]\	4	33	Mayfeng: "What is it, boy? Do you want to join the fun, too?"	s16a	0152
S016A [CM]\	4	34	Mayfeng looks at me with a provocative smile.	s16a	0153
S016A [CM]\	4	35	Mayfeng: "You've been waiting for it all this time, haven't you? In  that case, I'll let you have the first go at her. Just say  whichever hole you want."	s16a	0154
S016A [CM]\	4	36	Rikurou: "Cut the bullshit! Get away from Annerose you filthy  snake!"	s16a	0155
S016A [CM]\	4	37	Mayfeng: "You've got guts to stand up to me... were you expecting  a pat on the back or something?"	s16a	0156
S016A [CM]\	4	38	Mayfeng's eyes silently narrow in wrath.	s16a	0157
S016A [CM]\	4	39	Mayfeng: "Die!"	s16a	0158
S016A [CM]\	4	40	On Mayfeng's signal, three assassins turn to attack me.	s16a	0159
S016A [CM]\	5	1	I--	s16a	0160
S016A [CM]\	5	2	SELECCIONAR 1: S016B
S016A [CM]\	5	3	SELECCIONAR 2: S016C
