PV01_1301_A	1	1	Oboro: 「Ahahahahah?! Haven't you gotten big!」	s26a	0726
PV01_1301_A	1	2	Looking up at the flesh egg, which had grown, Oboro raised hysterical laughter.	s26a	0727
PV01_1301_A	1	3	The tentacles that stretched from the egg had taken root and extended a trunk, just like a tree, and the tip reached as far as the ceiling.	s26a	0728
PV01_1301_A	1	4	Greatly swollen like a fruit, the flesh egg that had swallowed up Asagi one week before was on one of the branches. Thus......	s26a	0729
PV01_1301_A	1	5	Oboro: 「Ara ara! So half of you has been forced out?」	s26a	0730
PV01_1301_A	1	6	From the bottom edge of the egg, which had transformed into flesh fruit, a naked woman's body was dangling loosely.	s26a	0731
PV01_1301_A	1	7	The woman's white skin, which had been exposed starting from just below the ribs, was covered with a film of mucus, and created a dazzling contrast with the colour of the flesh.	s26a	0732
PV01_1301_A	1	8	And, obvious to anyone's eyes, the woman's stomach was......	s26a	0733
PV01_1301_A	1	9	Oboro: 「Ahahahahaa! You seriously got knocked up, didn't you, Asagi?! Ahaha! What's with that stomach?! Kufu! Pitiful state, eh?!」	s26a	0734
PV01_1301_A	1	10	Looking up at Asagi, who was dangling in midair and not moving one bit, Oboro sneered at her.	s26a	0735
PV01_1301_A	1	11	Oboro: 「Besides, what's with that clit bean?! Just like a cock, isn't it?! Kyaha, and even though you've become like this, you're getting off?!」	s26a	0736
PV01_1301_A	1	12	Demonic Specialist Doctor: 「O, Oboro-sama, you mustn't do that. Giving her stimulation is......」	s26a	0737
PV01_1301_A	1	13	While hitting the outer wall of the huge flesh egg with her fist, Oboro looked back at the staffer.	s26a	0738
PV01_1301_A	1	14	Oboro: 「This much is okay. So, how about it? How long until this bitch gives birth to a monster?!」	s26a	0739
PV01_1301_A	1	15	Demonic Specialist Doctor: 「Water breaking is planned to commence in approximately 10 minutes.」	s26a	0740
PV01_1301_A	1	16	Oboro: 「Hmph...... Do it quickly, okay?!」	s26a	0741
PV01_1301_A	1	17	Oboro strongly bashed the egg mass once more.	s26a	0742
PV01_1301_A	1	18	Precisely 10 minutes after that──	s26a	0743
PV01_1301_A	1	19	Buruu, burururuh.	s26a	0744
PV01_1301_A	1	20	Oboro: 「Oh?!」	s26a	0745
PV01_1301_A	1	21	The flesh egg quivered greatly, and tentacles that slithered from the base twined around both of Asagi's legs and opened them wide.	s26a	0746
PV01_1301_A	1	22	Asagi: 「......Nn, guh......」	s26a	0747
PV01_1301_A	1	23	Asagi's faintly moaning voice was heard, and her body started slightly trembling.	s26a	0748
PV01_1301_A	1	24	Demonic Specialist Doctor: 「Her water's going to break.」	s26a	0749
PV01_1301_A	1	25	Oboro: 「I'll know that when I see it. Now, become a mama right away! An injuu's mama, eh, Asagi?!」	s26a	0750
PV01_1301_A	1	26	As if responding to Oboro's voice, Asagi's naked body shivered again, and......	s26a	0751
PV01_1301_A	1	27	Bushaaa! Buboboboboboboboh!!	s26a	0752
PV01_1301_A	1	28	Oboro: 「Whoa?!」	s26a	0753
PV01_1301_A	1	29	Demonic Specialist Doctor: 「Her water has broken.」	s26a	0754
PV01_1301_A	1	30	Oboro: 「Ahahaha! It came out, it came out! That was a large amount of semen water, wasn't it?!」	s26a	0755
PV01_1301_A	1	31	Watching cloudy yellowish liquid pour out from Asagi's genitals and anus, Oboro erupted into a joyful look.	s26a	0756
PV01_1301_A	1	32	Oboro: 「What's with this amount?! How much was shot into you? Aha! Your compatibility with the injuu was quite good, wasn't it!」	s26a	0757
PV01_1301_A	1	33	Asagi: 「Fu...... gu...... nnuuh......!」	s26a	0758
PV01_1301_A	1	34	Asagi, whose clitoris had been towering even while her water broke, emitted moans inside the egg.	s26a	0759
PV01_1301_A	1	35	That was the signal for delivery.	s26a	0760
PV01_1301_A	1	36	Larva: 「Kyumiiii! Kyumiiii!」	s26a	0761
PV01_1301_A	1	37	Oboro: 「Hyaaa! They came out?!」	s26a	0762
PV01_1301_A	1	38	Seamlessly pure white, pill bug-like injuu larvae spread out both of Asagi's holes and showed their faces.	s26a	0763
PV01_1301_A	1	39	Larva: 「Kyumii! Kyuuu! Kyukyuu!」	s26a	0764
PV01_1301_A	1	40	Whenever the two larvae twisted, Asagi's lower body convulsed.	s26a	0765
PV01_1301_A	2	1	The bodily fluids the larvae secreted displayed a strong aphrodisiac effect, and were forcibly guiding Asagi to climax.	s26a	0766
PV01_1301_A	2	2	Oboro: 「Orgasming while expelling monsters, huh? You really do make me laugh!」	s26a	0767
PV01_1301_A	2	3	While showered in Oboro's scorn, the birthing of Asagi and the larvae continued.	s26a	0768
PV01_1301_A	2	4	Larva: 「Kyumii! Kyuuu! Kyuu!」	s26a	0769
PV01_1301_A	2	5	Asagi: 「Gu, fu...... muuuh.」	s26a	0770
PV01_1301_A	2	6	Larva: 「Kyuuuuu!!」	s26a	0771
PV01_1301_A	2	7	Asagi: 「Fugugun......」	s26a	0772
PV01_1301_A	2	8	While spreading demonic fluids over their mother, the injuu's larvae finally slipped out from Asagi's body.	s26a	0773
PV01_1301_A	2	9	Oboro: 「They came out! Congratulations on the birth! From today on, you have become some shit insects' mama!」	s26a	0774
PV01_1301_A	2	10	Asagi was exposing her gaping-open vagina and anus in front of Oboro, who raised hysterical laughter.	s26a	0775
PV01_1301_A	2	11	Without even a word, Asagi's wide-open legs twitched repeatedly.	s26a	0776
PV01_1301_A	2	12	Being affected by the lewd liquid of the grotesque creature's larvae, which she had given birth to, her body was now fainting as she climaxed hard.	s26a	0777
PV01_1301_A	2	13	Oboro: 「Fufufufu. Now it'll start......」	s26a	0778
PV01_1301_A	2	14	Then, a surprising change occurred in Asagi's body.	s26a	0779
PV01_1301_A	2	15	Bushii! Bushuu! Buchuuu!!	s26a	0780
PV01_1301_A	2	16	The skin of Asagi, who squirted ostentatiously, had suddenly been tinted dark brown.	s26a	0781
PV01_1301_A	2	17	Demonic Specialist Doctor: 「The secretions of the larvae have spread through her whole body, and the darkening of her skin has started, but it will settle down immediately.」	s26a	0782
PV01_1301_A	2	18	Oboro: 「I know that when I see it! Kukuku, you've taken a lot from the sons you gave birth to, eh Asagi......?」	s26a	0783
PV01_1301_A	2	19	Larva: 「Kyumii♪ Kyumiih♪ Kyuuuh♪」	s26a	0784
PV01_1301_A	2	20	The tentacles that the larvae had just grown twined around the pointed clitoris of Asagi, who squirted and continued her silent climax, and they slurped up the love juices that overflowed.	s26a	0785
PV01_1301_A	2	21	Asagi, who had a mother's body, responded to that greedy action, which followed instinct, by thrusting her meat pillar out and squirting an even larger amount of current.	s26a	0786
PV01_1301_A	2	22	Oboro: 「Fufuu, that's one long leak.......! Looks like you've settled down at last.」	s26a	0787
PV01_1301_A	2	23	Asagi's squirting waned, and the colour of her skin also recovered its whiteness from before.	s26a	0788
PV01_1301_A	2	24	However, in that body, a definite change from before had been brought about.	s26a	0789
PV01_1301_A	2	25	Oboro: 「Are you listening? With this, you have reached the point where your entire sense of pain has transformed into pleasure. Isn't that nice?」	s26a	0790
PV01_1301_A	2	26	With the effect reaching even her nerves, and even a little stimulation changing into intoxicating pleasure, she had reached the point of reacting magnificently.	s26a	0791
PV01_1301_A	2	27	Oboro: 「Even if I tickle you juuust a little, even if you step on a thumb tack, you'll piss yourself and have a big climax☆ Fufufu! It's turned into a useful body, hasn't it?!」	s26a	0792
PV01_1301_A	2	28	Looking up at Asagi, who was still dangling from the flesh egg, Oboro raised ecstatic laughter.	s26a	0793
PV01_1301_A	2	29	Oboro: 「With this, the preparations are complete. Start getting ready immediately.」	s26a	0794
PV01_1301_A	2	30	Demonic Specialist Doctor: 「Right.」	s26a	0795
PV01_1301_A	2	31	Oboro: 「I'll carve a hypnotic seal into you...... into Shit Insect Orgasm Pig Asagi-chan!!」	s26a	0796
PV01_1301_A	2	32	High-pitched laughter echoed throughout the medical room.	s26a	0797
PV01_1301_A	2	33	SALTAR: S027A
