S007AM_END	1	1	Kousuke: 「Asagi-san, wh, what should we do?!」	s07a	0739
S007AM_END	1	2	Asagi: 「It's not 『What should we do?』...... Put your clothes on quickly...... nnh, nnnnhh!!」	s07a	0740
S007AM_END	1	3	Asagi stood up unsteadily.	s07a	0741
S007AM_END	1	4	Kousuke: 「That's right, I'm naked. Crap.」	s07a	0742
S007AM_END	1	5	Like his pushiness until just now was a lie, Kousuke hurriedly started to put on his clothes.	s07a	0743
S007AM_END	1	6	Asagi: 「Haa......」	s07a	0744
S007AM_END	1	7	Asagi looked at Kousuke and sighed a little.	s07a	0745
S007AM_END	1	8	Asagi: 「My clothes are...... There's no other way now...... Honestly, you made me like this......」	s07a	0746
S007AM_END	1	9	With her drenched panties on, Asagi reset her rolled-up skirt, and	s07a	0747
S007AM_END	1	10	Asagi: 「My bra...... Ah, well, I can do it later.」	s07a	0748
S007AM_END	1	11	Braless for now, she neatly fixed her opened outer garment.	s07a	0749
S007AM_END	1	12	Asagi: 「I wonder...... is this all right? Uuuh, I have no choice but to think it's fine......」	s07a	0750
S007AM_END	1	13	With an anxious-looking face, she checked her appearance, which was reflected in a full-length mirror.	s07a	0751
S007AM_END	1	14	Needless to say, the back of her suit was soaked with love juices and urine.	s07a	0752
S007AM_END	1	15	However, fortunately, it looked like that wasn't clear from the portion seen from the front.	s07a	0753
S007AM_END	1	16	Asagi: 「Kou-kun, I've put my clothes on now. I'm going to keep those two there, so you do something about the dirty floor in here. Okay?」	s07a	0754
S007AM_END	1	17	Asagi said, while quickly wiping the love juices oozing down her thighs with a handkerchief.	s07a	0755
S007AM_END	1	18	Kousuke: 「Eh? Do something? How??」	s07a	0756
S007AM_END	1	19	Asagi: 「Think of that much by yourself!」	s07a	0757
S007AM_END	1	20	Kousuke: 「R, right!!」	s07a	0758
S007AM_END	1	21	Kousuke said with a start, and he also took out a handkerchief and started to wipe the filth off the floor.	s07a	0759
S007AM_END	1	22	Kousuke hadn't become used to being assertive at any other time than during sex, in which he used the Bedroom Art.	s07a	0760
S007AM_END	1	23	Even though she was lightheaded from that sex just before, Asagi promptly tried to deal with it with composure.	s07a	0761
S007AM_END	1	24	They were a truly contrastive pair.	s07a	0762
S007AM_END	1	25	SALTAR: S008A
