S020A_02	1	1	Asagi: （Asuka is my daughter. I still want to believe in her.）	s20a	0198
S020A_02	1	2	As Yamamoto said, if she was receiving the backing of the American Federation, it appeared that Asuka was on the enemy side. Like Nomad. Like Black.	s20a	0199
S020A_02	1	3	However, the Asuka that Asagi knew hated Black more than anyone. The enemy of her family, her parents.	s20a	0200
S020A_02	1	4	She was working as an advance detachment of the American Federation, which supported Black?	s20a	0201
S020A_02	1	5	No, that was wrong.	s20a	0202
S020A_02	1	6	Asagi's intuition as her mother told her “That's wrong. Asuka's also a warrior seeking justice. Taimanin blood flows within her.”	s20a	0204
S020A_02	1	7	Asagi: （Still, if that's a mistake...... I'll......）	s20a	0205
S020A_02	1	8	SALTAR: 合流Ｃ
