T011A	1	1	The next day.	t11a	0000
T011A	1	2	The village of the Taimanin.	t11a	0001
T011A	1	3	Now under total control of the Kanda Brigade.	t11a	0002
T011A	1	4	The forest that spread out behind the Gosha Academy building.	t11a	0003
T011A	1	5	The medical room inside the underground facility there.	t11a	0004
T011A	1	6	That night, Oboro was in an unusually good mood.	t11a	0005
T011A	1	7	Oboro: 「I wonder if That Thing has arrived?」	t11a	0006
T011A	1	8	Oboro was searching for Furst, taking along three bakan.	t11a	0007
T011A	1	9	Furst: 「Hey hey. Oboro, I've been expecting you.」	t11a	0008
T011A	1	10	Oboro: 「I heard you took severe damage from the Steel Taimanin, but it seems you're well, huh?」	t11a	0009
T011A	1	11	Furst: 「Yeah...... Even though I regenerated my broken body, I ended up killing about 10 soldiers, mufufu.」	t11a	0010
T011A	1	12	Furst moved his brand-new arms in order to show them off.	t11a	0011
T011A	1	13	Furst: 「Apart from that, the girl. I heard you captured her. I'd really like you to hand her over to this Furst.」	t11a	0012
T011A	1	14	Oboro: 「Can't. Unusually, I was told by Black-sama not to execute her, but to give her lots of love. I also found a use for that girl.」	t11a	0013
T011A	1	15	Furst: 「Is that so? Well then, at that time, I'd really......」	t11a	0014
T011A	1	16	Oboro: 「Yes, I'll think about it. Hmm...... Pretty good facility, isn't it?」	t11a	0015
T011A	1	17	Oboro said, while viewing the equipment of the medical room.	t11a	0016
T011A	1	18	Furst: 「I think so. It's because I improved the equipment my unworthy pupil was using.」	t11a	0017
T011A	1	19	Oboro: 「By pupil, you mean Kiryuu? On that subject, what happened to that guy?」	t11a	0018
T011A	1	20	Furst: 「Ku fu fu, he's become tiny, like a bug. Even though he's recovering from that, it looks like it will take a substantial amount of time.」	t11a	0019
T011A	1	21	Oboro: 「Idiotic as ever. So, can you work with this equipment?」	t11a	0020
T011A	1	22	Furst: 「Of course. “That” treatment is possible at any time.」	t11a	0021
T011A	1	23	Furst expressed a gleeful smile at Oboro's question.	t11a	0022
T011A	1	24	Oboro: 「That's marvellous!」	t11a	0023
T011A	1	25	Furst: 「And now, the introduction of a certain young lady.」	t11a	0024
T011A	1	26	Furst pointed at a corner of the room.	t11a	0025
T011A	1	27	In that place was Ingrid, who had been restrained.	t11a	0026
T011A	1	28	Oboro: 「Ahaaaaa!!」	t11a	0027
T011A	1	29	Oboro's eyes began shining sadistically.	t11a	0028
